<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:03:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>South Koreans detained at Georgia Hyundai plant are headed home, but Trump offered to let them stay and train Americans, Seoul says</title>
      <description>The 316 South Koreans who were arrested at the Hyundai-LG plant in Georgia are now on their way home. The raid and the treatment of the workers could make South Korean companies “very hesitant” about operating in the United States, the country’s president said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30aa33e1-8f03-11f0-a2b3-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk. FBI lawsuit. Kamala Harris. Housing costs. Cancer and exercise. Humid summer. Life on Mars. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78cd1930-8efe-11f0-9925-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. dismisses its ambassador to the U.S., citing new information about his links to Jeffrey Epstein</title>
      <description>British Prime Minister Keir Starmer said he withdrew Peter Mandelson from his post after new information emerged about the ambassador’s links to the American sex offender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a960c6c0-8efc-11f0-b91b-0000a1ace852</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk, dead at 31, leveraged his debate skills to create viral moments that captured audiences across the political spectrum</title>
      <description>The Turning Point USA founder had an audience of millions of fervent conservative fans and fierce liberal critics, emerging as one of the most prominent — and often controversial — voices in the age of Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86091370-8eb2-11f0-a208-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person of interest in Charlie Kirk shooting is in custody, Utah governor says</title>
      <description>Utah Gov. Spencer Cox (R) said at a news conference that the person is being interviewed by officials. Cox said the shooting was a “political assassination” and vowed to hold the killer “accountable to the furthest extent of the law.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37fddd50-8e99-11f0-b493-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative activist Charlie Kirk dies at 31 after he was shot onstage at Utah college event, Trump says</title>
      <description>Kirk, the founder of Turning Point USA, was shot while speaking at an event at Utah Valley University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18184be0-8e87-11f0-84be-000a1ace778b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wing activist Charlie Kirk shot at Utah college event, two people familiar with matter say</title>
      <description>Kirk is the founder of Turning Point USA, an organization for young conservatives. He was speaking at an event at Utah Valley University. The school said the suspect was in custody, according to parents whose children received an email from the university.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a037ee0-8e79-11f0-ae8b-0000a1ace2c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI leaders sue Director Kash Patel, alleging they were unlawfully fired over perceived political disloyalty</title>
      <description>Former acting FBI director Brian Driscoll alleged in the federal lawsuit that a Trump administration official asked questions including: “Who did you vote for?,” “When did you start supporting President Trump?” and “Have you voted for a Democrat in the last five elections?”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b259c80-8e6c-11f0-8e00-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In new memoir, Kamala Harris says it was ‘recklessness’ to defer to Joe Biden’s decision to run at age 80</title>
      <description>In her forthcoming book, “107 Days,” Harris said she “perhaps” should have weighed in but worried it would have looked “incredibly self-serving” and disloyal for her to do as Biden’s vice president. She also wrote about not feeling supported by his staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a617eb51-8e62-11f0-9c07-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: This dad is so consumed by disapproval, it ate his marriage, too</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: This dad is so consumed by disapproval, it ate his marriage, too</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c2d9b61-8e5f-11f0-a6e1-000a1acec938</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Is drunk brunch getting out of control?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Is drunk brunch getting out of control?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43f54140-8e5b-11f0-b36b-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocks found on Mars are some of the strongest clues yet of past life on the dusty planet</title>
      <description>Detailed analysis of images of speckled rocks found by NASA’s Perseverance rover has confirmed a “potential biosignature.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a378330-8e57-11f0-9fce-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard documents say public finds D.C. mission wasteful and some veterans feel ‘shame’</title>
      <description>The assessments, which have not been previously reported, underscore how domestic mobilizations that are rooted in politics risk damaging Americans’ confidence in the National Guard. They also reveal, with a rare candor in some cases, that military officials have been kept apprised that their mission is viewed by a segment of society as wasteful, counterproductive and a threat to long-standing precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21857e50-8e50-11f0-bfab-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More political drama for this country in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72489991-8e4a-11f0-8331-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Qatar. National Guard. Trump’s signature. Russian drones. Rising prices. Missing storms. New iPhones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d2dbf60-8e35-11f0-9170-0000a1acedb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland says it shot down Russian drones that violated its airspace while attacking targets in Ukraine</title>
      <description>Russia’s actions posed “a real threat” to Polish citizens, the Polish military’s Operational Command said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bd8fb20-8e03-11f0-9974-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily blocks Trump’s firing of Federal Reserve board member Lisa Cook</title>
      <description>In a setback for the president, the judge ruled that Cook had shown strong evidence that the effort to dismiss her was illegal. The board will meet next week to consider an interest rate cut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3838e130-8dee-11f0-9e25-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired CDC director Susan Monarez, who clashed with RFK Jr. over vaccines, will testify before Senate next week</title>
      <description>The hearing will be Monarez’s first public appearance to address the tumult at the CDC. She has said Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. pressured her to alter vaccine policies and fire staff. Kennedy told senators last week that Monarez lied about their interactions and said she was untrustworthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">712f88e0-8dd0-11f0-b3d3-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court agrees to quickly weigh the legality of most of Trump’s tariffs in major economic case</title>
      <description>The far-reaching case is expected to determine the fate of a cornerstone of President Donald Trump’s economic agenda and could alter the course of the U.S. economy and global trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967b6550-8dbd-11f0-8000-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver North quietly married his former secretary Fawn Hall, four decades after their roles in the Iran-contra scandal</title>
      <description>The couple tied the knot on Aug. 27 in Virginia, according to a marriage license obtained by The Washington Post. As a National Security Council staffer under President Ronald Reagan, North was accused of illegally arranging the sale of U.S. weapons to Iran to fund a secret war against communists in Nicaragua. Hall, his young secretary at the time, had shred documents and even smuggled evidence out of the office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">507e4e90-8db4-11f0-b82a-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation wiped out income gains in 2024, but richest 10 percent of households got richer, census finds</title>
      <description>Most Americans’ household income remained steady last year, but women and Black people lost ground, the U.S. Census Bureau said Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f34aa000-8db0-11f0-b1b7-000a1ace0896</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri state House becomes latest to pass Trump-backed congressional map as partisan redistricting fight escalates</title>
      <description>The plan is expected to give Republicans one more U.S. House seat ahead of the midterm elections. It now heads to the state Senate, where it is expected to pass this month and later receive the signature of Gov. Mike Kehoe (R).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7657dd50-8da7-11f0-a94e-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Son’s classmate told him her mom is abusive. Report it?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Son’s classmate told him her mom is abusive. Report it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32aee960-8d96-11f0-921f-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out charges against Michigan Republicans who claimed to be electors after Trump lost 2020 election</title>
      <description>The dismissal of the charges is a victory for President Donald Trump and his allies and a blow to Michigan’s Democratic attorney general.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">558119a1-8d8b-11f0-a2f4-000a1ace9959</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: U.S. revises jobs reports down by 911,000 for year ending in March. A previous alert said 910,000.</title>
      <description>The revisions by the Bureau of Labor Statistics are the latest round of significant changes to labor market data, which has faced heightened scrutiny after President Donald Trump took the unprecedented step of firing the BLS commissioner over updated reports. A previous alert misstated the revised number. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87659c10-8d87-11f0-b6e1-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. revises jobs reports down by 910,000 for year ending in March, showing slower economy before Trump took office</title>
      <description>The revisions by the Bureau of Labor Statistics are the latest round of significant changes to labor market data, which has faced heightened scrutiny after President Donald Trump took the unprecedented step of firing the BLS commissioner over updated reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">195c0344-8d86-11f0-ba66-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A canceled award ceremony in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93d530e0-8d83-11f0-9915-0000a1aced86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets senior Hamas leadership in Qatar as explosions are heard in Doha</title>
      <description>The Israel Defense Forces said Tuesday that it carried out a strike targeting the senior leadership of Hamas. It did not say where the strike took place, but Qatar’s Foreign Ministry confirmed an attack on Hamas political leaders in the capital, Doha.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138f2ae0-8d82-11f0-9b6a-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein sketch. Chicago raids. E. Jean Carroll. Murdoch empire. Test scores. ‘Kissing bug’ disease. Banksy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eef9ed0-8d6c-11f0-8ec7-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘acoustic terror’ of Russia’s blasts makes people wonder if they are dead. Hear it for yourself.</title>
      <description>This summer, there were no quiet nights for Ukraine. Russian attacks have increased more than fivefold since January, deafening people with sirens, drones and ballistic missiles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0908bb20-8d07-11f0-9552-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch family resolves dispute over ownership of media empire in billion-dollar deal</title>
      <description>Lachlan Murdoch, whose politics are in line with those of his 94-year-old father, will remain in control after Rupert Murdoch’s death, with three other siblings splitting a $3.3 billion settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72682aa0-8cf9-11f0-855e-0000a1ace46b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House launches stepped up immigration enforcement operation in Chicago as Trump vows a broader crackdown on violent crime</title>
      <description>Authorities said “Operation Midway Blitz” is part of Trump’s efforts to target “sanctuary cities” that limit cooperation with the federal government. Democrats denounced the action as immigrant advocates said several people in heavily Hispanic communities had already been detained Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b9d34d0-8cf7-11f0-8688-0000a1acef13</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress receives documents it subpoenaed from Jeffrey Epstein’s estate, including book allegedly made for his 50th birthday</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee on Monday received documents from the estate of the sex offender as part of its broader probe into the federal sex-trafficking investigation of Epstein. Epstein’s jailed associate, Ghislaine Maxwell, allegedly gifted the book to him when he turned 50.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3e54840-8ce6-11f0-b43a-0000a1ace0d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth makes unannounced trip to Puerto Rico as Pentagon eyes island to assist drug cartel crackdown</title>
      <description>The Pentagon is weighing plans to make Puerto Rico a part of its operations in Latin America, possibly conducting military flights out of the island territory, said two U.S. officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The effort includes the possible deployment of fighter jets to the island, one of the officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f60abd60-8cdf-11f0-b7e4-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Parliament votes to oust prime minister, deepening Macron’s woes as government collapses for second time in under a year</title>
      <description>The French National Assembly voted “no confidence” in Prime Minister François Bayrou, which will force his resignation. The decision exacerbates the political problems of President Emmanuel Macron, who lost his parliamentary majority after calling snap elections in June 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ca7a660-8cd7-11f0-b681-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After her scary hospital detox, planning the next step with Mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After her scary hospital detox, planning the next step with Mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93c7a1c0-8cd2-11f0-9552-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says Trump can resume immigration raids in L.A. area for now, overturning a ruling that found race-based targeting</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court overturned a lower-court ruling that curtailed Los Angeles-area detentions after finding federal agents were indiscriminately targeting people based on race and other factors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad92f8c0-8ccd-11f0-82f1-0000a1ace121</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can fire a Democratic FTC commissioner while lawsuit proceeds, Supreme Court chief justice rules</title>
      <description>Supreme Court Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr.’s ruling comes after an appeals court found last week that Commissioner Rebecca Slaughter could be reinstated to her job because President Donald Trump had fired her “without cause.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a81a80-8cca-11f0-8846-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump loses his effort to appeal $83 million judgment in writer E. Jean Carroll’s defamation case against him</title>
      <description>A federal appeals court Monday upheld a jury’s $83.3 million judgment against President Donald Trump in a lawsuit brought by Carroll. She had accused Trump in 2019 of sexually assaulting her two decades earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee72e3a0-8cc8-11f0-a167-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta suppressed research on child safety, employees say. The company denies the allegations.</title>
      <description>Members of Congress have received a trove of internal company documents from four current and former employees who allege that Meta lawyers intervened to shape research that might have illuminated potential safety risks to children and teens on the company’s virtual reality devices and apps. A Senate Judiciary subcommittee is set to discuss the allegations, which Meta denies, at a hearing Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f7afee0-8cbc-11f0-8275-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s back! Get ready for this impending competition in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a94d970-8cb8-11f0-b766-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks Supreme Court to allow it to freeze billions in foreign aid</title>
      <description>The emergency request could set up a major test of the president’s assertion that he has the unilateral authority to block spending budgeted by Congress. The filing comes after a federal appeals court upheld a preliminary injunction requiring Trump officials to spend the money for food, medicine and development assistance before it begins to expire on Sept. 30, the end of the fiscal year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c397d3e0-8cb2-11f0-82f1-0000a1ace121</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. State spending cuts. RFK Jr. Russia-Ukraine war. Meta allegation. Carlos Alcaraz. Millennial saint. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f531af30-8ca2-11f0-b187-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting attack on a bus in Jerusalem kills at least five people</title>
      <description>Other people were injured after two attackers opened fire at a bus stop in north Jerusalem, according to Israel’s emergency services. The attackers were also killed at the scene, the Israeli police said. The Israeli military said troops had been deployed to “thwart terrorism and strengthen the defense effort.” Hamas praised the shooting and said it was “a natural response to the occupation’s crimes.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57519f50-8c98-11f0-ab8a-0000a1ace63d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Alcaraz of Spain wins U.S. Open, defeating Italy’s Jannik Sinner in third Grand Slam final between the rivals this year</title>
      <description>Alcaraz and Sinner became the first duo to face each other three times in a Grand Slam title match in a single season in the Open era. Alcaraz, who now has two U.S. Open championships and six total Grand Slams to his name, won this year’s French Open, while Sinner earned the Wimbledon title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f27ce450-8c32-11f0-9c95-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 21:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get a complainer to stop, according to a therapist</title>
      <description>Complaining can foster camaraderie and establish common ground, but when it becomes excessive, it can annoy listeners and wreck relationships. Here are five ways to cope.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e487130-8c2c-11f0-af78-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots and abuse troubled these former prisons. ICE plans to reopen them.</title>
      <description>The same private companies that closed facilities plan to reopen them to hold immigrants. Advocates say that puts detainees at risk of violence and mistreatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">828eba91-8c11-11f0-a4b1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd7e78c0-8c03-11f0-bf1e-0000a1acef8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Gov. Gavin Newsom won’t stop mocking Trump online, seeking to position himself as de facto head of Democrats' resistance</title>
      <description>Influencers on both the left and the right have discussed Newsom online more than any other potential 2028 presidential contender since President Donald Trump’s inauguration, according to a Washington Post analysis. The attention has been driven by his response to immigration raids in Los Angeles, his efforts to counter a Republican redistricting push and, most recently, his mocking impersonations of Trump’s social media style.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06bf3570-8bf8-11f0-9187-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95403c0-8bee-11f0-b723-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
