<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 19:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Without explanation, sister-in-law no-shows care for dying mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Without explanation, sister-in-law no-shows care for dying mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07891490-6bcc-11f0-b820-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is impacting 700 professions — and might impact yours</title>
      <description>How AI is impacting 700 professions — and might impact yours</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e881a290-6bc3-11f0-891e-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This person ‘will not be intimidated’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">704865c0-6bb9-11f0-9504-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA struggles to retain air traffic control recruits in a system with ‘hostile’ training</title>
      <description>One out of five trainees fail to get certified. In some cases, recruits failed their training and were dismissed. In others, they left of their own accord rather than endure what they described as haphazard instruction, organizational dysfunction and abusive conditions. “It’s this professional guild, but to me it also felt like a college hazing,” said a retired FAA psychologist. “It was hostile.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a0815c1-6bb5-11f0-9282-0000a1ace7f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand and Cambodia agree to ceasefire after days of border clashes</title>
      <description>The two sides agreed to “an immediate and unconditional ceasefire” starting at midnight, Malaysian Prime Minister Anwar Ibrahim said. President Donald Trump had spoken to both leaders to push for peace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77a59660-6ba2-11f0-957e-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza aid. Trump-Epstein. E.U. trade deal. Walmart stabbing. Plane evacuation. Walking benefits. Gwyneth Paltrow. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">061cf380-6ba2-11f0-8302-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fumes as Epstein scandal dominates headlines, overshadows his agenda</title>
      <description>The president's exasperation follows weeks of missteps and no clear strategy among top officials who underestimated the outrage, especially from the president’s base, and hoped the country would forget about the unreleased Epstein files and move on, according to nearly a dozen people close to the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef4a0780-6b4f-11f0-bcdd-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a microplastics researcher limits exposure to plastics in her day-to-day life</title>
      <description>Scientists have found microplastics in our livers, blood, brains and even placentas. And while more science is needed to fully understand how this affects our health, there’s enough evidence for us to be concerned, writes Tracey Woodruff, a professor at the University of California at San Francisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b77b0070-6b2c-11f0-b99c-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lehrer dies at 97. The musician and satirist subverted clichés about romance, patriotism and small-town life.</title>
      <description>His astute social commentary, verbal dexterity and often academic subject matter differentiated him from mere novelty acts during the 1950s and 1960s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e60c6bd0-6b1e-11f0-8ae4-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces outline of tariff deal with European Union, saying he will impose 15% duty on imports</title>
      <description>Leaders around the world are rushing to strike trade agreements with President Donald Trump ahead of an Aug. 1 deadline, when the White House is expected to begin collecting new tariffs on imports from dozens of countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9171fd10-6b14-11f0-8f56-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His son co-piloted the DCA-bound flight that crashed. Now Tim Lilley, also a pilot, is seeking answers.</title>
      <description>Lilley has found himself in two roles. He’s a dad in mourning. He’s also an aviation expert — one who has flown both types of aircraft in the Jan. 29 collision at Reagan National Airport — focused on finding answers and accountability for the families of all 67 people killed in the crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22bbca30-6b0b-11f0-82ee-0000a1ace3d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0bd2da0-6b02-11f0-a0ef-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de France confronts a new threat: Are cyclists using tiny motors?</title>
      <description>After a doping scandal, professional cycling is pursuing the dual challenges of keeping the sport honest and convincing a skeptical audience it is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd5e6590-6af1-11f0-bf2c-000a1aceddc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">446134e0-6aed-11f0-be02-0000a1ace991</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel allows airdrops of food into Gaza amid international pressure over mounting starvation</title>
      <description>The first pallets of flour, sugar and canned food were dropped late Saturday. A growing number of foreign governments, including Jordan and Britain, have volunteered to airdrop food into Gaza to relieve a deepening crisis that has included deaths from starvation. Aid workers have said the approach is inefficient and inadequate to what's needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf4c5c40-6a63-11f0-bc3d-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 21:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth team told to stop using polygraph tests to root out people leaking to news media after complaint to White House</title>
      <description>The White House directed Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth to cease the use of polygraph tests after a senior adviser to Hegseth complained to senior officials about being targeted, U.S. officials and others familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef8ab7b0-6a57-11f0-ad67-0000a1ace84c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 19:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Roommate reacts with ‘bafflement and confusion’ every time I vent</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Roommate reacts with ‘bafflement and confusion’ every time I vent</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ca49190-6a39-11f0-a8df-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A timeless Chinese game is hooking people across D.C. and the nation</title>
      <description>Interest in mah-jongg is surging, thanks in part to a coterie of coaches and instructors, social media influencers, and luxe spaces to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">838b9180-6a2d-11f0-a4fe-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2770dbc0-6a24-11f0-a42d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From David Ignatius: The 12 days that turned back the clock on Iran’s nuclear program</title>
      <description>Israeli and American assessments agree Tehran’s infrastructure to finish a bomb is shattered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e27360-69ac-11f0-8acc-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge dismisses Trump administration lawsuit against Illinois and Chicago over 'sanctuary city' policies</title>
      <description>District Judge Lindsay C. Jenkins ruled that the Justice Department "lacks standing" to sue the state and city over what the White House has characterized as impeding its efforts to crack down on undocumented immigrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b65b74e0-69a6-11f0-aedf-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 22:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration releases billions it withheld from school programs, ending weeks of educators’ anxiety before academic year</title>
      <description>With the school year beginning in just weeks, lawmakers of both parties had lobbied the administration to release the funds, which support English-language learning programs, teacher training and academic enrichment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a47644b0-6980-11f0-b9bb-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Deadbeat dad’s parents want to give me money. I don’t want it.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Deadbeat dad’s parents want to give me money. I don’t want it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68d79930-6977-11f0-ad7a-0000a1aceff0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They’re rich. They’re anti-Trump. And they don’t want their big tax cut.</title>
      <description>Affluent voters have become more Democratic in recent years, opposing President Donald Trump’s policies that will make them richer. Many of the biggest beneficiaries of the GOP tax law say they are getting millions of dollars they don’t want or need.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52436870-6968-11f0-930f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s iOS 26 public beta is here. Here are the 4 biggest changes.</title>
      <description>iOS 26 is one of the most significant software overhauls the tech giant has made for the iPhone in years, and we’ve been testing it for weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41652550-6960-11f0-85cd-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a58c2150-695b-11f0-ac2c-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza talks. IRS changes. Ghislaine Maxwell. Paramount merger. Hulk Hogan. iPhone update. Tour de France. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84b33690-6946-11f0-bedb-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC approves $8 billion Paramount-Skydance merger after lengthy review marked by controversy</title>
      <description>The merger, which drew allegations of political pressure on Paramount-owned CBS News, was approved by a 2-1 vote, with Biden-appointed commissioner Anna M. Gomez voting against the transaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc2b2d60-68db-11f0-bbdb-0000a1ace0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs order pushing for more forced hospitalizations of homeless people with mental illness and addiction</title>
      <description>The White House said the move would shift people into long-term institutional settings and restore public order. Critics of the policy said it threatens to return the nation to an era when people were often unjustly locked away in mental health institutions and does nothing to help Americans afford housing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03c02a50-68da-11f0-b61e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France will recognize a Palestinian state, Macron says, calling for an urgent end to the war in Gaza</title>
      <description>In a statement, French President Emmanuel Macron said he would recognize Palestine at the U.N. General Assembly in September. “The urgent need today is to end the war in Gaza and to rescue the civilian population,” he said, adding that there is no other way to build lasting security in the Middle East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dc8f860-68d5-11f0-bbdb-0000a1ace0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration sues New York City for using sanctuary city policies to impede immigration crackdown efforts</title>
      <description>The legal action comes days after an off-duty Customs and Border Protection officer was shot during an ambush robbery attempt in an upper Manhattan park, allegedly by a pair of undocumented immigrants.
The Justice Department says in its filing that the nation’s largest city has been flouting its obligations to assist in federal immigration enforcement by operating as a sanctuary city for decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9e71fe0-68d2-11f0-bdd0-0000a1ace430</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDA will relocate most of its D.C.-based workforce and close several key facilities</title>
      <description>The agency will move about 2,600 employees to five other locations in the country and shutter some facilities in the capital region. The closures will include the Henry A. Wallace Beltsville Agricultural Research Center, a 6,500-acre operation that dates back 115 years and is one of the world’s largest facilities of its kind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eedd480-68cf-11f0-89d7-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass starvation is stalking Gaza as Israel restricts aid and deaths from hunger rise</title>
      <description>Testimonies from doctors, relief workers and Gazans make it clear that a worst-case scenario is unfolding: Nearly 1 in 3 people are going multiple days without eating, according to the United Nations, and hospitals are reporting rising deaths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebf73930-68c1-11f0-9939-0000a1ace966</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amy Sherald, who painted Michelle Obama portrait, cancels Smithsonian show over alleged ‘censorship’ of a transgender-themed work</title>
      <description>The Smithsonian denied that it planned to censor the show at the National Portrait Gallery, whose leader recently resigned after President Donald Trump claimed he fired her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb1f4600-68b7-11f0-a211-0000a1aceb1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Gov. Tony Evers (D) announces he won’t seek a third term in his swing state</title>
      <description>The decision is expected to set off a scramble as other Democrats weigh running to replace Evers. He defeated Gov. Scott Walker (R) in 2018, ending Republicans’ eight-year run of complete control of state government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64766960-68b0-11f0-9617-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulk Hogan dies at 71. The pro wrestling star’s tabloid-centric private life became a legal battleground over the First Amendment.</title>
      <description>Florida wrestler Terry Bollea, who shot to stardom as Hulk Hogan, reigned supreme for a generation of professional wrestling fans. Decades after his heyday in the ring, Bollea became a fixture in the courtroom after suing the owners of a popular gossip website that showed portions of a sex tape featuring Bollea and the wife of a friend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52071ea0-68ab-11f0-88be-0000a1ace5fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband is losing his ability to manage small frustrations</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband is losing his ability to manage small frustrations</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5efc3720-68a7-11f0-8e9a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE moves to shackle some 180,000 immigrants with GPS ankle monitors, a sharp increase in round-the-clock monitoring</title>
      <description>In an internal ICE document reviewed by The Washington Post, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement ordered staff to place ankle monitors on all people enrolled in the agency’s Alternatives to Detention program “whenever possible.” Currently, just 24,000 of these individuals wear ankle monitors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71a95030-6896-11f0-88be-0000a1ace5fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sweaty crop in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b6ba2e0-6892-11f0-9c58-0000a1ace764</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Ankle monitors. Gaza starvation. Bryan Kohberger. Candace Owens. Corn sweat. Penis worm. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e2b6bb0-687d-11f0-9617-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia University and Trump administration strike a deal over federal funding</title>
      <description>White House officials have cast Columbia University as the epicenter of antisemitism. This deal would resolve a dispute over federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa6d2590-681e-11f0-aa9b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With GOP support, House Oversight subcommittee takes step to subpoena Justice Department for Epstein files</title>
      <description>Three Republicans joined with Democrats to advance language to force the full release of the Epstein files after an amendment was introduced by Rep. Summer Lee (D-Pennsylvania). Republican lawmakers have been feeling the same pressure as President Donald Trump to respond to anger from his base about the Justice Department's recent decision not to release the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a513d30-6819-11f0-a6af-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He got away with murder for 23 years. Video shows his response as police confront him.</title>
      <description>Eugene Gligor struggled to collect himself after learning his DNA was at the scene of a 2001 murder in Chevy Chase, Maryland. What came next wasn’t a confession. But it wasn’t exactly a denial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9524d5b0-6810-11f0-b135-0000a1acec6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to remove Democrats from agency that regulates safety of everyday consumer products</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had asked the justices to allow the president to remove three of the five members of the Consumer Product Safety Commission, which evaluates products such as strollers and bicycles and coordinates recalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21fd8280-6806-11f0-977e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclosures by Hegseth’s Signal account derived from email classified ‘SECRET,’ IG is told, contradicting Trump officials' claims</title>
      <description>The Pentagon’s independent watchdog has received evidence that messages from the defense secretary's Signal account previewing a U.S. bombing campaign in Yemen derived from a classified email labeled “SECRET/NOFORN,” people familiar with the matter said, contradicting repeated claims by the Trump administration that no classified information was divulged in unclassified group chats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2801cb21-67f5-11f0-bd4b-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department's request to release Epstein transcripts is denied by Florida judge</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Florida has denied the Justice Department’s request to unseal grand jury transcripts from the investigation of deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein in that state.
The department — facing increasing pressure from President Donald Trump’s political base — petitioned the court last week to release those typically closely held records of witness testimony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce473dc0-67f1-11f0-9d81-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who killed four University of Idaho students in 2022 gets four consecutive life sentences</title>
      <description>Bryan Kohberger pleaded guilty earlier this month as part of a plea deal that eliminated the possibility of the death penalty. The high-profile case disrupted a quiet Idaho town, inspired several books and became a subject of speculation by true-crime fans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69c730d0-67ec-11f0-86c9-000a1ace7c27</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Embarrassing, off-script officiant steals couple’s thoughtful show</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Embarrassing, off-script officiant steals couple’s thoughtful show</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">658e7180-67de-11f0-996f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N.’s highest court rules that countries have a duty to limit greenhouse gases, potentially bolstering climate lawsuits worldwide</title>
      <description>The International Court of Justice ruling said countries are obliged to cut planet-warming pollution and any breach represents an “internationally wrongful act.” While non-binding, the decision could boost cases across the globe and ultimately lead to reparations for vulnerable countries damaged by global warming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46210d90-67dd-11f0-a13f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Help! I’m routinely seated at bad tables.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Help! I’m routinely seated at bad tables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cd94310-67d6-11f0-aff8-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
