<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 10:03:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to release billions in backup funds for SNAP, relied on by 42 million Americans</title>
      <description>In an oral ruling, Judge Jack McConnell said the Agriculture Department must distribute $5.5 billion in the contingency funds “timely, or as soon as possible, for the November 1 payments to be made.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab2b1eb0-b689-11f0-ba3a-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1f0f20-b67b-11f0-b765-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela pleads with Moscow for help as U.S. ramps up the pressure</title>
      <description>Documents show Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro drafted a letter asking Russia for missiles, radar and upgraded aircraft as U.S. forces amass in the Caribbean.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13aef4e0-b674-11f0-a3fa-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Police seek hundreds more officers amid Trump’s crime crackdown</title>
      <description>A hiring spree in the nation’s capital is part of a plan to become “the premier law enforcement agency in D.C.,” according to documents obtained by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de76f0c0-b66e-11f0-9bc0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio approves new congressional map giving Republicans a leg up in two more House seats</title>
      <description>The new map received rare bipartisan agreement because Republicans who control the state legislature did not want to risk a challenge from Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">587bbc40-b66d-11f0-8531-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My family emigrated from Vietnam. Halloween in America astonished me.</title>
      <description>Coming from a communist-run nation, I was baffled by glimpses of life in my new home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bbdbe20-b663-11f0-9319-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c3d8ec0-b65e-11f0-925f-0000a1ace1f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center ticket sales have plummeted since Trump takeover</title>
      <description>Nearly nine months into the president’s oversight, sales for orchestra, theater and dance performances are the worst they’ve been since the pandemic, according to a Washington Post analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f131e2f1-b651-11f0-8c36-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s actions. Shutdown impacts. Kennedy Center. National Guard. Former prince Andrew. Autism study. Fall back. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70712c0-b648-11f0-8c1a-0000a1ace1bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of science’s biggest dinosaur debates may finally be settled</title>
      <description>For decades, paleontologists debated whether fossils were of a young T. rex or a species called nanotyrannus. A new study settles it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4641a1-b5e8-11f0-a63b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid in pregnancy tied to autism and developmental issues, study says</title>
      <description>A study published in the journal Obstetrics and Gynecology analyzed more than 18,100 births in Massachusetts of children born to women who contracted the virus starting in the early months of the pandemic through some of 2021, before vaccines were widely available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56201510-b5d5-11f0-87e9-000a1ace2f48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified U.S. report finds hundreds of possible Israeli human rights violations</title>
      <description>The State Department’s watchdog says it will take years to review credible allegations against Israeli military units in Gaza, according to officials, raising doubts about future accountability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e581e0-b5ce-11f0-9dfb-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Charles III strips brother Andrew of prince title and orders him to vacate his home at Royal Lodge over Epstein scandal</title>
      <description>The move marks the latest setback for the embattled royal as the scandal over his ties to the convicted American sex offender Jeffrey Epstein continues to cast a long shadow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00223b34-b5ca-11f0-bccd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans blame Trump and the GOP more than Democrats for the government shutdown, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>But the share saying Democrats are at fault has grown slightly, from 30 percent in a Washington Post flash poll when the shutdown began to 33 percent in the latest poll. Among registered voters, 37 percent now blame Democrats, while 46 percent blame Republicans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b889020-b5bb-11f0-b544-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Democrats know the truth about demonizing Trump</title>
      <description>Gov. Josh Shapiro and the Democratic state party leader are focused on winning back lost voters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d487bac0-b5ad-11f0-9924-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s brother knows no bounds with constant chatty calls</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s brother knows no bounds with constant chatty calls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1201a1d0-b5aa-11f0-bd9b-0000a1ace191</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland state Sen. Dalya Attar (D) indicted on extortion and conspiracy charges as she runs in tight race for full-term seat</title>
      <description>Attar, the first Orthodox Jewish woman to serve in the state’s senate, assumed the seat in January after it was vacated and the Baltimore City Democratic Central Committee voted to appoint her. She is running for a full term against Malcolm P. Ruff (D-Baltimore City), a civil rights attorney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82120e80-b5a8-11f0-8f5b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationals are expected to hire Blake Butera as their next manager. The 33-year-old comes from the Tampa Bay Rays organization.</title>
      <description>The Washington Nationals are finalizing a deal to hire Butera, according to three people with knowledge of the move. The skipper, chosen by new president of baseball operations Paul Toboni, is set to join a club that is at an inflection point in its rebuild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef421460-b5a2-11f0-b67c-0000a1ace7d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration makes misleading case in high-stakes asylum hearing</title>
      <description>Homeland Security asked a judge to deport a man to Afghanistan, where he expects the Taliban to kill him. What happens next could affect thousands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b84c250-b59d-11f0-8aaf-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitoes are showing up where?! Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc38b80-b595-11f0-bdae-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon readies thousands of National Guard ‘reaction forces,’ a sign deployment in U.S. cities could become the norm under Trump</title>
      <description>The Defense Department’s newly established “quick reaction force” within the National Guard is being readied for civil unrest missions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c52f6b70-b591-11f0-8c03-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans oppose the demolition of the East Wing for Trump’s ballroom, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Twenty-eight percent of Americans say they support the demolition project, paid for by $300 million in private donations from U.S. businesses and individuals, compared with 56 percent who oppose it, according to the poll. Another 16 percent are not sure whether they support or oppose the project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00c64960-b588-11f0-9f4f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear testing. Melissa damage. Ballroom poll. Food banks. Sonya Massey. Diverted flight. Historic hike. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c8cb0f0-b57f-11f0-8706-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces that he’ll cut tariffs on Chinese imports after Xi agrees to delay restrictions on rare earth minerals for a year</title>
      <description>The president said Chinese imports would now be subject to a 47 percent tariff, down 10 percentage points from the blanket rate before the meeting. In return, Beijing agreed to delay restrictions on rare earth minerals for a year and buy “tremendous amounts” of American soybeans, the president said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3925850-b552-11f0-afbb-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 05:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump directs Pentagon to test nuclear weapons, just before meeting with China’s Xi</title>
      <description>The president said he wanted testing to occur “on an equal basis” with Russia and China, raising pressure on Beijing less than an hour before he was scheduled to meet his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping for a high-stakes summit in South Korea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">199acba0-b533-11f0-ac04-0000a1acebdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 01:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump nominee at U.S. export bank withdraws amid scrutiny of Russia ties</title>
      <description>Bryce McFerran, the president’s pick for one of the top positions in the U.S. Export-Import Bank, is a former senior executive at a steel-trading business co-owned by one of Russia’s richest oligarchs and is married to a member of a Russian family with ties to the Kremlin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a4ad682-b512-11f0-92ca-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff’s deputy convicted in 2024 killing of Sonya Massey, an unarmed Black woman who called 911 to report prowler, lawyer says</title>
      <description>Sean Grayson was found guilty of second-degree murder, a lawyer representing the woman’s family said, in a case that renewed national outrage over police conduct against Black Americans. He faces the possibility of up to 20 years in prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fc69c70-b501-11f0-b896-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louvre heist suspects ‘partially admit’ involvement</title>
      <description>None of France’s crown jewels have been recovered. Paris’s public prosecutor said she remained hopeful, with two suspects in custody.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d96959c0-b4f6-11f0-b6d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed cuts rates again as shutdown clouds view of economy</title>
      <description>The central bank moved to steady a weakening job market as inflation stays elevated and key data goes dark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0049b080-b4f2-11f0-8f0e-0000a1ace76b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Kaine and Rand Paul: Why we’re forcing Senate votes on Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Why we’re forcing Senate votes on Trump’s tariffs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e9e6810-b4e4-11f0-a836-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How bad is it that boyfriend lied in shame over money? Hax readers give advice.</title>
      <description>How bad is it that boyfriend lied in shame over money? Hax readers give advice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a735fb0-b4e3-11f0-a02b-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two U.S. prosecutors suspended after describing Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol as a ‘riot’ in court document</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has placed two federal prosecutors in Washington on leave a day after they filed a document in court that referred to the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol as a “riot” carried out by a “mob,” two people familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bec4090-b4e2-11f0-9252-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The government shutdown could cost the economy up to $14 billion, according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office</title>
      <description>The report by the Congressional Budget Office said the longer the government stays closed, the more costly the pause will be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81476531-b4dc-11f0-9479-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A crowdsourced encyclopedia in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a31970-b4cc-11f0-ab99-0000a1aceb7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration used misleading videos to portray chaos, push deportations, a Post analysis has found</title>
      <description>Official videos purporting to show the triumph of recent immigration operations used footage that was months old or recorded thousands of miles away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e99ff460-b4c0-11f0-b117-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa. Misleading videos. Agency firings. Israeli strikes. Tylenol lawsuit. AI errors. Dr. Seuss. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6379a750-b4b6-11f0-b5d7-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland Senate president blocks anti-Trump redistricting fight led by fellow Democrats</title>
      <description>Senate President Bill Ferguson (D-Baltimore City) said in a letter to Senate Democrats that his chamber would not move forward with redrawing the boundaries in a special session. Gov. Wes Moore and House Speaker Adrienne Jones have been eager to jump into the redistricting arms race unfolding across the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cd1c2f0-b48b-11f0-a707-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 05:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong’s shadow war in Britain destroyed an ex-Royal Marine’s life</title>
      <description>U.K. officials have tracked what they describe as an escalating campaign of surveillance and intimidation against Hong Kong exiles living in Britain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d95bf1-b45c-11f0-891f-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate approves bipartisan resolution to end tariffs on Brazil</title>
      <description>The move reflects frustration over President Donald Trump’s trade actions among a group of GOP lawmakers, though it cannot pass the House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5a8d360-b454-11f0-ad88-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House fires arts commissioners expected to review Trump construction projects, including his planned triumphal arch in D.C.</title>
      <description>Former president Joe Biden appointed the six fired commissioners to four-year terms, several of which should have extended through 2028. Their termination comes as the White House gears up to implement several Trump construction projects, including his planned $300 million White House ballroom, and seeks to install allies on key review boards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef6d25e0-b44b-11f0-97ca-000a1ace697f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 22:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon moves to fire civilian personnel with ‘speed and conviction’</title>
      <description>A memo from the Defense Department’s top personnel official makes it easier to remove underperforming employees and warns managers that they will be held accountable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7de9e290-b43d-11f0-81a9-000a1ace8f3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza after Netanyahu accuses Hamas of violating truce</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu accused Hamas of returning remains that belonged to Ofir Tzarfati, a hostage whose body Israel partially recovered in November 2023. An Israeli military official also said Hamas militants fired a rocket-propelled grenade and sniper rounds at troops in southern Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a31210-b42e-11f0-b068-0000a1ace097</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category 5 Hurricane Melissa makes landfall in Jamaica, bringing catastrophic floods, storm surge and winds</title>
      <description>The outlook remains grim. Jamaican Prime Minister Andrew Holness said he had “been on my knees in prayer” and gave a dire prediction of what might come: roofs sheared from homes, roads inundated and infrastructure destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97755e50-b420-11f0-bf38-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic states sue to force SNAP payments during government shutdown</title>
      <description>A group of 23 attorneys general sued the Agriculture Department to force it to make billions of dollars in contingency funds available to help feed the most vulnerable individuals and families. SNAP, the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program commonly known as food stamps, needs $9.2 billion to pay benefits in November. The Trump administration has said there’s no money for next month because of the shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82745e0-b41d-11f0-b622-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: The big women in their family seem to ‘embarrass’ son’s petite wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: The big women in their family seem to ‘embarrass’ son’s petite wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d019ab3-b417-11f0-bed4-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military kills 14 people in strikes on four alleged drug boats in eastern Pacific</title>
      <description>Fourteen alleged traffickers were killed in the strikes, Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth said on social media, bringing the total to nearly 60 killed in more than a dozen strikes since early September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f3a0d66-b410-11f0-b55e-0000a1ace28f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which wing in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8b19860-b406-11f0-8215-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sues Tylenol maker, alleging painkiller can cause autism. The lawsuit echoed Trump’s warnings, despite a lack of evidence.</title>
      <description>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton filed a lawsuit against Tylenol maker Kenvue and its former parent company, Johnson &amp; Johnson, alleging the companies deceptively sold the painkiller. The suit, filed in a Texas state court, comes a month after President Donald Trump repeatedly warned pregnant women not to take Tylenol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3589080-b401-11f0-8858-0000a1ace570</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unforgettable night at the World Series lasted 18 incredible innings</title>
      <description>Monday night’s win for the Los Angeles Dodgers over the Toronto Blue Jays, was the second-longest World Series game ever played by time and tied for the longest by innings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9c16f0-b3fb-11f0-bed4-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa. Trump’s ballroom. Shutdown impacts. Stillbirth study. DEI battle. Grokipedia. MAGA dating scene. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38d17ec0-b3ed-11f0-b4a6-0000a1ace6b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
