<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 01:28:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted war criminal William Calley is dead at 80. He was the face of the My Lai massacre, one of the Army’s darkest chapters.</title>
      <description>Calley was the only person convicted in connection with the 1968 massacre, in which U.S. troops killed hundreds of unarmed South Vietnamese men, women and children. His death in April was not previously reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f1bdc50-4e04-11ef-83f5-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese migrants are illegally entering the U.S. from Mexico in record numbers, testing Biden and Xi</title>
      <description>U.S. authorities have encountered more than 55,000 Chinese migrants crossing illegally from Mexico during the past 18 months — up from 3,813 in 2022. It is the last stage of the journey known in Chinese as zouxian — “walking the line.” Driven in part by the stifling economic and political fallout of China’s extended covid-19 lockdowns, the Chinese arrivals have become a political and national security flash point in Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5caa6ec0-4dfe-11ef-98a3-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. women's basketball opens with a rout and Summer McIntosh coasts to swimming gold</title>
      <description>McIntosh, a 17-year-old Canadian star, won the women's 400-meter individual medley in dominant fashion. Elsewhere, the U.S. women’s basketball team opened group play with a blowout of Japan, Novak Djokovic defeated Rafael Nadal in the second round of the men’s tennis singles tournament, and the U.S. men earned their first medal in the gymnastics team event since 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5190b180-4df8-11ef-ae75-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 22:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gymnast Stephen Nedoroscik is at the Olympics for one reason: Pommel horse. Today, he became both a medalist and viral star.</title>
      <description>Pommel horse is an apparatus so fickle that one misstep can derail an athlete’s rhythm and send the routine into disarray. And in the waning moments of Monday’s final, Nedoroscik had to deliver for the United States to clinch its first Olympic team medal since 2008. He leaped onto the apparatus and began swinging, floating through each element and maneuvering his hands with precision. His teammates watched with their arms around one another, and as soon as he dismounted, the celebration began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbbf2c0-4de5-11ef-a7fe-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 2 children dead and 6 in critical condition after mass stabbing in English seaside town</title>
      <description>Police detained a teenage boy with a knife Monday in the attack that killed two and injured another nine children and two adults in Southport in North West England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">500583d0-4ddb-11ef-ae92-0000a1ace580</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. men win bronze in the gymnastics team competition. It’s the Americans’ first Olympic medal in the event since 2008.</title>
      <description>Over the past three years, the U.S. gymnasts have aggressively pushed to increase the difficulty of their routines after a disappointing output in Tokyo. Japan earned the gold medal while China took home silver Monday in Paris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">332dbbb0-4dd6-11ef-9b2a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Type A parent wants to tell chronically late partner to be on time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Type A parent wants to tell chronically late partner to be on time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccfd2b81-4dc3-11ef-ae93-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An enthusiastic phone call in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b07a0650-4dae-11ef-a343-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro claims victory in Venezuelan election; several countries, including U.S., cast doubt</title>
      <description>President Nicolás Maduro’s electoral council declared him the winner of Sunday's election, though his opponent, Edmundo González, also claimed victory. Multiple world leaders called for transparency over how votes were counted, while Russia, China and Cuba congratulated Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b899a2f1-4d9f-11ef-84e2-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In an op-ed, Biden calls for ‘three bold reforms’ to restore trust in the Supreme Court and American democracy</title>
      <description>President Biden pushes for term limits and a code of conduct for the Supreme Court, and a constitutional amendment making clear there is no immunity for crimes a former president committed while in office. Read his op-ed in The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9567570-4d9a-11ef-a8a5-0000a1acec72</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election countdown. Supreme Court. Israel. Venezuela’s disputed vote. Park Fire. Simone Biles. Chimp language. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4262af0-4d99-11ef-a24f-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Nicolás Maduro’s electoral council declared him the winner of Venezuela’s election</title>
      <description>Maduro’s electoral council claimed the authoritarian socialist won the hard-fought contest Sunday despite independent exit polling that suggested challenger Edmundo González captured twice as many votes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c486ea30-4d60-11ef-9394-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simone Biles advances to gymnastics all-around final and Torri Huske leads U.S. swimming's medal haul on Day 2 at Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>The Americans cruised into the women's gymnastics team final, with Biles and Sunisa Lee earning spots in the all-around final. Huske edged teammate Gretchen Walsh for a gold-silver finish in the women's 100-meter butterfly, and French star Leon Marchand set an Olympic record in the men's 400 individual medley. Elsewhere, the U.S. men's basketball and women's soccer teams won in group play, and two Americans featured in the women's fencing individual foil final.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4db870-4d2a-11ef-bc08-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kamala Harris took control of the Democratic Party</title>
      <description>In the hours and days after President Biden's departure from the race, party officials and campaign aides raced to flip an entire brand from fading hope to salute emojis. What resulted was a flash-bang midsummer swap at the top of the presidential ticket, an outpouring of volunteer energy, a rebound in the polls and a flood of hundreds of millions of dollars in donations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cf69fc0-4d23-11ef-94ab-0000a1ace713</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 20:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usha Vance once told friends Trump appalled her. Now, with her husband on his ticket, she’s working to elect him.</title>
      <description>Usha Vance rarely expressed her political views while rising through prestigious law schools and clerkships — but she expressed revulsion to her friends about president Donald Trump’s actions amid the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol. Some of those friends watched in disbelief earlier this month as she addressed a Republican National Convention crowd in support of Trump and his running mate: her husband, JD Vance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3729b271-4d1b-11ef-853d-0000a1ace6d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edna O’Brien dies at 93. The groundbreaking Irish writer of ‘The Country Girls’ captured women’s struggles in a male-dominated world.</title>
      <description>The book, which was banned in Ireland, made O’Brien a literary sensation and propelled her into the Swinging Sixties cultural whir.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37255230-4d06-11ef-8134-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 17:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a532550-4cfa-11ef-9394-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctions crushed this brutal regime’s elite. So they built a zombie economy fueled by drugs.</title>
      <description>A stimulant called Captagon has become the fabulously profitable core of Syria’s economy and helped the country’s political and military elite cling to power. The illicit pills, manufactured in Syrian factories and sold across the Middle East, are generating an estimated $10 billion a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">481a1ba0-4cef-11ef-a227-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c225e30-4ce7-11ef-850e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caeleb Dressel anchors relay to first U.S. gold and Katie Ledecky takes bronze in 'race of the century' on Day 1 at Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>The Summer Games are underway in Paris. The United States claimed its first gold medal in the men's 4x100-meter freestyle swimming relay, powered by Dressel in the final leg. Ledecky earned her first medal in Paris with bronze in the women's 400 freestyle, and NBA sensation Victor Wembanyama shined in his Olympic debut for host France.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e6451f0-4c64-11ef-9d2b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who do you think Harris’s VP pick should be? Choose what her ticket needs, and we’ll tell you who fits the bill.</title>
      <description>We have a sense of the contenders for Kamala D. Harris’s running mate, considerations in choosing one of them, and their strengths and weaknesses as candidates. Now, this is where you come in: Take our quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d162b41-4c5d-11ef-bfe6-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 21:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My brother stopped talking to me after a heated political discussion</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My brother stopped talking to me after a heated political discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e2c36a0-4c32-11ef-a191-000a1acef43f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 16:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance’s ‘Hillbilly Elegy’ echoes truths about Kentucky. But many locals question his theories about the White working class.</title>
      <description>Vance’s bestseller turned movie recounts the summers he spent with his grandmother in Jackson, Ky., the distressed Appalachian town of his ancestors. Numerous friends and neighbors there who are close to his family said they don’t doubt that his stories are broadly true. What many take issue with, though, are Vance’s conclusions about the root causes of the area’s poverty and violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee1f0a40-4c24-11ef-8ac9-0000a1aceb30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">586739d0-4c1c-11ef-a128-0000a1ace44d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best breakfast sandwiches in the D.C. area, according to our restaurant critic</title>
      <description>Ranging from the simple to the sublime, Tim Carman tasted more than 90 breakfast sandwiches in search of the best in the D.C. area. It wasn’t easy to narrow the field to 10, but there was one clear winner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfd49290-4c0f-11ef-80dd-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team USA has captured its first medal of the Paris Olympics, in diving. Follow our coverage here.</title>
      <description>Americans Sarah Bacon and Kassidy Cook won silver in the women's synchronized 3-meter diving competition, the first U.S. medal of the Summer Olympics. It's the first day medals are being awarded in Paris, where swimmer Katie Ledecky will compete for more hardware later today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18b7ed40-4c01-11ef-8ac9-0000a1aceb30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 10:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What we know about the man suspected of causing California’s largest wildfire</title>
      <description>The man suspected of causing the wildfire is a loner with a criminal record. Authorities say a witness saw him light a vehicle on fire and push it down a ravine, triggering an explosive conflagration that led to his arrest.


Neighbors of Ronnie Stout, a 42-year-old Chico resident, say they never imagined he’d do anything like this — a mysterious act that put them at mortal risk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68fcd114-4ba9-11ef-9857-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Boeing Starliner astronauts are stuck indefinitely in space. This is what their life is like.</title>
      <description>They spend their time conducting experiments and maintaining equipment, including the space station toilet, weeks after they were supposed to return to Earth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6eb65ea0-4ba4-11ef-a662-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 23:11:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. settles with ex-FBI officials Strzok, Page over leak of anti-Trump texts</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has agreed to settle claims by former senior FBI special agent Peter P. Strzok and FBI lawyer Lisa Page, who had sued saying the government violated their privacy rights when it leaked their politically charged text messages criticizing Donald Trump.


Strzok's attorneys say he will receive a $1.2 million settlement. Terms for Page were not disclosed. Strzok and Page said they were illegally targeted for retribution by the Trump administration after the FBI investigated Russia’s interference in the 2016 presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2e51bd0-4b9e-11ef-afcd-0000a1ace035</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 22:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia health staff failed Irvo Otieno as he suffocated at a state mental hospital last year, experts say</title>
      <description>A new Washington Post analysis of nearly two hours of surveillance footage inside and outside Central State Hospital identifies serious shortcomings in Otieno’s care by clinical personnel at the facility as officers and workers pinned him down for more than 11 minutes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5735fe50-4b83-11ef-9d5b-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 19:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world has changed overnight, and Trump is going to need a mulligan, Dana Milbank writes</title>
      <description>The former president is back to firing off random, late-night rage posts from his social media account.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf2489a1-4b7e-11ef-b0ea-000a1ace42f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 18:42:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most daring Opening Ceremonies in Olympic history are about to begin. Follow our live coverage from Paris.</title>
      <description>Years in the making, the Paris Games are planning to make an audacious statement with a boat parade of athletes on the Seine toward the Eiffel Tower.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d660e011-4b73-11ef-b1d1-000a1ace2cd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 17:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband says hyphenating baby’s last name is confusing</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband says hyphenating baby’s last name is confusing</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1af9c630-4b6d-11ef-8efc-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 16:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico says it wasn’t informed of operation to whisk Sinaloa cartel leaders to the U.S.</title>
      <description>Sinaloa cartel leaders “El Mayo” Zambada and a son of “El Chapo” Guzmán were flown to Texas in a private plane in a coup for U.S. agents fighting the fentanyl trade. Mexico didn’t learn of the arrests until hours later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5379a020-4b63-11ef-8efc-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 15:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Olympic records motivate athletes and fascinate fans. But one day, those milestones may be unbreakable.</title>
      <description>As advances in training, technology and technique continue, how close are we to reaching the limits of human performance?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38497f71-4b5c-11ef-8f9f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42bac582-4b53-11ef-b756-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Join Sen. Tim Kaine (D-Va.) and Post journalists for ‘First Look’ to discuss the 2024 election reset</title>
      <description>Vice President Harris is consolidating support for the Democratic nomination. Former president Donald Trump and Sen. JD Vance (R-Ohio) are hitting the campaign trail. And voters are beginning to assess a brand-new presidential contest. Join Washington Post associate editor Jonathan Capehart for a special, expanded edition of First Look.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1734a380-4b4f-11ef-8e20-0000a1ace040</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartel arrest. Harris’s VP search. French rail attack. Netanyahu visit. Wildfires. Komodo dragons. Mars discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34239f20-4b3e-11ef-a9cb-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barack and Michelle Obama endorse Kamala Harris for president</title>
      <description>The Obamas are the final key leaders in the Democratic Party to unite behind Harris after President Biden abandoned his bid for a second term. Barack Obama said in a call with Harris that the Democrats would be “underdogs,” but that he pledged to “get to work” on helping her defeat Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9794d620-4b2d-11ef-abd2-0000a1ace9c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France’s national rail says ‘malicious’ acts causing disruptions before Olympics</title>
      <description>France’s national rail service, SNCF, on Friday said several “malicious acts” targeted three of its high-speed lines, causing disruptions hours before the Opening Ceremonies of the Paris Olympic Games. “Arson attacks were started to damage our facilities,” SNCF said in a post on X. Some disruptions are expected to last through the weekend until Monday, SNCF said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52ae9121-4b25-11ef-8a67-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 08:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ismael ‘El Mayo’ Zambada, top leader of Sinaloa cartel, surrenders to U.S. authorities alongside son of Joaquin ‘El Chapo’ Guzman</title>
      <description>Zambada and the younger Joaquin Guzman surrendered on a flight on Thursday, according to a DHS official and a former U.S. official with knowledge of the situation. The Sinaloa cartel, a global drug-trafficking syndicate, has shipped tons of cocaine, heroin, fentanyl and methamphetamines into the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11608120-4ae8-11ef-8a67-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 00:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris, after meeting with Netanyahu on ending war in Gaza, calls for cease-fire deal and release of hostages</title>
      <description>Vice President Harris, not President Biden, gave public remarks Thursday afternoon after they each held separate bilateral meetings with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, a reflection of how much has changed in Washington since Biden announced he was exiting the presidential race and she became the likely Democratic nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e710a90-4adb-11ef-9741-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 23:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can Kamala Harris win? Three columnists share their impromptu thoughts on her candidacy — and the doubters.</title>
      <description>‘I do think she can win!’ Impromptu thoughts on Harris doubters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08f32ac0-4ad8-11ef-9595-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A network of political novices is building an online army for Kamala Harris, one video at a time</title>
      <description>Some TikTok creators, energized by the new likely Democratic nominee, are using their skill at playful video collages to build Harris a viral political powerhouse from scratch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfbba224-4ad1-11ef-b928-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 22:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Justice Elena Kagan calls for a way to examine alleged ethics violations by justices</title>
      <description>The justice said she would support the creation of a committee of outside judges to weigh potential violations of the ethics code, which was put in place last year amid concerns about unreported gifts and potential conflicts of interest but was criticized for lacking any enforcement mechanism. Kagan, one of three liberals on the court, spoke as President Biden and Democratic lawmakers are increasingly calling for changes at the high court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fffcd60-4ac7-11ef-9947-000a1ace7572</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested in connection with California’s largest fire of the year</title>
      <description>The fast-growing Northern California blaze, which has consumed at least 71,489 acres, has resulted in at least 3,500 people being ordered to evacuate. Though the cause of the Park Fire is still under investigation, authorities say that a 42-year-old man from Chico was seen pushing a burning car into a gully in Bidwell Park, outside the city where the fire began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be7065d0-4ac3-11ef-abb7-0000a1ace5c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 20:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Why does covid rise in the summer? What are the isolation guidelines? We’re taking your questions about the latest wave.</title>
      <description>Health reporter Fenit Nirappil gets you up to date with information about boosters, testing and isolation protocols. Ask your question now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a477d560-4aa9-11ef-884f-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 17:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law and his wife go on about themselves. And that’s it.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law and his wife go on about themselves. And that’s it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48d5ee90-4a9f-11ef-8fdb-0000a1ace66c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI CEO Sam Altman writes: Who will control the future of AI? The U.S., an allied nation — or an authoritarian one?</title>
      <description>A democratic vision for artificial intelligence must prevail over an authoritarian one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbd01120-4a9e-11ef-9083-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battles without bullets: How four U.S. presidents unleashed economic war across the globe with sanctions</title>
      <description>Over the past two decades, American presidents have massively increased the use of financial sanctions, which are now in effect in some form on roughly one-third of all countries. But the tools don’t always do what they’re meant to. Who pays the price when they go astray?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cfe2e90-4a91-11ef-9862-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 14:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
