<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 15:02:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Project 2025 ex-director condemns ‘violent rhetoric’ from president of the conservative Heritage Foundation</title>
      <description>Paul Dans, who led the right-wing policy and personnel blueprint Project 2025 until July, also called on Republican vice presidential nominee JD Vance to withdraw his foreword for Heritage President Kevin Roberts’s book.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d63ea8a1-8bca-11ef-84e1-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A welcome return in the nation’s capital in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9c8a1a0-8bc2-11ef-92f9-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign. Harris on Fox. Middle East. Hurricane relief. Tyron McAlpin. ‘Don’t Ask Don’t Tell.’ Hidden tomb. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8c8f171-8bad-11ef-a446-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge blocks requirement that counties hand-count ballots</title>
      <description>Critics said the new requirement, instituted by a pro-Trump majority on the state election board, would have almost certainly led to errors and could have disrupted the process of certifying the vote in a crucial battleground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">316e5e60-8b61-11ef-ba55-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 01:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change may be coming for your house. Look up your level of risk.</title>
      <description>The growing threat of extreme weather is starting to drag down home prices in the most exposed neighborhoods. Here are the tools you need to assess your risk and protect yourself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a9f9e40-8b41-11ef-bc83-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 22:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBA fund for disaster victims is out of money, Biden says, after two hurricanes recently struck the Southeast</title>
      <description>The Small Business Administration’s disaster loan program is a critical lifeline to small businesses, homeowners and renters affected by disasters. Hurricanes Helene and Milton have strained the government’s ability to respond, though FEMA still has money available for grants and assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e2367b0-8b36-11ef-927c-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse is aware of husband’s affair and ‘not really bothered by it’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse is aware of husband’s affair and ‘not really bothered by it’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b87df440-8b0e-11ef-80d8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may halt arms transfers to Israel unless humanitarian situation in Gaza improves, Biden administration warns</title>
      <description>The Biden administration intensified pressure on Israel this week to improve dire humanitarian conditions in the Gaza Strip, warning that the United States would be forced to undertake new actions — including a potential suspension of military assistance — if food and other aid to Palestinians is not increased within a month. Since the spring, the amount of aid delivered to Gaza “has dropped by more than 50 percent,” the United States says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46ff2420-8b08-11ef-9efe-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘climate of chaos’ went unchecked at this maximum-security psychiatric hospital, culminating in a brawl, rape and death</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found that officials didn’t act on staff complaints about violence at Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center in Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d55178a1-8afd-11ef-9b04-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An icy moon of this planet is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4037cab0-8afa-11ef-b185-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris vs. Trump. Israel’s plan. Helene misinformation. Jupiter mission. Covid impacts. Home values. Giant pandas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f87d2f0-8ae4-11ef-8513-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s a vast divide between Republicans and Democrats over fast food, our Department of Data found</title>
      <description>Campaign finance reports revealed strikingly partisan preferences for various restaurants, with few more polarizing than McDonald’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff708770-8a7b-11ef-8cb6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is waging a campaign against real-time fact checks</title>
      <description>The Trump campaign is pushing TV networks, journalism organizations and others to abandon the practice if they hope to interact with the Republican nominee. The moves are the latest example of his long-held resistance to being called to account for his falsehoods, which have formed the bedrock of his political message for years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab885e0-8a6f-11ef-86d7-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two giant pandas are departing China for D.C. Visitors will have to wait at least several weeks to see them at the National Zoo.</title>
      <description>Qing Bao, a 3-year-old female, and Bao Li, a 3-year-old male, are being transported to D.C., officials in China said. Veterinarians and zookeepers are escorting the bears, whose arrival will resume a beloved animal conservation program in Washington that goes back more than a half-century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95edf1a1-8a5f-11ef-972d-0000a1ace132</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six new lawsuits accuse Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs of sexual assault, including at his famous White Parties</title>
      <description>A 16-year-old male who attended one of the parties is among the accusers who filed civil lawsuits against Combs on Monday. Combs has remained in federal custody since his arrest last month on sex trafficking and racketeering charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f4edc10-8a5d-11ef-bdd9-000a1ace161c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA’s Europa Clipper launched from the Kennedy Space Center on a mission to see if a moon of Jupiter can sustain life</title>
      <description>The $5 billion mission, decades in the making, seeks to investigate ice-encrusted Europa, which appears to have a subsurface ocean and has long been identified by scientists as potentially habitable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e7da7d0-8a47-11ef-8463-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom pesters adult son about his budding online romance</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom pesters adult son about his budding online romance</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a633a30-8a45-11ef-8a4b-0000a1ace85d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane recovery officials in N.C. relocated amid report of ‘armed militia,’ email shows, underscoring threat of misinformation</title>
      <description>The setback is one of the latest examples of growing concerns about safety and security among federal responders to Helene in North Carolina. On Monday, authorities said they arrested an individual for making alleged threats against FEMA workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06cf1aa0-8a44-11ef-b002-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada expels 6 Indian diplomats, alleging wider campaign by Modi government against Sikhs</title>
      <description>India’s top diplomat in Ottawa, Sanjay Kumar Verma, was among those ordered to leave the country, Canadian officials said.

A statement by India’s Ministry of External Affairs said the government “strongly rejects these preposterous imputations.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e07fc70-8a3d-11ef-b256-0000a1ace514</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This person is sending a message in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc9db100-8a30-11ef-9a0d-0000a1ace2d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election polls. Middle East. Hurricane recovery. China threats. ER shortages. Marathon record. SpaceX. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72430680-8a1b-11ef-b256-0000a1ace514</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in economics awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James A. Robinson</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Monday to the three, who work at U.S. universities, “for studies of how institutions are formed and affect prosperity.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c8fd490-8a13-11ef-84e8-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘It’s devastating’: Asheville braces for peak tourism season without visitors after Helene changed everything</title>
      <description>Tourism brought nearly $3 billion to North Carolina’s Buncombe County last year. Now, Asheville’s businesses are entering what would normally be a prosperous October with the prospect of earning little to no revenue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7526951-89ab-11ef-9c7a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal flood maps vastly underestimated the threat in places hit hardest by Hurricane Helene, Post analysis shows</title>
      <description>Federal Emergency Management Agency flood maps identified just 2 percent of properties in the mountainous areas of western North Carolina as within the “Special Flood Hazard Area” that is at risk of a 1-in-100-year flood. A Washington Post analysis of data from First Street, a climate modeling group, found that the number of properties at risk could be seven times higher than what FEMA flood maps indicate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0439bd40-8995-11ef-ad19-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. will send an antimissile system and personnel to Israel to counter potential attacks from Iran, Pentagon says</title>
      <description>The Terminal High Altitude Area Defense missile system, or THAAD, will strengthen Israel’s defenses against an attack from Iran or its proxies, Pentagon spokesman Pat Ryder said in a statement. Israeli officials have said they will retaliate against Iran for the barrage of ballistic missiles it fired at Israel this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07f58000-8985-11ef-916d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">282f23b0-897d-11ef-9e58-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 16:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The inside story of the five little-known years Kamala Harris spent in Montreal amid political turmoil</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris has rarely mentioned years she spent living in Quebec between the ages of 12 and 17 amid a deepening conflict over the French-speaking majority’s treatment. But her path was profoundly shaped by her years in Canada at a time when a party advocating political separation had recently taken power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79fa8e90-8974-11ef-be99-0000a1ace7b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ce79d90-8967-11ef-9f97-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies fear the campaign’s ‘alpha male’ culture is losing women’s votes</title>
      <description>Staffers view men as former president Donald Trump’s path to victory — and many of them talk like it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20a047e1-88e8-11ef-9401-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 22:20:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents seized in Gaza’s tunnels reveal Hamas’s ambition to wreak havoc across Israel, with Iran’s support</title>
      <description>Dozens of pages found by Israeli troops in Gaza detail a potential Hamas plan far bigger than the Oct. 7, 2023, attack and show how militant leaders solicited Iranian funds and training.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb3dbe0-88d1-11ef-9dc0-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 19:41:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When people need a ride home from prison, he’s waiting outside with a car</title>
      <description>More than 600,000 people are released from America’s prisons every year, vowing never to go back. Many do. John “Freddie” Nole is trying to change that, one car ride at a time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2576a660-88ac-11ef-893b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 15:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best bagels in D.C.? We tried 9 shops and found a clear winner, with the help of a congressman, a pastry chef and a rabbi.</title>
      <description>It wasn’t that long ago that some D.C. denizens considered this area a bagel desert. But local bakers keep rising to fill the demand previously fed by national chains. We taste-tested a bunch to find the city’s top bagel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4331c70-88a3-11ef-97a6-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24964ef1-88a0-11ef-97a6-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 13:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vice President Harris’s doctor says she’s in ‘excellent health’ as she seeks contrast with Trump</title>
      <description>The Democratic nominee for president released her first medical report in an effort to draw a sharp contrast with her 78-year-old opponent, Republican Donald Trump. The letter concludes that Harris, 59, “possesses the physical and mental resiliency required to successfully execute the duties of the presidency.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d816601-889e-11ef-9f01-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 13:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing plans to cut 17,000 jobs, or 10 percent of its workforce, amid strike</title>
      <description>The announcement comes after talks broke down this week between the planemaker and the union representing 33,000 striking machinists, leaving little hope the weeks-long walkout would end soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1561d360-8818-11ef-8ccf-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 21:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man drops claims against women who allegedly helped his ex-wife get abortion pills in first-of-its-kind case</title>
      <description>The case, decried by abortion rights advocates as an attempt to deter the use of abortion pills, was dropped after a judge refused to compel the women to provide additional information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db5d9140-87fe-11ef-9b7a-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump makes unprecedented request for military aircraft and vehicles for his security amid Iran threat</title>
      <description>His campaign has also requested further expanded flight restrictions around his rallies and an array of military vehicles to transport him, according to emails reviewed by The Washington Post and people familiar with the talks. No nominee in recent history has been ferried around in military planes ahead of an election. The requests came after Trump’s campaign advisers received briefings where the government said Iran is still actively plotting to kill him. Trump was also the target of two assassination attempts that U.S. officials say are not tied to Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91da6201-87ea-11ef-99f0-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">769126f0-87d6-11ef-a3db-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 13:41:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milton aftermath. Barack Obama. Israeli strikes. Nobel Peace Prize. Mine rescue. Musk’s robotaxi. Northern lights. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3b0faa0-87bf-11ef-a1be-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Peace Prize awarded to Japanese organization Nihon Hidankyo</title>
      <description>The grassroots movement of atomic bomb survivors from Hiroshima and Nagasaki is receiving the prize for its efforts to achieve a world free of nuclear weapons, the Nobel Committee said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b704be70-87b0-11ef-86b4-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 09:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama admonishes Black men for hesitancy in supporting Kamala Harris, a key demographic she is struggling to reach</title>
      <description>At a campaign stop in Pittsburgh, the former president said he wanted to “speak some truths” and address Black men specifically.

 “You are thinking about sitting out?” he asked. “And you’re coming up with all kinds of reasons and excuses? I’ve got a problem with that. Because part of it makes me think — and I’m speaking to men directly — part of it makes me think that, well, you just aren’t feeling the idea of having a woman as president, and you’re coming up with other alternatives and other reasons for that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2979231-8761-11ef-8513-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Menendez brothers are the focus of two new Netflix shows. Neither improves our understanding of the case, our TV critic writes.</title>
      <description>Thirty-five years after they killed their parents in their Beverly Hills, Calif., home, Lyle and Erik Menendez are once again objects of enormous public interest. A hearing scheduled for Nov. 26 could conceivably overturn the controversial verdict that imprisoned them, and they are the subject of a Ryan Murphy series and a documentary, both streaming on Netflix.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7e3f7f0-875b-11ef-a950-0000a1ace37b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 23:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A firehose of antisemitic disinformation from China is pointing at two Republican legislators, Post analysis finds</title>
      <description>China is increasingly targeting down-ballot races in the United States, spreading divisive claims about politicians on the social media platform X, according to a Washington Post analysis and senior U.S. intelligence officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25cf94c0-874c-11ef-af14-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 21:10:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans challenge legitimacy of overseas votes, including military ballots, as legal fight expands</title>
      <description>A Pennsylvania lawsuit opens a new front in GOP efforts to raise questions about the validity of mail-in ballots, targeting a group once seen as off-limits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52147f71-873b-11ef-baab-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the damage caused by Hurricane Milton in photos, videos and maps of Florida</title>
      <description>Milton’s quadruple impact of deadly tornadoes, heavy rain, hurricane-force wind and storm surge left debris in Florida from coast to coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58b763f0-8728-11ef-9947-0000a1ace499</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Just found out once-close brother is getting married today</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Just found out once-close brother is getting married today</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca4d6df1-8720-11ef-9011-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethel Kennedy dies at 96. The widow of Sen. Robert F. Kennedy kept her family grounded through decades of tragedy.</title>
      <description>After Sen. Kennedy’s assassination in 1968, his wife — once labeled "America's most admired woman" — remained fiercely loyal to his memory and saw it as her life’s work to further his commitment to social justice and to anchor his ideas forever in American culture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95e1ec20-871c-11ef-b611-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein's 1989 interview with Trump was lost in storage for over 30 years. Woodward finally found the tape.</title>
      <description>The yet-to-be-president holds forth on strength, friendship, dealmaking, public service and building violations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a15a0190-8718-11ef-b723-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio voters dismiss false claims about Haitians, but Trump has slight lead, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>Most Ohio voters don’t believe former president Donald Trump’s debunked claim that Haitian immigrants in Springfield are “eating people’s pets,” and agree with Gov. Mike DeWine’s defense of Haitians as hard workers who are in the United States legally, a Washington Post poll finds.

But the former president holds a six percentage point edge over Kamala Harris among likely voters in the Buckeye State – 51 percent to 45 percent – similar to his eight-point winning margin four years ago. And a must-win Senate election for Democrats to keep control of the chamber is essentially tied, with 48 percent supporting Democratic Sen. Sherrod Brown and 47 percent supporting Republican Bernie Moreno, well within the poll’s margin of error of plus or minus 3.5 percentage points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ff7ddd0-8710-11ef-bd86-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rat Pack-era spot goes down in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3dbc480-870b-11ef-9f80-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
