<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:14:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $9 billion in spending cuts, sending package to Trump’s desk</title>
      <description>The House slashed funding for foreign aid and the Corporation for Public Broadcasting, which funds PBS and NPR. The Senate earlier this week passed the cuts, known as rescissions, meaning the bill will soon become law. The House vote was significantly delayed because of the political pressure facing Republicans around the release of government files related to convicted sex-offender Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffffc990-638c-11f0-9b6c-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS cancels Stephen Colbert’s ‘Late Show’ in what the network says was a financial decision</title>
      <description>The late-night talk show will end in May 2026. The announcement came days after Colbert spoke out against the $16 million paid by Paramount, the parent company of CBS News, to settle a lawsuit filed by Donald Trump during last year’s presidential campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80406970-636f-11f0-94bc-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Texas flooding was the deadliest tragedy for children in decades. Here’s who was lost.</title>
      <description>They adored animals and sports. They loved to draw and read. Their giggles were contagious, their hugs spontaneous. Amid the grief, relatives have sought to celebrate what made the children special — and hinted at the young adults they might have one day become.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb09a9e1-635a-11f0-bcb1-0000a1ace6ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 22:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil’s former president Jair Bolsonaro is charged with leading a coup. His son is pushing Trump to sanction a judge in his trial.</title>
      <description>Spurred on by Eduardo Bolsonaro, the White House is considering sanctions against Supreme Federal Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes, according to four people familiar with the situation, which could escalate a growing diplomatic feud between the United States and Brazil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddbb9960-6353-11f0-a312-0000a1ace99d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration adds level of approval to wind and solar projects, threatening to slow them down as tax credit deadline looms</title>
      <description>The Interior Department announced a new level of “enhanced oversight” for renewable energy projects, which will now require approval by the secretary’s office. The move introduces a hurdle to projects that were racing to begin construction before a July 2026 deadline to qualify for tax credits, which were gutted by President Donald Trump’s One Big Beautiful Bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d57c0b0-634f-11f0-a700-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world is choking on screens. Just as this book foretold.</title>
      <description>The world is choking on screens. Just as this book foretold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7577a0-6348-11f0-8871-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Visiting mom with memory loss and depression gets harder every time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Visiting mom with memory loss and depression gets harder every time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f79b2e0-6327-11f0-bbf5-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s best sandwiches, according to the experts: You</title>
      <description>We challenged readers to name the tastiest specimens around. Looking for an exemplary Reuben, Philly cheesesteak or Italian hoagie? Right this way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">871d75c1-6325-11f0-94e5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. seeks one-day sentence for officer involved in raid that killed Breonna Taylor. He faces up to life in prison.</title>
      <description>In an unusual sentencing memo, the federal government suggested to a judge that the Biden administration should not have prosecuted Louisville officer Brett Hankison on civil rights charges. A federal jury found Hankison guilty in November on charges connected to the March 2020 raid in which Taylor was fatally shot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54a7341-6313-11f0-89bc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celestial bodies in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70074090-6312-11f0-875e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connie Francis dies at 87. The popular 1950s and ’60s singer sold over 100 million records and was an unlikely TikTok sensation.</title>
      <description>Francis was known for such hits as “Who’s Sorry Now,” “Stupid Cupid” and “Where the Boys Are.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0073ae0-6302-11f0-993c-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA rift. ‘Alligator Alcatraz.’ Crypto stakes. Israeli strikes. Flood risks. AI cheats. Mars rock. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3246e400-62fd-11f0-a6a7-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate narrowly passes bill to slash $9 billion from foreign aid and public broadcasting</title>
      <description>Its passage is a victory for President Donald Trump, weeks after his triumph on tax and immigration legislation, and may signal the start of a more aggressive effort by his administration to claw back funding appropriated by Congress. The legislation now heads to the House, where the Republican leadership is confident about its passage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc5ddb00-62d9-11f0-9650-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department fires Diddy and Epstein prosecutor Maurene Comey, daughter of former FBI director Trump has feuded with</title>
      <description>Comey is a career prosecutor in the Southern District of New York who worked on the criminal cases of Jeffrey Epstein and Sean "Diddy" Combs. The reason for her firing was unclear, according to a person familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">400a0940-62a9-11f0-9bda-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials halt ‘dangerous’ research despite recommendations of NIH career scientists</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s action has raised concerns among outside scientists, who argue the move could block experiments that are safe and that could lead to new treatments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">261e0f10-62a7-11f0-9849-0000a1aced20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rich are preselecting their children based on their genes — and calling it the future of baby-making</title>
      <description>A start-up funded by Silicon Valley investors scores embryos for their genetic potential to develop disorders. Is it a path toward creating perfect babies or false hopes?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29c57f20-629a-11f0-b797-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 23:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one patient’s personal and political worlds collided at the doctor’s office</title>
      <description>My health and my politics walk into a doctor’s office …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">373bbe10-6260-11f0-8bd3-000a1acec913</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50fde5f0-625e-11f0-bea0-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘delicate subject’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8214f220-624d-11f0-b1ea-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. hits states with requests for voter rolls and election data, sparking concerns of interference ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>Election clerks in both parties, already facing harassment and lawsuits over President Donald Trump’s false 2020 election claims, worry about efforts to examine voting machines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4ef490-6245-11f0-ad01-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Voter data. Extreme rainfall. Confession letter. Obesity study. Emmy nominations. Sycamore Gap tree. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f954e70-6234-11f0-9e35-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelita Grijalva wins Democratic nomination for U.S. House in Arizona special election</title>
      <description>Grijalva won a contested primary in a safely Democratic district, defeating Gen Z content creator Deja Foxx and others. The contest underlined intraparty tensions over age, experience and dynastic politics. Grijalva will be a heavy favorite in the special election to succeed her father, liberal stalwart Raúl Grijalva, who represented the district until his death in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a2bcda0-61f4-11f0-bf2b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expelled D.C. Council member Trayon White Sr. (D) projected to win special election for his former Ward 8 seat</title>
      <description>White, who was expelled in February after his arrest and indictment on a federal bribery charge, will return to the council for a term that ends in January 2029. He has pleaded not guilty to the charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02736f50-61e5-11f0-b547-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 01:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth lashed out at a top DOGE official in tense Pentagon confrontation</title>
      <description>The episode in April, which has not been reported previously, was sparked by claims that a team leader with Elon Musk’s cost-cutting organization had summoned law enforcement to remove a subordinate from the Pentagon installation, people familiar with the matter said. Hegseth, these people said, deemed it an unacceptable overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcc2f90-61d7-11f0-bfba-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to automate the work of federal employees. Here are 6 agencies to watch.</title>
      <description>The Pentagon, IRS and other federal agencies are rapidly adopting AI tools to improve efficiency, an idea championed by Elon Musk that could replace some government workers with technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e7cf30-61d3-11f0-aa71-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William H. McRaven writes in an op-ed: Cuts to the State Department and USAID will put every American at risk</title>
      <description>Soft power for a tough world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012a44f0-61ce-11f0-a925-000a1ace3781</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Mike Johnson and other Republicans break with Trump administration on Epstein files as Democrats call for documents' release</title>
      <description>Johnson (R-Louisiana) called for the Justice Department to release any files related to convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein just days after the Trump administration effectively declared the matter closed. Johnson's interview was released moments after House GOP leaders barely defeated a Democratic effort to force a House vote to release the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86db6c60-61b4-11f0-ab7a-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3222240-6197-11f0-949b-000a1ace7963</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 16:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Severance,’ ‘The Penguin,’ ‘The White Lotus’ and ‘The Studio’ lead the Emmy nominations. See the list here.</title>
      <description>The annual awards show honoring the best in TV is set to take place Sept. 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90b43a71-6194-11f0-8f80-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 244 people Trump proposed for his $40 million hero garden, including a few surprises</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump first proposed the “National Garden of American Heroes” during the racial justice protests of 2020, when many Confederate monuments were being toppled. Now it has the funds to become a reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35291eb0-6184-11f0-bc47-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An interactive performance in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">118f0860-6180-11f0-ab82-0000a1aceb40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation heated up in June, as Trump’s tariffs began to pressure more sectors in the economy</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed that inflation picked up momentum in June, after months of progress bringing prices under control, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbdcb20-6177-11f0-8aa0-0000a1ace936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Putin. ICE’s bond order. Education cuts. Camp Mystic. Wildfire smoke. Elmo hacked. Solar eruptions. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db6e4530-616a-11f0-8d84-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE declares millions of undocumented immigrants no longer eligible for bond hearings</title>
      <description>A memo sent by ICE’s acting director and obtained by The Washington Post instructs officers to hold immigrants who entered the country illegally “for the duration of their removal proceedings,” which can take months or years. Lawyers say the policy will apply to millions of immigrants who crossed the U.S.-Mexico border over the past few decades, including under former president Joe Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27679210-6112-11f0-b2ca-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump administration to proceed with deep cuts at Education Department, for now</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a temporary lower-court ruling that prevented Trump officials from slashing more than a third of the department’s more than 4,100 workers and shifting some of its functions to the states and other departments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaf15170-60eb-11f0-9fb7-0000a1acef70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 19:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Distance from critical mom comes with guilt for not trying harder</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Distance from critical mom comes with guilt for not trying harder</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5b89000-60cb-11f0-8eae-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens new tariffs and sanctions on Russia and announces European countries will buy U.S. weapons to send to Ukraine</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte made the announcement Monday during a meeting at the White House. The move to increase support for Kyiv follows Trump’s frustration with Russian President Vladimir Putin’s continued bombardment of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc594b1-60c7-11f0-9d54-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quite the discovery in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1a792e0-60b6-11f0-81f7-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camp Mystic waited over an hour to evacuate after receiving ‘life threatening’ flood alert</title>
      <description>Interviews with nearly two dozen counselors, emergency officials, parents and experts reveal that as Camp Mystic Executive Director Dick Eastland conferred with family members and other employees about how to respond to the alert, the camp descended into chaos as the river rose to record levels.

Water was at least four feet high around many of the cabins, a Washington Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0675270-60af-11f0-b920-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA warning. ICE deportations. Israeli strike. Texas floods. Air quality. Jannik Sinner. Dinosaur bones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d43c20-60a1-11f0-a729-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Trump assassination attempt supercharged beliefs in a divine right of MAGA</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and many of his followers have described the rally shooting on July 13, 2024, as a mass spiritual awakening, promoting the belief that Trump enacts God’s will.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46cd0c00-603d-11f0-b582-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 23:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After franchise upheaval, Washington Nationals select infielder Eli Willits with the No. 1 pick in the MLB draft</title>
      <description>The selection of Willits, a 17-year-old high school shortstop from Oklahoma, came just one week after Washington fired its longtime general manager, Mike Rizzo. Mike DeBartolo has taken the helm as interim GM of the Nationals, who also fired manager Dave Martinez. The Nationals previously used No. 1 picks on Bryce Harper and Stephen Strasburg, setting a high bar for their choice this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1e829e0-6037-11f0-8c3f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 22:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A clinic blames its closing on Trump’s Medicaid cuts. Some patients don’t buy it.</title>
      <description>A clinic in rural Nebraska has become a political flash point after tying its pending closure to Trump’s law cutting Medicaid. Residents of Curtis — a one-stoplight town in deep-red farm country — are sorry to lose the clinic but skeptical of the rationale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95a8b40-602f-11f0-8c59-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 21:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jannik Sinner wins first Wimbledon championship and fourth Grand Slam title, denying Carlos Alcaraz a third straight victory there</title>
      <description>It was the first appearance in the Wimbledon final for Sinner, the 23-year-old Italian who avenged his loss to Alcaraz at last month's French Open. He and Alcaraz, a 22-year-old from Spain, have combined to win the last seven men’s Grand Slam titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40694340-6017-11f0-9b1d-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service tells its gift shops to remove anything that ‘disparages Americans’</title>
      <description>Park staff were ordered to report any retail items containing content that “inappropriately disparages Americans past or living” or that includes “matters unrelated to the beauty, abundance or grandeur” of a natural feature in its description. The move is part of the administration’s wider campaign to scrub federal institutions of “corrosive ideology” recognizing historical racism and sexism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5658db0-600b-11f0-aa7e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 17:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae4899c0-6002-11f0-ac06-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 16:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six less-expensive beach vacations in the U.S., from Georgia to California</title>
      <description>Even if we’re not exploring the Mediterranean or living it up at an all-inclusive resort in Mexico, we still crave the beach — especially one relatively close to home that won’t eat up our vacation funds. We asked professional travel planners for help identifying these top budget picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">588c0410-5ff6-11f0-aa9d-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 14:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95887a90-5fee-11f0-9140-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 13:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE memo outlines plan to deport migrants to countries where they are not citizens</title>
      <description>Federal immigration officers may deport immigrants with as little as six hours’ notice to countries other than their own even if officials have not provided any assurances that the new arrivals will be safe from persecution or torture, a top official said in a memo this week. The dramatic shift in policy could result in thousands of people being sent to places where they lack family ties or even a common language.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ab604d0-5f87-11f0-ad55-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He knows he was adopted from South Korea. When he started digging into his past, red flags emerged.</title>
      <description>For years, Aaron Grzegorczyk thought his birth mother had left him at a South Korean clinic in 1988. A recent report found the country had allowed a “profit-driven” adoption “industry” to flourish for decades, leaving Grzegorczyk wondering whether he’s yet another victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b873291-5f6f-11f0-9ed1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
