<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 02:15:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses Alec Baldwin’s manslaughter case in 'Rust' shooting, saying prosecutors failed to provide defense with evidence</title>
      <description>The shocking dismissal came after defense lawyers claimed that investigators had improperly withheld potential evidence that would have helped Baldwin's defense in the 2021 fatal shooting of Halyna Hutchins on a film set.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cce00010-409d-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI rushed through safety tests, undermining its White House AI pledge</title>
      <description>The start-up promised the White House it would rigorously safety-test new versions of its tech to make sure it wouldn’t inflict damage. But this spring, some members of OpenAI’s safety team felt pressured to speed through a new testing protocol, designed to prevent the technology from causing catastrophic harm, to meet a May launch date set by company leaders, according to three people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity for fear of retaliation. The previously unreported incident sheds light on the changing culture at OpenAI, where company leaders including CEO Sam Altman have been accused of prioritizing commercial interests over public safety — a stark departure from the company’s roots as an altruistic nonprofit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeeda460-4091-11ef-9bf6-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out Giuliani’s bankruptcy case, making it easier for former election workers he defamed to try to seize his assets</title>
      <description>A federal judge in New York threw out Rudy Giuliani’s bankruptcy case and paved the way for a litany of creditors, including two former Georgia election workers who won a $148 million defamation claim against him, to pursue and potentially seize his assets. They and other creditors have accused the former New York mayor of using the proceedings to avoid paying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fec74b00-4080-11ef-8915-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole almost everyone’s AT&amp;T phone records. What should you do?</title>
      <description>Here’s what you need to know about AT&amp;T’s massive data breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f9a9750-4071-11ef-849d-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My husband never wants to visit my family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My husband never wants to visit my family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffe7f7e1-406d-11ef-a0c0-000a1aceb390</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. sent text apologizing to woman who accused him of sexual assault</title>
      <description>Eliza Cooney called the unsolicited late-night message from Kennedy “disingenuous and arrogant.” In a message that Cooney shared with The Washington Post, the independent presidential candidate told Cooney that he did not recall the incident but that any harm he caused was “inadvertent.” Cooney has described inappropriate behavior and sexual advances from Kennedy when she worked as his family’s weekend nanny in the late 1990s, including an incident in which Kennedy approached her from behind and allegedly groped her in a pantry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eecb460-405a-11ef-bae3-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c35f66c0-4052-11ef-bdde-0000a1acebc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch live: Post journalists join expanded edition of ‘First Look’ with Jonathan Capehart to discuss 2024 election</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters and columnists discuss President Biden’s make-or-break stretch in his 2024 campaign, the countdown to the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee, the pending announcement of Donald Trump’s running mate and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3caa4f0-404e-11ef-9fdd-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden mix-ups. Trump immunity. Texas blackouts. Gaza pier. Shelley Duvall. Gatorade lawsuit. Playful whales. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e316ce00-403d-11ef-b4bb-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Biden mostly handled a crucial news conference, but a few key moments could still give his party pause</title>
      <description>Five takeaways from a performance that played to the president’s foreign-policy strengths but also included stumbles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1df9ea0-3ff7-11ef-b5f5-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 02:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden holds a news conference amid rising calls within his party to drop out. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Two weeks after a disastrous performance in the first general-election debate that left Democratic officials, donors and voters with doubts about the president’s ability to defeat Donald Trump and serve another term, Biden will take reporters’ questions.
All eyes will be on how the president handles the unscripted question-and-answer session with reporters, as more lawmakers in recent days have called for him to leave the party’s ticket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">184a4ea0-3fdd-11ef-895b-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 23:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump seeks dismissal of N.Y. charges and conviction, citing Supreme Court’s sweeping ruling on presidential immunity</title>
      <description>Trump is seeking to toss out the guilty verdict after the Supreme Court ruled that a president’s official conduct cannot be used as evidence against him. In a court filing, Trump’s lawyers said Trump’s tweets and testimony from two White House aides should not have been allowed at his New York hush money trial, where he was convicted of 34 counts of falsifying business records in an attempt to impact the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4362de0-3fd3-11ef-91ec-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 22:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. has a plan to protect millions of workers from heat. Here’s whom it would safeguard.</title>
      <description>Some 500,000 agricultural workers and 4.3 million construction workers nationwide could receive greater heat protections under a new OSHA proposal, according to a Washington Post analysis. The plan, which would require rest breaks for employees when the heat index tops 90 degrees, faces industry opposition, but it could be transformative for workers — especially in the South.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">896c6750-3fb8-11ef-b5ce-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 19:05:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s military admits ‘severe mistakes’ in defending border kibbutz in first probe of Oct. 7 failings</title>
      <description>The results of an internal Israel Defense Forces investigation said its troops failed to protect residents of Kibbutz Beeri during the Hamas attack that killed as many as 1,200 people in Israel. Some army units waited outside as the massacre unfolded, the report said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">733db9b0-3faa-11ef-8144-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Tara: Waking up to pee often? It might be a different problem. We’re taking your sleep questions.</title>
      <description>Ask Tara: Waking up to pee often? It might be a different problem. We’re taking your sleep questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56e7c70-3fa9-11ef-9b98-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 17:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shelley Duvall dies at 75. The versatile actress became a face of 1970s film and was chased by Jack Nicholson in ‘The Shining.’</title>
      <description>Duvall was among the most distinctive actresses to emerge out of the so-called New Hollywood era of the late 1960s and ’70s, when directors were making personal, idiosyncratic films that ran counter to the old studio mold. Discovered by director Robert Altman at a party in Houston, she appeared in many of his acclaimed ensemble-driven movies, including “Brewster McCloud,” “McCabe &amp; Mrs. Miller” and “Nashville.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3741760-3fa1-11ef-b069-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:22:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it controlling for boyfriend to ask not to be written about?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it controlling for boyfriend to ask not to be written about?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be0b50d0-3f9e-11ef-8f2f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A six-day workweek in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e04fcb90-3f89-11ef-8f2f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 13:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual inflation eased further in June, widening the Fed’s path to a rate cut</title>
      <description>Inflation continues to trend downward from highs of two years ago, although some categories, including rent, have made slower progress. Fed watchers and financial markets are eyeing a potential cut in September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbc7f320-3f81-11ef-a9fb-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 12:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Democrats want Biden to drop out, but overall presidential race is static, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>The Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll finds that 56 percent of Democrats say that President Biden should end his candidacy, while 42 percent say he should continue to seek reelection. Biden and former president Donald Trump are in a dead heat in the contest for the popular vote, with both candidates receiving 46 percent support among registered voters. Those numbers are nearly identical to the results of an ABC-Ipsos poll in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0daef550-3f78-11ef-9b0f-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign. Trump and NATO. Abortion rights. Gaza bombs. Heat deaths. Three Mile Island. ‘Simpsons’ joke. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb083c10-3f74-11ef-a9db-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Biden administration appears close to a Gaza cease-fire deal, a senior U.S. official tells David Ignatius</title>
      <description>U.S. officials say the framework of a three-stage deal is down to implementation details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e899490-3f1b-11ef-923c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2024 00:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden should provide evidence he can beat Trump after politically disastrous debate, Democratic leaders say</title>
      <description>The calls came as union leaders, more lawmakers and even some Biden campaign staff members expressed grave concerns about his candidacy. Democrats say the defections are likely to increase in the coming days, as additional lawmakers and donors privately signal that they may publicly call for Biden to step aside for another nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66a45c61-3f17-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘For the good of the country, I’m calling on President Biden to withdraw from the race,’ Democratic Sen. Peter Welch writes</title>
      <description>"The stakes this November could not be higher," the Vermont Democrat writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96cf3d60-3f12-11ef-8915-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 23:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregg Berhalter is out as U.S. men's national soccer team coach after early Copa América exit</title>
      <description>With arguably the most talented roster in program history, the U.S. men's team fared well in regional competition this year but stumbled under this summer’s bright lights. Berhalter's squad made a disappointing early exit at Copa América, flaming out in the group stage with losses to Panama and Uruguay. The move comes two years before the United States will be one of the hosts of the 2026 World Cup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88b6bf10-3f0c-11ef-8e1a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 22:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme heat has killed at least 27 people in the U.S. in the past week. Experts say the true death toll is certain to rise.</title>
      <description>The searing heat wave that has gripped much of the United States in recent days is suspected of killing dozens of people, according to state officials, medical examiners and media reports.

Many of the deaths were in California and Oregon, but the actual number is difficult to track because of variations in how states and counties investigate fatalities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ebea5d0-3f03-11ef-ab29-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 21:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP jump-starts 2024 election challenges with Trump-inspired lawsuits in key swing states</title>
      <description>Republicans have moved to challenge voting procedures since presumptive nominee Donald Trump installed new leaders at the party's central committee. Democrats view the lawsuits as legally frivolous but still damaging to public confidence and a potential precursor to efforts to overturn the vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78221e31-3efb-11ef-b5f5-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 20:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. area until 10 p.m., with damaging winds possible. A break in the heat could follow.</title>
      <description>A line of storms is likely to approach the region around sunset and could contain damaging winds in addition to heavy rain and lightning. An isolated tornado cannot be ruled out. The storms and weak cold front passing will help lower the heat and humidity on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3119a100-3ee9-11ef-8915-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 18:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The great burger debate: To smash or not to smash? Our food writers are taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>The great burger debate: To smash or not to smash? Our food writers are taking your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bf146e1-3edb-11ef-8833-0000a1ace74c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:43:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Clooney calls for Biden to leave ticket, weeks after the actor co-hosted a star-studded fundraiser for the campaign</title>
      <description>Clooney said in a Wednesday op-ed in the New York Times that he “love[s]” the 81-year-old President Biden but argued that Biden’s age has imperiled his reelection bid against former president Donald Trump.

“It’s devastating to say it, but the Joe Biden I was with three weeks ago at the fund-raiser was not the Joe ‘big F-ing deal’ Biden of 2010,” Clooney wrote. “He wasn’t even the Joe Biden of 2020. He was the same man we all witnessed at the debate.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98b77540-3ed9-11ef-bd31-0000a1ace445</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents ‘very opinionated’ about how their children’s partners look</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents ‘very opinionated’ about how their children’s partners look</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">874aff11-3ed5-11ef-a523-0000a1acef7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A group of Republican women in Texas begged their party to back off on abortion. Then came the backlash.</title>
      <description>The fight waged at the Texas Republican Convention highlights the deep divisions on abortion within the Republican Party as the GOP's national convention looms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a699df0-3ecc-11ef-9d5d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 14:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t cuddle this animal in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f742050-3ec0-11ef-9264-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Mile Island’s owner is weighing a revival of the nuclear plant, site of 1979 partial meltdown, to meet surging energy demands</title>
      <description>The plant along the Susquehanna River in Pennsylvania is part of a burst of fresh activity at mothballed plants as tech companies, manufacturers and energy regulators scramble to find enough zero emissions electricity to keep up with demand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf31d5b1-3ebd-11ef-80f4-0000a1ace8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 13:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden concerns. NATO summit. Dvontaye Mitchell. Power outages. Boeing incident. Plague. Tourism protest. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">900178c0-3eab-11ef-83f9-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This House race reflects how the Supreme Court has narrowed options for Black voters</title>
      <description>The high court gave the go-ahead for a South Carolina district that a lower court had deemed an unconstitutional racial gerrymander. Now a Black Democrat is campaigning against the odds to win the seat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c87b4460-3e42-11ef-83c3-0000a1ace3d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 22:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. is under an excessive heat warning as indexes climb above 110</title>
      <description>The combination of heat and humidity is among the most extreme in the United States. The long-range forecast shows little relief amid what's been the region's second-hottest start to a summer on record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ae36a10-3e23-11ef-a675-0000a1ace286</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 18:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Marriage at breaking point over husband’s approach to addicted son</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Marriage at breaking point over husband’s approach to addicted son</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">354c1410-3e0d-11ef-95ce-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 16:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Out of a coconut tree and into today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a9546c0-3df9-11ef-9b4e-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a first, federal regulators ban anonymous messaging app from allowing minors on the platform</title>
      <description>In a groundbreaking settlement, the Federal Trade Commission accused the app NGL of exaggerating its ability to use artificial intelligence to curb cyberbullying and aggressively marketing to young users despite risks. NGL, internet shorthand for “not gonna lie,” agreed to pay $5 million and to stop marketing to kids and teens to settle the lawsuit, marking a milestone in the federal government’s efforts to tackle concerns that tech platforms are profiting from exposing noxious material to youths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a19ad4f0-3df7-11ef-994d-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 13:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO summit. Biden support. Beryl damage. Israeli offensive. Baldwin trial. Ticks. Free tuition. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">618d2d00-3de2-11ef-99b0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could you pass a math test for fourth-, eighth- and 12th-graders? Take our quiz and get your score.</title>
      <description>The pandemic reversed years of academic progress for children across the country. They’re bouncing back, but a full recovery is still a long way off, experts predict.
This quiz features some math questions on the National Assessment of Educational Progress, commonly called “the nation’s report card.” How do you stack up?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b3ef660-3d6d-11ef-a70a-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 2.6 million are without power and at least two people have died as Beryl moves through Houston. Follow our live updates.</title>
      <description>Beryl was downgraded to a tropical storm Monday morning, the National Hurricane Center said, after making landfall as a Category 1 hurricane. The storm continues to pound Houston and the surrounding area with intense winds and rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8993da90-3d49-11ef-afb5-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom sees different parenting styles as critiques of her own choices</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom sees different parenting styles as critiques of her own choices</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95eaa220-3d43-11ef-a8c3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes scaled-back platform that softens language on abortion, same-sex marriage</title>
      <description>The document, which is set to be discussed and voted on ahead of the GOP national convention in Milwaukee, hews to former president Donald Trump’s current position on abortion being an issue that should be decided by states — a departure from previous years when the party called for a nationwide restriction. It also affirms GOP support for deporting millions of undocumented immigrants, embracing tariffs and ending the Education Department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2088b221-3d42-11ef-a08d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No one had ever charged a school shooter’s parents with homicide. She did it anyway.</title>
      <description>A Post reporter embedded with Michigan prosecutor Karen McDonald as she pursued involuntary manslaughter charges against Jennifer and James Crumbley, whose 15-year-old son killed four students at Oxford High School. Go behind the scenes to see what it took for McDonald and her team to make legal history in a case few believed they could win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c144890-3d3d-11ef-80f4-0000a1ace8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s described as ‘boring’ but ‘sensible’ in today’s On the Record?</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d34c61-3d2e-11ef-8c94-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Beryl. France election. Biden concerns. Boeing plea deal. Russian troops. Coco Gauff. Koala cuddles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4148edf1-3d19-11ef-8fab-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beryl makes landfall near Matagorda, Tex., as a Category 1 hurricane</title>
      <description>Beryl came ashore at 4 a.m. Central time with peak winds of 80 mph. The storm is forecast to produce a “life-threatening” ocean surge and damaging hurricane-force winds. It is the first Atlantic hurricane to make landfall in the United States this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7a983b0-3d09-11ef-84a2-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing agrees to plead guilty to conspiring to defraud the government in a case linked to two jet crashes that killed 346 people</title>
      <description>Prosecutors alleged two Boeing pilots concealed key information from the government about a new automated control system aboard the 737 Max aircraft that was implicated in two fatal crashes in 2018 and 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c80a8180-3cdf-11ef-9e05-000a1acef361</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
