<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 11:04:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sanae Takaichi is set to become Japan’s first female prime minister</title>
      <description>The new leader will take the helm of the world’s fourth-largest economy at a time of unusual political instability, rising prices and increasing regional tensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40353110-a0e8-11f0-994d-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 06:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Kavanaugh assassination plotter sentenced to eight years in prison</title>
      <description>Nicholas Roske, 29, had flown across the country, with a gun packed in a suitcase, intending to break into the justice’s Maryland home to kill him. The punishment was 22 years less than the minimum of 30 years sought by prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cdd3d40-a0a4-11f0-8440-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs sentenced to 50 months in prison</title>
      <description>The judge will also fine Combs $500,000, and impose five years of supervised release once he completes his sentence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">973bd060-a09b-11f0-9f17-0000a1aceb72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas accepts Trump’s plan to end Israel’s war in Gaza but with conditions</title>
      <description>The plan aims to secure the release of Israeli hostages held in the Gaza Strip and end a two-year conflict that has reduced much of the enclave to rubble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97d3d960-a095-11f0-88f2-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. kills four more alleged drug smugglers near Venezuela, Hegseth says</title>
      <description>Questions remain as to the legal justification underpinning the administration’s ongoing attacks targeting Latin American drug cartels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6253ed40-a084-11f0-84f2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Abigail Spanberger holds wide lead in Virginia governor’s race, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Spanberger leads Republican Winsome Earle-Sears by double digits in the contest for governor, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll of Virginia voters, picking up strong support from independent voters as well as those who are worried about the state’s job market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13984a80-a079-11f0-a614-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I handle my mother-in-law correcting my kids?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I handle my mother-in-law correcting my kids?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deb128b0-a077-11f0-b58e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean “Diddy” Combs to be sentenced and is expected to speak in court for first time since his arrest. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Prosecutors want the music producer to be imprisoned for more than 11 years following his conviction in the prostitution case, arguing at trial earlier this year that he used beatings, blackmail and drugs to abuse two girlfriends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb83c9d0-a066-11f0-8330-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Blurb: Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80b629f0-a05d-11f0-ac4b-000a1acecc9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS News to name Bari Weiss, a frequent critic of mainstream media, as its top editor</title>
      <description>The newly formed media giant Paramount Skydance will acquire the Free Press, an online publication, and install its founder as editor in chief, according to two people familiar with the matter. The move heralds a new era at the 98-year-old broadcast network, whose corporate parents had sought to address the Trump administration’s allegations of liberal bias.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5b7d8e0-a05b-11f0-9486-0000a1acebfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. monthly jobs report won’t be released today due to the shutdown. Here’s why the data was much anticipated.</title>
      <description>Three days into the government shutdown, it’s increasingly unclear where the U.S. economy is headed — not because of a direct hit from the federal closures, but a lack of official data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ae67a0-a055-11f0-b282-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 12:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate votes. Abortion pill. Trump and colleges. Manchester attack. Balin Miller. AI toxins. Taylor Swift. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e03cb60-a048-11f0-9f17-0000a1aceb72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift’s new album: A guide to the songs everyone is talking about</title>
      <description>“The Life of a Showgirl,” which dropped Friday, is an ode to the superstar’s life behind the scenes on her record-breaking Eras Tour. And it has some eyebrow-raising lyrics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c6461d0-a044-11f0-b284-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 10:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to live to 117? Researchers find clues in the world’s oldest woman.</title>
      <description>A new study offers insights about what made Maria Branyas Morera exceptional — and what it could mean for the rest of us.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaabb0a0-9fdb-11f0-a48e-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 22:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. in ‘armed conflict’ with drug cartels, Trump tells Congress</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is seeking legal justification for strikes on what it has claimed are Venezuelan drug traffickers at sea. Some lawmakers and legal experts have said the notification is dubious cover for what have been unlawful military strikes on alleged civilian criminals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d08878-9fcf-11f0-8daa-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration quietly approved a new abortion drug, infuriating the right</title>
      <description>The FDA has little power to reject generic versions of approved drugs, but that hasn’t stopped an outcry from abortion opponents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d9d4c90-9fcd-11f0-8daa-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 20:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents blatantly favored brother, so all elder care is on him</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents blatantly favored brother, so all elder care is on him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76747b40-9fa9-11f0-949e-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior government officials privately warn federal agencies against firings during shutdown</title>
      <description>Senior officials have quietly counseled several agencies against firing employees while the government is shut down — as President Donald Trump has suggested he will — warning the strategy may violate appropriations law, according to two people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5fc790-9fa5-11f0-ab59-0000a1ace589</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know your halftime shows in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dbfb170-9f94-11f0-8172-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We asked 1,000 Americans who they blame for the shutdown. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>The Post’s poll finds significantly more Americans blame President Donald Trump and congressional Republicans for the shutdown than Democrats, though many say they are not sure. A large majority support Democrats’ call to extend federal health insurance subsidies in general, though just under half support the party demanding this if it extends the government shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae759f61-9f8b-11f0-aedd-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attack at synagogue on Yom Kippur leaves two dead in England</title>
      <description>Police officers shot a suspect who had rammed a car into some victims and stabbed others outside the synagogue in Manchester, police said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93a85f30-9f84-11f0-b5c5-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:40:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadlock. Lie detector tests. Trump firings. Gaza flotilla. Jane Goodall. Warm October. Living longer. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebcf1c41-9f7e-11f0-9c05-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 10:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots are learning to make human babies. Twenty have already been born.</title>
      <description>According to the World Health Organization, one in six adults experiences infertility. Can groundbreaking automation help answer their prayers?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">542ce290-9f16-11f0-887d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House fires much of the National Council on the Humanities</title>
      <description>Fired council members described the terminations as abrupt. An agency website listed only four Trump appointees remaining on the board, which advises the National Endowment for the Humanities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3cb8ad0-9efe-11f0-a5a2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Goodall dies at 91. Her long-term study of wild chimpanzees led her to see them as individuals.</title>
      <description>Jane Goodall’s startling observations about chimpanzee behaviors — from making tools to making war — revolutionized not only scientific understanding of the capabilities and inner lives of our simian cousins, but also long-held notions about what it means to be human.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7da31780-9ef2-11f0-a687-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Bonding over estranged daughters now feels like a competition</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Bonding over estranged daughters now feels like a competition</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10a88d70-9ee0-11f0-91b2-000a1ace93d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plans widespread random polygraph testing and nondisclosure agreements to stanch leaks</title>
      <description>The Pentagon is planning to require thousands of uniformed officials and civilian personnel to sign nondisclosure agreements and submit to random polygraph testing, according to two officials and documents obtained by The Washington Post. The moves come as Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth ramps up restrictions on media and a war on leakers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa5fa010-9edc-11f0-bc23-000a1ace5fc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How our critic decides where to eat</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How our critic decides where to eat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f484520-9edc-11f0-a446-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Lisa Cook to stay on Fed Board for now</title>
      <description>The justices denied President Donald Trump’s request to allow him to remove Cook immediately. The court will hear arguments in the case later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df2a3d50-9ed7-11f0-b2e6-0000a1ace120</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 100,000-mile check-up in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7c7d530-9eca-11f0-9388-0000a1aced81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government shutdown. Pete Hegseth. Drug prices. Abortion pills. Comedy controversy. Delivery bots. Fat Bear Week. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccb616c0-9eb5-11f0-aa8f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They scaled the equivalent of Mt. Everest in 36 hours, carrying with them scars, belief, bricks and the memory of a 3-year-old boy</title>
      <description>For most, the pull was less about prizes than about something deeper. For them, the mountain is a metaphor — a physical challenge, but also a mental and spiritual trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8aa729c1-9e62-11f0-a0f1-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 01:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House withdraws the nomination of E.J. Antoni to run the Bureau of Labor Statistics</title>
      <description>Trump nominated Antoni after firing the previous BLS chief, after he accused her of manipulating jobs report data, which came in weaker than expected. Antoni’s nomination appeared uncertain in the Senate, which had yet to schedule a confirmation hearing. A White House official said that the administration looked forward to nominating a new candidate soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a63ea10-9e60-11f0-959e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The government will shut down at 12:01 a.m., after Senate Democrats blocked a Republican bill to extend the funding deadline</title>
      <description>It’s the first shutdown since 2018-2019. Democrats say they won’t vote to fund the government unless Republicans agree to extend expiring health care subsidies. The GOP says Democrats are holding the government hostage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14e70010-9e54-11f0-911f-0000a1ace485</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORRECTION: The Trump administration illegally arrested and sought to deport international students for their pro-Palestinian activism, judge rules. A previous alert incorrectly stated that the students in the case were deported.</title>
      <description>A previous alert headline incorrectly stated the Trump administration had illegally deported international students for their pro-Palestinian activism. No students in the case have yet been deported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b9cbb0-9e2b-11f0-abf4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration illegally arrested and deported international students for their pro-Palestinian activism, judge rules</title>
      <description>In a blistering rebuke of the administration, U.S. District Judge William Young said that the push to deport noncitizens for their activism against Israel's war in Gaza was a “truly scandalous and unconstitutional suppression of free speech.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e6e65e0-9e25-11f0-bfea-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump delivers highly partisan presentation at unprecedented gathering to U.S. military leaders who remained mostly silent</title>
      <description>The hastily organized event became a forum for President Donald Trump to tout his political agenda while Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth lectured the brass on standards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee1785f0-9e1b-11f0-bf84-0000a1ace8b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is insomnia putting you at a higher risk of dementia? Ask our brain health expert.</title>
      <description>Richard Sima is chatting with readers about how to reduce your risk of dementia. Send in your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb2bc30-9e10-11f0-bf97-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropping out in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d15d1660-9e01-11f0-a5bf-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth begins his address to senior military leaders; Trump expected to follow. See our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The extraordinary meeting with hundreds of senior U.S. military officers at Marine Corps Base Quantico in Virginia was ordered by Hegseth last week, requiring some top generals and admirals to fly thousands of miles on short notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dd7da00-9df7-11f0-b9f3-0000a1ace6b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. Military meeting. Gaza plan. Stranded aid. YouTube settlement. Dangerous heat. Landlines. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6089b70-9dec-11f0-89d0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will mining destroy America’s most-visited wilderness?</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is moving quickly to approve a mine next to the Boundary Waters that many fear will pollute the pristine wilderness area in Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e301fc0-9d94-11f0-9f6e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lally Weymouth dies at 82. The Post journalist, a member of the storied Graham family, interviewed presidents and prime ministers.</title>
      <description>As the granddaughter, daughter, sister and mother of five different Washington Post publishers, Weymouth moved in social circles that helped shape American media and government.
While her younger brother Donald E. Graham was tapped to succeed their mother, Katharine Graham, as publisher of The Post in the 1970s, Weymouth initially pursued a career outside the paper. She joined The Post in 1986, eventually rising to become a senior associate editor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83d191d0-9d8b-11f0-9f6e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military leaders have raised concerns over Hegseth’s new Pentagon strategy, exposing divide among officials ahead of defense summit</title>
      <description>The critiques from multiple top officers, including Gen. Dan Caine, chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, come as Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth reorders U.S. military priorities — focusing the Pentagon on perceived threats to the homeland, narrowing competition with China, and downplaying America’s role in Europe and Africa, according to people familiar with the classified planning document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">249a7220-9d88-11f0-938d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will pay $24.5 million to settle Trump lawsuit over company’s decision in 2021 to remove his account after Jan. 6 attack</title>
      <description>The agreement says that President Donald Trump has directed YouTube to contribute $22 million of the settlement to help construct the new White House ballroom. The rest of the money will go to a handful of other plaintiffs who accused YouTube of censoring them. The settlement follows similar deals earlier this year with social platforms Meta and X, which also suspended or blocked Trump’s accounts after the Jan. 6, 2021, attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b74cbe00-9d80-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu agrees to Trump peace deal. If Hamas refuses, Trump offers Israel full support to keep fighting.</title>
      <description>The plan, which is subject to approval by Hamas, would require an immediate ceasefire as well as the release of all remaining Israeli hostages within 72 hours of both sides agreeing to the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82d0ab0-9d66-11f0-a9a2-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding for federal agencies expires tomorrow night. Here's how this potential shutdown may differ from previous ones.</title>
      <description>Broad swaths of the federal government — from national parks to small business loans to taxpayer services — could go offline this week unless lawmakers and President Donald Trump strike a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c70b8830-9d58-11f0-9a38-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26144d41-9d4e-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7d13c70-9d48-11f0-af6a-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing work from this platform in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4352b60-9d38-11f0-a4a3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
