<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 08:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ICE memo details how Trump officials will try to deport more than 1 million migrants admitted during the Biden administration</title>
      <description>By expanding use of the "expedited removal" law — from within 100 miles of a border to the entire country — the Trump administration will try to remove more than 1 million migrants admitted to the United States when President Joe Biden was in office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8a124d1-f633-11ef-bc4f-0000a1aceb37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Hackman likely died nine days before his body was found, sheriff says</title>
      <description>Data from the pacemaker of Oscar-winning actor Gene Hackman indicates he died on Feb. 17, nine days before investigators found his body and that of his wife Betsy Arakawa in their New Mexico home, said Santa Fe County Sheriff Adan Mendoza. Carbon monoxide poisoning has been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39f41671-f627-11ef-89cc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS rejected request from immigration officials for addresses of suspected undocumented immigrants, people tell The Post</title>
      <description>Homeland Security officials made the request recently and also sought skilled auditors to investigate businesses believed to be employing undocumented workers, a sign of a shift in how the government is pursuing its enforcement actions. The IRS is legally barred from sharing taxpayer information even with other government departments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde11ac0-f61c-11ef-8f5a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump cancels news conference with Zelensky after heated Oval Office meeting</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky emerged from the West Wing after President Donald Trump and Vice President JD Vance accused him of being insufficiently grateful for U.S. support.
“He disrespected the United States of America in its cherished Oval Office,” Trump wrote on social media. “He can come back when he is ready for Peace.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1424a531-f605-11ef-b61f-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Zelensky Oval Office meeting turns contentious ahead of scheduled news conference. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky asked President Donald Trump what his message is for allies worried that he’s aligned too closely with Russian President Vladimir Putin. Trump raised his voice, calling Zelensky “disrespectful” and saying, “You don’t have the cards” because of Ukraine’s weakened military position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb752a30-f5fd-11ef-8aaf-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMI won’t renew superintendent’s contract. Cedric Wins, the college’s first Black leader, faced criticism over DEI policies.</title>
      <description>Wins, a retired Army major general, was appointed superintendent of the Virginia Military Institute in 2021, after months as its interim leader and amid scrutiny of incidents of racism at the nation’s oldest state-supported military college. His contract was set to expire at the end of June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">057fa9e0-f5f5-11ef-89ef-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75142a71-f5e0-11ef-b8e8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s firings. Zelensky visit. Gene Hackman investigation. Trans rights. Epstein files. Planet parade. The Oscars. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89b01801-f5cb-11ef-830b-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The federal government plans to send workers a second “What did you do last week?” email. It might require a response.</title>
      <description>The message is set to come from individual agencies rather than from the centralized Office of Personnel Management. Multiple departments and offices told employees not to respond to an initial email last weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3b1b2f2-f5c7-11ef-8092-0000a1ace600</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI is investigating EPA’s claims of fraud in $20 billion Biden-era climate fund, escalating a contentious criminal probe</title>
      <description>A prosecutor resigned. Another refused to seek a warrant. A judge said there wasn’t enough evidence. But Citibank appears to have frozen up to $20 billion in grants as a Justice Department probe continues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3360e1-f575-11ef-90e9-0000a1ace2c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa is poised to become the first state to revoke nondiscrimination protections for transgender people</title>
      <description>The state Senate and House debated for several hours before passing the legislation overwhelmingly along party lines after protesters packed the Capitol on Thursday. The governor is expected to sign the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a99a060-f572-11ef-89ee-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five former defense secretaries denounce Trump’s firings of Pentagon leaders as ‘reckless’ and urge Congress to intervene</title>
      <description>In a letter to lawmakers, the former defense secretaries — having served in Republican and Democratic administrations — called President Donald Trump’s abrupt dismissal last week of the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff and six other top military officers “reckless” and implored Congress to “exercise fully its Constitutional oversight responsibilities.”

The public appeal to Congress was dated Thursday and signed by Lloyd Austin, Jim Mattis, Chuck Hagel, Leon E. Panetta and William Perry after the firings created an uproar among lawmakers and veterans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f670d101-f567-11ef-95c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump administration’s mass firings of federal workers, ruling them likely to be illegal</title>
      <description>A federal judge ruled that the terminations at several agencies, including the Department of Defense, Park Service, Bureau of Land Management, National Science Foundation and others, were probably illegal. The ruling came in a lawsuit brought by a group of union plaintiffs and advocacy organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c86abe0-f562-11ef-99e4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes, GOP senators including Lindsey Graham press Secretary of State Marco Rubio on legality of Trump’s aid freeze</title>
      <description>Graham, a close Trump ally, joined Democrats in expressing alarm. The senators have asked Rubio to defend the freeze in a hearing on Capitol Hill in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff410f10-f54f-11ef-b195-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico extradites 29 drug-trafficking suspects to the United States</title>
      <description>The announcement comes days before the Trump administration plans to impose economic sanctions related to Mexico’s failure to stop the flow of narcotics over the border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6d44cf0-f549-11ef-9870-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom’s extra work is to pay, unknowingly, for Dad’s ‘sugar babies’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom’s extra work is to pay, unknowingly, for Dad’s ‘sugar babies’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c4f65f1-f52c-11ef-a1e4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKK leader Abdullah Ocalan, imprisoned in Turkey, issues historic call for militant group to disarm and dissolve</title>
      <description>The appeal by Abdullah Ocalan raised the possibility of an end to a decades-long insurgency against Turkey that killed an estimated 40,000 people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84d0f4e0-f520-11ef-9fd9-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This food delivery app is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90605520-f517-11ef-ab04-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 14:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court. DOGE firings. Gene Hackman. Measles death. Gaza ceasefire. Egg prices. Antiaging dog pill. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56578250-f502-11ef-8742-000a1aced8fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Gene Hackman and his wife found dead in their New Mexico home, according to the Santa Fe County sheriff’s office</title>
      <description>The actor and his wife, musician Betsy Arakawa, were discovered dead Wednesday afternoon at their home, where a dog was also found deceased, the sheriff's office said, adding that there was no immediate indication of foul play and the exact cause of death had not been determined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">017a5bb1-f4ec-11ef-98dd-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 09:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court pauses midnight deadline for Trump administration to pay nearly $2 billion in foreign aid</title>
      <description>Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. granted a request by the Trump administration, which faced a lower court's 11:59 p.m. deadline for releasing the money to organizations that provide food and medical assistance overseas through the U.S. Agency for International Development.
Roberts’s brief order will give the full court time to review the case. It follows nearly two weeks of motions and hearings before U.S. District Judge Amir H. Ali, who had ordered that foreign assistance resume after President Donald Trump directed a sweeping 90-day pause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">511778e1-f4b7-11ef-bc66-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 03:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas turned over the bodies of four hostages in exchange for the release of hundreds of Palestinian prisoners</title>
      <description>The exchange is set to be the final one of the first phase of the ceasefire deal between Israel and Hamas. The fragile truce may now be entering an even more precarious juncture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f95b34e2-f4a5-11ef-ac04-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Trachtenberg dies at 39. The ‘Harriet the Spy’ star also had major roles in ‘Gossip Girl’ and ‘Buffy the Vampire Slayer.’</title>
      <description>The cause of death was not disclosed, but it was not believed to be suspicious, according to an NYPD spokesperson. Representatives for Trachtenberg did not respond to requests for comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3953b10-f472-11ef-8308-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas child is first confirmed death in state’s spreading measles outbreak, which has sickened more than 100 people</title>
      <description>An unvaccinated child was the first confirmed fatality in the state’s worst measles outbreak in three decades, Texas health officials said Wednesday. The school-aged child was hospitalized in Lubbock last week, according to the Texas Department of State Health Services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96b9d800-f469-11ef-bc66-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems poised to lower bar for White people to sue for job bias</title>
      <description>A majority of justices appeared to support making it easier for men, White people and straight people to sue for job discrimination. They heard oral arguments in the case of an Ohio woman who claims she faced anti-straight bias in the workplace, and who is challenging past rulings that set a higher bar for proving discrimination against members of non-minority groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db199040-f463-11ef-9529-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Real Housewives of Potomac’ star sentenced to 12 months for crashing Maserati while drunk</title>
      <description>After Karen Huger wrecked in Maryland, she refused a Breathalyzer. But on police video, she said, “Oh, God. I'm lit.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">489305c1-f45f-11ef-bea6-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How do I deal with my in-laws who chronically under-tip?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How do I deal with my in-laws who chronically under-tip?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">473be191-f45c-11ef-a5f5-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s business empire is built on $38 billion in government funding</title>
      <description>Musk and his businesses have received billions in government contracts, loans, subsidies and tax credits, often at critical moments, a Washington Post analysis has found, helping seed the growth that has made him the world’s richest person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89174ad0-f454-11ef-8967-0000a1aced3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 15:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Oscars throwback in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab0d720-f44e-11ef-b67c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 14:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cherry blossoms to hit peak bloom around March 25, according to Capital Weather Gang predictions</title>
      <description>Mild March temperatures will help the Tidal Basin blossoms reach full bloom several days earlier than normal. Fueled by human-caused climate change, the average peak bloom date has advanced by about a week since the 1920s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b657e580-f441-11ef-8ab9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA urges White House to repeal finding on threat of greenhouse gases, a move that could loosen restrictions for cars, power plants</title>
      <description>Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Lee Zeldin has privately told the White House to strike down the 2009 "endangerment finding," which says that greenhouse gases pose a threat to public health and welfare.  If approved, it would be one of the most consequential steps yet to derail federal efforts to combat climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7006b3f0-f43b-11ef-92af-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 12:15:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Budget plan. Musk’s empire. Ukraine’s minerals. Unknown illness. Fluoride in water. AI skepticism. ‘Canadianos.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">291240b1-f439-11ef-a4a2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes GOP budget bill, setting up talks with Senate on how to enact Trump’s agenda on taxes, immigration and safety net cuts</title>
      <description>Republicans narrowly overcame internal disagreements on a budget resolution that would extend 2017 tax cuts and could help dodge a Democratic filibuster in the Senate. But the GOP-led chambers are far apart on how to proceed from here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6368ef60-f3e0-11ef-9836-000a1ace5702</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 01:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teachers union sues to overturn Trump’s crackdown on race and DEI in schools</title>
      <description>The American Federation of Teachers accuses Trump’s Education Department of trying to rewrite civil rights law and America’s history of racist and discriminatory laws in a lawsuit filed Tuesday. The lawsuit cites a letter that the department sent to schools and colleges across the country threatening to withhold federal funding in response to any programs that aim for diversity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b861fbe0-f3c9-11ef-84eb-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 22:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine and U.S. agree to framework for mineral deal, Ukrainian official says, after rift between Zelensky and Trump</title>
      <description>The deal provides the United States preferential access to the country’s mineral deposits, a Ukrainian official says. The White House has not confirmed a deal. The Trump administration has pushed Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to repay U.S. war aid with such an agreement, amid broader pressure to come to a peace deal with Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">451a3720-f3b9-11ef-ab3a-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband says wife is overreacting to post-Roe pregnancy scare</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband says wife is overreacting to post-Roe pregnancy scare</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73b10970-f39a-11ef-86bf-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 17:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants sent to Guantánamo describe humiliating strip searches and suicide attempts</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke with three Venezuelan migrants who were detained at the U.S. military prison in Guantánamo Bay. They said they were denied calls to lawyers and loved ones, subjected to humiliating searches and left in isolation for prolonged periods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1fb8762-f391-11ef-a04d-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 16:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court orders new trial for Oklahoma death row inmate in case that centers on prosecutorial misconduct</title>
      <description>Richard Glossip’s case became a focal point in the national debate over the death penalty, which critics say is unjust or unfairly applied. His request for a new trial was backed by Oklahoma’s top law enforcement official, who agreed with the defense team that prosecutors suppressed evidence and elicited false testimony from a key witness also implicated in the 1997 murder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc484a80-f38c-11ef-bbdf-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 15:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $500 billion investment in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4d49d0-f385-11ef-ab3a-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Russia. Elon Musk. Immigration raids. DoorDash payout. Roberta Flack. Tea benefit. Fyre Festival. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe3dd800-f36f-11ef-b0b2-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration breaks with Elon Musk, telling federal agencies they can ignore his order on email reply</title>
      <description>The Office of Personnel Management told HR officials that employees wouldn’t be let go for not replying to an email asking what they did last week — nor did staff have to respond to the email. It marks a major break with the billionaire, who has exerted significant power to slash the 2.3 million-person federal workforce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67361621-f2f2-11ef-ba12-0000a1ace8f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump repeals directive that aimed to ensure allies don’t use U.S. weapons in violation of human rights laws</title>
      <description>The decision to rescind the order, which President Joe Biden imposed as his administration struggled to reconcile its support for Israel’s war against Hamas militants in the Gaza Strip and its alarm about the widespread civilian toll there, comes as the Trump administration puts its “America First” mark on U.S. foreign policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c681d040-f2ea-11ef-bc1b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clint Hill dies at 93. The Secret Service agent tried to shield President John F. Kennedy when he was assassinated.</title>
      <description>Mr. Hill dove onto Kennedy’s uncovered limousine in a heroic attempt to shield him from the fatal gunshots of Lee Harvey Oswald. “I have a great deal of guilt,” Mr. Hill later said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8965c00-f2e9-11ef-944a-0000a1ace07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Previous homeowners drop by unannounced, expecting to see inside</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Previous homeowners drop by unannounced, expecting to see inside</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">faca3880-f2d4-11ef-a2a5-0000a1ace45c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. sides with Russia to vote against a U.N. resolution condemning Moscow for the Ukraine war</title>
      <description>Washington’s dramatic shift on the conflict marks a major break with its European allies and coincides with the Trump administration’s bid to repair relations with the Kremlin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21142630-f2d1-11ef-8d0d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salena Zito is on a year-long quest to solve the riddle of Pennsylvania politics. First stop: Braddock, birthplace of U.S. steel.</title>
      <description>Two senators from opposing parties focus on the commonwealth’s industrial heritage, not politics. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f1f09c1-f2cd-11ef-82d5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberta Flack dies at 88. The Grammy-winning singer and pianist was known for hits including ‘Killing Me Softly With His Song.’</title>
      <description>Flack, a classically trained pianist, taught in the D.C. school system before launching a singing career that made her one of the most popular performers of the 1970s, with No. 1 hits including “The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23b6a200-f2c7-11ef-87de-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This magazine’s anniversary is in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7045ca0-f2bc-11ef-9012-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Dan Bongino. German election. Ukraine war. Measles outbreak. Black plastic. Weight-loss drugs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0952b60-f2a6-11ef-af9c-0000a1ace726</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several administration officials tell federal workers not to respond to Musk email demanding accounting of their work</title>
      <description>Top officials at the Defense Department, Homeland Security and HHS were among those who told employees that they don’t need to immediately comply with the request to more than 2 million workers over the weekend. Other agencies offered different guidance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0447c11-f246-11ef-9bd2-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
