<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 07:03:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agent shoots person in leg as Minneapolis protests flare</title>
      <description>In a statement, Department of Homeland Security alleged that an individual attempted to evade arrest by driving their vehicle away from federal law enforcement officers, crashing it into a parked car and then running away on foot. Both the officer and the person shot were being treated at a hospital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9db290-f1c5-11f0-8040-0000a1ace31b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She made a Facebook comment about her mayor. Then the police arrived.</title>
      <description>Raquel Pacheco says she was asserting her right to free speech. Miami Beach police said they dispatched officers to assess whether there was a safety threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8215b81-f1ad-11f0-a252-000a1ace8848</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks Venezuela war powers bill after Vance breaks deadlock</title>
      <description>The vote failed after two Republicans withdrew their previous support under intense pressure from the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">625df590-f1a8-11f0-af5e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland meeting between U.S. and Danish officials ends in standstill: ‘We didn’t manage to change the American position’</title>
      <description>Diplomats from Denmark and Greenland agreed to set up a “high-level working group” after meeting with Vice President JD Vance and Secretary of State Marco Rubio at the White House, but they said there was little agreement so far about the future of the Arctic territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">123f81c0-f18d-11f0-89c5-0000a1acef3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Iran secretly reassured each other via a Russian mediator that they would not preemptively attack</title>
      <description>The communications between Israel and Iran last month — and the role played by Russia as the intermediary — were unusual given the hostility between the two Middle Eastern rivals, which engaged in a 12-day war in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a49dd60-f185-11f0-8760-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration indefinitely pauses immigrant visa processing for 75 nations, including Brazil, Iran, Russia and Somalia</title>
      <description>The State Department has ramped up efforts in recent months to restrict migration, particularly from nations President Donald Trump has deemed a threat to national security. The visa order takes effect Jan. 21, and a full list of the countries on the administration’s list has not been released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5459ab10-f16c-11f0-92c5-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Husband’s new car obsession burns their couple time’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘Husband’s new car obsession burns their couple time’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce39fea1-f16a-11f0-a9bd-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are more restaurants plating fish skin side up?</title>
      <description>Why are more restaurants plating fish skin side up?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">137f22f0-f167-11f0-86e8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. withdraws some forces from key Qatar base as Trump weighs Iran strikes, echoing moves before summer attack on nuclear sites</title>
      <description>The Pentagon’s partial withdrawal from al-Udeid Air Base occurs as President Donald Trump broadcasts his administration’s support for Iranian civilians protesting the country’s leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">383c8bf0-f15d-11f0-92c5-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unlikely phone call in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6bc2e30-f155-11f0-8c91-0000a1ace750</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI executes search warrant at Washington Post reporter’s home amid investigation into government contractor</title>
      <description>The reporter, Hannah Natanson, was at her home in Virginia at the time of the search on Wednesday. The warrant said that law enforcement was investigating Aurelio Perez-Lugones, a system administrator in Maryland who has a top secret security clearance and has been accused of accessing and taking home classified intelligence reports, according to an FBI affidavit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fffdb01-f151-11f0-b3d7-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump reiterates Greenland’s importance before meeting Vance will host with officials from Denmark and the self-governing territory</title>
      <description>Visiting officials appeared unnerved by the vice president’s planned involvement in today’s talks after they had sought a meeting with Secretary of State Marco Rubio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aad137b0-f149-11f0-9a0d-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran protests. ICE shooting. Trump’s obscene gesture. ‘Anti-vaxxer.’ Earnings calls. Polar vortex. Red meat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85cad970-f140-11f0-a01f-000a1ace6293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saks Global — parent company of Saks Fifth Avenue, Neiman Marcus and Bergdorf Goodman — files for bankruptcy</title>
      <description>Saks Global has faced declining sales and crushing debt. The holding company commenced voluntary Chapter 11 cases in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas, it said in a news release. Its stores remain open, it added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5e9c8d1-f115-11f0-a099-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New RFK Jr. pick for advisory panel: ‘I was not anti-vaccine. I am now.’</title>
      <description>Two OB/GYNs appointed to the influential Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices have criticized vaccination during pregnancy and more broadly. One called the vaccine industry “disgusting.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">636aec10-f0d4-11f0-a3dd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claudette Colvin dies at 86. She refused to give up her seat on a segregated Alabama bus 9 months before Rosa Parks made history.</title>
      <description>Colvin’s arrest in 1955 inaugurated what the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. described as a pivotal period for Black people in Montgomery. She became a star witness in a civil rights case that reached the Supreme Court, which ordered an end to bus segregation in 1956.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a387a7a0-f0c7-11f0-98d0-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top federal prosecutors in D.C. and Minneapolis leave amid turmoil over Minneapolis shooting probe</title>
      <description>The departures followed demands by Justice Department leaders to investigate the widow of Renée Good, the 37-year-old woman killed last week in Minneapolis by an Immigration and Customs Enforcement officer, according to a person familiar with the resignations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b2f37d0-f0c2-11f0-8d82-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to uphold two states’ bans of trans athletes in women’s sports</title>
      <description>The justices heard arguments on whether bans in West Virginia and Idaho violate the Constitution’s equal protection clause. The outcome of the pair of cases could determine what happens with similar laws in more than half the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c2bcf50-f0b9-11f0-b0c0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Tomlin steps down as Pittsburgh Steelers coach after 19 seasons</title>
      <description>The move comes a day after the Steelers’ 30-6 loss to the Houston Texans in the opening round of the AFC playoffs in Pittsburgh. The Steelers remain without a postseason victory since the 2016 season, even after signing quarterback Aaron Rodgers to a one-year contract last summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4afaa621-f0b6-11f0-9cb8-0000a1ace981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’ve waited for this electrifying moment in Iran for 10 years, Jason Rezaian writes</title>
      <description>A decade after I was freed from Evin prison, protests are rocking Iran — and planning is vital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26285791-f0aa-11f0-b247-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is their single-mom commune idea too good to be true?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is their single-mom commune idea too good to be true?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b113231-f0a6-11f0-bc14-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian forces have killed at least 2,000 people in demonstration crackdown, rights group says, as Trump encourages protesters</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said “help is on its way” to anti-regime protesters in Iran and said its government will pay a “big price.” The warning came as human rights groups warned of an escalating death toll amid a nationwide communications blackout. The U.S.-based Human Rights Activists News Agency estimated that more than 2,000 protesters have been killed since the demonstrations began last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53126cd0-f0a2-11f0-9cb8-0000a1ace981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Adams dies at 68. The ‘Dilbert’ creator drew criticism after he veered into far-right political terrain.</title>
      <description>Years before the film “Office Space” and TV series “The Office” satirized the workplace on-screen, Adams’s comic strip poked fun at corporate jargon, managerial ineptitude and the indignities of life in the cubicle farm. “Dilbert” once ran in more than 2,000 newspapers, but publishers cut ties with its creator after he made racist comments on a YouTube live stream.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427ffc90-f096-11f0-99a4-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new Golden Globe in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85dee370-f08c-11f0-ab6a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price growth held firm in December, capping a year of persistent inflation</title>
      <description>New government figures show that prices rose by 0.3 percent between November and December, in line with September’s reading of 0.3 percent. Overall, prices were 2.7 percent higher than they were a year ago, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bfb18e1-f085-11f0-8a8d-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat strike. Jerome Powell. ICE lawsuit. Transgender athletes. Rising emissions. Sick kids quiz. Decluttering tips. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aa4a740-f077-11f0-8b99-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which jobs have grown (and declined) fastest during your working life?</title>
      <description>Here are the fastest-growing and fastest-shrinking jobs over the years, based on information from the Census Bureau’s Current Population Survey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd1aa2e0-f020-11f0-b568-000a1acef855</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota and the Twin Cities sue DHS and ICE to halt immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>Minnesota officials claim the Trump administration’s “unprecedented surge” of immigration agents is politically motivated and violates the U.S. Constitution. The state of Illinois filed a separate suit Monday seeking to place limits on Department of Homeland Security agents in the Chicago area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84098ad1-f016-11f0-a6ad-0000a1ace7c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 25 percent tariff on countries that trade with Iran</title>
      <description>Tehran says it’s ready for “war” or dialogue as Washington weighed its response to mass protests against the government. The tariffs would mean higher prices for American importers of products from dozens of countries, including China, India, Russia, Turkey and Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df01de70-f010-11f0-aa91-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Kelly (D-Arizona) sues Hegseth seeking to reverse his censure and potential demotion</title>
      <description>In the lawsuit filed in federal court in D.C., Kelly’s lawyers argued that the Pentagon’s inquiry, and formal reprimand, unlawfully violated the free speech rights of the retired Navy officer and due process. The lawsuit sharply escalates a confrontation between Kelly and Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth over a video reminding U.S. service members that they can refuse illegal orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b46ada0-eff6-11f0-b419-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis can be brutal. Here’s why I stay.</title>
      <description>By K. Woodman-Maynard</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f05d220-efee-11f0-902c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is trying to change how midterms are conducted</title>
      <description>Many of the president’s endeavors go far beyond typical political persuasion, challenging long-established democratic norms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">befe4710-efe5-11f0-a556-0000a1aceb18</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband sees hyphenating name for fairness as too much of a hassle</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband sees hyphenating name for fairness as too much of a hassle</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e39d9630-efda-11f0-8770-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best moments — and biggest shocks — of the 2026 awards</title>
      <description>“One Battle After Another” and “Hamnet” are now the front-runners of the awards season. But there’s drama to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1549fe30-efc2-11f0-a9ec-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Powell. Iran protests. ICE and Minneapolis. Midterms. Longevity boom. Fast-growing jobs. Golden Globes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f6324e0-efae-11f0-8fd9-0000a1aced70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘One Battle After Another’ takes home four awards at the Golden Globes, while ‘Hamnet’ wins for best drama</title>
      <description>“Adolescence” won four TV categories. “The Pitt” and “The Studio” had strong nights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b2ecc30-ef6f-11f0-ae0c-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Globes kick off as ‘One Battle After Another’, ‘Sinners’ and ‘The White Lotus’ eye big night</title>
      <description>Nikki Glaser returns to host the ceremony for a second year. The stand-up comedian and actress became the first solo female host in Golden Globes history when she emceed the show last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24e7b600-ef51-11f0-8e40-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Justice Department launches a criminal investigation of Fed chair</title>
      <description>The Federal Reserve confirmed Sunday it had received subpoenas related to Senate testimony of its chairman, Jerome Powell, about renovations to the headquarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d22a3911-ef50-11f0-837a-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration flipped the food pyramid. Can you guess whether these foods meet the new guidelines?</title>
      <description>While not all the recommendations are new, the latest Dietary Guidelines for Americans endorse some items that had once been discouraged by many nutritionists, such as those with higher saturated fat content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6e18bf0-ef3d-11f0-8353-0000a1ace817</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds killed as Iran seeks to crush protests, rights groups say; U.S. considers military options</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is considering responses, including military strikes, as reports that Iranian security forces were escalating their lethal crackdown against demonstrators began to break through an internet blackout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b86ce90-ef32-11f0-b880-0000a1ace2fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cdc2c20-ef0f-11f0-83cc-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A powerful force has been holding back the housing market. It’s finally easing.</title>
      <description>There are now more Americans with mortgage rates higher than 6 percent than below 3 percent. It matters because those ultralow, pandemic-era rates — while great for the homeowners who nabbed them — have been something of a problem for the housing market ever since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97271370-ef09-11f0-a27e-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cfd4e10-eefb-11f0-b9b8-0000a1ace3c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two congressmen watched a video of the Minneapolis ICE shooting. Only one is sure of what he saw.</title>
      <description>Rep. Eric Swalwell (D-California) and Rep. Mike Flood (R-Nebraska) watched the same video of the shooting of Renée Good. Swalwell was certain: “I saw a murder.” Flood said, “I couldn’t really see what was happening there.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab12e380-eef7-11f0-8a63-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Weir, Grateful Dead rhythm guitarist and founding member, dies at 78</title>
      <description>Mr. Weir, a rhythm guitarist, vocalist and co-founder of the Grateful Dead band, “succumbed to underlying lung issues” after being diagnosed with cancer in July, according to a family statement shared on his website Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb3a190-ee8f-11f0-902c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the agencies that were cut the most by Trump, new data shows</title>
      <description>About 335,000 federal workers left government from January to November 2025, with a vast majority of those people quitting or retiring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a136610-ee89-11f0-b61a-0000a1ace5c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian removes Trump impeachment text as it swaps his portrait</title>
      <description>The National Portrait Gallery removed a swath of text that mentioned President Donald Trump’s two impeachments and the Jan. 6, 2021, insurrection as it replaced a prominent photo of him this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63ee47b0-ee75-11f0-a2c9-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE tactics and training under scrutiny after Minneapolis shooting</title>
      <description>Policing experts say ICE officer who fired shots that killed Renée Good may have placed himself at needless risk by standing in front of her SUV.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72482be1-ee67-11f0-b5c3-0000a1ace043</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hunt for a stolen Jackson Pollock — and answers to a family’s pain</title>
      <description>Decades after a brazen art theft drove Merry White’s father to despair, federal agents closed in on one last missing work. For White, the search is personal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e166c4b1-ee48-11f0-b5cc-0000a1ace659</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b9f4540-ee31-11f0-995d-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
