<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:03:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israel captures Rafah border crossing, imperiling aid efforts to Gaza</title>
      <description>The Israel Defense Forces said it has taken “operational control” of the Gazan side of the Rafah crossing. Egypt has condemned the move, calling it a dangerous escalation. A Gaza border official said the flow of aid into the Strip “stopped completely” as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e10ae20-0c64-11ef-b2b2-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cease-fire talks. Trump warning. Tornadoes. Putin’s inauguration. Social Security. Highway 1. Met Gala. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f516f190-0c60-11ef-be7a-0000a1ace201</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vladimir Putin sworn in for a fifth term as president, positioning him as Russia’s leader-for-life</title>
      <description>Putin, who has circumvented term limits repeatedly to remain Russia’s supreme political leader for a quarter-century, was inaugurated for a new six-year term that will run through 2030. Putin has vowed to persist with his war in Ukraine and is presiding over a sweeping transformation of Russia into a regressive militarized state in conflict with America and the West.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee584b0-0c54-11ef-84a4-0000a1ace3b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the best looks from the Met Gala</title>
      <description>“The Garden of Time” dress code promised florals, decadence and the ephemeral beauty of nature. See The Post’s favorite looks from the Met Gala, including Ayo Edebiri, Nicole Kidman and Bad Bunny.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043b93e0-0c13-11ef-85b8-0000a1ace228</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to press attack on Rafah as it negotiates possible Gaza cease-fire agreement</title>
      <description>Israel’s war cabinet said late Monday its mediators would return to the negotiating table after Hamas announced it had agreed to a Qatari-Egyptian proposal to pause fighting and release hostages. But the Israeli government also vowed to maintain military pressure on Rafah, where airstrikes and a mass evacuation order stirred panic among the more than a million displaced Palestinians sheltering there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c469e7b0-0bf6-11ef-8357-0000a1aceb43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars arrive for the 2024 Met Gala, themed ‘Sleeping Beauties: Reawakening Fashion.’ Follow our live red-carpet coverage.</title>
      <description>We’ll have updates from the scene and analysis of the looks, so follow along for all things Met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">197e85f0-0bf5-11ef-8235-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. soldier has been detained in Russia on criminal charges, Army says</title>
      <description>An Army spokeswoman said Russia’s government notified the State Department earlier this month of the soldier’s detention in Vladivostok. The soldier’s identity was not disclosed, and neither were the circumstances surrounding the criminal charges or why the solider was in Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d974a300-0be9-11ef-be92-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security and Medicare will run out of money in just over a decade if Congress doesn’t act, report warns</title>
      <description>A hot job market has delayed the expected fiscal crash, but an aging population and rising federal debt still will put pressure on lawmakers to address the budget, the trustees for Social Security and Medicare said Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fd9b670-0be4-11ef-81f6-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post wins Pulitzer Prizes for national reporting, editorial writing and commentary</title>
      <description>The awards recognize The Post’s series on the political power and cultural impact of the AR-15 rifle, as well as editorials by veteran staffer David E. Hoffman on the troubling rise of autocracy around the world and commentary by Vladimir Kara-Murza, a contributing columnist who has been imprisoned in Russia since April 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d62997b0-0bde-11ef-8357-0000a1aceb43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sisters were close — then one accused the other’s husband of abuse</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sisters were close — then one accused the other’s husband of abuse</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6c84b50-0bc1-11ef-86e0-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin is forging a new Russia: Ultraconservative, militarized and anti-West</title>
      <description>The Russian leader is harnessing his invasion of Ukraine to transform his country into a regressive, militarized state and to fulfill his vision of a restored superpower set on upending the U.S.-led global order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f098b1-0bb5-11ef-835b-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia University cancels school-wide commencement, moves ceremonies off main campus amid protests</title>
      <description>Columbia will instead hold “smaller-scale, school-based celebrations.” The university has drawn national attention for an encampment of pro-Palestinian protesters, who occupied a campus building last week before being removed by police.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b6c450-0baf-11ef-b33c-0000a1acedb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to the brain during what? Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d34fcf20-0baf-11ef-8a7e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial finds him in contempt on more gag order violations, warns former president of jail time</title>
      <description>“I find you in criminal contempt for the tenth time,” said New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan, who said he is concerned Donald Trump has not apparently taken heed from his prior findings. “Going forward, this court will have to consider a jail sentence. The last thing I want to do is put you in jail.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7a4bfd0-0bad-11ef-80c6-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel orders 100,000 civilians to evacuate Rafah, says it will operate with ‘extreme force’</title>
      <description>The southern Gazan city is home to more than a million displaced Palestinians and, according to Israel, the last Hamas battalions. Aid agencies have said there is nowhere for civilians to go and U.S. officials have warned a major operation in Rafah would be a “disaster.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">159b6381-0ba1-11ef-8eca-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s warning. Trump trial. Missing surfers. Henry Cuellar. Gas stoves. Kentucky Derby. Starliner launch. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbd89230-0b97-11ef-8da2-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer’s far-right rhetoric has repelled many would-be MAGA allies, with one notable exception: Trump himself</title>
      <description>People around the former president apparently see Loomer — an anti-Islam, anti-immigration activist — as a liability at a time when Donald Trump’s campaign (if not the candidate himself) is making a conscious effort to make their man appear less extreme, according to several sources close to the campaign’s inner circle. Still, Loomer is dead set on landing a role in a second Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1ded171-0b23-11ef-92e9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 21:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ad0c80-0af9-11ef-a431-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 16:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Pratt’s demolition of a historic home to build a modern farmhouse is part of a disturbing trend</title>
      <description>Few people realized the Zimmerman House in Los Angeles was in any danger before it was unceremoniously razed by the actor and his wife, author Katherine Schwarzenegger, who bought the mid-century home and its nearly one-acre plot last year for $12.5 million. Increasingly, preservationists say, these demos are not driven by changing tastes but rather by Americans’ ravenous appetites for larger and larger homes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a10021-0af1-11ef-a431-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 15:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11ca0c11-0ae4-11ef-a0c8-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 13:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 protesters at University of Virginia arrested after violent clash with police</title>
      <description>The university said 25 pro-Palestinian demonstrators at the University of Virginia were arrested, after law enforcement officers in riot gear surrounded a student encampment that the administration said was prohibited</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85dddf60-0a70-11ef-a376-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystik Dan finishes first in a photo finish in the 150th running of the Kentucky Derby</title>
      <description>The Derby field at Churchill Downs on Saturday also included Dornoch, who is co-owned by former MLB star Jayson Werth, and Fierceness, a colt trained by Todd Pletcher. The Triple Crown continues with the Preakness Stakes on May 18 and the Belmont Stakes on June 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfabc750-0a6b-11ef-bc46-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Stella, celebrated artist of minimalist power, dies at 87</title>
      <description>Stella achieved early fame with a series of monochromatic paintings that helped establish minimalism as an alternative to abstract expressionism in the late 1950s. He then spent the next several decades creating colorful works that seemed to repudiate his youthful principles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c51f5a50-0a5c-11ef-a82f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Abnormal and unprecedented’: Surge in sea level rise is imperiling the American South</title>
      <description>Americans from Texas to North Carolina are grappling with one of the most rapid sea level surges on Earth, one that is choking septic systems, swallowing roads and drowning wetlands. Search The Post’s data to see how sea levels have changed across the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6cc81d0-0a46-11ef-a6b4-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s not the Kentucky Derby without a mint julep. Here are six ways to make one.</title>
      <description>It’s not the Kentucky Derby without a mint julep. Here are six ways to make one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67b39e0-0a33-11ef-8bfd-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Responding to microaggressions is taking a toll on me. Can I stop?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Responding to microaggressions is taking a toll on me. Can I stop?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eb645b0-0a2f-11ef-81a9-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More senior homes refuse to pick up fallen residents, dialing 911 instead: ‘Why are they calling us?’</title>
      <description>Frustrated cities and states have begun fining facilities for nonemergency calls, but some just keep calling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de7ab570-0a2b-11ef-a814-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 15:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The children who seem to remember past lives</title>
      <description>What happens when a toddler is haunted by memories that aren’t theirs? The phenomenon, with its aura of the paranormal, has long been fodder for books, academic studies and dramatized documentaries. But there is no scientific means to conclusively prove — or disprove — a mechanism that might explain how a person could recall living a past life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f287ec00-0a20-11ef-9df1-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 14:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08b29210-0a1b-11ef-b45e-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 13:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claims of sexual assault, violence: How the myth of Sean Combs came undone</title>
      <description>Diddy’s downfall built up slowly and then arrived dizzyingly fast, as rumors and accusations turned into lawsuits, raids and a decaying of Combs’s empire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34e80850-099a-11ef-a40f-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. tells Qatar to evict Hamas political leaders if militant group obstructs Israeli deal for Gaza cease-fire, hostage release</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken delivered the message to Qatar’s prime minister, Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani, last month, said a U.S. official. Diplomats familiar with the situation said the Gulf emirate, which has hosted Hamas’s political leaders for years at the United States’ request, has anticipated the request for months and advised them to devise a backup plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46789430-0991-11ef-b372-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada arrests three men in killing of Sikh separatist, an official says; Trudeau linked killing to Indian government</title>
      <description>The three men are Indian Canadians believed to be part of an organized crime network acting on the behalf of the Indian government and its intelligence apparatus, according to the official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive law enforcement matter.
Prime Minister Justin Trudeau told lawmakers in September that authorities were pursuing “credible allegations” that agents of the Indian government were behind the killing of Hardeep Singh Nijjar last June in Surrey, British Columbia. Nijjar, a Canadian citizen, advocated for an autonomous Sikh state in India.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">236171e0-097f-11ef-abb4-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-Tex.) and his wife charged with accepting $600,000 in bribes from foreign companies</title>
      <description>The congressman and his wife, Imelda Cuellar, are accused of setting up front companies that entered into sham contracts with an oil company controlled by the Azerbaijan government and a bank headquartered in Mexico. In a statement, Cuellar said he is innocent and will continue his campaign for another term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4edf0201-097b-11ef-b372-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My boyfriend’s closest confidante is his on-again, off-again ex</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My boyfriend’s closest confidante is his on-again, off-again ex</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d388d50-096e-11ef-b83e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors question Hope Hicks on ‘Access Hollywood’ tape that they say helped lead to hush money payment. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Called as a witness in Donald Trump’s New York hush money trial, the former aide told jurors she was “stunned” by the release of a hot mic tape in which Trump made light of forcing himself on women.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7966000-096c-11ef-bd01-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas man’s ex-partner left the state to get an abortion. Now he’s asking a court for permission to investigate.</title>
      <description>The previously unreported legal action reflects a potential new antiabortion strategy to block women from traveling to end their pregnancies in states where abortion is legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7153530-095d-11ef-b0c7-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1b48cf0-0950-11ef-9a00-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added 175,000 jobs in April, as labor market growth slowed, compared to earlier in the year</title>
      <description>Despite high interest rates, the labor market continues to show resilience in 2024, according to the latest data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e030910-0949-11ef-a9c8-0000a1ace665</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Campus protests. Jobs report. Boeing whistleblower. Hottest April. Russian TikTok. Kentucky Derby. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b05c60-093c-11ef-abc9-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen A. Smith and his naked-as-ever ambition are testing just how much of the ESPN star America wants</title>
      <description>Sports, politics, sex, SpongeBob: There’s nothing Smith won’t argue about — as long as you keep listening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5dc6d80-08c8-11ef-937e-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Will request for a postnup offend much younger wife?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Will request for a postnup offend much younger wife?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76c9ec00-08a7-11ef-9b9b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden expands boundaries of two national monuments in California, protecting land that Native American tribes consider sacred</title>
      <description>President Biden signed two proclamations enlarging the San Gabriel Mountains National Monument and the Berryessa Snow Mountain National Monument, using his executive authority to protect vast swaths of land of cultural significance to tribes and nearby communities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e0c6e40-08a1-11ef-9548-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A botched drone strike in Syria killed a civilian, not a terrorist as the U.S. first claimed, Defense Department acknowledges</title>
      <description>The U.S. military’s findings, to be released later Thursday, follow a Washington Post investigation that cast doubt on its initial assertion the operation last year targeted a senior al-Qaeda figure. A Defense Department official said the real suspect got away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6983aea0-089d-11ef-a530-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden urges campus protesters to refrain from violence and says demonstrations have not changed his policies</title>
      <description>The president called on pro-Palestinian demonstrators at campuses around the country to avoid chaos and intimidation, saying that Americans have a right to peaceful protest but strongly condemning some of the tactics that have been used. “We’ve all seen the images, and they put to the test two fundamental American principles,” Biden said in quickly scheduled remarks at the White House. “The first is the right to free speech and for people to peacefully assemble and make their voices heard. The second is the rule of law. Both must be upheld.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad43571-089a-11ef-83f6-0000a1ace705</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wait, a baseball game was delayed by what?! Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c44a1c0-0888-11ef-aaf9-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of fifth victim in Baltimore bridge collapse has been recovered, authorities say</title>
      <description>The victim, one of six construction workers who died when the Key Bridge collapsed, was identified as Miguel Angel Luna Gonzalez, 49, of Glen Burnie, Md.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26c42af0-0879-11ef-b5ab-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA protests. Arizona abortion. Mike Johnson. Harvey Weinstein. Bird flu. Menopause drugs. Missing cat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f3f7b50-0873-11ef-bdda-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This middle school’s battle against cellphones yielded surprising results</title>
      <description>Illing Middle School in Manchester, Conn., navigated objections from students and some parents to lock up cellphones in a bid to improve focus and reduce social media-fueled conflicts. What unfolded reflects a broader struggle underway in education as some administrators turn to increasingly drastic measures to limit the reach of a technology that is both ubiquitous and endlessly distracting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3754b920-0806-11ef-b7d2-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes divisive antisemitism bill as Republicans seek to crack down on campus protests over Gaza war</title>
      <description>Critics of the Antisemitism Awareness Act, which has some Democratic support, call the legislation an effort to silence opinions of Israel and an affront to the First Amendment. It’s unclear what the bill’s prospects are in the Democratic-controlled Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">076ccb00-07ff-11ef-b3a8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-led Arizona Senate votes to repeal Civil War-era abortion ban. The Democratic governor is expected to sign it into law.</title>
      <description>The state’s highest court revived the ban on nearly all abortions in early April and it was set to take effect in June. The repeal is expected to be signed into law by Gov. Katie Hobbs in the coming days, but the state attorney general’s office said the repeal would not take effect until 90 days after the legislature adjourns for the summer. So, barring successful court challenges, the 1864 ban could take effect for a short time in the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb7582c0-07f6-11ef-8be6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
