<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 18:04:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Will rewards entice a traumatized kid to reengage with school?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Will rewards entice a traumatized kid to reengage with school?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fd35100-d1d0-11ef-9d5a-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How New Orleans failed to protect Bourbon Street from the deadly New Year’s truck attack, block by block</title>
      <description>A poorly positioned police SUV and a plan that called for only a single anti-vehicle barrier on the street that night were among the failures that allowed an ISIS-inspired attacker to drive a truck down the pedestrian thoroughfare in the early hours of Jan. 1, killing 14 people and injuring dozens, according to a Washington Post examination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b8ef0d0-d1cd-11ef-b83f-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Albuquerque home is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b940dca0-d1bb-11ef-b2f8-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles fires. Trump inauguration. Ceasefire talks. TikTok ban. Pain pill. NFL playoffs. Bat surfing. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebe0ec11-d1a5-11ef-9db6-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders beat Buccaneers in Jayden Daniels’s NFL playoff debut</title>
      <description>Washington won, 23-20, on Sunday night in Tampa and will play at the Detroit Lions in the second round next weekend. It is Washington’s first postseason victory since 2006 and continues a breakout season for the franchise and its rookie quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f762f5c0-d163-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 04:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landlords are accused of colluding to raise rents. See whether this is happening near you.</title>
      <description>Millions of rents across the country may now be set using one company’s algorithmic software, according to a federal lawsuit and a Washington Post analysis. RealPage, a property management software company, uses a trove of data to suggest rental prices to landlords. The software has been widely adopted by property managers — and is now facing strenuous legal pushback. Look at just how widespread its use may be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7383970-d134-11ef-856a-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: We moved to the suburbs, and I’m miserable. I blame my husband.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: We moved to the suburbs, and I’m miserable. I blame my husband.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9d15d50-d119-11ef-b5f4-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 19:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">910dc630-d107-11ef-aea7-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes Commanders wide receiver Terry McLaurin great? See for yourself.</title>
      <description>Washington’s star, who will appear in his second career playoff game Sunday night against the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, is elite at ball-tracking, a skill that is difficult — but not impossible — to measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e56efa50-d102-11ef-8ac7-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 16:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets turned to ash: Before and after the Los Angeles fires, in photos and videos</title>
      <description>Multiple wildfires have devoured neighborhoods in Los Angeles. Here’s what some of these areas looked like before the catastrophic blazes — and what they look like now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75cc7630-d0fa-11ef-bb65-0000a1acef0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94f18b1-d0f1-11ef-b8e6-0000a1ace658</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 14:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Smith, the special counsel named to oversee the federal cases against Donald Trump, resigns from the Justice Department</title>
      <description>The news came in a footnote of a court filing. Smith spent the last two months winding down the two federal criminal prosecutions of Trump and said he would resign before Inauguration Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e677bb31-d067-11ef-8678-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 22:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest of L.A. fires is creeping closer to the 405 freeway, triggering a new wave of alarm as flames spread. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>When flames from the Palisades Fire appeared to spread east to Mandeville Canyon, locals knew that meant the blaze was creeping closer to Interstate 405, near a busy mountain pass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dc94760-d05c-11ef-a58a-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 20:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The original, science‑backed 7‑minute workout to get fit fast</title>
      <description>Research shows this simple routine can rapidly improve endurance and health — no gym required. The workout features 30 seconds of familiar calisthenics — exercises that use your own body weight, such as jumping jacks and push-ups — capped with five seconds of rest. Each calisthenic exercise should be somewhat challenging, said Chris Jordan, the exercise physiologist who developed the workout, feeling like “about an eight on a scale of effort from one to 10.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5be5f750-d055-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 19:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how a small fire in L.A. turned into a monster, hour by hour</title>
      <description>As winds near Pacific Palisades approached extreme levels, the first signs emerged of a fire that would later grow out of control. Videos and images taken by residents and area-camera networks show how each hour after that, the blaze grew stronger, spreading from hilltops and eventually through a densely populated and beloved community. In the coming days, the fire’s sheer devastation would become clearer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">879b5160-d032-11ef-8259-0000a1acedb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d70a2411-d028-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine captured two North Korean soldiers in Russia, Zelensky says, in move that could shed light on Pyongyang’s role in the war</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s announcement marks Ukraine's first confirmation it has detained North Korean troops since they were deployed late last year. He said that capturing them alive “was not an easy task.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eef8a8f0-d01c-11ef-9043-0000a1ace65b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 13:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Significant’ flare-up of Palisades Fire prompts expansion of evacuation orders in Los Angeles</title>
      <description>The upgraded orders now cover much of the Brentwood neighborhood. The Getty museum, a Los Angeles landmark, is in the area affected by the orders. A Cal Fire spokesperson said the flare-up is a “significant development” and that the Palisades Fire — which has burned more than 21,000 acres — is growing “really, really fast.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5282ae01-cfde-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 05:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The death toll in the California fires rises to 11 people. Gov. Newsom launches a water supply investigation. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>As firefighters battle six blazes, California Gov. Gavin Newsom has launched a probe of lost water supply and pressure in Los Angeles’s municipal water systems during the fires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ca87e51-cfa9-11ef-b1f0-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden shields nearly 1 million immigrants from Venezuela, El Salvador, Ukraine and Sudan from deportation for 18 months</title>
      <description>The Biden administration on Friday extended temporary humanitarian protections for nearly 1 million immigrants living in the United States, announcing the move days before the start of a possible deportation campaign by the incoming Trump administration. Advocates had been urging the Department of Homeland Security to extend the protected designation for these nationalities and others under a 1990 law that shields immigrants from being deported to countries engulfed in conflict or natural disasters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b56482a0-cf93-11ef-84cb-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We don’t cry — yet’: A Pacific Palisades native on what has been lost</title>
      <description>"The Pacific Palisades was a village, my village — and now it’s gone," E.A. Hanks writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de428ce0-cf88-11ef-8d93-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter weather advisory for light snow issued for D.C. area</title>
      <description>Snow is expected to move into the area around 10 p.m. Friday and continue into early Saturday morning. One to two inches could fall, causing slippery roads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f1fff91-cf85-11ef-8b92-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I get my instincts back after a bad relationship?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I get my instincts back after a bad relationship?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a087470-cf82-11ef-9843-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to clear the way for ban or sale of TikTok</title>
      <description>After more than two hours of exchange with lawyers for the Chinese-owned social platform, its users and the U.S. government, a majority of the justices seemed to embrace Congress's national security concerns over the free speech implications of the law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6e27570-cf7f-11ef-adde-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration targets two of Russia’s largest oil companies and 183 oil tankers in sanctions, delivering a parting blow</title>
      <description>The White House, now less concerned about the effect on gas prices and inflation, also has measures against a list of entities involved in virtually all sectors of Russia’s energy business in a move to put pressure on President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed47e690-cf6a-11ef-b810-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court is hearing a challenge to the law ordering that TikTok be either banned in the U.S. or sold. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Justices are listening to oral arguments on the Chinese-owned social platform’s claim that the law, based on national security concerns, violates free speech guarantees for its owners and some 170 million U.S. users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95e2b050-cf66-11ef-bd80-000a1ace7928</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sentenced without penalty in hush money case, formalizing his status as first president or president-elect who is a felon</title>
      <description>Trump was convicted in May on 34 felony counts of falsifying business records in connection with a hush money payment made to an adult-film actress during the 2016 presidential campaign. On Thursday the Supreme Court rejected a bid by Trump’s attorneys to stop the sentencing on the grounds that it would interfere with his transition to a second term as president after his November election victory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a1d73f0-cf65-11ef-b1f0-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 15:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9a3ed00-cf5e-11ef-a50d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 14:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 256,000 jobs in December, a strong uptick in the labor market, which sped up toward the end of 2024</title>
      <description>The December report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics adds more evidence that the labor market is healthy enough to allow the Federal Reserve to be more cautious about lowering interest rates in 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17b9530-cf57-11ef-b4cf-0000a1ace2f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 13:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angles fires. Trump sentencing. Carter funeral. TikTok ban. La Niña. College football. ‘Breaking Bad’ house. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a1e12a0-cf4a-11ef-b4e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 was the hottest year on record, scientists say, reaching 1.6 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels</title>
      <description>The world’s nations have pledged not to breach the threshold of 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 Fahrenheit) for a sustained period of time, and new data from the European Union’s Copernicus Climate Change Service means the globe is edging closer to that mark. Aside from Australia and Antarctica, every continent experienced its warmest year on record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e166ae80-ceff-11ef-a7e0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 03:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court allows release of special counsel report on Trump’s Jan. 6 case</title>
      <description>A federal appellate court has cleared the way for the Justice Department to publicly release special counsel Jack Smith’s report on Donald Trump’s efforts to undo the results of the 2020 election. The timing of that release remains unclear, however, and the ruling could be appealed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16489370-cef1-11ef-bbac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 01:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL moves Rams-Vikings playoff game from Southern California to Arizona because of wildfires</title>
      <description>The Monday night game, which was scheduled to be held at the Rams’ home in Inglewood, California, will instead be played at State Farm Stadium, the Phoenix-area home of the Arizona Cardinals. It is the last of six first-round playoff games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46834101-ceee-11ef-a5b2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 01:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court refuses to delay Trump’s hush money sentencing in New York on Friday</title>
      <description>The trial judge has said his sentence will not include jail time or probation for Donald Trump's felony conviction on charges of falsifying business records related to a hush money payment. The sentencing hearing will be the final step in Trump being formally classified as a felon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23110ff1-cee8-11ef-958a-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan opposition leader is detained after attending anti-Maduro protests on eve of inauguration</title>
      <description>María Corina Machado, the driving force of Venezuela’s opposition movement, was arrested by government security forces Thursday as she left a rally in Caracas on the eve of Nicolás Maduro’s inauguration after a widely discredited election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0161a3b1-cec5-11ef-b80c-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 20:04:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several L.A. wildfires continue to burn unabated, with death toll expected to rise, officials say. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>About 180,000 people are under evacuation orders as five active wildfires burn in Los Angeles County. The Palisades and Eaton fires remain uncontained, according to Cal Fire. Some areas “look like a bomb was dropped on them,” said L.A. County Sheriff Robert Luna.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">758ff280-cec2-11ef-85dc-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 19:46:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Daughters seem standoffish as dad’s illness progresses</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Daughters seem standoffish as dad’s illness progresses</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">681faad0-ceab-11ef-9c53-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An updated coat of arms in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de0f3d0-ce96-11ef-b10f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter will be honored at Washington National Cathedral today. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The former president is being celebrated one more time in Washington on Thursday with a national funeral service, before his remains are flown back to Georgia to be buried in his beloved hometown of Plains, Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b498baf1-ce92-11ef-b676-0000a1ace641</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 14:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon’s parliament elects army commander Joseph Aoun as president after years of political deadlock</title>
      <description>Aoun, widely seen as the preferred candidate of the United States, received 99 out of 128 total votes from across the political spectrum, including from Hezbollah lawmakers and their rivals in parliament.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b89b0a50-ce87-11ef-9858-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:46:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles fires. Trump investigations. Carter funeral. Syria’s future. Snow. Roman pollution. Lost hiker. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43612e01-ce81-11ef-bfb7-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Is there anyone who didn’t lose their house?’ In Pacific Palisades, a beloved community is leveled by wildfire.</title>
      <description>Firefighting and emergency response officials have been stretched to the limit since fires blew up around Los Angeles, flanking much of the region and spurring mass evacuations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a06660-ce28-11ef-bd58-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 01:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shippers, union reach tentative deal to avert strike that would have shut down major East and Gulf coast ports next week</title>
      <description>The longshoremen’s union still must approve the deal, which protects jobs while allowing ports to modernize, addressing concerns over automation of jobs to avert a work stoppage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0d0cf31-ce1e-11ef-8b07-000a1ace5c2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2025 00:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta embraces Elon Musk’s volunteer fact-checking program on X. Its users describe it as ‘whack-a-mole.’</title>
      <description>The legions of X users who volunteer their time policing misinformation on the site through a feature called Community Notes praise the program for giving power to a diverse set of users. But they also warn it’s an inadequate replacement for professional fact-checking — and fear it will be even harder for regular people to combat falsehoods on Meta’s array of global platforms. Some users said their efforts feel futile.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f41b80e0-ce0b-11ef-a426-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 22:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will defer to Trump on terrorist designation for Syria’s new leaders</title>
      <description>The terrorist designation for Hayʼat Tahrir al-Sham, or HTS, will remain in place through the end of President Joe Biden’s term, said three U.S. officials familiar with the matter. The label is a key obstacle to Syria’s long-term economic viability, but U.S. officials said the Islamist militants who stunned the world late last year by overthrowing Syrian President Bashar al-Assad must demonstrate they’ve made a clean break with extremist groups, in particular al-Qaeda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32c18780-cdea-11ef-b86e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:58:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friendship matters more than political differences — right?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friendship matters more than political differences — right?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ccde2f0-cde2-11ef-be1f-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 17:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the L.A. fires became so bad, so quickly</title>
      <description>For days, the National Weather Service warned of extreme fire risk amid a “life-threatening” and “destructive” windstorm. Those dire predictions came true as devastating wildfires broke out across the city — some in mountainous zones where the strongest winds had been predicted. Hurricane-force Santa Ana winds, some gusting to nearly 90 mph, and bone-dry conditions helped fuel the fast spread of numerous fires. Winds were expected to intensify Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56ae8bb3-cde1-11ef-9ea8-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How do you ask fellow diners to cool it with the profanity? Our food critic is answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How do you ask fellow diners to cool it with the profanity? Our food critic is answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb6aa2fa-cddb-11ef-b34b-0000a1aced15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 16:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department plans to release special counsel report on Trump Jan. 6 probe, withhold classified document report for now</title>
      <description>The Justice Department said in a court filing that it would not publicly release special counsel Jack Smith’s findings on Donald Trump’s alleged mishandling of classified documents until the ongoing litigation against his co-defendants concludes. But prosecutors said Attorney General Merrick Garland intends to release a portion of Smith’s report outlining his investigation into Trump’s efforts to undo the results of the 2020 election and allow members of Congress to review the portions withheld on the classified documents investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c0b4e2-cdd6-11ef-9473-0000a1acec15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 15:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first major acting award for this performer in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3425d8a0-cdcd-11ef-ae94-000a1acef974</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
