<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 20:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to uphold two states’ bans of trans athletes in women’s sports</title>
      <description>The justices heard arguments on whether bans in West Virginia and Idaho violate the Constitution’s equal protection clause. The outcome of the pair of cases could determine what happens with similar laws in more than half the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c2bcf50-f0b9-11f0-b0c0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Tomlin steps down as Pittsburgh Steelers coach after 19 seasons</title>
      <description>The move comes a day after the Steelers’ 30-6 loss to the Houston Texans in the opening round of the AFC playoffs in Pittsburgh. The Steelers remain without a postseason victory since the 2016 season, even after signing quarterback Aaron Rodgers to a one-year contract last summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4afaa621-f0b6-11f0-9cb8-0000a1ace981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I’ve waited for this electrifying moment in Iran for 10 years, Jason Rezaian writes</title>
      <description>A decade after I was freed from Evin prison, protests are rocking Iran — and planning is vital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26285791-f0aa-11f0-b247-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 18:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is their single-mom commune idea too good to be true?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is their single-mom commune idea too good to be true?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b113231-f0a6-11f0-bc14-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian forces have killed at least 2,000 people in demonstration crackdown, rights group says, as Trump encourages protesters</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said “help is on its way” to anti-regime protesters in Iran and said its government will pay a “big price.” The warning came as human rights groups warned of an escalating death toll amid a nationwide communications blackout. The U.S.-based Human Rights Activists News Agency estimated that more than 2,000 protesters have been killed since the demonstrations began last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53126cd0-f0a2-11f0-9cb8-0000a1ace981</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 17:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scott Adams dies at 68. The ‘Dilbert’ creator drew criticism after he veered into far-right political terrain.</title>
      <description>Years before the film “Office Space” and TV series “The Office” satirized the workplace on-screen, Adams’s comic strip poked fun at corporate jargon, managerial ineptitude and the indignities of life in the cubicle farm. “Dilbert” once ran in more than 2,000 newspapers, but publishers cut ties with its creator after he made racist comments on a YouTube live stream.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">427ffc90-f096-11f0-99a4-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 15:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new Golden Globe in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85dee370-f08c-11f0-ab6a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price growth held firm in December, capping a year of persistent inflation</title>
      <description>New government figures show that prices rose by 0.3 percent between November and December, in line with September’s reading of 0.3 percent. Overall, prices were 2.7 percent higher than they were a year ago, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bfb18e1-f085-11f0-8a8d-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 13:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat strike. Jerome Powell. ICE lawsuit. Transgender athletes. Rising emissions. Sick kids quiz. Decluttering tips. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aa4a740-f077-11f0-8b99-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which jobs have grown (and declined) fastest during your working life?</title>
      <description>Here are the fastest-growing and fastest-shrinking jobs over the years, based on information from the Census Bureau’s Current Population Survey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd1aa2e0-f020-11f0-b568-000a1acef855</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota and the Twin Cities sue DHS and ICE to halt immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>Minnesota officials claim the Trump administration’s “unprecedented surge” of immigration agents is politically motivated and violates the U.S. Constitution. The state of Illinois filed a separate suit Monday seeking to place limits on Department of Homeland Security agents in the Chicago area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84098ad1-f016-11f0-a6ad-0000a1ace7c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 25 percent tariff on countries that trade with Iran</title>
      <description>Tehran says it’s ready for “war” or dialogue as Washington weighed its response to mass protests against the government. The tariffs would mean higher prices for American importers of products from dozens of countries, including China, India, Russia, Turkey and Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df01de70-f010-11f0-aa91-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 23:46:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Kelly (D-Arizona) sues Hegseth seeking to reverse his censure and potential demotion</title>
      <description>In the lawsuit filed in federal court in D.C., Kelly’s lawyers argued that the Pentagon’s inquiry, and formal reprimand, unlawfully violated the free speech rights of the retired Navy officer and due process. The lawsuit sharply escalates a confrontation between Kelly and Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth over a video reminding U.S. service members that they can refuse illegal orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b46ada0-eff6-11f0-b419-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 20:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis can be brutal. Here’s why I stay.</title>
      <description>By K. Woodman-Maynard</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f05d220-efee-11f0-902c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is trying to change how midterms are conducted</title>
      <description>Many of the president’s endeavors go far beyond typical political persuasion, challenging long-established democratic norms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">befe4710-efe5-11f0-a556-0000a1aceb18</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 18:37:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband sees hyphenating name for fairness as too much of a hassle</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband sees hyphenating name for fairness as too much of a hassle</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e39d9630-efda-11f0-8770-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best moments — and biggest shocks — of the 2026 awards</title>
      <description>“One Battle After Another” and “Hamnet” are now the front-runners of the awards season. But there’s drama to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1549fe30-efc2-11f0-a9ec-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 14:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Powell. Iran protests. ICE and Minneapolis. Midterms. Longevity boom. Fast-growing jobs. Golden Globes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f6324e0-efae-11f0-8fd9-0000a1aced70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘One Battle After Another’ takes home four awards at the Golden Globes, while ‘Hamnet’ wins for best drama</title>
      <description>“Adolescence” won four TV categories. “The Pitt” and “The Studio” had strong nights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b2ecc30-ef6f-11f0-ae0c-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 04:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Golden Globes kick off as ‘One Battle After Another’, ‘Sinners’ and ‘The White Lotus’ eye big night</title>
      <description>Nikki Glaser returns to host the ceremony for a second year. The stand-up comedian and actress became the first solo female host in Golden Globes history when she emceed the show last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24e7b600-ef51-11f0-8e40-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Justice Department launches a criminal investigation of Fed chair</title>
      <description>The Federal Reserve confirmed Sunday it had received subpoenas related to Senate testimony of its chairman, Jerome Powell, about renovations to the headquarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d22a3911-ef50-11f0-837a-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 00:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration flipped the food pyramid. Can you guess whether these foods meet the new guidelines?</title>
      <description>While not all the recommendations are new, the latest Dietary Guidelines for Americans endorse some items that had once been discouraged by many nutritionists, such as those with higher saturated fat content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6e18bf0-ef3d-11f0-8353-0000a1ace817</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 22:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds killed as Iran seeks to crush protests, rights groups say; U.S. considers military options</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is considering responses, including military strikes, as reports that Iranian security forces were escalating their lethal crackdown against demonstrators began to break through an internet blackout.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b86ce90-ef32-11f0-b880-0000a1ace2fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 21:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cdc2c20-ef0f-11f0-83cc-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A powerful force has been holding back the housing market. It’s finally easing.</title>
      <description>There are now more Americans with mortgage rates higher than 6 percent than below 3 percent. It matters because those ultralow, pandemic-era rates — while great for the homeowners who nabbed them — have been something of a problem for the housing market ever since.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97271370-ef09-11f0-a27e-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 16:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cfd4e10-eefb-11f0-b9b8-0000a1ace3c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:37:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two congressmen watched a video of the Minneapolis ICE shooting. Only one is sure of what he saw.</title>
      <description>Rep. Eric Swalwell (D-California) and Rep. Mike Flood (R-Nebraska) watched the same video of the shooting of Renée Good. Swalwell was certain: “I saw a murder.” Flood said, “I couldn’t really see what was happening there.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab12e380-eef7-11f0-8a63-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 14:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Weir, Grateful Dead rhythm guitarist and founding member, dies at 78</title>
      <description>Mr. Weir, a rhythm guitarist, vocalist and co-founder of the Grateful Dead band, “succumbed to underlying lung issues” after being diagnosed with cancer in July, according to a family statement shared on his website Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb3a190-ee8f-11f0-902c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:46:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are the agencies that were cut the most by Trump, new data shows</title>
      <description>About 335,000 federal workers left government from January to November 2025, with a vast majority of those people quitting or retiring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a136610-ee89-11f0-b61a-0000a1ace5c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 01:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian removes Trump impeachment text as it swaps his portrait</title>
      <description>The National Portrait Gallery removed a swath of text that mentioned President Donald Trump’s two impeachments and the Jan. 6, 2021, insurrection as it replaced a prominent photo of him this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63ee47b0-ee75-11f0-a2c9-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 22:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE tactics and training under scrutiny after Minneapolis shooting</title>
      <description>Policing experts say ICE officer who fired shots that killed Renée Good may have placed himself at needless risk by standing in front of her SUV.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72482be1-ee67-11f0-b5c3-0000a1ace043</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 21:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hunt for a stolen Jackson Pollock — and answers to a family’s pain</title>
      <description>Decades after a brazen art theft drove Merry White’s father to despair, federal agents closed in on one last missing work. For White, the search is personal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e166c4b1-ee48-11f0-b5cc-0000a1ace659</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b9f4540-ee31-11f0-995d-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For 64 days, he took on the world’s hardest sailing race. His cancer was kept secret.</title>
      <description>Charlie Dalin kept his illness a secret, treating himself with immunotherapy pills on a 24,000-mile journey around the world. What would it do to his body?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8ff42a0-ee2f-11f0-984a-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 14:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ICE agent’s cellphone video: Five key moments</title>
      <description>New footage sheds light on fatal shooting of Renee Good in Minneapolis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3935b26-edcc-11f0-bf74-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 02:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington National Opera to move out of the Kennedy Center</title>
      <description>The 70-year-old organization said Friday that it had decided to leave its longtime home amid ongoing upheaval at the center since President Donald Trump’s takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c056c4d0-edb9-11f0-a5fa-0000a1acefcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 00:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exxon CEO calls Venezuela ‘uninvestable’ without significant changes to its legal and commercial framework</title>
      <description>At a White House meeting with oil executives, President Donald Trump promised that industry leaders would spend $100 billion in Venezuela. The companies are worried about the numbers adding up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03b6bd20-edb0-11f0-8448-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 23:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is treating Washington like his chew toy, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Trump’s triumphal arch will be harder to undo than his gilding of the Oval Office, Will writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44363cb0-eda4-11f0-b4ec-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 21:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the frantic global race to find an escape route for Maduro</title>
      <description>A previously unreported Christmas Eve meeting in Vatican City was one of many failed attempts to find safe harbor for the Venezuelan leader before the U.S. raid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c3ac880-ed9b-11f0-bad6-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 20:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-law’s fertility journey keeps changing my wedding plans</title>
      <description>In-law’s fertility journey keeps changing my wedding plans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a156d310-ed94-11f0-9771-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:51:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota woman killed by ICE was supporting neighbors, wife says</title>
      <description>Speaking out for the first time since the fatal shooting, Rebecca Good said in a statement that she and Renee Good were raising their son to believe that everyone deserves “compassion and kindness.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a47ad490-ed82-11f0-805d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33321850-ed6b-11f0-a4fc-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 50,000 jobs in December, a solid gain capping off weak 2025</title>
      <description>The unemployment rate ticked down to 4.4 percent at the end of the worst year for the labor market since the pandemic-era recession.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29c31720-ed60-11f0-8677-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday briefing: Minneapolis ICE shooting; White House ballroom; Grok images; health tips for 2026; and more</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3437890-ed52-11f0-8134-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE officer who fatally shot a Minneapolis woman in her SUV had been dragged by a driver months earlier</title>
      <description>Federal authorities did not publicly name the officer who killed Renee Nicole Good. But court records reviewed by The Washington Post of the prior incident in Bloomington, a suburb of Minneapolis, identify the officer as Jonathan Ross, who works for an Immigration and Customs Enforcement division that detains immigrants for civil violations and attempts to deport them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66cd7fb0-ecfd-11f0-85bc-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agents shoot two people in Portland, Oregon, mayor says</title>
      <description>The victims’ conditions were not made public. Mayor Keith Wilson (D) did not identify the agency to which the federal agents who fired the shots belonged but called for Immigration and Customs Enforcement to end all operations in the city and referenced the fatal shooting of a woman by an ICE officer in Minneapolis on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed56f601-ecf4-11f0-8957-0000a1ace94b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill extending health care subsidies for 3 years, bucking GOP leaders. Its fate in the Senate remains unclear.</title>
      <description>More than a dozen House Republicans joined every Democrat to pass a bill to extend enhanced Affordable Care Act subsidies — the sharpest rejection by GOP members of the party’s leadership yet. The pandemic-era subsidies expired at the end of last year, driving up costs for millions of Americans who buy health insurance on the ACA marketplace and qualified for the assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89cc1c50-ece0-11f0-a498-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is planning to make his addition as tall as the mansion itself, breaking with architectural norms</title>
      <description>The president’s architect disclosed the change as federal review panels begin a fast-track review of the $400 million project. The significant change of plans defies long-standing norms requiring additions to be shorter than the main building.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94481821-ecd4-11f0-b985-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate advances bill to block further military action in Venezuela. The measure still awaits final passage.</title>
      <description>The headline of a previous alert incorrectly stated the Senate had passed the bill. The Senate voted to advance the measure toward final passage, though the timing for a vote was not immediately clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9f12cc0-ecbb-11f0-80ef-000a1ace8d41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota officials say the FBI is freezing the state out of the probe into the deadly ICE shooting</title>
      <description>The Minnesota Bureau of Criminal Apprehension said the FBI’s decision to take over the investigation into the shooting in Minneapolis will keep state officials from accessing evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">505c28c0-ecb8-11f0-8c26-0000a1ace588</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
