<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:27:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Can you pass the new, more challenging U.S. citizenship test?</title>
      <description>The test changes come after the Trump administration signaled it will increase scrutiny on citizenship applications and threatened to revoke some Americans’ citizenship. The Washington Post set 10 questions to represent the 2025 civics test.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d479cbf0-b066-11f0-afa3-0000a1acef72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration will allow controversial road through Alaskan refuge</title>
      <description>The deal allows a road to cut through the Izembek National Wildlife Refuge, a pristine stretch of coastal wildlands. Interior Secretary Doug Burgum also announced the reopening of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge to oil and gas development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d374060-b05e-11f0-a000-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House annex has been completely demolished to make way for Trump’s $300 million ballroom</title>
      <description>The little that remained just after lunchtime included a small section of the East Colonnade, a corridor that previously connected the East Wing to the main White House. Also visible: dump trucks with sandy-colored debris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc8b4b50-b043-11f0-8359-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks bills to pay federal workers during shutdown as it stretches into a fourth week, with no end in sight</title>
      <description>Lawmakers acted mostly along partisan lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fdba480-b040-11f0-b181-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons founder of crypto exchange Binance, Changpeng Zhao, who pleaded guilty to enabling money laundering in 2023</title>
      <description>Zhao agreed to step down as chief executive of Binance as part of a plea deal. The company also agreed to pay a $4.3 billion fine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f454d5b0-b02e-11f0-b7ed-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He’d be a great dad. Is it wrong to marry him just for that?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He’d be a great dad. Is it wrong to marry him just for that?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0836a01-b029-11f0-9d2e-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support for Virginia Democratic attorney general nominee has tumbled since text message scandal, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Likely voters have not transferred much support to Jay Jones’s opponent — Republican incumbent Jason S. Miyares — and the race is a tie, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll. The scandal has not affected the contest for governor, where Democrat Abigail Spanberger holds a 12-point lead over Republican Winsome Earle-Sears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eb145c0-b028-11f0-96d8-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA’s Portland Trail Blazers head coach and Miami Heat player arrested in sports gambling probe</title>
      <description>FBI agents reportedly arrested Trail Blazers coach Chauncey Billups, a Hall of Famer who played 17 seasons in the league, and the Heat’s Terry Rozier, a former first-round draft pick. Former NBA player Damon Jones was also taken into custody, according to a person familiar with the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cf21cb0-b019-11f0-bbfd-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealing jewels in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef7aa00-b014-11f0-8056-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Anglican Church archbishop accused of sexual misconduct, abuse of power</title>
      <description>An attempted kiss, cash payments and other allegations roil the Anglican Church in North America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89264f80-b010-11f0-a346-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s ballroom. Boat strikes. Shutdown. Nuclear submarines. Citizenship test. mRNA vaccines. Brain surgery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6415d8c0-afff-11f0-9899-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. imposes sanctions on Russian oil companies after strikes on Ukraine kill 7</title>
      <description>The move against two of Russia’s largest oil companies, Rosneft and Lukoil, reflects the Trump administration’s waning patience with Russian President Vladimir Putin. The Treasury Department cited Putin’s alleged “lack of serious commitment to a peace process to end the war in Ukraine” in its announcement of the measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f598430-af9a-11f0-b5b2-0000a1acef7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s teardown of the East Wing moves full steam ahead as shocked preservationists fear their hands are tied</title>
      <description>The president said Wednesday that the project would cost $300 million, up from his initial claim of $200 million, as he defended the decision to demolish the East Wing of the White House to build his long-desired ballroom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db2b7960-af96-11f0-8283-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Virginia agrees to follow Trump administration’s guidance barring discrimination in deal to pause investigations</title>
      <description>The deal could be the first such agreement between any public university and the White House, as President Donald Trump seeks to remake higher education. His administration contends that many universities have violated civil rights laws by embracing diversity, equity and inclusion programs or failing to adequately protect Jewish students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9af5d2e0-af88-11f0-abe1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. kills 2 people in strike on alleged drug boat in Pacific, expanding Trump’s counternarcotics campaign beyond Caribbean</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth announced the strike but declined to identify the victims or offer evidence verifying that they were hauling narcotics. Previous strikes were launched exclusively in the Caribbean Sea targeting what President Donald Trump contends are criminal organizations linked to Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96208cd0-af77-11f0-984c-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon announces its new right-wing press corps after mass walkout over Defense Department’s reporting restrictions</title>
      <description>A new crop of conservative media and influencers — including the Gateway Pundit, The Post Millennial, Human Events and the National Pulse — signed an agreement with the Defense Department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d5bb140-af73-11f0-9b10-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I need alone time, but my husband is always home: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>I need alone time, but my husband is always home: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f4b601-af60-11f0-beed-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘rogue’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d865900-af4c-11f0-8668-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans see insurance costs surge as health subsidy fight fuels shutdown</title>
      <description>Many states have shown rising premiums ahead of open enrollment for Affordable Care Act plans. The government shutdown is driven by Democratic demands to extend subsidies for this insurance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b74afd21-af43-11f0-a0be-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>East Wing demolition. Vladimir Putin. Shutdown impact. Trump nominee. AI warnings. CNN’s future. Gen Z at work. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44850b30-af36-11f0-985b-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s controversial nominee to lead the Office of Special Counsel withdraws from confirmation hearing</title>
      <description>Paul Ingrassia withdrew after at least five GOP senators said they opposed him, in the wake of reports that he sent racist and inflammatory texts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b6c7600-aed8-11f0-ad5d-000a1ace3f2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eating meat is worse for the planet in some cities than in others. Look up yours.</title>
      <description>For the first time, researchers calculated the planet-warming pollution emitted from raising the beef, pork and chicken Americans eat for every town and city in the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">457d1ab0-aed1-11f0-b2df-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Trump administration seeks to move special education to a different agency as it works to close the Education Dept.</title>
      <description>An earlier alert said the government was seeking to move special education programs to the Department of Health and Human Services. Education officials have floated the idea of moving special education to HHS, but the official who confirmed Tuesday that a move was being explored said there are multiple agencies involved in the discussions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d2f15b0-aecd-11f0-a8ac-0000a1ace274</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New photo shows much of the White House East Wing torn down as demolition continues for Trump’s ballroom</title>
      <description>More of the structure was torn down Tuesday to make way for President Donald Trump’s planned ballroom, despite complaints about the project’s lack of transparency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba840c0-aec9-11f0-b2df-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration seeks to move special education to HHS as it works to close the Education Department</title>
      <description>The move comes on the heels of the agency’s decision this month to lay off the vast majority of employees working on special education services and months after Education Secretary Linda McMahon talked about moving the program to the Department of Health and Human Services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b399df1-aebe-11f0-99d8-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 20:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The administration’s push to overhaul the U.S. refugee program seeks 7,000 White South Africans — and virtually no one else</title>
      <description>If the Trump administration succeeds, almost all people admitted to the United States as refugees could be Afrikaners, a group not traditionally eligible for the program. The remainder may be chosen because of their ability to speak English or their views on “free speech,” people familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea283051-aea3-11f0-9f7c-0000a1ace52d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 17:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Putin meeting postponed after Russia’s top diplomat signaled a wide chasm between U.S. and Kremlin on Ukraine</title>
      <description>The Trump administration said there are “no plans” for President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin to meet in Hungary in the immediate future. The decision came after Russia’s foreign minister said Trump’s call for a ceasefire contradicted the understandings he reached with Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">735af4b0-ae9b-11f0-b2df-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband wants to hide their Halloween from his devil-fearing mother</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband wants to hide their Halloween from his devil-fearing mother</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76fe5700-ae97-11f0-8051-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futures of CNN and HBO at stake as Warner Bros. Discovery announces it’s open to a full or partial sale</title>
      <description>The media company, which previously announced a plan to split its entertainment offerings from its sports and news programming, has decided to explore sale opportunities after receiving multiple bids. David Ellison, whose company Skydance recently took over Paramount, has reportedly expressed interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">705c6312-ae8d-11f0-96a9-0000a1acecb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina lawmakers vote to add GOP House seat, in win for Trump ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>Republican state senators heeded President Donald Trump’s request to help protect the party’s narrow majority in next year’s elections. The state House is expected to sign off on the measure later this week. Gov. Josh Stein (D) does not have the power to veto it, leaving Democrats with few options but to sue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aba7cf0-ae8a-11f0-a1d6-000a1aceb228</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 14:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The greatest game in baseball history in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">436b8e80-ae7e-11f0-b2df-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Joe Rogan’s podcast with Mel Gibson led Florida to promise research into ivermectin as a cancer treatment</title>
      <description>Ivermectin, an antiparasitic drug that gained fame as a possible covid treatment despite research showing its ineffectiveness, has taken on symbolic power in the backlash against traditional public health guidance that helped spawn the “Make America Healthy Again” movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f18d6eb0-ae75-11f0-b589-0000a1acebfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 12:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>East Wing demolition. Trump and Zelensky. Louvre heist. Mel Gibson. Climate ‘hoofprint.’ Good sleep. World Series. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b435070-ae6d-11f0-b3ed-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Toronto Blue Jays advanced to the Fall Classic for first time since 1993, where they will take on the Los Angeles Dodgers</title>
      <description>The Blue Jays rallied past the visiting Seattle Mariners, 4-3, in Game 7 of the American League Championship Series on Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7207d220-ae2a-11f0-ba79-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 03:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four surprising things that may reduce your risk of Parkinson’s</title>
      <description>Research on Parkinson’s is revealing several risk factors related to our lifestyles and environment, and you can act on some of them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01eaba10-ae12-11f0-b9f2-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six of nine top colleges have rejected the Trump administration’s funding deal ahead of Monday deadline</title>
      <description>Despite strong pressure from the White House, including a Friday call, colleges and universities are largely rejecting President Donald Trump’s offer of preferential treatment for funding in exchange for compliance with his ideological priorities. On Monday, the University of Arizona and Vanderbilt University did not accept the deal, but said they were open to more discussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5c80a50-ae09-11f0-b665-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James B. Comey asks judge to dismiss criminal case against him, calling it vindictive</title>
      <description>In court filings, Comey’s attorneys accused President Donald Trump of personally instigating the case against their client. When several prosecutors refused to proceed, the attorneys wrote, Trump installed a loyalist in a key position to ensure that charges would be filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7da94e0-adf5-11f0-b01b-0000a1ace171</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more teens charged in August attack on DOGE staffer that propelled Trump’s D.C. takeover</title>
      <description>An 18- and a 19-year-old face charges including robbery and assault for their alleged role in the Aug. 3 attack on Edward Coristine — a 19-year-old software engineer known as “Big Balls” — and another person at a nearby gas station, U.S. Attorney for D.C. Jeanine Pirro announced Monday. Earlier this month, two 15-year-olds were sentenced to probation for their role in the incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5808e9d0-adf4-11f0-ba79-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can deploy National Guard in Portland, appeals court rules</title>
      <description>A federal judge appointed by President Donald Trump had blocked him from sending federalized National Guard members to Oregon’s largest city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be2968b1-adeb-11f0-ae6a-0000a1ace57c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demolition of White House facade begins, contradicting Trump’s claim that addition wouldn’t interfere with current structure</title>
      <description>Construction teams Monday demolished a portion of the East Wing, with a backhoe ripping through the structure, according to a photo shared with The Washington Post and two people who witnessed the activity. The ballroom project, long desired by President Donald Trump, is estimated to cost $250 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08b9cb90-ade7-11f0-b622-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was driving in reverse when he plowed through child’s party in Maryland on Saturday, killing 1 and injuring 13, police say</title>
      <description>The driver, identified Monday as 66-year-old Sunday Joseph, ran before turning himself in to authorities Sunday morning, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6647c160-ade5-11f0-9849-000a1ace2541</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He regrets not exploring his bisexuality before he married his wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He regrets not exploring his bisexuality before he married his wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6326f0d0-adce-11f0-9b15-0000a1acec62</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials and locals undercut Trump’s claims that boats off Venezuela are carrying deadly fentanyl to the U.S.</title>
      <description>Records and interviews with 20 people familiar with the route or the strikes show that the targeted passage in the waters between Venezuela and Trinidad and Tobago typically carries cocaine and marijuana to other continents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41402da0-adbb-11f0-bb35-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Mad Mike’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86e3a921-adb8-11f0-af5c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes. Marco Rubio. Military exercise. Inflation. Louvre heist. Parkinson’s prevention. Rare comets. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5f6ebc0-ada3-11f0-a35f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Stanford scientist and Berkshire Hathaway heir is on a mission to thwart redistricting efforts in California</title>
      <description>Charles Munger Jr. is the largest individual donor opposing the California ballot measure that would redraw the state’s congressional map to favor Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08517cd2-ad37-11f0-9c35-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 22:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These two infectious disease experts say this is when you should get covid and flu shots</title>
      <description>Flu season is here. The summer wave of the coronavirus has receded, but the winter uptick is likely around the corner. The Washington Post spoke to two experts about how they make their own decisions and how they talk about vaccines with friends and families.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d79e9c61-ad15-11f0-a35f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 18:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z slang is everywhere. Test your knowledge of teen talk with this quiz.</title>
      <description>Gen Z slang is everywhere. Do you understand it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d0a26e0-ad0b-11f0-8101-0000a1aced91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf03c2d0-ad04-11f0-b80f-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She spurned the concertmaster’s advance. Now she’s classical music’s #MeToo vigilante.</title>
      <description>Baltimore Symphony oboist Katherine Needleman’s online shaming campaign has sidelined several musicians — and outraged others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8f523b0-acf8-11f0-97b7-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
