<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 09:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires at least 12 independent inspectors general in late-night purge</title>
      <description>The White House is firing many inspectors general — the independent watchdogs at major Cabinet departments charged with identifying fraud and abuse. It is a purge that could lead to the president installing loyalists to the crucial roles overseeing major agencies like Energy and Transportation. Most of those dismissed were Trump appointees from his first term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca212861-dad3-11ef-be8f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth confirmed as Trump’s defense secretary, an appointment expected to bring a dramatic shift in national security policy</title>
      <description>The former Fox News personality, whose nomination was overshadowed by a raft of misconduct allegations, overcame withering opposition from lawmakers who deemed him unfit to run the Pentagon and oversee the nation’s military.

Three Republicans, Sens. Mitch McConnell (Kentucky), Lisa Murkowski (Alaska) and Susan Collins (Maine), joined the chamber’s Democrats in opposing his nomination. Vice President JD Vance cast the tiebreaking vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693e1c80-dac7-11ef-a55d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 02:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. skipped an official meeting meant to prepare the White House for a possible pandemic</title>
      <description>Kennedy, who’s been nominated to serve as the United States’ top health official, was instead on Capitol Hill to lobby senators for their votes. National security and health experts said they were troubled by Kennedy’s absence from the session, given the possibility of a serious health crisis like avian flu on the Trump administration’s watch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">282718b1-daa3-11ef-afac-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to decide whether states can allow religious public schools</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court agreed Friday to consider whether the state of Oklahoma may fund a proposed Catholic charter school, a blockbuster case that could redraw the line between church and state by allowing religious public schools for the first time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab4c26f0-da9d-11ef-a1d8-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. to sharply curtail prosecutions of antiabortion protesters who disrupt access to clinics</title>
      <description>A day after President Donald Trump pardoned 23 people convicted under the 1994 FACE Act, the Justice Department said it would drop three pending cases and would prosecute future cases only under "extraordinary circumstances," including if protesters cause “death, serious bodily harm, or serious property damage.” Trump and his allies have accused the Biden administration of bringing cases against "peaceful pro-life protestors."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68069cd0-da99-11ef-afac-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified to announce my pregnancy. How do I handle this?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified to announce my pregnancy. How do I handle this?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cccc7a40-da7b-11ef-a037-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration raids are alarming communities, but ICE has arrested fewer people this week than when Trump took office in 2017</title>
      <description>The Trump administration circulated photos Friday showing U.S. troops loading shackled detainees onto a military cargo plane, as the White House declared a start to the mass deportation campaign the president promised along the campaign trail. But ICE arrest numbers suggest the show of force has so far outpaced the government’s capacity to quickly increase deportations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14dbd032-da7a-11ef-af69-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">922b3c30-da5f-11ef-af69-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s executive orders. Elon Musk. Explicit texts. Wildfires. Oscar snubs. NFL playoffs. Pandas debut. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc923bf0-da4a-11ef-9528-0000a1ace97c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TikTok's frantic scramble to halt the ban in the U.S.</title>
      <description>The China-based company said it would "go dark" unless the outgoing administration assured the app's service providers they would not be punished under the ban-or-sale law. The White House demurred, calling it a "stunt,"  and the app went offline for 14 hours — until Donald Trump said he would act fast to give it a reprieve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c690300-d9f1-11ef-97b5-0000a1ace537</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 01:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to close down Pentagon office focused on the prevention of civilian deaths resulting from U.S. military activity</title>
      <description>The Civilian Protection Center of Excellence, a small directorate established by Congress to help the military limit unintended civilian harm in conflict zones, is under scrutiny from the new administration. The Department of the Army, where the center is housed, is drafting a proposal to defund and potentially “disestablish” the office, according to people familiar with the matter and an internal document reviewed by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20faa901-d9de-11ef-9188-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 23:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman indicted in crash that killed NFL rookie Khyree Jackson, two others</title>
      <description>Minnesota Vikings rookie Khyree Jackson, 24, and former high school teammates Anthony Lytton Jr., 24, and Isaiah Hazel, 23, were killed in a car crash last summer. Cori Clingman, the driver of the vehicle that hit them, was allegedly speeding, impaired by alcohol. She faces up to 30 years in prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdd60d30-d9da-11ef-a328-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth’s nomination for defense secretary clears a key procedural step in the Senate, moving him closer to confirmation</title>
      <description>Republicans have appeared largely unmoved by the allegations of personal misconduct clouding Hegseth’s nomination, though two indicated Thursday they plan to vote against his confirmation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c654110-d9c5-11ef-a5b2-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson aide advised against subpoena of Jan. 6 witness Cassidy Hutchinson to prevent release of ‘sexual texts’ lawmakers sent her</title>
      <description>An aide to House Speaker Mike Johnson advised Republican colleagues against subpoenaing Hutchinson, a former White House aide, as part of their investigation into the Jan. 6, 2021, attack to prevent the release of sexually explicit texts that lawmakers told the office they sent her, according to written correspondence reviewed by The Washington Post and a person familiar with the effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c9b2620-d9bb-11ef-ac59-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge issues temporary restraining order blocking Trump policy banning birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>U.S. District Court John C. Coughenour granted the request to a coalition of states that had sued. President Trump signed an executive order Monday to end birthright citizenship for the children of undocumented immigrants and foreign visitors. The order is facing a bevy of legal challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f4ea2d1-d9ba-11ef-b9e2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Angry at a lifelong friend for a recent, shocking arrest</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Angry at a lifelong friend for a recent, shocking arrest</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">befa6291-d9ab-11ef-b0ce-0000a1ace6d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An artist photographed abortion clinics. What caught her eye hung on the walls.</title>
      <description>Artist Carmen Winant’s photos are inspired by the fraught timetable of abortion rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25382940-d9aa-11ef-be4c-0000a1ace464</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising prices again in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece9c5c0-d996-11ef-aea4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Emilia Pérez,' 'Wicked' and 'The Brutalist' led the Oscar nominations, followed by 'A Complete Unknown' and 'Conclave'</title>
      <description>There was no Barbenheimer, but 2024 was an especially dynamic year at the movies. "Anora" and "The Substance" also had numerous Academy Awards nods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c0df6f0-d991-11ef-8a9e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 13:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump interview. Border plans. Laken Riley Act. New wildfire. College enrollment. Coffee benefits. Statue discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9444f350-d981-11ef-a55d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This was cruel’: These migrants waited months for a chance to legally cross the border. Under Trump, they’re stuck in Mexico.</title>
      <description>The migrants at El Buen Samaritano shelter had applied through the U.S. government’s CBP One app to be granted parole and enter immigration proceedings. Then, within hours of his swearing-in, President Donald Trump argued in an executive order that the program violated federal law, resulting in appointment cancellations, frustration and fear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eb25f00-d921-11ef-99bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons two D.C. officers convicted of misconduct. Their fatal pursuit of a young Black man sparked civil unrest in 2020.</title>
      <description>In granting clemency, President Donald Trump waded into a case that stoked racial tensions and resulted in the first murder conviction of a D.C. police officer for on-duty actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">650530e1-d91e-11ef-99bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department freezes all civil rights cases, including police investigations</title>
      <description>The Justice Department ordered its civil rights division to halt any litigation left over from the Biden administration and not pursue any new cases or settlements. The decision seems likely to jeopardize multiple police reform agreements finalized in recent months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e25473d0-d919-11ef-beab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 23:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes Laken Riley Act, first bill of Trump’s new term and sign of immigration crackdown to come</title>
      <description>The bill would allow Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents to detain undocumented immigrants accused of theft-related crimes, raising questions about due process. The act was named in memory of a nursing student killed in February by an undocumented immigrant in Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c21720-d90d-11ef-9726-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 22:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to order at least 1,000 additional U.S. troops to Mexico border in what may be first of several deployments, officials say</title>
      <description>The Defense Department is expected to order the additional military personnel to bolster security at the southern border under President Donald Trump, according to two U.S. officials familiar with the plans. The officials said the personnel will augment the roughly 2,500 service members already deployed to the border under the Biden administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e009800-d8f6-11ef-a92b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Pushy mom won’t take ‘busy’ for an answer on playdates</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Pushy mom won’t take ‘busy’ for an answer on playdates</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de075d1-d8e2-11ef-86d8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: I think a driver ate my food delivery</title>
      <description>Dining chat: I think a driver ate my food delivery</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b0d6020-d8de-11ef-9df9-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Columbia law professor criticized Israeli students. An investigation put her job at risk.</title>
      <description>Columbia Law School professor Katherine Franke alleged Israeli students bullied Palestinian peers, spurring colleagues’ complaints and a school investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbe2531-d8d8-11ef-9281-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A huge navy boater in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f40f30b0-d8d3-11ef-a838-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. threatens to prosecute local officials who do not comply with Trump’s plans for immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>In a memo, acting deputy attorney general Emil Bove said state and local officials must "comply with the Executive Branch’s immigration enforcement initiatives,” including mass deportation efforts. The directive is likely to face blowback from legal advocacy groups and local officials who say deporting otherwise lawful undocumented immigrants destabilizes their communities and makes immigrants afraid to report crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88250ec1-d8cd-11ef-9df9-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pardons. Elon Musk. West Bank. Prince Harry. Winter storm. Ichiro Suzuki. Drug-addicted rats. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66bc8e30-d8b8-11ef-8d27-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry settles lawsuit with Rupert Murdoch’s newspapers for a ‘substantial’ sum and an apology</title>
      <description>The trial over claims of illegal information gathering and high-level cover-up ended practically before it began as Murdoch’s group paid the prince and former Labour Party deputy leader Tom Watson an undisclosed sum. The newspaper group apologized for “serious intrusion” into their private lives. Over the years, 1,300 others had agreed to settle with the media conglomerate over similar issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cfcd4b1-d8b0-11ef-b6c1-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration orders all federal diversity, equity and inclusion workers to be placed on paid leave, with layoffs to follow</title>
      <description>The administration wants the workers to be placed on leave no later than Wednesday, and for DEI offices to be closed down, according to a memorandum sent Tuesday by the Office of Personnel Management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98c3eba2-d898-11ef-b5e9-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 08:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy's ‘DOGE’ vision broke down over deep philosophical differences</title>
      <description>Putting the new “Department of Government Efficiency” inside a White House digital office could give Musk sweeping insight into government operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c94d9370-d85c-11ef-95eb-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ichiro Suzuki, CC Sabathia, Billy Wagner headline five-player class of inductees to National Baseball Hall of Fame</title>
      <description>Ichiro, a trailblazing Japanese outfielder, narrowly missed becoming the second player unanimously selected by the Baseball Writers’ Association of America. Sabathia and Wagner will also be honored at the annual induction ceremony in Cooperstown, New York, on July 27. Dick Allen and Dave Parker were previously selected for induction by the Classic Baseball Era Committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ae137a1-d84f-11ef-875b-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and tech CEOs announce up to $500 billion in private investments to build new data centers for AI</title>
      <description>President Trump hosted the CEOs of OpenAI, Oracle and SoftBank at the White House to announce the new private-sector investments. Oracle and SoftBank's leaders said they decided to invest more into AI data centers after Trump's election win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99712d20-d84c-11ef-96dd-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Files reveal Tulsi Gabbard staffers’ struggle to contain the fallout from her meetings with Syria’s Assad</title>
      <description>Gabbard’s 2017 trip to Syria, where she met as a member of Congress with authoritarian leader Bashar al-Assad, is expected to be a focus of questions from senators weighing her nomination to be director of national intelligence under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77a11de0-d847-11ef-9de1-0000a1aceb07</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration removes senior Justice Dept. officials from key positions, a sign the agency will be dramatically reshaped</title>
      <description>At least 15 experienced career staffers across several offices, including the national security and criminal divisions, were reassigned, in many cases to lesser roles, according to people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the changes hadn’t been publicly announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53f7fb20-d83d-11ef-84a8-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil rights groups and 18 states sue to stop Trump’s executive order to end birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>The coalition of states is filing a lawsuit challenging President Donald Trump’s sweeping effort, which legal experts say runs counter to more than a century of legal precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a61ffc60-d81d-11ef-bd5d-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Daughter’s mixed marriage unlocks her aunt’s ‘offensive views’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Daughter’s mixed marriage unlocks her aunt’s ‘offensive views’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611673c2-d81c-11ef-8bc4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders are one win away from the Super Bowl. What’s on your mind ahead of Sunday’s game? Our reporters take your questions.</title>
      <description>Join Post Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier to discuss the upcoming NFC championship game between upstart Washington and the Philadelphia Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b46b7d21-d819-11ef-8cf7-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How executive orders work — and how Trump’s could be overturned</title>
      <description>Donald Trump signed a flurry of executive orders hours after being sworn in as president on Monday. They include withdrawing the United States from the Paris agreement on climate change, ordering federal workers back to the office and cracking down on illegal immigration. But such orders have limitations and do not always last.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddbf1aa0-d810-11ef-8bc4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s second inaugural is memorable for its staggering inappropriateness, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s second inaugural speech will be remembered as worse than 59 others, including his first.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09b7b1b0-d80e-11ef-9c50-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military chief says he will resign over Oct. 7, 2023, attacks, citing ‘terrible failure’ to protect citizens</title>
      <description>Lt. Gen. Herzi Halevi announced Tuesday his plans to resign in March, in the highest-level departure of a military or security official over the Hamas-led attacks in 2023. His resignation coincides with the start of a fragile ceasefire in the Gaza Strip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0e33070-d809-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration ousts Coast Guard’s top admiral in first move on military leadership</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has removed the Coast Guard’s top admiral, according to a message to the service’s members, a first move in what could be several changes to military leadership under President Donald Trump. Adm. Linda Fagan was relieved of her duties by Benjamine Huffman, the acting secretary of homeland security. He did not provide a reason for the decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1504f881-d808-11ef-b7de-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A director is at the center of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7e6aa21-d805-11ef-a7a3-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birthright citizenship, Jan. 6 pardons, federal workforce changes: Tracking the executive actions Trump took on Day 1</title>
      <description>Donald Trump has also long vowed to dismantle federal regulations, exact revenge on his political enemies, uproot the federal bureaucracy he has referred to as the “deep state” and eliminate what he sees as government waste.

There are limitations to what a president can legally do via executive action, and many of Trump’s orders are expected to be challenged in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de764cc0-d7fc-11ef-9c50-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel fire kills 66 people at popular Turkish ski resort</title>
      <description>The early morning blaze at the upscale Grand Kartal Hotel at the Kartalkaya resort in northern Turkey forced guests to jump from the building or to try to escape using sheets hung from windows, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72c4aa81-d7f7-11ef-b91d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jules Feiffer, cartoonist, playwright and screenwriter, dies at 95</title>
      <description>His Pulitzer-winning weekly strip ran in the Village Voice from 1956 to 2000 and was syndicated to more than 100 newspapers. Later comic strips such as Garry Trudeau’s “Doonesbury” are indebted to Mr. Feiffer’s brand of acerbic wit and literate satire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d028f510-d7f1-11ef-904b-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s inauguration. Jan. 6 pardons. Biden’s last day. Gaza ceasefire. Winter storm. Ozempic. College football. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f42c230-d7ef-11ef-a666-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
