<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:03:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Francis Ford Coppola, Bonnie Raitt and the Grateful Dead are among this year’s Kennedy Center honorees</title>
      <description>The Kennedy Center will also honor the historic Apollo theater along with celebrated Cuban American trumpeter and composer Arturo Sandoval in a ceremony on Dec. 8. The 47th edition of the Kennedy Center Honors will be broadcast Dec. 23 on CBS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eacfcd0-44fb-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.D. Vance. Biden crisis. Secret Service. Drug kingpin. Emmys. Paris Olympics. Pompeii skeletons. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1b502a1-44f4-11ef-b32d-000a1ace7857</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic leaders Hakeem Jeffries and Charles E. Schumer told Biden his candidacy imperils the party’s ability to win Congress</title>
      <description>In their separate meetings with the president last week, each congressional leader discussed their members’ concerns that he could deprive them of congressional majorities, giving Republicans a much easier path to push through legislation, according to four people briefed on the meetings who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe private encounters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66daa700-449b-11ef-9fd5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RNC will learn more about Sen. J.D. Vance as the vice-presidential pick delivers the keynote on Night 3. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The onetime Trump critic, who has emerged in recent years as one of the former president’s most vocal and fervent backers, is scheduled to give a prime-time address in Milwaukee. Other speakers include Vance’s wife, Usha Vance, and Donald Trump Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">196762c1-4490-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tests positive for covid while campaigning in Las Vegas, is experiencing ‘mild symptoms,’ according to White House</title>
      <description>The president, 81, will return to his home in Rehoboth Beach, Del., to isolate, White House press secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said in a statement. Biden’s doctor said the president has received his first dose of Paxlovid and is experiencing a runny nose, cough and “general mailaise,” according to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa833360-448b-11ef-87c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ flags and quinoa: Here’s the liberal Va. enclave where Trump’s VP pick J.D. Vance lives</title>
      <description>Vance, an arch conservative and a self-professed Trump acolyte, lives in the Del Ray neighborhood of Alexandria, which went for Joe Biden by more than 80 percent in 2020. His neighbors aren't thrilled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16c55e21-4484-11ef-845f-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. area as highs reach the triple digits for record fourth straight day</title>
      <description>Storms could contain damaging winds, lightning and torrential rain, while putting an end to the historic heat wave. Temperatures have reached at least 100 daily since Sunday, making this only the third time there have been four consecutive highs at or above the century mark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a388b590-4476-11ef-a238-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. ends its troubled Gaza pier mission, shifts humanitarian operation to Israeli port, officials say</title>
      <description>The project was beset by challenges from almost the moment President Biden announced it months ago. Though U.S. officials say the floating structure enabled delivery of millions of pounds of food, aid groups in Gaza were reluctant to distribute much of it, citing safety concerns amid Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71647690-4470-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service was alerted that police did not have the resources to watch the building scaled by the Trump rally shooter</title>
      <description>Officials are still investigating how the gunman was allowed to reach the roof of the building, where he opened fire on the former president. But local law enforcement's warning of insufficient manpower adds to questions about whether there was adequate security for the high-stakes campaign visit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a85c3b1-446c-11ef-bd87-0000a1ace017</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) calls on Biden to drop out of the presidential race, questioning his ability to beat Trump</title>
      <description>Schiff, who is heavily favored to win a Senate seat in November, is among the highest-profile members of his party urging President Biden to abandon his bid. Schiff said he believes it is time for Biden “to pass the torch.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b030e40-4464-11ef-a213-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sleeper hit of Emmy nominations was ‘The Morning Show.’ See the list.</title>
      <description>The 76th Emmy Awards cover shows aired between June 1, 2023, and May 31, 2024. The ceremony will be held Sept. 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d817b0-445f-11ef-845f-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casa Ruby founder pleads guilty to fraud after diverting pandemic relief money from her nonprofit focused on homeless LGBTQ+ youth</title>
      <description>Ruby Corado received more than $1.3 million in 2020 and 2021 from the Paycheck Protection Program and the Economic Injury Disaster Loan program. The FBI said she stole at least $150,000 by transferring the money to bank accounts in El Salvador that were hidden from the IRS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">528056f0-445b-11ef-87a7-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent hits the ceiling over ‘egregious’ class superlatives</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent hits the ceiling over ‘egregious’ class superlatives</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a312ec50-4455-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Which chain restaurants are the best? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Which chain restaurants are the best? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b600ac50-444e-11ef-ade8-000a1ace6c43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘clown prince of fitness’ stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1a0e60-4440-11ef-84cc-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley. Rally shooting response. Supreme Court. Bob Menendez. Elon Musk. Amazon tribe. Rare whale. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3d57cd0-442b-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Trump’s former rivals make the case for him, and other takeaways from Day 2 of the GOP convention</title>
      <description>Seventy-two hours after the attempted assassination, Republicans returned to their ominous and combative posture as they went hard after Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd8f68f0-43f0-11ef-89c5-000a1ace4bbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obstructed view may have delayed Secret Service sniper response at Trump rally, according to a 3D analysis by The Washington Post</title>
      <description>The analysis found two countersniper teams likely faced difficulty seeing the gunman before he fired. The examination, based on more than 40 videos and photos, established that the units may have been hampered by the slant of the roof where the shooter was positioned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47cfd9b0-43cf-11ef-b892-0000a1ace8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley, Ron DeSantis scheduled to speak on second night of Republican convention. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The former U.N. ambassador and the Florida governor, who each challenged Donald Trump for the Republican nomination, are expected to give speeches in support of the newly minted ticket a day after the former president selected Sen. J.D. Vance (R-Ohio) to be his running mate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3311c451-43c7-11ef-aa8c-0000a1ace335</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden set to announce support for major changes to the Supreme Court</title>
      <description>The plans include proposals for legislation to establish term limits for the justices and an enforceable ethics code. President Biden, who has long resisted such revisions, and other Democrats have been outraged by a wave of sharply conservative rulings from the high court, including a decision this month granting presidential immunity from prosecution for official acts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c5d9300-43b9-11ef-8cd8-0000a1aced38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. security officials recently learned of Iranian threat against Trump, apparently unrelated to rally shooting</title>
      <description>The Biden administration warned the Secret Service and the former president's security detail about an unspecified threat before Saturday’s shooting, according to a national security official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss security decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0bb3630-43b7-11ef-b892-0000a1ace8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 21:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. J.D. Vance says wife Usha Vance is ‘brilliant.’ Here's what to know about the potential next second lady.</title>
      <description>The lawyer and mother of three could add second lady to her list of titles if Donald Trump is elected in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc9cdd0-43b2-11ef-9bd0-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. ties a temperature high of 104 set in 1988 for the calendar day amid its most intense heat wave since the Dust Bowl</title>
      <description>It is the District's highest temperature since July 2012. It's the third straight day above 100, matching the longest such streak since 1930. One more day of extreme heat is expected on Wednesday before some relief.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7d18350-43ad-11ef-b892-0000a1ace8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:58:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s allies are planning a series of artificial intelligence ‘Manhattan Projects’ to develop military technology</title>
      <description>The framework would also lift "burdensome regulations" and create “industry-led” agencies to evaluate AI models and secure systems from foreign adversaries, according to a copy of the document viewed exclusively by The Washington Post. It presents a markedly different strategy for the booming sector than that of the Biden administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd8524d0-43a5-11ef-a0d4-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Schumer, N.J. Gov. Murphy lead calls for Sen. Menendez to resign following his guilty verdict in bribery case</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-N.Y.) and New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) issued swift calls for Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) to step aside after he was convicted of taking bribes from three businessmen who showered him and his wife with cash, gold bars and a Mercedes-Benz. “Senator Menendez must now do what is right for his constituents,” Schumer said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c872ff31-43a1-11ef-86b3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) found guilty in federal bribery and corruption trial in Manhattan</title>
      <description>Menendez had been accused of accepting gold bars, a Mercedes-Benz convertible and other bribes from businessmen with ties to the governments of Egypt and Qatar, as well as trying to derail criminal investigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7a7e4a0-4394-11ef-b06c-0000a1ace647</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: 20-year-old listens to racist rapper. Should his parent speak up?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: 20-year-old listens to racist rapper. Should his parent speak up?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c48eccb0-438c-11ef-aa51-000a1ace43c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their cup of woes runneth over in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2972b80-4377-11ef-a8b6-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandaged Trump. Rally shooting. Aileen Cannon. Brutal heat. Prime Day. Longer days. Extinct butterfly. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ccf5a30-4362-11ef-97f5-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump made an emotional entrance at the GOP convention, seizing his moment after an assassination attempt and a string of wins</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s appearance at the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee was a fitting culmination to a two-and-a-half-week stretch during which the former president survived an attempt on his life — and scored crucial victories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d1972f0-4324-11ef-8f10-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 03:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Dodgers outfielder Teoscar Hernández wins Home Run Derby in Texas</title>
      <description>The 31-year-old Hernández beat Kansas City Royals shortstop Bobby Witt Jr. in the final Monday night at Globe Life Field in Arlington, Tex., to win this year’s event. He has 19 home runs this season. The All-Star Game is Tuesday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bf62580-431f-11ef-a8d5-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 02:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans kick off their convention just days after the assassination attempt against Donald Trump. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Convening in Milwaukee, the party adopted a new platform earlier Monday, while Trump announced J.D. Vance as his running mate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f9bbba0-42fd-11ef-9255-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses warned police of Trump shooter at least 86 seconds before gunfire, video shows</title>
      <description>A Post analysis of the newly surfaced video backs up reports from other witnesses, who have said they tried to alert police before shots rang out. Growing evidence that law enforcement was made aware of the shooter before he opened fire has put the Secret Service under pressure to explain what analysts have described as a major security failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94817750-42f8-11ef-8d27-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rifle used by Trump rally shooter was bought 11 years ago, person familiar says</title>
      <description>Thomas Matthew Crooks, who fired shots at former president Donald Trump at a rally in Butler, Pa., Saturday evening, used a rifle legally purchased by his father in 2013, said a person familiar with the investigation, speaking on the condition of anonymity to share details that have not been made public. Crooks, who was shot dead by the Secret Service after opening fire, bought 50 rounds of ammunition at a local gun shop Saturday morning, this person said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ed9750-42e5-11ef-9843-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. soars to 101 degrees, setting record amid hottest summer to date</title>
      <description>Monday’s high of at least 101 set a record for the second straight day. An excessive heat warning is in effect for Tuesday, too, when heat indexes — factoring in heat and humidity — are expected to reach 105 to 110.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e686a2c0-42e2-11ef-9c21-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Sen. J.D. Vance (R-Ohio) to be his running mate</title>
      <description>A onetime sharp critic of Donald Trump turned staunch loyalist, Vance rose to prominence after his 2016 memoir, “Hillbilly Elegy.” Now 39, he would be one of the youngest vice presidents in history if elected in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9743f10-42dd-11ef-8c4d-000a1acec7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans at convention approve new platform without long-held positions on abortion and same-sex marriage</title>
      <description>Antiabortion activists had wanted to explicitly call for a constitutional amendment to give embryos or fetuses legal rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55918a80-42da-11ef-a669-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse takes over as class parent for husband who dropped the ball</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse takes over as class parent for husband who dropped the ball</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318cf7c1-42c4-11ef-a9bd-0000a1aceb03</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses classified documents case against Trump</title>
      <description>Aileen Cannon, the federal judge overseeing the classified documents charges against former president Donald Trump, has dismissed the indictment on the grounds that special counsel Jack Smith was improperly appointed, according to a new court filing Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5021120-42b2-11ef-8c38-000a1acedf4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A show that predicts the future in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac1e62f0-42ae-11ef-9e3a-0000a1acebd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gunman. Secret Service. Biden’s message. Israeli strikes. Baldwin trial. Richard Simmons. Spain’s victories. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6359be31-4299-11ef-a8d5-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s close call: Seven columnists respond to the attempt on former president Donald Trump’s life — and its aftermath.</title>
      <description>Seven columnists respond to the attempt on former president Donald Trump’s life — and its aftermath.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9218110-423b-11ef-9588-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden is set to speak from the Oval Office at 8 p.m. ET. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The president said earlier on Sunday that he was directing an “independent review of the national security” at Saturday’s Trump rally to assess exactly what happened in the shooting that left one attendee dead and two injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bf329a0-4239-11ef-be0b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain wins European Championship, beating England, 2-1, for its third title since 2008</title>
      <description>La Roja finished a dominant run Sunday in Berlin, claiming its fourth continental championship in its fifth title-game appearance and denying England its first major trophy since the 1966 World Cup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60e6f7a0-4224-11ef-bde2-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 21:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It could feel like 110 degrees in the D.C. area on Monday. Officials have issued an excessive-heat warning.</title>
      <description>Highs are forecast to reach 100 or so but heat indexes, factoring in humidity, will near 110. Tuesday could be just as hot, and an excessive-heat watch is in effect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d761830-421b-11ef-9588-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive material found in Trump rally shooter’s car. Biden expected to speak on attempted assassination soon. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro (D) identified the person killed during Saturday’s rally as Corey Comperatore, saying he died “protecting his family.” And former president Donald Trump on Sunday urged Americans to “stand united” after the shooting at the Pennsylvania rally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac660240-4209-11ef-bfd5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">866e0a51-41fb-11ef-9654-0000a1ace02f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 16:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Alcaraz wins Wimbledon men’s singles title, beating Novak Djokovic in the final for the second straight year</title>
      <description>Alcaraz, a 21-year-old from Spain, beat Djokovic on Sunday at the All England Club for his second Wimbledon title and his fourth Grand Slam championship overall.
Djokovic, 37, was playing for a record-tying eighth Wimbledon men’s singles title and a 25th Grand Slam singles title that would have given him the most of any player in any era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47424e30-41f7-11ef-a9ca-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 15:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses describe chaos, fear at Trump rally shooting: ‘Oh my god, they got Trump’</title>
      <description>For those who had been waiting hours in the heat on Saturday in Butler, Pa., to hear Donald Trump speak, elation turned instantly to disbelief, horror, terror and anger after a sniper opened fire. They struggled in real time to comprehend what millions would soon grapple with from afar — a brazen attack on a former president and presumed GOP nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf66c853-41f2-11ef-bde2-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Shannen Doherty dies at 53. ‘Beverly Hills, 90210’ made her a star before ‘Charmed’ cemented her as an early-2000s TV icon.</title>
      <description>She announced in 2015 that she was being treated for breast cancer and last year said the cancer had spread to her brain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">285c4b10-41e8-11ef-ad04-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
