<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 10:03:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump’s request, scores of career diplomats resign from State Department ahead of inauguration</title>
      <description>The forced departures, the prerogative of an incoming administration, indicate a desire to quickly shift the makeup of the department as President-elect Donald Trump seeks to upend the global diplomatic chessboard after four years of President Joe Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e2a6820-d6c8-11ef-b91d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s first executive orders could include border, oil drilling, DEI and federal worker policies, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Congressional Republican leaders were briefed on the broad contours of what Donald Trump is expected to sign shortly after he is sworn in as president, including sweeping changes related to the southern border, energy and the federal government workforce, two people familiar with the call said. Many of the executive orders are expected to be challenged in court. Follow our Inauguration Day coverage Monday for live updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab268360-d6b4-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 22:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burst of snow moving through D.C. area and roads will freeze tonight, ahead of Inauguration Day</title>
      <description>The snow will end by 6 or 7 p.m. in most areas, but falling temperatures mean wet and slushy roads will turn icy tonight. Bitter cold is expected Monday with wind chills in the single digits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25cd4d80-d6ae-11ef-ae05-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden reflects on Nancy Pelosi, Donald Trump and other relationships</title>
      <description>The first lady, after a half-century in public life, gives The Washington Post an exclusive exit interview — and looks to the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a9f05c0-d6a0-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says it’s coming back online after Trump vowed to halt ban</title>
      <description>The social media platform thanked the president-elect for giving companies enough “clarity and assurance” to restore services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4de32061-d690-11ef-bf71-0000a1ace0dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 18:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31bf3bc0-d687-11ef-aede-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 17:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Israeli hostages released from Gaza under ceasefire deal. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Three Israeli women kidnapped by Hamas-led fighters on Oct. 7, 2023, were transferred by the International Committee of the Red Cross to the Israeli military Sunday. Prior to their release, Hamas named them as Romi Gonen, 24, Emily Damari, 28, and Doron Steinbrecher, 31.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76f5efe0-d67d-11ef-b6d5-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump promises to delay TikTok ban in U.S. with Monday executive order</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump says the order on the first day of his term will delay enforcement of the ban so “we can make a deal to protect our national security” with partial U.S. ownership of the platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70b9faa0-d67c-11ef-b6d5-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders won again? Who are these guys, columnist Barry Svrluga wonders. What is happening here?</title>
      <description>Washington made clear there is no team it can’t beat, no game it can’t win. This completely new football reality has become the talk of the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f25f0db1-d678-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c91cefa1-d671-11ef-bf71-0000a1ace0dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting halts in Gaza as ceasefire takes effect after nearly three-hour delay</title>
      <description>The ceasefire in Gaza has come into effect, Israel said, after Hamas provided the names of three hostages set to be released later Sunday. The halt in fighting was delayed after Hamas failed to provide the list of names on time, during which Israeli strikes killed at least 19 people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08fbd650-d64e-11ef-af2a-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 10:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Deadly Israeli strikes continue in Gaza as ceasefire is held up over hostage names</title>
      <description>An earlier alert to this story incorrectly stated that a ceasefire between Israel and Hamas took effect in Gaza. The ceasefire has been held up over Hamas’s list of hostage names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7516a21-d63f-11ef-abea-0000a1acebd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Israeli strikes continue in Gaza as ceasefire is held up over hostage names</title>
      <description>The ceasefire was set to take effect at 8:30 a.m. local time. Hamas said it was late on delivering a list of hostages’ names for “technical reasons.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318d4b60-d63c-11ef-9db7-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ceasefire between Israel and Hamas takes effect in the Gaza Strip, pausing 15 months of war</title>
      <description>The truce began at 8:30 a.m. local time ahead of the first exchange of Israeli hostages for Palestinian prisoners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eb10680-d63b-11ef-a7ec-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders upset Lions to advance to the NFC championship</title>
      <description>Washington won a shocker, 45-31, on Saturday night in Detroit and will play next weekend with a Super Bowl berth on the line. This is the deepest Washington has progressed since 1992, when the franchise won its third Super Bowl. The turnaround led by rookie quarterback Jayden Daniels and first-year coach Dan Quinn is one of the biggest surprises in recent NFL history. In the NFC championship game, the Commanders will meet either the Philadelphia Eagles or Los Angeles Rams, who play Sunday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8707b680-d61d-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 04:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok shuts down as U.S. ban takes effect</title>
      <description>TikTok’s app and website effectively shut down in the United States late Saturday just before a nationwide ban against the video-sharing platform came into force.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee5730c0-d61a-11ef-9c3c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 04:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders visit the Lions in Washington's first divisional playoff game in 19 years. Follow for updates.</title>
      <description>Jayden Daniels and the upstart Washington Commanders look to continue their magical run but face a huge test tonight at top-seeded Detroit. The matchup is set to begin at 8 p.m.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f192010-d600-11ef-aecb-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 00:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials are reassessing post-inauguration immigration raids in Chicago after plans leak, says ‘border czar’ Tom Homan</title>
      <description>Homan says the incoming administration is assessing plans to launch post-inauguration immigration raids in Chicago after plans leaked in news reports. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials had been planning a large operation in the Chicago area next week that would require additional officers to ramp up arrests, according to two people with knowledge of the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cecfd10-d5f3-11ef-98d4-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 23:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol is arrested. He is accused of leading an insurrection.</title>
      <description>Yoon, accused of abusing his power last month when he declared martial law, is the first sitting South Korean president to be arrested. The warrant was issued early Sunday by a Seoul court. Yoon was already in custody.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1311500-d5dc-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A key ‘weakness’ in L.A.’s wildfire strategy went unaddressed for years, a Post investigation shows</title>
      <description>L.A. Fire Chief Kristin M. Crowley warned in a previously unreported 2023 memo that the lack of a professional wildland unit was the “one significant area of weakness” in her department’s ability to contain wildfires. After years of bureaucratic and political delays, the city still has no such unit — a gap that offers new insight into how the metropolis failed to reckon with the threat posed by wildfires intensified by climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbc97640-d5cd-11ef-b2b9-0000a1ace319</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several inches of snow could fall in the D.C. area on Sunday, followed by bitter cold</title>
      <description>The heaviest snow will occur between midafternoon and early evening, when travel could be difficult. The coldest air in years will settle in Monday through Wednesday, with freezing temperatures and wind chills frequently in the single digits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65d6fb81-d5cb-11ef-a34c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 18:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the biggest rock band in the world disappeared</title>
      <description>R.E.M. did something more or less no other band has ever done: It stopped playing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">738424f1-d5bd-11ef-8cc1-0000a1acec3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 16:58:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you remember which campaign promises Trump kept his first time in office? Take our quiz.</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump has once again made sweeping promises on what he will do on Day 1 of his presidency. See whether you remember what happened to the promises he made the first time around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29fa5a70-d5b3-11ef-9f9b-0000a1ace8dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 15:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2b2c980-d5a8-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says the app is set to ‘go dark’ in the U.S. when the ban hits Sunday</title>
      <description>The company said the app will “go dark” on Sunday barring a last-minute intervention from the Biden administration to halt enforcement of a federal ban.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cc35aa1-d540-11ef-9c3c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 02:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s government approves ceasefire and hostage release deal with Hamas in critical step toward halting 15-month conflict</title>
      <description>The government vote was delayed by wrangling between Israel and Hamas and by negotiations between Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and his far-right political allies. Israel's approval paves the way for the release of hostages and Palestinian prisoners and the surging of humanitarian aid to Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d9c5b10-d52a-11ef-a290-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 23:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Department will begin ‘extraordinary measures’ to keep U.S. from default, signaling rising concern about debt ceiling</title>
      <description>Starting Tuesday, the government will stop funding some retirement accounts to keep cash on hand to pay creditors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87212510-d524-11ef-a797-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 22:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to weigh whether schools must give parents a chance to remove kids from lessons with books that have LGBTQ+ themes</title>
      <description>The case out of Montgomery County, Maryland, stems from a challenge by a group of parents who said the language arts curriculum went against their religious convictions. The school system did not allow parents to opt out of lessons using several storybooks with LGBTQ+ characters and themes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e43b16a3-d512-11ef-a424-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 20:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA analyst pleads guilty in leak of top-secret Israeli military plans on Iran</title>
      <description>The leaks came in October as the Biden administration was publicly lobbying Israel not to target Iranian nuclear sites or energy facilities — and led Israel to delay its attack plans, U.S. officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4462afa0-d4fc-11ef-abe5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:55:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vivek Ramaswamy, co-leader of Trump’s DOGE initiative, plans to run for Ohio governor</title>
      <description>Biotech entrepreneur Ramaswamy, a former presidential candidate, is the leader with Elon Musk of President-elect Donald Trump’s outside-government group on cutting federal spending. His decision to run for governor was shared by two people familiar with his plans who spoke on the condition of anonymity to speak ahead of an expected announcement. Ramaswamy is seeking to succeed Ohio Gov. Mike DeWine (R), who is term-limited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c7fa4d0-d4fa-11ef-9001-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS commissioner Danny Werfel will resign Monday, clearing the way for Trump to install new pick</title>
      <description>The tax chief's term isn't due to expire until 2027. President-elect Donald Trump has already announced he wants former congressman Billy Long to replace him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">216b7e20-d4fa-11ef-9627-000a1aceb869</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 17:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s inauguration will be moved indoors due to extreme cold forecasted in Washington</title>
      <description>The swearing-in ceremony will be held indoors instead of outside the Capitol, according to two people familiar with the decision, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to share plans that haven’t been publicly announced. Temperatures Monday are expected to be the most frigid for an inauguration since President Ronald Reagan’s ceremony in 1985, which was also moved inside.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e06f0b90-d4f3-11ef-a220-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 16:55:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds law to ban TikTok if it remains under Chinese ownership</title>
      <description>Congress passed the law to address national security concerns about China's ability to retrieve sensitive data from U.S. users of the popular video-sharing app. President-elect Donald Trump, who has pledged to "save TikTok," asked the Supreme Court to delay the law to give him an opportunity to act once he returns to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fc19990-d4e4-11ef-9a3e-0000a1acef39</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">418cbd00-d4e0-11ef-9411-000a1ace3f41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 14:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden commutes the sentences of nearly 2,500 nonviolent drug offenders</title>
      <description>The commutations cut short the prison terms of those serving disproportionately long sentences for drug convictions compared with the punishments they would receive today, according to the White House. “It is time that we equalize these sentencing disparities,” the president said in a statement. “This action is an important step toward righting historic wrongs.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad362a0-d4d2-11ef-83e9-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 12:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s final moves. Kristi Noem. Gaza ceasefire. David Lynch. Los Angeles fires. SpaceX debris. Switch 2. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b68fad0-d4ca-11ef-99c6-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joan Plowright, English actress of dazzling versatility, dies at 95</title>
      <description>Her marriage to Laurence Olivier conferred on her instant rank among the theatrical nobility, and she carved her own considerable and singular place on the British stage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b73ada91-d4c8-11ef-9627-000a1aceb869</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 11:46:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The long-term trends that turned the L.A. fires into a catastrophe</title>
      <description>In Altadena, California, climate change collided with decades of development to produce a new kind of urban conflagration — one that reached deep into a community that was previously thought safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25bad720-d462-11ef-962a-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 23:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As ceasefire looms in ravaged Gaza, deadly airstrikes continue and anxiety abounds</title>
      <description>Palestinians in Gaza waited for a ceasefire and hostage deal between Israel and Hamas to begin, with many expressing modest hopes for what could come next: A return to homes reduced to ruins. A night of sleep without fear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde72a11-d442-11ef-bfb6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:49:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Lynch dies at 78. The filmmaker mixed melodrama and horror in ‘Blue Velvet,’ ‘Mulholland Drive’ and the series ‘Twin Peaks.’</title>
      <description>The surrealist filmmaker shined an eerie light on hypocrisy, moral corruption and sexual violence, revealing the darkness lurking even in sweet-as-cherry-pie small towns. His work explored the sinister recesses of the human psyche with an unsettling blend of melodrama, whimsy and nightmarish horror.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82c32960-d438-11ef-b71d-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland does not want to be part of the U.S., but we are open for business, a government minister from Greenland writes</title>
      <description>We welcome more American investments in our mineral sector.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">beadb350-d433-11ef-ba16-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Try a long-distance relationship after swearing never again?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Try a long-distance relationship after swearing never again?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78a789f1-d42c-11ef-9770-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 17:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Uecker dies at 90. He was a comic bard of baseball, known for his work as a broadcaster and an actor in ‘Major League.’</title>
      <description>Before he was known for two enduring catchphrases — “I must be in the front row!” from a Miller Lite commercial and “Just a bit outside” from the movie “Major League” — Uecker spent six years in the major leagues as a backup catcher and first-string clubhouse comedian. Among a long list of baseball jokers, he is widely considered the funniest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0673971-d428-11ef-89ad-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportation at ‘light speed’: How Trump’s immigration crackdown could unfold</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump has said he would like to deport everyone living illegally in the United States, though he has not set a specific numerical target. Who is most at risk?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27471b10-d423-11ef-a828-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 16:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis picks ally Ashley Moody, the Florida attorney general, to replace Marco Rubio in the Senate</title>
      <description>Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) said Monday he would appoint Moody, a close ally, to fill the vacancy after President-elect Donald Trump tapped Rubio for secretary of state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f146fa10-d41f-11ef-99c6-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate continues to move briskly on hearings for key Trump posts, including treasury secretary and EPA chief. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Committees are considering Scott Bessent for treasury secretary and Lee Zeldin to lead the Environmental Protection Agency. Confirmation hearings are also scheduled Thursday for interior secretary and housing secretary. And a panel of outside witnesses will offer thoughts on Pam Bondi for attorney general after her testimony Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c61e9c0-d41a-11ef-acd7-0000a1ace35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok CEO to attend Trump’s inauguration on Monday, a day after the U.S. ban is set to start</title>
      <description>TikTok CEO Shou Zi Chew plans to attend Donald Trump’s inauguration on Monday, a day after a nationwide ban against the app that the president-elect has pledged to “save” is set to take effect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdfa7280-d417-11ef-89ad-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ban of this dye in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d24fa0-d416-11ef-ae76-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza ceasefire. Biden’s farewell. Trump’s TikTok plan. Los Angeles fires. Food dye ban. Polar vortex. Celtic tribe. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66e53d50-d401-11ef-aa65-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 11:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Origin’s rocket successfully reaches orbit for the first time, advancing the company’s hopes of competing for U.S. contracts</title>
      <description>The uncrewed test flight marked a milestone for the company as it works to get certified to launch national security missions for the Pentagon as well as fly commercial satellites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">534448d0-d3da-11ef-8135-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 07:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
