<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:03:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s retaliatory strike on Iran appears to have been designed to avoid escalating tensions, officials and analysts say</title>
      <description>Israeli officials said the strike was meant to send Iran a message after Tehran launched hundreds of drones and missiles at Israel last weekend — the vast majority of which were shot down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4453b680-fe5b-11ee-9b6e-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ef904e0-fe52-11ee-95bf-0000a1ace0d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the first time, polluters may have to pay to clean up PFAS, commonly known as ‘forever chemicals,’ under new EPA rule</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency designated two of the most pervasive forms of PFAS as hazardous substances under the nation’s Superfund law. The rule could help hundreds of communities affected by contamination and could mean billions of dollars of liabilities for major chemical manufacturers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f00d9ec0-fe4f-11ee-801e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump jury. Title IX. Land rules. Rising temperatures. Women’s sleep. Taylor Swift’s surprise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f86f66c0-fe3b-11ee-b42d-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel carries out airstrike on Iran in retaliation for Tehran’s drone and missile attack, Israeli official says</title>
      <description>The official, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discus sensitive military matters, said it was intended as a message to Iran that Israel had the ability to strike inside the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd27a6c0-fe0a-11ee-a296-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley is alive this year. A super bloom is the latest sign.</title>
      <description>Just weeks after the resurrection of a long-dead lake, the area’s native wildflowers are bursting into bloom. These fleeting phenomena can be traced to the unusual and record-setting precipitation that has inundated California in recent months. Scientists estimate that tens of thousands of acres have bloomed simultaneously, sparking delight from new arrivals and those who have carefully tended Death Valley — more often one of the world’s most extreme places.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8fba2d0-fddb-11ee-90d2-0000a1ace1cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 23:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. vetoes U.N. resolution that would grant full member status to Palestinian state</title>
      <description>The United States voted against a U.N. Security Council resolution that aimed to extend full member status to a Palestinian state. Robert Wood, the alternate American representative to the United Nations, said afterward that Washington “continues to strongly support a two-state solution.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">284270f1-fdcd-11ee-b057-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve jurors have been selected in Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial after two were dismissed earlier in the day</title>
      <description>A dozen jurors have been selected to hear former president Donald Trump’s hush money trial in Manhattan, rapidly pushing the proceedings closer toward opening statements. Jury selection is expected to continue Friday as alternates are sought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2b18ce0-fdc5-11ee-873f-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 20:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can blood tests detect cancer? Some patients are using them already.</title>
      <description>New tests can detect cancer by measuring “signals” in your blood. Many experts say these tests represent a remarkable new chapter in cancer detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88e465e0-fdbd-11ee-bcee-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. just changed how it manages a tenth of its land, putting conservation on equal footing with mining, grazing and drilling</title>
      <description>The Interior Department’s rule represents a seismic shift in the management of roughly 245 million acres of public property.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">963d3c80-fda9-11ee-87cb-000a1acedd72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which U.S. congressional districts benefit from Ukraine aid? Marc Thiessen has the details.</title>
      <description>We mapped the U.S. congressional districts producing weapons for Ukraine. Many are represented by members who have been vocal opponents of Ukraine aid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a74174a0-fda5-11ee-9bc6-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dickey Betts dies at 80. The singer and guitarist co-founded the Allman Brothers Band and wrote hits including ‘Ramblin’ Man.’</title>
      <description>Betts wrote several of the band’s most enduring compositions, including the instrumentals “In Memory of Elizabeth Reed” and “Jessica,” and the pastoral love song “Blue Sky.” He remained best known for the 1973 song “Ramblin’ Man,” which became the band’s only top-10 hit on the Billboard Hot 100. The lyrics, set against a bouncy, upbeat melody, expressed the resigned and unrepentant wanderlust of a man “born in the back seat of a Greyhound bus / Rollin’ down Highway 41.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de2b1a00-fda2-11ee-881e-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: What will this parent do after the kids graduate and move out?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: What will this parent do after the kids graduate and move out?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7d05280-fd9d-11ee-902c-0000a1ace171</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico city enduring toxic arsenic levels in water offers a reminder: Safe water is not available to all Americans</title>
      <description>State and federal records show that in each of the past 16 years, drinking water samples tested in majority-Latino Sunland Park, N.M., have contained illegally high levels of arsenic. Now, residents fear the health consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80d44550-fd9a-11ee-9a21-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump trial juror was dismissed, and potential issues arose with a second juror. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>One of the seven jurors who had been sworn in was excused after telling New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan that news reports described her profession and other personal details that led her to be identified as a juror. Jurors’ names are not being released publicly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4cb8a25-fd8d-11ee-beee-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. imposes new sanctions after Iran’s attack on Israel. The economic penalties target Iranian drone production.</title>
      <description>U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet L. Yellen said the Biden administration’s actions would “degrade and disrupt” Iran’s drone program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5566aad0-fd8a-11ee-b711-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did this animal cross the road? Play today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee2e0630-fd87-11ee-8be6-0000a1ace9b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s hush money trial further splinters his relationship with his beloved New York</title>
      <description>He was a publicity hound and a tabloid star — a Queens boy made good who burst onto the Manhattan scene through sheer force of personality. But now, in a trial that began Monday, the former president’s long-running and turbulent love affair with the city seems to have finally run into irreconcilable differences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c1f2020-fd84-11ee-bd1e-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine strike. Trump trial. Impeachment vote. Arizona abortion. Toxic water. Volcanic eruption. Escaped elephant. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfbfb2d0-fd72-11ee-9a60-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change is turning camels into the new cows</title>
      <description>See these humped creatures as they parade into a village in East Africa, cheered on by families who have lost so much.
It’s a grand experiment in climate adaptation for traditional herders whose wealth and sustenance depends on raising animals that produce milk. Will camels be the cure?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cf5df00-fd12-11ee-b002-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 23:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. troops in Niger are vulnerable as Biden administration resists order to withdraw, whistleblower says</title>
      <description>Niger’s military junta last month declared the U.S. military presence there “illegal” and said that it was ending all accords, effective immediately.
In a complaint to Congress, a senior Air Force leader deployed in Niger accused top officials at the U.S. Embassy there of having “intentionally suppressed intelligence” as they seek to maintain the “facade of a great country-to-country relationship.” Administration officials rejected the whistleblower’s claims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3c67ac0-fd0d-11ee-9280-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 22:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-backed ‘Alpha Male’ Nick Adams is teaching young men the art of being hard to deal with</title>
      <description>In some ways, Adams’s shtick is conventionally conservative: He’s Christian, he’s very concerned about there being only two genders, he rails against “woke.” In other ways, his version of MAGA manhood is so over-the-top, so uncanny that it almost seems like performance art. Is he serious?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e41e840-fd04-11ee-80fa-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:51:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate votes to dismiss impeachment charges against Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas</title>
      <description>Senate Democrats voted quickly to dismiss two articles of impeachment against Mayorkas that alleged he mismanaged an influx of migrants at the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adfa3910-fcf8-11ee-8612-0000a1ace371</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 20:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA bans Raptors forward Jontay Porter for violating gambling policy, including limiting his playing time for betting purposes</title>
      <description>The league announced Wednesday that an investigation found Porter had disclosed confidential information to bettors, limited his participation in games for betting purposes and wagered on NBA games — an array of brazenly inappropriate actions that jeopardize the integrity of competition. The investigation was launched last month in response to suspicious betting activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9267ab0-fcdb-11ee-b33d-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Is it really better to crack an egg on a flat surface than on the edge of a bowl? Chat with our food writers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Is it really better to crack an egg on a flat surface than on the edge of a bowl? Chat with our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99703560-fcd7-11ee-a2c5-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Youngkin (R) and lawmakers agree to seek new state budget, aiming to avert a government shutdown</title>
      <description>Gov. Glenn Youngkin met with General Assembly leaders to find a way around a budget impasse over taxes and spending priorities, according to two people close to the arrangements who spoke on the condition of anonymity to share private negotiations. Lawmakers and the governor agreed to create a new budget and hold a special legislative session, probably in mid-May, to wrap up the budget process well before the June 30 deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4b18360-fcd3-11ee-9df3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They criticized Israel. This X account upended their lives.</title>
      <description>Nearly three dozen people have been fired or suspended from their jobs after being featured by StopAntisemitism, according to the group’s X feed, part of a wave of digital activism related to the Israel-Gaza war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5cfb720-fccb-11ee-904a-0000a1ace9b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘remarkable slowdown in demand’ for this company’s product in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1c1d4c0-fcbe-11ee-b71b-0000a1acec99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A secret Russian document offers a rare, official glimpse into Moscow’s campaign against the West</title>
      <description>The classified Russian Foreign Ministry document calls for an “offensive information campaign” and other measures spanning “the military-political, economic and trade and informational psychological spheres” against a “coalition of unfriendly countries” led by the United States. The document was provided to The Washington Post by a European intelligence service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8b4fe20-fcbc-11ee-aae5-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump jurors. Supreme Court. House speaker. Pro-Palestinian protests. Camel milk. Cancer tests. Space junk. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8521bd0-fca9-11ee-9df3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Graham dies at 87. The former U.S. senator and Florida governor was a consensus-builder and an ardent opponent of the Iraq War.</title>
      <description>Mr. Graham, a moderate Democrat, served two terms as Florida’s governor and three terms as a senator. He made a short-lived bid for the 2004 Democratic presidential nomination, campaigning largely on his opposition to President George W. Bush’s invasion of Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbf39d10-fc69-11ee-8e83-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 03:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Dead ships’: Before a cargo ship hit Baltimore’s Key Bridge, hundreds of others lost propulsion in U.S. waters in recent years</title>
      <description>A Washington Post analysis of Coast Guard records found that 424 cargo ships longer than 600 feet reported losing propulsion — meaning the engines were shut down — in U.S. waters during the three years before the Key Bridge disaster in Baltimore. About a quarter of the incidents occurred near a port, bridge or other infrastructure. Experts say a lack of consistent rules on when cargo ships should be escorted by supportive tug boats adds to the danger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d0bcab0-fc45-11ee-9fa6-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven jurors picked to serve on Trump hush money jury, and other key takeaways</title>
      <description>Manhattanites spilled into a courtroom on Tuesday and were quizzed about their media diet, hobbies and families — all to see if they could be fair jurors in the criminal trial of former president Donald Trump,, who also happens to be the likely 2024 Republican presidential nominee. Seven were chosen, and some were passed over for problematic social media posts or other reasons. Opening statements could be as soon as Monday, the judge said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74f2b8a1-fc3e-11ee-9182-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom yearns for her kids to feel the same freedoms of her youth</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom yearns for her kids to feel the same freedoms of her youth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53720811-fc1c-11ee-a223-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum builds to oust House Speaker Mike Johnson as two fellow Republicans say they would vote to remove him</title>
      <description>Rep. Thomas Massie (R-Ky.) announced Tuesday morning he would join Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s (R-Ga.) bid to depose Johnson (R-La.) after the speaker introduced a complex foreign aid package decoupling Israel from Ukraine aid.

Neither Massie nor Green has officially brought up the so-called motion to vacate, which would trigger a vote on Johnson’s leadership. But Republicans are now one vote short of being able to oust him if Democrats don’t step in to support him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05c20c20-fc15-11ee-aa54-0000a1aceb83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears deeply divided over Jan. 6 obstruction charges in case that may impact Trump’s election interference trial</title>
      <description>After nearly two hours of argument, it was unclear whether the court would allow the Justice Department to apply to Jan. 6 rioters a statute that makes it a crime to obstruct or impede an official proceeding — in this case the joint session of Congress that convened to formally certify Joe Biden’s 2020 victory. Some conservative justices seemed wary of giving prosecutors too much discretion. The obstruction charge is also among the counts Donald Trump is facing in his federal trial for trying to block the 2020 election results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f61e0140-fc0d-11ee-bf6c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian paramedics said Israel gave them safe passage to save a 6-year-old girl in Gaza. They were all killed.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post examination of audio recordings and the damage to the car and ambulance, as well as the presence of Israeli forces in the immediate area that day, raise questions about Israel’s assertion that its forces were “not present near the vehicle or within the firing range.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7827c660-fc06-11ee-aef9-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court is hearing arguments in a case that could undo convictions of Jan. 6 rioters. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Defense lawyers say prosecutors improperly stretched the law by charging more than 350 people with obstruction of an official proceeding, a case with implications for former president Donald Trump’s election interference trial in D.C. The high court’s ruling has the potential to undo the convictions and sentences of those who have already gone to trial or pleaded guilty and upend the charges still pending for many more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa94211-fbfc-11ee-b8b8-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 14:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gift of trees in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef37db0-fbf5-11ee-8657-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 13:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Jan. 6 case. Ukraine aid. ‘Rust’ sentencing. Coral bleaching. Caitlin Clark. Abba and Biggie. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7af6ba20-fbe0-11ee-969e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They were liberal public school teachers. Now they teach kids to be anti-‘woke.’</title>
      <description>Kali and Joshua Fontanilla taught English in a deep-blue California district — but quit their jobs and moved to Florida to start their own school after growing convinced the curriculum was left-wing propaganda. While the claim that public schools promote left-wing “indoctrination” has become a commonplace on the right, it’s not usually an allegation repeated by teachers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24f6cbc0-fb85-11ee-981d-0000a1aced49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fever selects Caitlin Clark with first pick in WNBA draft, officially launching her professional basketball career</title>
      <description>Clark, a record-setting guard at the University of Iowa, was virtually certain to be taken with the No. 1 pick once she announced in February that she would enter this year’s draft. She joins the WNBA shouldering unprecedented expectations to increase its visibility after her college games drew sellout crowds and record television ratings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d631b981-fb81-11ee-99d0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 23:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Idaho ban on gender-affirming care for minors to take effect as case continues</title>
      <description>While the underlying case concerns the constitutionality of a ban on gender-affirming medical care for minors, the court’s order did not address the merits of the issue – only whether the law could take effect for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85622ae0-fb76-11ee-8348-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 22:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for region until 10 p.m.</title>
      <description>Hit-or-miss storms could produce large hail and damaging wind gusts, in addition to dangerous lightning. The threat for storms gradually shifts southward through the region during the afternoon and into the evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86d6fe20-fb56-11ee-ad8b-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Rust’ armorer sentenced to 18 months for involuntary manslaughter in fatal on-set shooting of cinematographer</title>
      <description>Hannah Gutierrez-Reed was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter in June. She was accused of failing to ensure gun safety on the set of the low-budget Western movie in 2021. Alec Baldwin was rehearsing with a revolver on set when the gun went off, killing cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and wounding director Joel Souza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">192ae410-fb54-11ee-bb3f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you afford to buy a house? Take our quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>Homeownership is how many Americans accumulate wealth, but affording a home is a growing challenge for many. Mortgage rates have more than doubled and are now at nearly 7 percent on a typical 30-year loan. So, should you buy a home right now? To help you decide, take this quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3f17d0-fb4a-11ee-840c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27864bb0-fb42-11ee-9eed-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This should be a global wake-up call’: Corals are bleaching in every corner of the ocean, threatening its web of life, scientists say</title>
      <description>The fourth-ever bleaching event in history, declared by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration and International Coral Reef Initiative, is the second in a decade. More than 54 percent of all the reef areas on the planet have experienced bleaching-level heat stress in the past year, and the overall amount could soon pass a record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bb41d0-fb39-11ee-a5c4-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla to shed more than 10 percent of its workforce as EV demand cools</title>
      <description>The move by CEO Elon Musk comes after the company, which employed more than 140,000 as of December, reported a sharp decline in vehicle deliveries in the first quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5664cd01-fb31-11ee-ac6b-0000a1ace217</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A historical location hosts a film festival in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bff74450-fb2c-11ee-9274-000a1aced311</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
