<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 11:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Father of Michigan school shooter found guilty of involuntary manslaughter, a month after teen’s mother was convicted</title>
      <description>James Crumbley's teenage son Ethan Crumbley killed four students at Oxford High School in 2021. Both James and his wife, Jennifer Crumbley, were accused of failing to secure a weapon in their home and ignoring their son's pleas for help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85523cb0-e259-11ee-9973-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Georgia case hangs on the decision of a relatively new judge, who plans to rule on Willis misconduct allegations by Friday</title>
      <description>Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee’s ruling is likely to be a career-defining moment for the 34-year-old judge. His decision, whatever it is, will almost certainly be questioned because of its implications for the 2024 presidential election and is sure to draw political attacks in an already contentious election year in which he, Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis and former president Donald Trump will each be on the ballot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee6bea2-e24e-11ee-ab1a-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA suggests one-month delay to Donald Trump’s hush money trial</title>
      <description>Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg suggested that the pending trial of former president Donald Trump be delayed a month from its planned March 25 start because of new documents turned over by federal prosecutors — a surprising twist in what has been expected to be the first criminal trial of a former president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4162dcd2-e23b-11ee-9ac8-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump adviser Peter Navarro must go to prison for ignoring Jan. 6 subpoena, appeals court says</title>
      <description>Navarro was convicted for refusing to testify before Congress about his involvement in efforts to undo the results of the 2020 election. He has been ordered to report to a prison in Miami by Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2550d9e0-e22f-11ee-8fc6-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$730 hotel rooms and $75 parking for fans? Youngkin’s own report calls forecasts for proposed Capitals-Wizards arena rosy.</title>
      <description>The analysis, commissioned by the administration of Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R), found the financing plan assumes thousands of fans will pay $75 for parking, the teams’ owner will host 53 more events annually in Alexandria than it did last year at its current D.C. arena, and a new luxury hotel will book rooms at a “historically unprecedented” rate of $731 a night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95093e0-e22d-11ee-a832-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All that is true about aging is illuminated on a walk, Anne Lamott writes</title>
      <description>We work, love and help others as best we can, gawk at nature, rest. Is that it? Pretty much.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89073360-e222-11ee-9973-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: His version of respect for women results in few second dates</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: His version of respect for women results in few second dates</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1259a2d0-e21c-11ee-b91b-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Orleans police officer took a 14-year-old girl for a rape kit. Then he sexually assaulted her, too.</title>
      <description>Hundreds of police officers have been charged with sexually abusing children over the past two decades, a Washington Post investigation found. This is how one patrol officer preyed on a girl he met on the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ccdabd0-e210-11ee-8ee3-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer to call for ‘new election’ in Israel as U.S. frustrations grow over Netanyahu’s handling of Gaza</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer’s remarks are the clearest signal to Israel yet that frustrations over Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu have reached the highest echelons of the U.S. government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1516da0-e20d-11ee-b104-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpaceX’s Starship makes it to space on its third test flight after two previous setbacks</title>
      <description>The spacecraft lifted off at 9:25 a.m. Eastern and has now traveled farther than on either of its previous test flights. If the spacecraft continues to perform, it’s expected to splash down in the Indian Ocean about an hour after liftoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21b6b871-e209-11ee-92cc-0000a1acef07</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A room of one’s own — at an ex’s museum! — in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dc91571-e207-11ee-bd93-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA curbs cancer-causing chemical used by facilities that sterilize medical supplies</title>
      <description>The new Environmental Protection Agency rule is aimed at helping disadvantaged communities across the country reduce their exposure to ethylene oxide, a highly toxic gas. But critics say it could create a shortfall of sterilized medical devices for hospitals and clinics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27472fa0-e203-11ee-8893-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 13:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok ban. Trump hearing. Gaza strike. Online abuse. Iron lung. Early spring. Whale grandmothers. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">020ce9c0-e1f2-11ee-924a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dorie Ladner dies at 81. The civil rights activist braved gunfire, tear gas, police dogs and the KKK for racial equality.</title>
      <description>At a time when Mississippi was one of the most dangerous places in the South for African Americans and civil rights workers, Ladner led marches and sit-ins, mounted voter registration drives, and helped organize events including the 1963 March on Washington. She traveled around the country encouraging Black people to embrace their civic responsibility to vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b61fe00-e186-11ee-87c2-000a1ace5899</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 22:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could TikTok really face a nationwide ban? We break down what the House bill demands — and how likely it is to pass the Senate.</title>
      <description>House lawmakers today approved a bill that could eventually lead to a ban of the social media platform if it doesn’t cut ties with its Beijing-based parent company. It now heads to the Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60376f20-e16b-11ee-977c-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 18:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: National Park Service to remove 140 cherry trees for D.C. sea wall project. A previous alert said 300.</title>
      <description>The removal of the iconic Japanese flowering trees between the Thomas Jefferson Memorial and the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial will begin in May, the Park Service said.

In all, about 300 trees of different varieties, including cherry trees, will be removed from the Tidal Basin and West Potomac Park during a three-year project to rehabilitate crumbling sea walls in the area. When work is completed, the Park Service said, it will plant hundreds more trees.

An earlier version of this alert misstated the number of cherry trees that would be removed. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f3d810-e15e-11ee-9657-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service to cut down 300 cherry trees over a 3-year span for D.C. sea wall project. Most will be replaced.</title>
      <description>The removal of the first 140 of the iconic Japanese flowering trees between the Thomas Jefferson Memorial and the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial will begin in May, the Park Service said.

Ultimately, 300 cherry trees around the Tidal Basin and West Potomac Park will be removed during a three-year project to rehabilitate crumbling sea walls in the area, but 274 of the trees will be replaced, according to the Park Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b326711-e154-11ee-87f7-0000a1ace202</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother is a risk to ‘cut and run’ on his premature newborn twins</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother is a risk to ‘cut and run’ on his premature newborn twins</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8d994d0-e152-11ee-a874-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge drops a small number of the charges against Trump in sweeping election interference case</title>
      <description>The judge overseeing the election interference case against former president Donald Trump and several allies dismissed six counts of the 41-count criminal racketeering indictment, ruling that the charges lacked specific detail, but he declined to dismiss the case.

In a nine-page order issued Wednesday morning, Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee dismissed six charges alleging Trump and five co-defendants had illegally urged elected officials in Georgia to violate their oaths of office in their attempts to overturn Trump’s 2020 election loss in the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e36eaa0-e14b-11ee-aed9-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the best way to split the bill at a restaurant? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>Post food critic Tom Sietsema answers your restaurant-related questions, solves your dining dilemmas and gives suggestions on the best places to eat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2214cf51-e14b-11ee-94ff-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The House overwhelmingly passed a bill that could ban TikTok in the U.S. Its fate in the Senate is uncertain.</title>
      <description>The legislation, approved less than a week after advancing out of committee, would force TikTok to split from its parent company or face a national ban — a sweeping bipartisan rebuke of the popular video-sharing app. It now goes to the Senate, where some lawmakers have expressed concern it may run afoul of the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87b97530-e147-11ee-ba83-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predatory groups are coercing children into violent and degrading acts on popular online platforms, then boasting about it</title>
      <description>An emerging network of groups motivated by cruelty seeks out children with mental health issues and blackmails them into self-harm, in some cases pressuring them to take their own lives, a global examination by The Washington Post and several media partners found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f49a82a0-e13f-11ee-8a5a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘A pivot out of nowhere’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef302ab0-e13d-11ee-9ac0-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexei Navalny’s widow, Yulia Navalnaya, writes: Putin isn’t a politician, he’s a gangster</title>
      <description>Putin isn’t a politician, he’s a gangster</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bf3d640-e13c-11ee-93fa-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vs. Trump. Robert Hur. TikTok ban. Ukraine aid. Andrew Tate. Trailblazing pilot. Fox disguise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cce894c0-e128-11ee-a811-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officially wins the GOP nomination for president, AP projects, setting up a rematch with Biden</title>
      <description>Donald Trump secured the 1,215 delegates needed to make him the party’s official nominee, the Associated Press reported. He is set to be formally nominated at the Republican National Convention from July 15-18 in Milwaukee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42cb9710-e0e7-11ee-86fd-0000a1acec72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden formally gains enough delegates to secure the 2024 Democratic presidential nomination, AP projects</title>
      <description>President Biden clinched the 1,968 delegates needed to earn the 2024 presidential nomination, the Associated Press reported, setting up a likely rematch with former president Donald Trump.
He is set to be formally nominated at the Democratic National Convention from Aug. 19-22 in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">003856b0-e0c7-11ee-a3ca-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 23:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. will send Ukraine $300 million in weapons as Biden’s request for more aid remains stalled in the House</title>
      <description>The emergency package, announced by the White House on Tuesday, will be funded by “unanticipated cost savings” from contracts the Pentagon had brokered to replace weapons previously provided to Ukraine, national security adviser Jake Sullivan said. President Biden’s request for billions of dollars in additional funding has been stalled for months amid a broader political dispute that includes aid for Israel and U.S. border security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3647ad1-e0a2-11ee-8bc3-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast. Subtweet. If you’re still using these dated words, you’re not alone, Benjamin Dreyer writes.</title>
      <description>If you’re still using these dated words, you’re not alone</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a82820-e08f-11ee-b1aa-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband mulls unemployment as preferable to a ‘step down’ job</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband mulls unemployment as preferable to a ‘step down’ job</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0e52fe0-e089-11ee-85e4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Robert Hur will testify to Congress that he did not ‘disparage the president unfairly.’ Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Hur is testifying before Congress this morning about why he did not recommend seeking charges against President Biden for his possession of classified documents after Biden’s vice presidency ended. The former prosecutor’s description of Biden’s memory lapses during an interview has become fodder for Republicans in the 2024 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7f00850-e079-11ee-9643-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 14:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My eyes see ... today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4c5720-e074-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump last year asked Elon Musk if he wanted to buy Truth Social, a sign they continue to communicate more than previously known</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump’s overture to the billionaire did not lead to a deal. But the two have had other conversations, too, Trump advisers say, about politics and business.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26b7fe30-e072-11ee-80d3-0000a1acef5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The annual inflation rate rose in February, underscoring concerns prices could be heating up again despite the Fed’s efforts</title>
      <description>The central bank is eyeing multiple interest rate cuts this year — but only if progress on inflation keeps up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d736d9d0-e06c-11ee-88a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript of Biden’s interview paints nuanced portrait of his cognitive abilities ahead of Robert Hur’s congressional testimony</title>
      <description>The president doesn’t come across as absent-minded as Hur has made him out to be — and Hur doesn’t appear as crass as Biden has made him out to be. Hur is slated to testify about his probe into Biden’s handling of classified documents today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e39fe20-e06a-11ee-88a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 election. Special counsel. Haiti violence. LGBTQ+ law. Boeing whistleblower. Airbnb cameras. Sycamore Gap tree. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1725880-e05f-11ee-9384-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a doctored photo of the Princess of Wales triggered a media crisis</title>
      <description>Celebrities aspire to look perfect. Journalism aspires to tell the truth. But those two standards clashed when Kensington Palace released its first photo of Catherine since her abdominal surgery, with obvious manipulations that may have exacerbated a royal PR crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc04d121-e000-11ee-a8ae-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC fires dozens of employees after Trump-backed leadership takes over</title>
      <description>Communications and political staff members were fired from the party’s central committee, according to three people familiar with the firings but who weren’t authorized to speak publicly. The staffing changes came just days after Michael Whatley and Lara Trump, former president Donald Trump’s chosen candidates, were elected to head the RNC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15204b00-dffa-11ee-8b84-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Biden’s $7.3 trillion budget proposal would raise taxes on the wealthy to cover health and child care. A previous alert said $7.2 trillion.</title>
      <description>The White House proposal is unlikely to become law due to Republican control of the House. Aides say it would lower the soaring national debt by $3 trillion over 10 years.

An earlier version of this alert misstated the cost of the proposed budget. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85fa6360-dfc3-11ee-b517-0000a1ace62c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s $7.2 trillion budget proposal would raise taxes on the wealthy to cover health and child care. It’s unlikely to be approved.</title>
      <description>The White House proposal is unlikely to become law due to Republican control of the House. Aides say it would lower the soaring national debt by $3 trillion over 10 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">226af0a1-dfc1-11ee-b13f-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO members must raise their defense spending to 3 percent of GDP, Polish President Andrzej Duda writes</title>
      <description>On March 12, 1999, Poland realized its dream of joining NATO. Twenty-five years later, we know that strengthening the alliance is vital amid rising threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed70d220-dfb6-11ee-9d5c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest moments at the Oscars, including ‘Oppenheimer,’ Emma Stone, Ken and a naked John Cena</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic biopic dominated the Oscars, and the best actress category held the biggest surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7471b070-dfb0-11ee-81e0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sink your teeth into today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c983b6a0-dfae-11ee-8260-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest moments of the Academy Awards, including ‘Oppenheimer,’ Emma Stone, Ken and a naked John Cena</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic biopic dominated the Oscars, and the best actress category held the biggest surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a62040b0-dfaa-11ee-9ed0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar winners. Trump and Biden. Shutdown deal. Ramadan in Gaza. Kate Middleton. Small houses. Aliens. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d6232a1-df96-11ee-91ac-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine, Princess of Wales, says she altered official photo and apologizes after some photo agencies removed it from circulation</title>
      <description>Princess Catherine posted on social media that she was experimenting with photo editing and apologized for the confusion caused by the family photograph. Several news agencies suspended use of the photo after determining that parts of it had been digitally edited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fc6b6b0-df95-11ee-ac2d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Oppenheimer’ wins best picture at the Oscars, nabbing seven Academy Awards</title>
      <description>The ceremony looked back on a year in which audiences and critics found a lot to love.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72521851-df4e-11ee-ad37-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the latest updates on tonight’s winners, surprises and snubs as ‘Oppenheimer’ vies for a record number of awards</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic-age biopic is poised to have a big night, while Lily Gladstone looks to make history as the first Native American to win an Oscar in an acting category. Join us for live coverage and analysis of the night’s biggest moments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df50260-df31-11ee-b49f-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign insider recounts failed hunt for 2020 fraud in new book</title>
      <description>Ken Block, an expert hired by the campaign, writes that he shot down false claim after false claim in an election that was not stolen. Emails from 2020 reviewed by The Washington Post show one tip was routed to the campaign via the manager of one of Donald Trump's golf clubs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068fc650-df1f-11ee-9c5c-0000a1ace007</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars could make history this year. Here’s everything you need to know about the frontrunners, how to watch and more.</title>
      <description>Will “Oppenheimer” dominate? What are the potential upsets and historic firsts? Is Ryan Gosling really performing as Ken? (Yes!) Here’s your complete rundown before the Academy Awards begin at 7 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ca04540-deff-11ee-93b4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
