<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 18:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The District now has a realistic option for Commanders’ stadium at the old RFK site after political Hail Mary</title>
      <description>In a stunning, last-second twist, Congress passed federal legislation early Saturday to allow D.C. to redevelop the RFK Stadium site and potentially bring the Washington Commanders back to the city. The bill extends the National Park Service’s lease to the city for 99 years and allows for mixed-use development, including commercial, residential and a stadium.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">124a9c00-bfb5-11ef-aa5e-0000a1ace802</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 16:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the secret to living — and aging — well? Get a 12-week newsletter from bestselling author Anne Lamott to find out.</title>
      <description>Sign up for A User's Guide to Aging from The Washington Post</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7136810-bfaf-11ef-bd95-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 15:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1e7aaf0-bfa7-11ef-ae3e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 14:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Christmas market attack toll rises to at least five dead and over 200 injured, officials say</title>
      <description>Many of the injured were in critical condition, German Chancellor Olaf Scholz said. The suspect, a 50-year-old Saudi doctor who arrived in Germany in 2006, had expressed anti-Islam views and described himself as a Saudi dissident, according to a German official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss an open investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55cb2561-bf8f-11ef-9dd4-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress passes bill giving D.C. control of RFK Stadium, allowing city to develop it into home for Commanders</title>
      <description>The U.S. Senate passed the Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Stadium Campus Revitalization Act by unanimous consent early Saturday – a Hail Mary action that appeared close to impossible months ago. The bill previously cleared the House on a broad bipartisan basis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48e8f970-bf63-11ef-ac60-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 06:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress averts government shutdown as Senate passes funding bill</title>
      <description>Lawmakers sealed the deal after the midnight deadline after a week of political turmoil. The bill now goes to President Joe Biden, who is expected to sign it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cd7ee70-bf5e-11ef-91c9-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 05:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill to avert government shutdown, but Senate has just hours to act before deadline</title>
      <description>The measure would keep the government operating into mid-March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc7b3490-bf26-11ef-817b-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The House is voting on legislation to avert a government shutdown. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Lawmakers are racing to beat a midnight deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ecef720-bf23-11ef-9b66-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 22:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. seized a Russian superyacht. Now taxpayers are footing the bill.</title>
      <description>Documents released by the Justice Department show how the U.S. government is paying to maintain the vessel seized as part of a sanctions campaign against Russian oligarchs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">407ab320-bf1b-11ef-9af1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 21:42:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Car slams into crowd at Christmas market in Germany; ‘Numerous’ people injured, says city spokesman</title>
      <description>The suspected driver was apprehended by police, a regional government spokesperson told local media. Authorities did not say what caused the incident or publish any information about the victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05dfb170-bf11-11ef-9dd4-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 20:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This high school banned phones. Here’s what students have to say about it.</title>
      <description>Wakefield High School in Virginia is one of many schools that want to restrict phone use to remove classroom distractions and reduce the harmful effects of social media. The Post interviewed eight students and reviewed some of their phone screen-time reports to better understand how they used the devices before and after the ban started.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a3d2ce1-bef0-11ef-bd95-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 16:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump voters have faith he will help economy and their finances, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s victory in November came down to classic political forces, as the voters who put him over the top in the seven battleground states say the economy was the single most important reason they backed him over Vice President Kamala Harris, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e134d4f0-beec-11ef-bd95-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 16:10:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">559e5900-bedf-11ef-ade0-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House GOP leadership is set to propose a third funding plan today in hopes of averting a government shutdown. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>After the failure of a Trump-backed plan, House Speaker Mike Johnson (R-Louisiana) was considering offering two options hours before a midnight deadline. One would extend the current fiscal levels until mid-March and a farm bill for one year, and includes $110 billion for natural disasters. It would not include Trump’s demand for raising the debt ceiling. Another plan floated is just a clean extension, known as a continuing resolution or CR, for several weeks into the new year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4977c2d0-bedd-11ef-b1a7-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 14:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. Fani Willis. Luigi Mangione. School shooting arrest. Drones. Amazon strike. White Christmas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eedd5000-bec9-11ef-ab2f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House fails to pass legislation to keep the government open, leaving next step unclear as shutdown deadline rapidly approaches</title>
      <description>The new measure, negotiated solely among Republicans, replaced a bipartisan plan that House Speaker Mike Johnson had worked out with Democrats. The GOP scrapped the earlier deal this week after President-elect Donald Trump and billionaire Elon Musk criticized it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71cd77c0-be65-11ef-89cf-0000a1ace1ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European allies consider deploying troops to Ukraine after the war, as they prepare for Trump and possible ceasefire talks</title>
      <description>European leaders firmly rejected sending troops when the idea was floated in February. They are now willing to consider deployment in the context of a ceasefire as a way to provide security guarantees to Ukraine while NATO membership remains out of Kyiv's reach. It would also play to President-elect Donald Trump’s insistence that Europe shoulder more of its own defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ca97a0-be56-11ef-b4b3-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 22:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans say they have a deal that could avert a government shutdown this weekend, and a vote is expected later today</title>
      <description>Rep. Tom Cole (R-Oklahoma), the chairman of the House Appropriations Committee, and Rep. Stephanie Bice (R-Oklahoma) told reporters the GOP had reached a new agreement. They didn't share details of the plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8021f0a1-be4a-11ef-ab4a-0000a1acedb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:47:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 12 delays, a former West Virginia police chief who paid $100 to rape a teen sentenced to federal prison</title>
      <description>Former Gauley Bridge police chief Larry Clay Jr. was sentenced Thursday to 25 years in federal prison for sex trafficking a 17-year-old girl, then trying to derail the investigation into his crimes. Clay, who was found guilty by a jury last year of paying to rape the teen while on duty, got his sentencing delayed 12 times before a federal judge refused to grant another postponement. Clay was the subject of a Washington Post investigation published in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8250010-be45-11ef-9934-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. deported 271,484 immigrants to nearly 200 countries last fiscal year, the highest tally in a decade</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden took office in 2021 pledging to halt deportations, sending Congress a bill that would have offered paths to citizenship for most of the country's 11 million undocumented immigrants. But surging border crossings derailed his plans, and Biden officials ended up expanding deportations, according to data published Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79d6b60-be44-11ef-ab49-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 20:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friends insinuate daughter’s race is why she got into a top college</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friends insinuate daughter’s race is why she got into a top college</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd9ca4a0-be2a-11ef-9855-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 17:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Will a possible government shutdown affect air travel? A Post reporter and TSA official are taking your questions.</title>
      <description>Washington Post travel reporter Natalie Compton and Transportation Security Administration spokesperson Lisa Farbstein are chatting now about airport security during the busy holiday flying season. Send in your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22c2e4c0-be25-11ef-8f08-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 16:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO shooting suspect has agreed to be extradited to New York to face murder charges</title>
      <description>The suspected attacker, 26-year-old Luigi Mangione, appeared in court for hearings related to his extradition as well as separate criminal charges he faces in Pennsylvania, where he was arrested last week. UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson, 50, was gunned down outside a Manhattan hotel on Dec. 4 in an attack that was captured on video.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80f52db0-be1f-11ef-8339-0000a1ace456</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fani Willis disqualified from election interference case against Trump and his allies by Georgia appellate court</title>
      <description>A Georgia appellate court overturned a judge’s ruling allowing Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis (D) to remain in charge of the criminal racketeering case against Donald Trump and several of his allies charged with conspiring to overturn Trump’s 2020 election loss in the state — a decision that could potentially doom the high-profile prosecution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">334e6ea0-be1a-11ef-b1ac-0000a1ace7f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House drafting order to open federal lands to data center development and new power plants</title>
      <description>The Biden administration wants to speed construction of massive data centers and power plants on federally owned lands, responding to worries the United States could fall behind other nations in the race to dominate artificial intelligence, according to people involved with the deliberations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d95837d0-be16-11ef-8f08-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privatizing what? Answer now in today's On the Record.</title>
      <description>Earn your Thursday points as we head into the holidays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec0584b0-be15-11ef-bd95-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 14:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looming shutdown. Trump poll. School shooting victims. Mass rape trial. Bird flu. Microplastics. Murder hornets. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6632b01-be00-11ef-b79b-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frenchman found guilty in trial over mass rape of wife that shocked the world</title>
      <description>Dominique Pelicot, 72, had been on trial for repeatedly drugging his wife and recruiting dozens of men to rape her over nine years. Gisèle Pelicot, 72, asked that the trial take place in open court because she wanted the world to know what had happened to her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab124110-bde7-11ef-ba9e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How antisemitism, Israeli nationalism and anger over Gaza flared into violence around a soccer match in Amsterdam</title>
      <description>A Washington Post visual reconstruction based on 100 videos, WhatsApp and Telegram chats, and interviews with more than 30 witnesses reveals the elements that led to escalating violence around the Ajax-Maccabi match on Nov. 7.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3995850-bd93-11ef-8aa8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 23:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House scraps plan for sweeping government spending bill after Trump, Musk and GOP lawmakers blast Speaker Johnson’s proposal</title>
      <description>A shutdown deadline looms at the end of the week if Congress doesn’t extend current funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d0b4830-bd8f-11ef-ae20-0000a1acec8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 22:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have you seen your 2024 Newsprint yet? Uncover your reader type with our year-end recap.</title>
      <description>Have you seen your 2024 Newsprint yet? Uncover your reader type with our year-end recap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c3d58c0-bd87-11ef-b9c0-0000a1ace74f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Americans oppose Trump’s proposals to test democracy’s limits, Post-UMD poll finds</title>
      <description>A majority of Americans oppose President-elect Donald Trump’s plans to use the U.S. military to deport millions of undocumented immigrants, to instruct the U.S. Justice Department to investigate his political rivals and to pardon rioters charged with breaking into the U.S. Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021. Even larger majorities of Americans oppose Trump’s plans to jail reporters for writing stories he doesn’t like and having police use force against anti-Trump protests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7999e931-bd83-11ef-a6a6-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 21:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microplastics may be leading to lung and colon cancer, new study shows</title>
      <description>Researchers from the University of California at San Francisco reviewed thousands of studies to find that microplastics are linked to certain carcinogenic effects and reproductive problems. It’s the latest evidence of harms from plastic production, which is projected to triple by 2060.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d26c850-bd7c-11ef-9ad4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 20:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve cut rates by a quarter of a point and signaled a slower pace of cuts in 2025 on concerns about inflation</title>
      <description>The Federal Reserve’s decision could lead to lower costs for an array of loans, from mortgages to credit cards, helping the economy heading into 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25e72a13-bd73-11ef-878d-0000a1ace4b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes expansive Pentagon policy bill despite Democrats’ anger over restrictions targeting troops’ transgender children</title>
      <description>Several Democrats refused to support the annual bill, which typically enjoys broad bipartisan backing in both chambers of Congress, after House Speaker Mike Johnson's late intervention to include a provision barring the use of federal funds for specialized medical treatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be1ee1e0-bd6b-11ef-8f74-0000a1ace79f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 18:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz ethics report to be released by House panel, people familiar with matter say. The move is a reversal for the committee.</title>
      <description>The release of the report is expected within the week and comes despite opposition from some Republicans. The long-running investigation is focused on allegations of sexual misconduct and illegal drug use by Gaetz, a former congressman. A majority vote of the committee is required to publicly release a report, meaning that at least one Republican lawmaker joined with Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7366eb0-bd65-11ef-af16-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Widowed mom sent to hotel for snooping in daughter-in-law’s records</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Widowed mom sent to hotel for snooping in daughter-in-law’s records</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed7cc831-bd61-11ef-9ccc-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 17:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court agrees to hear challenge to a TikTok ban in the U.S., scheduling oral arguments for January</title>
      <description>The justices said they will quickly take up the constitutionality of a federal law that would shutter TikTok next month unless the company divests from Chinese ownership. The high court will weigh whether the law, passed with bipartisan support to address national security concerns, violates the First Amendment rights of millions of TikTok users and the owners of the wildly popular video-sharing platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3f7b110-bd5c-11ef-aac8-0000a1ace724</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 16:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was the ‘perfect’ predator: How a Texas police chief with a troubled past groomed a small town</title>
      <description>The people of Maypearl trusted their police chief, Kevin Coffey. Few were aware that Maypearl was the eighth law enforcement agency that Coffey had worked at in 11 years. Fewer knew that there was a trail of accusations and secrets in his past. And none could have predicted the destruction he'd wreak in their community, where he was eventually convicted of sexually abusing a 14-year-old girl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46298250-bd55-11ef-a57f-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 15:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Spanish version of this board game is the star of today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5fe0d60-bd4c-11ef-b502-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 14:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School shooting motive. Luigi Mangione. Trump lawsuit. Shutdown deadline. Drones. Supplement risk. Young diners ban. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99f73261-bd37-11ef-b80a-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One-time D.C. drug kingpin Rayful Edmond III dies in final year of federal sentence</title>
      <description>Edmond, who played a role in fueling the District’s murderous crack cocaine epidemic in the 1980s, had been completing his prison term at a halfway house in Florida. He was set for release in late 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35505670-bcd8-11ef-864a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:37:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. gets RFK bill, Maryland gets full funding for Key Bridge rebuild under federal spending legislation</title>
      <description>The two measures have been linked in negotiations over the must-pass continuing resolution, with D.C. officials seeking greater control of the RFK Stadium site in hopes of luring back the Washington Commanders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f35cc51-bcd2-11ef-9f3a-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 23:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO shooting suspect indicted in New York on first-degree murder charge, among others</title>
      <description>Luigi Mangione, who was arrested last week in Pennsylvania after a days-long search, was charged with 11 counts, including one count of murder in the first degree and two counts of murder in the second degree. Mangione is in custody in Pennsylvania, where he faces other criminal charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d72e91-bcb6-11ef-b166-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 20:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT consultant found guilty in fatal stabbing of Cash App founder Bob Lee, a case that shocked the tech world</title>
      <description>A San Francisco jury convicted Nima Momeni of second-degree murder, rejecting arguments that he was acting in self-defense during the April 2023 altercation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb27360-bca2-11ef-b9d6-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Are you a jerk for dialing back a one-sided friendship?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Are you a jerk for dialing back a one-sided friendship?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc892b90-bc99-11ef-a1f5-0000a1aceb67</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. wants fluoride out of drinking water — but about a dozen states require it</title>
      <description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr., President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run the nation’s health agency, wants to remove fluoride from drinking water. Fluoridation efforts have not followed traditional political lines. Here’s how common fluoridation is in each state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">740199c0-bc8c-11ef-bae0-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new biopic in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b33ecdf0-bc83-11ef-88df-000a1ace40c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School shooting. Moscow explosion. Trump ruling. Elon Musk. Health insurers. CNN report. ‘Dirty Dancing.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a1a8ec2-bc6e-11ef-b242-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of Russia’s nuclear defense forces killed in bombing, officials say</title>
      <description>An explosive device on a parked scooter near the entrance of a residential building killed Lt. Gen. Igor Kirillov and his assistant in Moscow on Tuesday morning, Russia’s Investigative Committee said in a statement shared on Telegram.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f97295a0-bc4b-11ef-b792-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 07:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
