<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Brazil. Federal firings. Ukraine-Russia shift. Tunnel collapse. Texas search. X CEO. French national hero. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0808b950-5d7d-11f0-9fa4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos and videos show how the Texas flooding surged in a matter of hours and how rescues unfolded</title>
      <description>See how water from the swollen Guadalupe River surged into Camp Mystic and other parts of Kerr County, and how people have searched for and recovered victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b94cfbb1-5d12-11f0-bae7-0000a1acec23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 22:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 50% tariffs on Brazil starting Aug. 1, citing its treatment of former president Jair Bolsonaro</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump scrambled his trade agenda and delivered a broadside against the government of Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva over its treatment of Bolsonaro, the former leader who is on trial for trying to overthrow the government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73cedc20-5d0d-11f0-b157-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 21:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flooding and severe thunderstorm watches issued, with worst weather expected toward evening</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service is cautioning that storms could produce locally significant flooding, damaging wind gusts and isolated large hail. Storms are expected to be heavier and more widespread than Tuesday’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5541810-5cf0-11f0-9c42-0000a1ace777</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 18:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think surprise medical bills are in the past? Surprise!</title>
      <description>The surprise medical bills just keep coming</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">542c4f80-5ced-11f0-b335-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 17:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Gay man avoids homophobic brother-in-law. But at what cost?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Gay man avoids homophobic brother-in-law. But at what cost?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee858160-5cdd-11f0-88d4-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 16:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Yaccarino steps down as CEO of Elon Musk’s X. The resignation comes a day after the Grok chatbot’s antisemitic outbursts.</title>
      <description>Yaccarino announced her departure from the social media site in a post on X, one day after Grok made posts referencing Hitler that were later deleted. She did not provide a reason for her decision. She was hired by Musk to run the social network formerly known as Twitter in 2023, after he acquired the company for $44 billion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe9c7ab0-5cd6-11f0-a7aa-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Can I tip less now that Trump's bill has mostly done away with taxes on gratuity?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Can I tip less now that Trump's bill has mostly done away with taxes on gratuity?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40a0e40-5cd6-11f0-bea5-0000a1ace5cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s moves on immigration, Ukraine and the Epstein case are roiling the MAGA base</title>
      <description>Some of his most loyal supporters fear President Donald Trump is going back on promises crucial to his political movement. White House officials disputed the idea that the unrest seriously threatens Trump’s support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7a9c780-5ccd-11f0-b822-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 14:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red spots in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fce84360-5cc8-11f0-a148-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 13:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass firings. Trump vs. Putin. Texas floods. Spy agency logs. Chatbot rant. Airport shoes rule. AI music. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e118ddd0-5cb3-11f0-80d2-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>161 people known to be missing from flooding in Kerr County area, Texas governor says</title>
      <description>Gov. Greg Abbott said the confirmed death toll in the state was 109. The incident is among the deadliest flood events in the past 50 years, shaking the region in a scene that Abbott has described as “nothing short of horrific.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79b45bc0-5c44-11f0-8589-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to launch mass layoff and restructuring plans at federal agencies, including CDC, Social Security Administration</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a lower-court order that temporarily blocked the plans to fire thousands of workers at 19 agencies and departments while litigation continues. Their order said they were not ruling on the legality of specific firing plans but simply allowing the administration to launch such efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d33b3420-5c35-11f0-b732-000a1ace520d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches in effect into this evening, fueled by sweltering heat and humidity</title>
      <description>Dangerous thunderstorms are possible between about 3 and 8 p.m. In addition to lightning, some storms could contain damaging winds and flooding rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac88cd30-5c24-11f0-adc9-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 1956, her father was planning to run for president. She attended Camp Mystic.</title>
      <description>Lynda Bird Johnson Robb recalls how the Texas camp shaped her childhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98290470-5c1c-11f0-9e5b-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to fix dull life with incurious spouse — but not blow it all up</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to fix dull life with incurious spouse — but not blow it all up</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b465f80-5c1a-11f0-87df-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA tests security lines allowing passengers to keep their shoes on at some airports, a change that may be rolled out more widely</title>
      <description>The change in security protocol began at certain airports over the weekend, according to a union official and passenger accounts. TSA officials would not confirm reports Monday that the agency was ending the requirement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c9d8ee0-5c17-11f0-b98d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: What’s next for the Nationals now that they’ve fired their manager and GM? Our reporters are answering your questions.</title>
      <description>How will the last-place Nationals move forward after firing longtime manager Dave Martinez and GM Mike Rizzo? And what went into the decision to make a change now? Post staffers Barry Svrluga, Chelsea Janes and Spencer Nusbaum are answering reader questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5669f11-5c14-11f0-87df-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team created by Tulsi Gabbard shows interest in spy agencies’ emails, chat logs amid hunt for efforts to undermine Trump’s agenda</title>
      <description>The Director’s Initiative Group has expressed an interest in gaining access to emails and chat logs of the largest U.S. intelligence agencies to root out “weaponization,” according to multiple people familiar with the effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bdd01f0-5c13-11f0-94eb-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to ban Chinese purchases of U.S. farmland, citing national and food security threats</title>
      <description>In a joint news conference with Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth and Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem, Agriculture Department Secretary Brooke Rollins said the administration would work with state partners and pursue executive actions to halt farmland purchases by foreign adversaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26c33100-5c0a-11f0-989b-0000a1ace0cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trending downward in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b46f0c51-5bff-11f0-89a4-0000a1aced75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Marco Rubio impostor using AI has contacted three foreign ministers, a U.S. governor and a member of Congress</title>
      <description>An impostor pretending to be the secretary of state contacted high-level officials by sending them voice and text messages that mimic Rubio’s voice and writing style using artificial intelligence-powered software, according to a senior U.S. official and a State Department cable obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b01950-5bec-11f0-8dcf-0000a1ace7df</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas floods. Trump’s tariffs. Netanyahu’s gift. Elon Musk. Epstein files. Credit scores. Fateful kisses. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b52ac7c0-5bea-11f0-ac58-0000a1ace38c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Affairs reverses course on large-scale job reductions after promising to cut 83,000 roles</title>
      <description>The agency says it will have reduced the number of staff by the end of fiscal 2025 by approximately 30,000 through hiring freezes, retirements and attrition.

Further cuts to the agency would have brought deep political risks for President Donald Trump, who remains popular with military veterans and has promised to not do anything that would affect their benefits or care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b99c72d0-5b73-11f0-93d7-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals name Miguel Cairo interim manager amid franchise shake-up</title>
      <description>The Nationals announced Cairo would take over as interim manager Monday, one day after ousting Dave Martinez and longtime general manager Mike Rizzo. Cairo, who previously served as Martinez's bench coach, will now guide a Nationals team that includes outfielder James Wood and lefty MacKenzie Gore, two young talents who were named all-stars Sunday. The changes in Washington come amid a long rebuild for the franchise, which has shed its stars in the years since its 2019 World Series triumph.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8993e5b2-5b5e-11f0-b98b-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will extend pause on ‘reciprocal’ tariffs until Aug. 1, White House says</title>
      <description>An initial 90-day freeze on new tariffs was set to expire Wednesday. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters Monday that the president would push the date back to continue negotiations on trade deals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37692851-5b5d-11f0-87ad-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tells Japan and South Korea to expect at least 25 percent tariffs starting Aug. 1. He plans to target additional countries.</title>
      <description>The White House has begun sending letters to trade partners threatening new tariff rates while negotiations on trade deals continue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">297ab980-5b52-11f0-8634-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 16:48:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Twins live half hour apart, but one insists on keeping his distance</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Twins live half hour apart, but one insists on keeping his distance</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9945ab01-5b4b-11f0-a062-0000a1ace502</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I lived on a cliff with 10,000-year-old icebergs and a beagle’: What it’s like to work as one of Canada’s last lighthouse keepers</title>
      <description>‘I lived on a cliff with 10,000-year-old icebergs and a beagle’: What it’s like to work as one of Canada’s last lighthouse keepers</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">947e3180-5b43-11f0-aa3e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas floods death toll reaches at least 81, including 27 girls and counselors at Camp Mystic. Follow our coverage of the searches.</title>
      <description>South-central Texas is again at an elevated risk of excessive rainfall Monday, threatening to bring further flooding to the ravaged region as search operations for the missing enter a fourth day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b439800-5b3e-11f0-b6d7-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring out the proxy quitters in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your daily points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cdf2040-5b36-11f0-b421-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. measles cases reach highest level in 33 years amid distrust in vaccines</title>
      <description>Measles cases have climbed to at least 1,277 across the United States, according to data from the Johns Hopkins University Center for Outbreak Response Innovation. The case count surpasses the annual tally in 2019 and marks the highest since 1992. Public health experts say the resurgence of a vaccine-preventable disease was avoidable and unnecessarily endangers children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8906b00-5b2d-11f0-b4eb-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas floods. Elon Musk’s party. Netanyahu visit. Measles. ‘Mushroom murder’ verdict. Storm Chantal. Lost ring. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a35b7b0-5b21-11f0-a9c7-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australian woman found guilty in ‘mushroom murder case’</title>
      <description>Erin Patterson, a 50-year-old mother of two, was found guilty of murdering three relatives and attempting to murder a fourth by feeding them a lunch laced with death cap mushrooms at her home outside Melbourne in 2023. The “mushroom murder case,” as it was known in Australia, transfixed the country, and the verdict brings to a close a dramatic two-month trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f666e170-5aea-11f0-8019-0000a1aced55</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Hill Country is no stranger to flash floods. Why were so many caught off guard?</title>
      <description>Even in the most flood-prone region in the country, the disaster during Fourth of July weekend exposed gaps in the ability to warn people about the coming deluge. Many people failed to receive or respond to flood warnings at riverside campsites and cabins that were known to be in the floodplain. And Kerr County itself didn’t send a push alert amid continued rains on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">675314b1-5ad4-11f0-82fa-0000a1ace24b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 01:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationals fire manager Dave Martinez, GM Mike Rizzo amid dismal season for rebuilding club</title>
      <description>The Nationals on Sunday ended one of the longest partnerships in baseball, which included a World Series title in 2019 — the first in franchise history — and the second-worst record in baseball in the six years that followed. Martinez had spent eight years with the organization, while Rizzo was promoted to general manager in 2009. Mike DeBartolo will take over as interim GM; an interim manager will be announced Monday, the team said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f62ebb40-5aba-11f0-a323-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 22:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why aren’t Italians as obese as Americans? It’s not really what they eat, our food policy columnist writes.</title>
      <description>Multicourse meals, charcuterie, ravioli, pizza, gelato: On its face, this doesn’t seem like a recipe for avoiding weight gain. But there’s a much lower obesity rate in Italy than in the U.S. Here’s why.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">653d76c0-5ab6-11f0-b1a6-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These twins were college divers. Then new NCAA rules cost them their spots.</title>
      <description>Nick and Noah Wanzer thrived as freshman athletes at Virginia and North Carolina State. Landmark changes to the college sports economy — stemming from a multibillion-dollar legal settlement last month that permits colleges to directly pay athletes for the first time — left their futures in jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ebeee70-5a9b-11f0-ac66-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 18:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Israeli strike hit four areas in a notorious Tehran prison complex and killed civilians, a Post visual investigation finds</title>
      <description>A review of satellite imagery and videos revealed damage that pointed to multiple strikes, experts said, with structures nearly 2,000 feet apart in ruins. At least four civilians were killed, two of them children, according to online death notices and witness interviews.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9e0fb0-5a8b-11f0-9c22-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 17:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26044df0-5a82-11f0-bb06-0000a1ace857</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top chain restaurants at airports, and why they all feel the same, according to our Department of Data</title>
      <description>While ranking airport eateries, we stumbled on the real reason most airports (and their food offerings) feel so oddly homogenous.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b8dce0-5a75-11f0-a2ce-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90964e32-5a6d-11f0-86cd-0000a1ace797</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 13:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: One father's search for his daughter, one of the many children missing after Texas floods swept through a summer camp. A previous alert had an incorrect link.</title>
      <description>Between broken tree limbs and muddied cabins, Michael McCown spent Saturday searching the devastated grounds of Camp Mystic for his little girl. She is one of about two dozen girls from the camp who are unaccounted for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0ba8470-5a0b-11f0-840c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 01:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One father’s search for his daughter, one of the many children missing after Texas floods swept through a summer camp</title>
      <description>Between broken tree limbs and muddied cabins, Michael McCown spent Saturday searching the devastated grounds of Camp Mystic for his little girl. She is one of about two dozen girls from the camp who are unaccounted for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6469a0-5a09-11f0-b6f4-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buc-ee’s just opened its first Virginia location. It is truly a behemoth.</title>
      <description>As the supersize Texas-based chain expands toward the Mason-Dixon Line, a new region discovers what the beaver’s all about.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcca8100-59ef-11f0-8def-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 22:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four months of rainfall in four hours: How a deadly downpour caught Texans by surprise</title>
      <description>Meteorologists had cautioned there was potential for flooding across Central Texas. But there was little indication of just how torrential the rain would become, killing more than two dozen people, many of them children at camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e33e1e50-59bf-11f0-9279-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best advice about in-laws from therapist Sahaj Kaur Kohli</title>
      <description>Best advice about in-laws from therapist Sahaj Kaur Kohli</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0c4dc0-59ba-11f0-87de-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 16:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A town tried to heal racial divides by removing a statue. It revived Confederate support instead.</title>
      <description>What started as an effort to promote unity in Edenton, North Carolina, by reconsidering its most prominent downtown symbol did the opposite: A chapter of the Sons of Confederate Veterans, long extinct locally, sprang to life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a6b16b0-59ae-11f0-a1d8-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 14:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2dbc3c0-59a3-11f0-a26b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 24 dead, children still missing after heavy flooding in Central Texas, sheriff says</title>
      <description>Twenty girls were missing from a summer camp on the Guadalupe River after the waterway swelled to historic highs, authorities said earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1985671-594a-11f0-ab17-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 02:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
