<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 12:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine deal. Kamala Harris. Vaccine change. Supreme Court. Gaza map. Pacific Northwest quake. Axolotl hope. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a794250-267b-11f0-a9a1-0000a1ace973</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris condemns Trump’s policies and ‘unconstitutional demands’ in her first major speech since leaving the White House</title>
      <description>The 2024 Democratic presidential nominee urged her supporters to summon the courage to fight what she called President Donald Trump’s efforts to stoke fear and “punish truth tellers.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0223a80-263b-11f0-b737-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitals beat Canadiens in Game 5 to advance to the second round of the Stanley Cup playoffs for the first time since 2018</title>
      <description>Washington, the No. 1 seed in the Eastern Conference, topped scrappy Montreal on home ice Wednesday to take the best-of-seven series. The Capitals, who will meet the Carolina Hurricanes in the second round, had not clinched a playoff series at home since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba3d5c62-262e-11f0-9616-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. will require shift in how new vaccines are tested, HHS says</title>
      <description>The potential change outlined in a statement says all new vaccines will be required to undergo placebo testing, a procedure in which some people receive the vaccine and others receive an inert substance — such as a saline shot — before the results are compared. The Department of Health and Human Services says the move will increase transparency but medical experts fear it could limit access to vaccines and undermine the public’s trust in immunization depending on how it is implemented. HHS did not fully clarify how the change would work and for which vaccines the testing would apply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f91d7c71-2625-11f0-8806-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and Ukraine sign a deal to develop Ukraine's mineral resources with Washington, affirming a ‘long-term strategic alignment’</title>
      <description>The deal’s language marks a win for Kyiv, which has been seeking any concrete show of support from the United States since President Donald Trump returned to power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c22014e1-2610-11f0-9dbe-000a1ace826d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Can the D.C. Council really say no to RFK Stadium site deal? We’re answering your questions.</title>
      <description>D.C. and the Washington Commanders this week unveiled a $3.7 billion deal to transform the crumbling RFK Stadium site into a new home for the NFL franchise, surrounded by retail, housing and park space. How are the D.C. Council and D.C. residents reacting? Post Metro and Sports reporters Jenny Gathright, Meagan Flynn, Sam Fortier and Nicki Jhabvala are answering your questions now during a live chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">babaace0-25e5-11f0-87da-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems open to allowing religious public schools, a major move that would redraw the boundary between church and state</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court on Wednesday appeared open to allowing the creation of the nation’s first public religious charter school in Oklahoma. A ruling for St. Isidore of Seville Catholic Virtual School would allow taxpayer money to directly flow to a faith-based school for the first time and give government sponsorship to a curriculum that calls for students to adhere to Catholic beliefs and religious mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f036adf0-25e1-11f0-b1ba-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dinner guest feels ‘censored’ by one person’s no-politics plea</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dinner guest feels ‘censored’ by one person’s no-politics plea</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f3d9f1-25dc-11f0-ae47-0000a1ace91b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Hegseth has an unorthodox role shaping Pentagon affairs, appearing at high-level meetings, vetting job candidates and more</title>
      <description>The activities of Jennifer Hegseth throughout her husband’s budding tenure in President Donald Trump’s Cabinet has snapped into focus in recent weeks, after damaging news reports about Pete Hegseth’s stumbles as his on-the-job training plays out in public view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe33ecd0-25cb-11f0-b028-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An e-commerce giant and tariffs in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to get your Wednesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41449a62-25c7-11f0-bead-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy shrank in the first quarter by an annual pace of 0.3%, as tariffs sapped economic growth</title>
      <description>In the first few months of the year, President Donald Trump's tariffs unexpectedly dragged down the U.S. economy, even before fully taking effect, according to fresh data released by the Commerce Department on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65893f00-25bf-11f0-9eac-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s 100 days. Kamala Harris. Tariff impacts. Fluoride ban. DEI. Strength training. Escaped kangaroo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40b92fd0-25b2-11f0-9937-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service’s law enforcement arm is aiding Trump’s immigration crackdown, according to people and documents</title>
      <description>Homeland Security officials are seeking access to postal records, including photos of the outside of mail and other items, and the Postal Inspection Service participated in a recent raid that led to the arrest of more than 100 undocumented migrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ec8c660-2542-11f0-aea6-0000a1ace017</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 21:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive order to ease some auto industry tariffs in administration’s latest retreat on levies</title>
      <description>The move eases tariffs on imported autos to ensure they aren't “stacked” on top of other levies, such as for steel and aluminum. Automakers will also get tariff relief on imported parts for cars completed in the United States over the next two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f572110-2538-11f0-8a85-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department begins prosecuting migrants who breach expanded military zone at southern border, charging at least 28 so far</title>
      <description>The migrants were charged with crossing into the 170-mile “National Defense Area” in New Mexico, a 60-foot-deep strip of land that has effectively been turned into part of a U.S. military installation. Prosecutors added the charge to the more common misdemeanor of entering the United States illegally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">182a7a20-2525-11f0-a10e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EPA is canceling nearly 800 grants issued under Biden, a little-noticed court filing reveals</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to cancel a total of 781 grants issued under President Joe Biden, EPA lawyers wrote in a court filing last week — nearly twice the number previously reported. The filing in the case Woonasquatucket River Watershed Council v. Department of Agriculture will affect projects across the nation, from sealing homes against wildfire smoke to addressing coastal flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d8cf8f0-251e-11f0-bdc2-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sister says they’re ‘not friends,’ so why keep making plans?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sister says they’re ‘not friends,’ so why keep making plans?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70b26070-2513-11f0-b83f-000a1acedd66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Ukrainian journalist tried to expose how Russia is detaining and abusing civilians in occupied territories. She ended up dead.</title>
      <description>A coalition of 45 international journalists, led by Paris-based Forbidden Stories and including The Washington Post, continued the work of Viktoriia Roshchyna and conducted a months-long investigation into her death and the torture of Ukrainian civilians at Russian detention centers stretching from occupied Ukraine to northern Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3ac47f0-2504-11f0-b444-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fiery statement by a Democratic governor in today's On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">424c38b1-24fe-11f0-a985-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most think Trump is serious about Canada, Greenland and third-term proposals, but oppose them all, poll finds</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has proposed taking over Canada and Greenland, imprisoning U.S. citizens overseas, and serving an unconstitutional third term. Most Americans say they think he’s serious about each proposal. And most oppose each one, including many Republicans, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c47fdab0-24fb-11f0-b967-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common chemicals in plastic linked to more than 350,000 deaths from heart disease each year</title>
      <description>Exposure to phthalates — a set of chemicals found in food packaging plastics, and lotions and shampoos — contributes to 13 percent of all heart disease deaths in people between ages 55 and 64 each year worldwide, researchers have found. The findings were published Tuesday in the journal EBioMedicine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d613540-24f5-11f0-8f7e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 12:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Carney. Lie detector tests. Deadly crash. Deepfake nudes. Power outage. Plastic dangers. Shipwreck mural. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1965d790-24e9-11f0-b404-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberal Mark Carney projected to remain as Canada's prime minister</title>
      <description>The result, projected by the country’s public broadcaster, was a stunning reversal in fortunes for the Liberal Party, fueled in part by President Donald Trump’s attacks on Canada. Carney, a former central banker, pitched himself as best placed to handle Trump’s trade war, annexation threats and the profound rupture in U.S.-Canada relations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a79e2a0-24a1-11f0-b5f4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 02:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI, national security agencies are using polygraph tests to search for ‘leakers’</title>
      <description>Current and former officials say the crackdown is creating a climate of fear that goes beyond prior leak investigations and harms national security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07d4b540-248b-11f0-937d-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 23:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers leave Justice Department civil rights office en masse as new leaders shift priorities</title>
      <description>New civil rights division chief Harmeet Dhillon told a conservative podcaster more than 100 attorneys have left their jobs, in many cases because they disagreed with the office’s new focus on combating anti-Christian bias, transgender athletes in women’s sports, antisemitism and “woke ideology.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87d561c1-2474-11f0-937d-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 21:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Ghosts of elite-college ambition haunt parent of accomplished teen</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Ghosts of elite-college ambition haunt parent of accomplished teen</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b15d10f1-2452-11f0-a366-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 17:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Gerry Connolly (D-Virginia) announces he will not seek reelection because of cancer resurgence</title>
      <description>Connolly, elected to his Northern Virginia seat in 2008, was first diagnosed with esophageal cancer in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5077be50-244a-11f0-89ee-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 16:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. and Commanders announce $3.7 billion deal to transform RFK Stadium site into a new home for the NFL team</title>
      <description>The Washington Commanders would put up $2.7 billion for the roofed stadium, while total taxpayer costs are expected to top $1 billion — a price tag likely to spur heated debate on the D.C. Council and among residents about how public money is used. The council still needs to approve the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ae581b0-2444-11f0-95fb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 15:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These red-eyed bugs are singing in today’s On The Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12944961-2435-11f0-8e30-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conclave to select new pope, the largest such gathering in the history of the Catholic Church, will begin May 7, Vatican announces</title>
      <description>The announcement, a week after the death of Pope Francis, sets up the most unpredictable selection process in decades, with several strong contenders emerging, but no clear front-runner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d987d0-2423-11f0-9bb0-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 11:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Child removals. Vancouver attack. North Korea. ‘60 Minutes.’ Neck pain. Rock and Roll Hall of Fame. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1b56b30-241f-11f0-9bb0-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C., Commanders plan to announce deal for new stadium at RFK on Monday</title>
      <description>The deal, which must be approved by the D.C. Council, would bring the team back to the city where it last played in 1996. D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) and Commanders principal owner Josh Harris are set to announce details Monday, according to a person familiar with the plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">468b8830-23ce-11f0-9f1a-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which cities have the most trees? See how yours stacks up.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post analysis shows how climate and population influence tree cover. Find out which places are growing their urban forest and how your area compares.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bde0e393-23aa-11f0-b756-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 21:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a696930-2381-11f0-97fd-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 16:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eat it or toss it? Test your food safety knowledge with this quiz.</title>
      <description>Moldy cheese. Old yogurt. That pot of soup you left on the counter overnight. Your appetite for reducing food waste just might be tied to your risk tolerance. Take our quiz to see where you land.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04dcf590-2379-11f0-b5c2-0000a1ace2b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 15:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s approval rating sinks as Americans criticize his major policies, Post-ABC-Ipsos finds</title>
      <description>As he nears his 100th day in office, President Donald Trump is facing growing opposition to his ambitious and controversial agenda and perceptions that his administration is seeking to avoid complying with federal court orders, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">943f2185-2370-11f0-926c-000a1ace61c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 14:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78de9aa0-236c-11f0-9bb0-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 13:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 9 people killed after vehicle plows through crowd at Vancouver festival for Filipino community</title>
      <description>Police said the “mass casualty incident” took place during the Lapu Lapu Day festival. Police arrested a 30-year-old man at the scene and said they are not treating the incident as an act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d932a230-2352-11f0-8f5e-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 10:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: ‘If I don’t do it, nothing gets done.’ My husband says deal with it.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: ‘If I don’t do it, nothing gets done.’ My husband says deal with it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4589d180-22cf-11f0-8fdf-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:50:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado quarterback Shedeur Sanders selected by Cleveland Browns in the fifth round of the NFL draft, ending a multi-day slide</title>
      <description>Sanders was projected to be picked as high as the top five of the first round, yet slipped to the draft’s third day before he was taken. The son of Hall of Fame cornerback and Colorado Coach Deion Sanders, Shedeur Sanders’s fall became the primary storyline of this year’s draft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8eb77aa0-22cb-11f0-8441-0000a1ace3dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At 77, she’s as fit as a 25-year-old. Here’s what her body tells us about aging.</title>
      <description>Researchers are studying runner Jeannie Rice, who has “outstanding” fitness, to learn how we can stay healthy as we age. She proves “it’s never too late to start exercising,” one scientist said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ce8851-22af-11f0-a176-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0e22da1-22a2-11f0-be59-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the Catholic Church lays Pope Francis to rest, tens of thousands are paying respects at funeral, procession</title>
      <description>The solemn proceedings began under crystalline skies, in the shadow of St. Peter’s Basilica, with a requiem Mass. The guests of honor were monarchs, presidents and cardinals. Migrants, prisoners, indigent and transgender faithful are expected at the burial site to celebrate the “people's pope.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a357c710-228c-11f0-a176-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 10:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Giuffre dies at 41. She was the public face of women who said they were sexually abused and trafficked by Jeffrey Epstein.</title>
      <description>In court papers, lawsuits and interviews spanning nearly a decade, Giuffre recounted coming under Epstein’s control as a 16-year-old and being “passed around like a platter of fruit” to his influential friends, including Britain's Prince Andrew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18fe1d40-2245-11f0-a186-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former congressman George Santos sentenced to more than 7 years in prison after pleading guilty to financial misconduct</title>
      <description>Santos’s attorneys had asked for him to face two years in prison, saying that he had accepted responsibility for his actions and writing in court filings that his actions “stemmed largely from a misguided desperation related to his political campaign, rather than inherent malice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c318db0-21f5-11f0-a30d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: We were on a date. And then his estranged wife showed up.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: We were on a date. And then his estranged wife showed up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ab5750-21f3-11f0-914f-0000a1ace74d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says Wisconsin judge has been arrested, accused of shielding an immigrant in her courthouse from being detained by ICE</title>
      <description>The arrest of Milwaukee County Circuit Judge Hannah Dugan was announced on X by FBI Director Kash Patel. The tweet was later deleted. It would be the first publicly known instance of the Justice Department charging a local official with allegedly interfering with immigration enforcement since President Donald Trump returned to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e44dd0-21e9-11f0-af3c-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bfe9ce0-21d9-11f0-a940-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A baby-faced GM swooped in for Travis Hunter and rocked the NFL draft. Here’s what we learned in the first round.</title>
      <description>As the NFL draft began Thursday night, the Jacksonville Jaguars executed one of the boldest trades in draft history to secure the Heisman Trophy winner, the Cleveland Browns gave themselves multiple options to draft a quarterback, and the New York Giants traded up for Mississippi quarterback Jaxson Dart, leaving Colorado’s Shedeur Sanders still available at the close of a fascinating night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a44d9070-21d6-11f0-abc2-0000a1ace67b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Americans now disapprove of Trump’s handling of immigration, a change from earlier this year, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Fifty-three percent of Americans say they disapprove of President Donald Trump’s handling of immigration, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll this month. In February, 48 percent said they disapproved and 50 percent approved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a0dbc60-21cc-11f0-a69c-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
