<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 11:03:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump selects transition co-chair Linda McMahon to be education secretary</title>
      <description>McMahon led the Small Business Administration from 2017 to 2019 and is the co-founder and former chief executive of World Wrestling Entertainment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e401910-a6ea-11ef-ac46-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden approves antipersonnel land mines for Ukraine, reversing his 2022 policy and drawing criticism from arms control groups</title>
      <description>The decision comes after the White House recently authorized Ukraine to use a long-range missile system to strike inside Russia — part of a sweep of urgent actions the outgoing Biden administration is taking to boost Kyiv’s faltering war effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4558360-a6d8-11ef-af3c-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Social investors hoped to get ‘very rich’ after Trump’s win. Instead, they ‘are in trouble.’</title>
      <description>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group’s revenue and share price have sagged as its losses have piled up. The president-elect’s return to the White House could complicate things even more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9694d51-a6ce-11ef-837a-0000a1ace815</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 23:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Trump in attendance, Elon Musk’s SpaceX aborts a second attempt to re-capture Starship booster at launch pad</title>
      <description>A SpaceX Starship rocket splashed down in the Gulf of Mexico on Tuesday after the company aborted its second attempt to “catch” the returning booster at the launch pad — a disappointing outcome to a test mission observed by President-elect Donald Trump, who traveled to Texas to watch</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80b9e7d0-a6c5-11ef-828d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks celebrity doctor Mehmet Oz to serve as administrator of the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump announced his plans to nominate the onetime U.S. Senate candidate in Pennsylvania to lead the agency that administers the Medicare and Medicaid programs. “I have known Dr. Oz for many years, and I am confident he will fight to ensure everyone in America receives the best possible Healthcare, so our Country can be Great and Healthy Again!” Trump said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62b8f0b0-a6ba-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas education officials back optional Bible lessons in public elementary schools</title>
      <description>The Texas State Board of Education voted 8-7 to move forward with approval for the optional curriculum, which opponents say promotes Christian beliefs in public school. The final vote is scheduled for Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19720950-a6b5-11ef-b9ef-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 20:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Do they apologize for mocking in-law’s ‘weird’ Thanksgiving meal?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Do they apologize for mocking in-law’s ‘weird’ Thanksgiving meal?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da6fb6e0-a69f-11ef-99bf-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents with damaging testimony against Matt Gaetz were accessed in an apparent breach</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run the Department of Justice was investigated on allegations of sexual misconduct with a 17-year-old girl; he was never charged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d1383f0-a697-11ef-886a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is expected to name Wall Street banker Howard Lutnick as commerce secretary, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Lutnick, who serves as co-chair of President-elect Donald Trump’s transition team, had been under consideration for treasury secretary. He is the CEO and chairman of Cantor Fitzgerald, an investment firm, and has donated to both Democrats and Republicans in the past. He also once appeared on Trump’s NBC reality TV show, “The Apprentice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81f13781-a692-11ef-8612-0000a1acef27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unlikely find in Australia is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ed62b21-a687-11ef-b529-0000a1ace284</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine used U.S.-made ATACMS missiles inside Russia for the first time, according to Russian and Ukrainian officials</title>
      <description>A Ukrainian official confirmed the ATACMS missiles were used inside Russia overnight. Russia said it shot down five of the six missiles fired at a facility in the Bryansk region. The attack comes soon after the Biden administration lifted restrictions on the use of the powerful, long-range, guided missiles inside Russia, long a Ukrainian request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d73fdb0-a674-11ef-a28f-0000a1ace0f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz. Trump’s plans. Gaza gangs. Hong Kong. Atmospheric river. Doctors and AI. Wave power. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5a389d0-a66d-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong sentences 45 pro-democracy leaders to jail terms of up to 10 years, including the city’s most prominent activists</title>
      <description>Benny Tai, a 60-year-old legal scholar who spearheaded the Occupy Central movement, received the harshest sentence. Former student activist Joshua Wong, one of the most recognizable of the group, was sentenced to four years and eight months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd6a72a0-a624-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks former congressman and Fox Business host Sean Duffy as transportation secretary</title>
      <description>Duffy, a former reality TV star who was elected to the House in 2010, will head a department that oversees the funding of roads, bridges and rail lines, as well as the running of the aviation system — and that plays a major role in overseeing companies run by billionaire Elon Musk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0c99b90-a603-11ef-855a-0000a1ace880</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 23:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two women told House Ethics Committee that Matt Gaetz paid them for sex, lawyer says</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s pick for attorney general has been met with shock and pushback, including from Senate Republicans. Some have raised doubts that Gaetz would have the 50 votes needed to be confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9380200-a5fb-11ef-ad0c-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 22:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs looting aid convoys in Gaza operate in areas under Israeli military control, humanitarian officials say</title>
      <description>Criminal looting near Israel’s Kerem Shalom crossing has become the greatest impediment to distributing aid in the southern half of Gaza, aid groups say, amid a deepening hunger crisis. The gangs “may be benefiting from a passive if not active benevolence” or “protection” from the Israeli military, according to an October U.N. memo obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">066b7c20-a5f6-11ef-8559-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smithsonian quietly removed the American Art Museum director this summer after years of staff complaints about her management style</title>
      <description>The Smithsonian Institution placed Stephanie Stebich in a role as a senior adviser after Smithsonian American Art Museum staff complained of feeling frustrated and confused, according to interviews with current and former museum employees and an internal email confirming her job change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdf22cf0-a5e7-11ef-b113-0000a1ace520</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 20:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Attorney General Jason Miyares (R) announces he’s running for reelection, not governor, in 2025</title>
      <description>By running for reelection, Miyares avoids a potentially expensive and bruising gubernatorial primary with fellow Republican Lt. Gov. Winsome Earle-Sears, who has already announced her campaign to succeed the term-limited Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1580bee0-a5d9-11ef-832b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Late mother’s best friend was like a second mom — till she vanished</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Late mother’s best friend was like a second mom — till she vanished</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6ba1840-a5d0-11ef-b04d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans are exploring significant changes to Medicaid and food stamps to help offset the cost of extending Trump’s tax cuts</title>
      <description>Continuing the 2017 tax law would cost trillions. Seeking some budget savings, GOP lawmakers say safety net spending has ballooned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c6f3561-a5cc-11ef-a3b1-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 16:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress must stop offensive weapons sales to Israel, Sen. Bernie Sanders writes</title>
      <description>Continuing to provide Israel with the offensive weapons it uses on civilians is morally wrong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f691cd01-a5c7-11ef-97de-0000a1ace478</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 16:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A taped message has solved the mystery of a World War I doughboy’s death</title>
      <description>Foster Stevens was killed nine days before the Nov. 11, 1918, armistice that ended the Great War. Now his family knows about the man who was with him when he died.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">700d2bf1-a5c0-11ef-9a8b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A masterpiece restored in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f41a2b0-a5ba-11ef-8c84-000a1ace9234</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s team. Ukraine weapons. Pope Francis. Carrot recall. Spirit Airlines. Ancient kitten. Gladiator Airbnb. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2628580-a5a4-11ef-bfa1-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Airlines files for bankruptcy, says it will continue to operate as it seeks to restructure its debt</title>
      <description>“Spirit expects to continue operating its business in the normal course throughout this prearranged, streamlined chapter 11 process,” it said in a release. “Guests can continue to book and fly without interruption and can use all tickets, credits and loyalty points as normal.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b5a4041-a59c-11ef-a646-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 10:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Brendan Carr, who vowed to take on 'censorship' by Big Tech companies in Project 2025, as FCC chairman</title>
      <description>Carr, the senior Republican commissioner on the Federal Communications Commission, laid out an aggressive agenda in Project 2025 and has vowed in recent days to challenge Facebook, Google, Apple and Microsoft, which he called a “censorship cartel.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c53e650-a54b-11ef-a81e-0000a1acef32</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 01:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The mysterious Virginia mansion allegedly bought with stolen Nigerian money</title>
      <description>The way Nigerian authorities tell it, their country’s former national security adviser misappropriated more than $2 billion from his own government, routing some of it to a family friend: the man who bought the mansion in McLean.
The allegations against him, experts say, underscore a significant global issue: The U.S. real estate market has become a money-laundering haven for corrupt officials and criminals across the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f838461-a536-11ef-90e4-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 22:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bills’ Josh Allen and the burden of the modern franchise quarterback</title>
      <description>Allen, Buffalo’s Atlas, is carrying the Bills more than ever as they get set to face their longtime nemesis, the two-time defending Super Bowl champion Kansas City Chiefs, yet again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9b75f0-a529-11ef-8460-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 21:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has authorized Ukraine to use long-range weapons inside Russia, senior officials say, a significant reversal of U.S. policy</title>
      <description>The decision to allow Kyiv to use the Army Tactical Missile System, or ATACMS, to hit targets inside Russia comes as thousands of elite North Korean troops have been sent to Kursk to bolster Moscow’s forces. Russian President Vladimir Putin in September declared that the use of long-range missiles would change “the very essence, the nature of the conflict,” warning that his country would retaliate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56b97f1-a50f-11ef-8d0f-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 18:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96f0d5c0-a505-11ef-8d0f-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa167700-a4f0-11ef-8f43-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 14:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bela Karolyi, who coached Olympic gymnastics superstars and polarized his sport, dies at 82</title>
      <description>Karolyi and his wife, Martha, came to prominence in their native Romania when Nadia Comaneci scored a historic perfect 10. Karolyi later led the United States to gymnastics superstardom with athletes such as Mary Lou Retton and Kerri Strug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3c0690-a491-11ef-929e-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Defense pick Pete Hegseth paid sexual assault accuser but denies wrongdoing, attorney says</title>
      <description>The lawyer said Hegseth paid an accuser as part of a nondisclosure agreement but maintained that their sexual encounter was consensual. President-elect Donald Trump's transition team has been unsettled by a memo shared with them by a woman who said she is a friend of the accuser, describing in detail the 2017 incident at a California hotel. Police investigated Hegseth on the sexual assault allegation but prosecutors did not file charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffdc040-a47a-11ef-9a89-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump chooses Chris Wright, an oil industry CEO and Trump donor who questions aspects of climate change, as energy secretary</title>
      <description>Wright, chairman of the board of Liberty Energy, runs a foundation focused on dispelling the conventional wisdom on climate change and promoting expanded fossil energy production. His views are at odds with many climate scientists and some top energy executives, who endorse curbing greenhouse gas emissions in tune with the Paris climate agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4aa7310-a466-11ef-92e6-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four nights a week, scientists go out to kill owls. Their goal: saving owls.</title>
      <description>The federal government plans to shoot up to nearly half a million barred owls throughout the West Coast. Scientists in Northern California who have been doing this nocturnal hunting for years say it is the only way to save the northern spotted owl from extinction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">083d07c0-a449-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 18:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My ex’s mom blackmailed him into breaking up with me</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My ex’s mom blackmailed him into breaking up with me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b2a0fa0-a43c-11ef-a976-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jake Paul-Mike Tyson fight was a sad, silly spectacle, columnist Sally Jenkins writes</title>
      <description>The boxing charade had a lesson about true power vs. pixels, Jenkins writes, if you could get through all the nonsense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b507970-a434-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell us how many people you’re cooking for and their preferences, and we’ll plan your Thanksgiving feast for you</title>
      <description>Whether you’re a first-time Thanksgiving host or just looking for a little recipe inspiration, our new holiday menu planner will help you build a meal to meet your needs. You can filter based on gathering size or dietary considerations and choose your recipes, and we’ll compile a printable grocery list to give you a head start on the holiday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c91ba350-a42d-11ef-9cad-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 15:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f102c70-a427-11ef-9705-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Gladiator II,’ ‘Wicked’ and 17 other movies everyone will be talking about this holiday season</title>
      <description>Whether your taste runs to Disney or more grown-up fare — terrorism, eros, triumph and pain — these are the movies people will be laughing, crying and chatting about between now and the new year, and their estimated opening dates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6e546b0-a3b0-11ef-8897-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Karoline Leavitt as White House press secretary</title>
      <description>Leavitt, who served in the same role on the 2024 presidential campaign and also worked in the White House communications office during the first Trump administration, steps into the role of the president's most visible spokesperson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84072d61-a3ac-11ef-9eef-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin at his side, North Korea’s Kim Jong Un has never been more brazen — or in demand</title>
      <description>Donald Trump, who courted the North Korean leader during a first term that included two chummy summits, says Kim “misses” him. But as he returns to the White House, Trump will find Kim is much more confident, not least because he has a new alliance with Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8448b521-a3aa-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team weighs Pentagon pick after receiving details of past sexual assault claim</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s team debated the future of Pete Hegseth amid new revelations that police investigated an allegation that he sexually assaulted a woman in 2017.

Extensive details of the claim were shared with senior transition officials this week by a woman who said she was the accuser’s friend, who she said signed a nondisclosure agreement with Hegseth. Hegseth has denied wrongdoing and the police investigation did not result in charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e1a98d0-a39f-11ef-8719-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law makes a sexualized joke about his toddler niece</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law makes a sexualized joke about his toddler niece</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2a75280-a388-11ef-b3c0-0000a1ace0b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccines. Raw milk. Food dyes. Here are the changes RFK Jr. could make as the nation’s health secretary.</title>
      <description>If he is confirmed, Kennedy has pledged to pursue his “Make America Healthy Again” agenda to combat the causes of chronic disease and childhood illness. He has also discussed other goals, such as conducting more research on vaccines, revisiting federal vaccine requirements, taking fluoride out of public water, boosting access to raw milk, removing food dye and other ingredients and banning puberty blockers for children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">096179b0-a37c-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House speaker says he ‘strongly’ discourages release of ethics report on Matt Gaetz, Trump’s pick for attorney general</title>
      <description>Rep. Mike Johnson (R-Louisiana) said it would set a “terrible” precedent if the committee issued a report on its investigation into allegations that former congressman Matt Gaetz (R-Florida) engaged in sexual misconduct and illegal drug use and accepted improper gifts. Others, including some Republicans, have argued that the report should be considered as part of Gaetz’s confirmation process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e258db71-a375-11ef-a6ae-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">516bd750-a35e-11ef-9c6b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Trump’s controversial team. Tropical storm. Police chief. The Onion. Tyson vs. Paul. Bear disguise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24bad9a0-a349-11ef-8dbd-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks North Dakota Gov. Doug Burgum to lead the Interior Department</title>
      <description>The president-elect made the announcement, which he said would be made official on Friday, while speaking at the America First Policy Institute gala at his Mar-a-Lago estate in Florida.
The Interior Department oversees more than 500 million acres of federal land, managing oil, gas and mineral reserves that will be key to the Trump administration’s plans to boost U.S. energy production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d145820-a2f7-11ef-8897-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If confirmed, Hegseth and Gabbard would do more to doom Trump's presidency than Democrats ever could, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>Neither is remotely qualified for two of the most important management jobs in government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef357640-a2ea-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
