<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 20:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s allies are planning a series of artificial intelligence ‘Manhattan Projects’ to develop military technology</title>
      <description>The framework would also lift "burdensome regulations" and create “industry-led” agencies to evaluate AI models and secure systems from foreign adversaries, according to a copy of the document viewed exclusively by The Washington Post. It presents a markedly different strategy for the booming sector than that of the Biden administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd8524d0-43a5-11ef-a0d4-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 19:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Schumer, N.J. Gov. Murphy lead calls for Sen. Menendez to resign following his guilty verdict in bribery case</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-N.Y.) and New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) issued swift calls for Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) to step aside after he was convicted of taking bribes from three businessmen who showered him and his wife with cash, gold bars and a Mercedes-Benz. “Senator Menendez must now do what is right for his constituents,” Schumer said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c872ff31-43a1-11ef-86b3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) found guilty in federal bribery and corruption trial in Manhattan</title>
      <description>Menendez had been accused of accepting gold bars, a Mercedes-Benz convertible and other bribes from businessmen with ties to the governments of Egypt and Qatar, as well as trying to derail criminal investigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7a7e4a0-4394-11ef-b06c-0000a1ace647</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: 20-year-old listens to racist rapper. Should his parent speak up?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: 20-year-old listens to racist rapper. Should his parent speak up?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c48eccb0-438c-11ef-aa51-000a1ace43c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Their cup of woes runneth over in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2972b80-4377-11ef-a8b6-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 13:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandaged Trump. Rally shooting. Aileen Cannon. Brutal heat. Prime Day. Longer days. Extinct butterfly. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ccf5a30-4362-11ef-97f5-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump made an emotional entrance at the GOP convention, seizing his moment after an assassination attempt and a string of wins</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s appearance at the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee was a fitting culmination to a two-and-a-half-week stretch during which the former president survived an attempt on his life — and scored crucial victories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d1972f0-4324-11ef-8f10-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 03:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Dodgers outfielder Teoscar Hernández wins Home Run Derby in Texas</title>
      <description>The 31-year-old Hernández beat Kansas City Royals shortstop Bobby Witt Jr. in the final Monday night at Globe Life Field in Arlington, Tex., to win this year’s event. He has 19 home runs this season. The All-Star Game is Tuesday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bf62580-431f-11ef-a8d5-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 02:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans kick off their convention just days after the assassination attempt against Donald Trump. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Convening in Milwaukee, the party adopted a new platform earlier Monday, while Trump announced J.D. Vance as his running mate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f9bbba0-42fd-11ef-9255-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:55:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses warned police of Trump shooter at least 86 seconds before gunfire, video shows</title>
      <description>A Post analysis of the newly surfaced video backs up reports from other witnesses, who have said they tried to alert police before shots rang out. Growing evidence that law enforcement was made aware of the shooter before he opened fire has put the Secret Service under pressure to explain what analysts have described as a major security failure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94817750-42f8-11ef-8d27-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 22:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rifle used by Trump rally shooter was bought 11 years ago, person familiar says</title>
      <description>Thomas Matthew Crooks, who fired shots at former president Donald Trump at a rally in Butler, Pa., Saturday evening, used a rifle legally purchased by his father in 2013, said a person familiar with the investigation, speaking on the condition of anonymity to share details that have not been made public. Crooks, who was shot dead by the Secret Service after opening fire, bought 50 rounds of ammunition at a local gun shop Saturday morning, this person said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07ed9750-42e5-11ef-9843-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 20:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. soars to 101 degrees, setting record amid hottest summer to date</title>
      <description>Monday’s high of at least 101 set a record for the second straight day. An excessive heat warning is in effect for Tuesday, too, when heat indexes — factoring in heat and humidity — are expected to reach 105 to 110.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e686a2c0-42e2-11ef-9c21-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Sen. J.D. Vance (R-Ohio) to be his running mate</title>
      <description>A onetime sharp critic of Donald Trump turned staunch loyalist, Vance rose to prominence after his 2016 memoir, “Hillbilly Elegy.” Now 39, he would be one of the youngest vice presidents in history if elected in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9743f10-42dd-11ef-8c4d-000a1acec7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 19:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans at convention approve new platform without long-held positions on abortion and same-sex marriage</title>
      <description>Antiabortion activists had wanted to explicitly call for a constitutional amendment to give embryos or fetuses legal rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55918a80-42da-11ef-a669-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 18:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse takes over as class parent for husband who dropped the ball</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse takes over as class parent for husband who dropped the ball</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318cf7c1-42c4-11ef-a9bd-0000a1aceb03</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses classified documents case against Trump</title>
      <description>Aileen Cannon, the federal judge overseeing the classified documents charges against former president Donald Trump, has dismissed the indictment on the grounds that special counsel Jack Smith was improperly appointed, according to a new court filing Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5021120-42b2-11ef-8c38-000a1acedf4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 14:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A show that predicts the future in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac1e62f0-42ae-11ef-9e3a-0000a1acebd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 13:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gunman. Secret Service. Biden’s message. Israeli strikes. Baldwin trial. Richard Simmons. Spain’s victories. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6359be31-4299-11ef-a8d5-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s close call: Seven columnists respond to the attempt on former president Donald Trump’s life — and its aftermath.</title>
      <description>Seven columnists respond to the attempt on former president Donald Trump’s life — and its aftermath.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9218110-423b-11ef-9588-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden is set to speak from the Oval Office at 8 p.m. ET. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The president said earlier on Sunday that he was directing an “independent review of the national security” at Saturday’s Trump rally to assess exactly what happened in the shooting that left one attendee dead and two injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bf329a0-4239-11ef-be0b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 23:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spain wins European Championship, beating England, 2-1, for its third title since 2008</title>
      <description>La Roja finished a dominant run Sunday in Berlin, claiming its fourth continental championship in its fifth title-game appearance and denying England its first major trophy since the 1966 World Cup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60e6f7a0-4224-11ef-bde2-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 21:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It could feel like 110 degrees in the D.C. area on Monday. Officials have issued an excessive-heat warning.</title>
      <description>Highs are forecast to reach 100 or so but heat indexes, factoring in humidity, will near 110. Tuesday could be just as hot, and an excessive-heat watch is in effect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d761830-421b-11ef-9588-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 19:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosive material found in Trump rally shooter’s car. Biden expected to speak on attempted assassination soon. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro (D) identified the person killed during Saturday’s rally as Corey Comperatore, saying he died “protecting his family.” And former president Donald Trump on Sunday urged Americans to “stand united” after the shooting at the Pennsylvania rally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac660240-4209-11ef-bfd5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 17:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">866e0a51-41fb-11ef-9654-0000a1ace02f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 16:10:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Alcaraz wins Wimbledon men’s singles title, beating Novak Djokovic in the final for the second straight year</title>
      <description>Alcaraz, a 21-year-old from Spain, beat Djokovic on Sunday at the All England Club for his second Wimbledon title and his fourth Grand Slam championship overall.
Djokovic, 37, was playing for a record-tying eighth Wimbledon men’s singles title and a 25th Grand Slam singles title that would have given him the most of any player in any era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47424e30-41f7-11ef-a9ca-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 15:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witnesses describe chaos, fear at Trump rally shooting: ‘Oh my god, they got Trump’</title>
      <description>For those who had been waiting hours in the heat on Saturday in Butler, Pa., to hear Donald Trump speak, elation turned instantly to disbelief, horror, terror and anger after a sniper opened fire. They struggled in real time to comprehend what millions would soon grapple with from afar — a brazen attack on a former president and presumed GOP nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf66c853-41f2-11ef-bde2-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actress Shannen Doherty dies at 53. ‘Beverly Hills, 90210’ made her a star before ‘Charmed’ cemented her as an early-2000s TV icon.</title>
      <description>She announced in 2015 that she was being treated for breast cancer and last year said the cancer had spread to her brain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">285c4b10-41e8-11ef-ad04-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b908270-41e5-11ef-81f6-00000a1ace07</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 13:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI has identified the suspected Trump rally shooter as Thomas Matthew Crooks, a 20-year-old man from Bethel Park, Pa.</title>
      <description>The attack at the Butler, Pa., rally left one spectator dead and critically injured two others. The suspect was also killed. In a post on Truth Social, the former president said he was “shot with a bullet that pierced the upper part of my right ear.” The FBI said they were still trying to determine Crooks’s motive and asked members of the public to come forward with anything they know about him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2857ab40-41a8-11ef-8d7e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 06:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says bullet hit his ear during Pa. rally. Secret Service confirms one spectator dead and two injured.</title>
      <description>Secret Service confirms one attendee dead, two injured and shooter was killed. Trump extended his condolences to the family of the victim shot and killed at Pa. rally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece4b130-417e-11ef-a614-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 01:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting at Trump rally being investigated as assassination attempt, officials say</title>
      <description>The FBI, Secret Service and ATF are working on the case, according to two people familiar with the matter, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f93cea40-4176-11ef-b8ac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead, including apparent shooter, after gunfire broke out at Trump’s rally, an official said</title>
      <description>President Biden has received an initial briefing on the incident, according to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1a6e730-4171-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 23:43:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is ‘fine’ after being rushed away from a rally when loud noises were heard, spokesperson says</title>
      <description>The former president is "being checked out at a local medical facility," according to Steven Cheung, Trump's spokesperson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebf9e130-416c-11ef-b9bb-0000a1aceb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 23:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rushed offstage after loud noises heard at rally in Pennsylvania</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump was escorted away from an event in Butler, Pa., about 30 miles north of Pittsburgh, after loud noises were heard at the rally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fb15d20-4168-11ef-b9bb-0000a1aceb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 22:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My husband treats me badly. When do I get to stand up to him?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My husband treats me badly. When do I get to stand up to him?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0680abb0-4136-11ef-981e-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 16:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI illegally barred staff from airing safety risks, whistleblowers say in a letter to the SEC</title>
      <description>In a letter obtained by The Washington Post, whistleblowers asked the Securities and Exchange Commission to probe the artificial intelligence company’s allegedly restrictive nondisclosure agreements. OpenAI made staff sign employee agreements that required them to waive their federal rights to whistleblower compensation, the letter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b44de6c0-412e-11ef-9e7e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 15:43:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbora Krejcikova wins Wimbledon, capping an unexpected run to her second Grand Slam singles title</title>
      <description>Krejcikova, a 28-year-old from the Czech Republic, beat Jasmine Paolini of Italy at the All England Club. She won the French Open in 2021 but was seeded No. 31 at Wimbledon and had never advanced past the fourth round in the singles draw at the event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6ac6271-4129-11ef-94c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 15:08:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Westheimer dies at 96. The sex therapist was known to millions as ‘Dr. Ruth.’</title>
      <description>Westheimer was over 50 when she debuted on New York radio in the 1980s to explain, in straightforward fashion, the ways of making love. A child survivor of the Holocaust, she once said that “because I was not killed by the Nazis — because I survived — I had an obligation to make a dent in the world.” Her mix of candor and can-do cheer made her a popular guest on late-night talk shows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b79c3d81-4125-11ef-a22c-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 14:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In small-town Oklahoma, a mother worries about feeding her kids after GOP governor turns down millions in summer aid</title>
      <description>Tabitha Shinn calculates down to the penny for groceries for her three teens but still must rely on giveaways from a food pantry to make it through the month. Even so, there are days when the refrigerator is almost bare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcfe2340-4122-11ef-b5f2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 14:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bac7da1-411c-11ef-bf8b-0000a1ace77d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 13:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targeted Hamas’s military leader in a strike in southern Gaza. At least 71 were killed, health officials there said.</title>
      <description>It was unclear whether the strike killed Mohammed Deif, who is considered one of the main architects of the Oct. 7 attack on Israel. The Gaza Health Ministry said the strike on Mawasi was a “massacre” that also left hundreds injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">985803e1-410d-11ef-b4e7-0000a1ace325</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 11:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses Alec Baldwin’s manslaughter case in 'Rust' shooting, saying prosecutors failed to provide defense with evidence</title>
      <description>The shocking dismissal came after defense lawyers claimed that investigators had improperly withheld potential evidence that would have helped Baldwin's defense in the 2021 fatal shooting of Halyna Hutchins on a film set.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cce00010-409d-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 22:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI rushed through safety tests, undermining its White House AI pledge</title>
      <description>The start-up promised the White House it would rigorously safety-test new versions of its tech to make sure it wouldn’t inflict damage. But this spring, some members of OpenAI’s safety team felt pressured to speed through a new testing protocol, designed to prevent the technology from causing catastrophic harm, to meet a May launch date set by company leaders, according to three people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity for fear of retaliation. The previously unreported incident sheds light on the changing culture at OpenAI, where company leaders including CEO Sam Altman have been accused of prioritizing commercial interests over public safety — a stark departure from the company’s roots as an altruistic nonprofit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeeda460-4091-11ef-9bf6-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 20:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out Giuliani’s bankruptcy case, making it easier for former election workers he defamed to try to seize his assets</title>
      <description>A federal judge in New York threw out Rudy Giuliani’s bankruptcy case and paved the way for a litany of creditors, including two former Georgia election workers who won a $148 million defamation claim against him, to pursue and potentially seize his assets. They and other creditors have accused the former New York mayor of using the proceedings to avoid paying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fec74b00-4080-11ef-8915-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackers stole almost everyone’s AT&amp;T phone records. What should you do?</title>
      <description>Here’s what you need to know about AT&amp;T’s massive data breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f9a9750-4071-11ef-849d-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 17:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My husband never wants to visit my family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My husband never wants to visit my family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffe7f7e1-406d-11ef-a0c0-000a1aceb390</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 16:44:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. sent text apologizing to woman who accused him of sexual assault</title>
      <description>Eliza Cooney called the unsolicited late-night message from Kennedy “disingenuous and arrogant.” In a message that Cooney shared with The Washington Post, the independent presidential candidate told Cooney that he did not recall the incident but that any harm he caused was “inadvertent.” Cooney has described inappropriate behavior and sexual advances from Kennedy when she worked as his family’s weekend nanny in the late 1990s, including an incident in which Kennedy approached her from behind and allegedly groped her in a pantry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eecb460-405a-11ef-bae3-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 14:23:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c35f66c0-4052-11ef-bdde-0000a1acebc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch live: Post journalists join expanded edition of ‘First Look’ with Jonathan Capehart to discuss 2024 election</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters and columnists discuss President Biden’s make-or-break stretch in his 2024 campaign, the countdown to the Republican National Convention in Milwaukee, the pending announcement of Donald Trump’s running mate and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3caa4f0-404e-11ef-9fdd-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 13:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden mix-ups. Trump immunity. Texas blackouts. Gaza pier. Shelley Duvall. Gatorade lawsuit. Playful whales. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e316ce00-403d-11ef-b4bb-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
