<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:03:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Despite reversal of hundreds of CDC layoffs, federal biodefense workers are among health staff who still lost jobs, officials say</title>
      <description>Officials have reversed more than half of the about 1,300 layoff notices sent to staff at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, sparing personnel who were leading the response to measles outbreaks in the United States and an Ebola outbreak abroad. But details emerged about the other health workers who lost their jobs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cecfd460-a88c-11f0-95c3-0000a1ace322</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microplastics are everywhere. You can do one simple thing to avoid them.</title>
      <description>The biggest sources of microplastics have one thing in common, scientists say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed41c9b0-a87f-11f0-8a31-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent news outlets reject Pentagon’s press policy before signing deadline</title>
      <description>The Washington Post joined the New York Times, CNN and the Atlantic in refusing to sign the policy, which says that reporters cannot obtain or solicit any information that the Defense Department does not explicitly authorize.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47654651-a868-11f0-aa48-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A surge in retirements is putting huge strains on the government as it deals with a shutdown and layoffs</title>
      <description>The mass exodus — unprecedented in its scale — includes 154,000 federal employees who accepted buyout offers and were largely removed from the payroll as of the end of last month. Some of those are among nearly 105,000 employees who took regular retirement during the fiscal year that ended in September, an 18 percent surge from the previous year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f734f1d0-a844-11f0-a453-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Sister Jean in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">155464e0-a839-11f0-8956-000a1acedd61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares 'dawn of a new Middle East,' celebrating return of all living hostages to Israel</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is addressing the Israeli parliament after Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu called him “the greatest friend that the state of Israel has ever had in the White House.” All 20 living hostages have been returned to Israel from Gaza, and Israel has begun releasing Palestinian prisoners and detainees. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5822f6d0-a828-11f0-be19-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 11:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostage release. Shutdown impacts. Blue states. Deadly explosion. Gender pay gap. AI videos. Longevity tips. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5000540-a823-11f0-b976-0000a1ace930</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel prize in economics awarded to trio for their work explaining creative destruction in innovation, growth</title>
      <description>The Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences was awarded to Joel Mokyr of Northwestern University, Philippe Aghion of College de France, INSEAD and the London School of Economics, and Peter Howitt of Brown University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd8bb080-a81c-11f0-81fc-0000a1acec81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas releases first seven Israeli hostages as swap brokered under ceasefire deal gets underway</title>
      <description>The group, who were handed over to the International Committee of the Red Cross, are among the last living captives in Gaza about two years after Hamas-led militants attacked Israel, unleashing Israel’s destructive war in the Gaza Strip</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4a43800-a7fa-11f0-a643-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A conservative influencer was arrested in Portland. The president was watching.</title>
      <description>After Nick Sortor was arrested earlier this month outside an Immigration and Customs Enforcement facility in Portland, Oregon, President Donald Trump latched on to justify a federal crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d88c1e0-a7b6-11f0-a9c2-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The pain from the government shutdown is about to hit the public</title>
      <description>Americans are bracing for the worst effects of the ongoing shutdown to collide with the U.S. economy this week as missed paychecks and the absence of billions of dollars of government services sink in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b250f40-a791-11f0-b844-0000a1ace9f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c46aa350-a784-11f0-ba25-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 16:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A group ditched their smartphones for a month. It changed them.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post reporter joined 16 strangers who had also agreed to give up their smartphones for all of July as part of a program called Month Offline. They didn’t know what they were about to step into — which was in part by design.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95310cb0-a774-11f0-acc4-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 14:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cecec070-a76f-11f0-8a12-0000a1ace80d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 13:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diane Keaton, ‘Annie Hall’ star and rom-com legend, dies at 79</title>
      <description>The Academy Award-winning actress was featured in 1972’s “The Godfather” and its sequels, and co-starred in the 1991 comedy “Father of the Bride.” In 2003, she earned her fourth Oscar nomination for “Something's Gotta Give.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bc90a60-a6e8-11f0-acab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 21:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders Defense Dept. to issue military paychecks during shutdown</title>
      <description>The president said the Pentagon would repurpose money to make payroll, as military service members were poised to miss paychecks on Wednesday. Most other government workers will not be paid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7b3ee81-a6d3-11f0-a05b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities expect no survivors after Tennessee plant explosion left 18 missing</title>
      <description>Investigators do not anticipate finding any survivors after a munitions plant in rural Tennessee exploded Friday, leaving 18 people unaccounted for as of Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88bb3890-a6c3-11f0-8de4-0000a1ace8c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 16:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arab states expanded cooperation with Israeli military during Gaza war, files show</title>
      <description>Leaked U.S. documents reveal that key Arab states quietly met with the Israeli military to coordinate on regional threats even as they condemned the war in Gaza. Those military ties were thrown into crisis after Israel’s September airstrike in Qatar but could now play a significant role in overseeing the ceasefire in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0847b7c0-a6b3-11f0-b10c-0000a1ace627</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 15:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden undergoes radiation treatment for cancer, adjusts to private life as Trump and Democrats attack</title>
      <description>The former president is undergoing hormone therapy and radiation treatment as part of a plan to treat the aggressive form of prostate cancer he was diagnosed with earlier this year — and, according to interviews with multiple people close to him, remains bitter about being pushed to drop out of the 2024 race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a781740-a6b0-11f0-8b23-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4541b20-a6a6-11f0-a42d-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hiker vanished into thin air. Twenty years later, her family is left with unknowns.</title>
      <description>Michelle Vanek’s disappearance mystified investigators, inspired conspiracy theories and became a cautionary tale of the American wilderness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a895690-a6a2-11f0-9a65-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 13:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas Aces complete WNBA Finals sweep to cement dynasty status</title>
      <description>Behind superstar A’ja Wilson, the Aces beat the Phoenix Mercury four straight times and won their third championship in four seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">790c10f0-a64a-11f0-86a8-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces new 100 percent tariffs on China</title>
      <description>The president said he might cancel a meeting with Chinese leader Xi Jinping in retaliation for Beijing’s “hostile” move to limit access to rare minerals used in manufacturing. Stocks sank on his earlier threats to increase tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63835b92-a621-11f0-a89f-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration begins laying off federal workers amid shutdown, fulfilling president’s threat</title>
      <description>White House budget director Russell Vought said reductions-in-force were underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e42a09e0-a5fb-11f0-801d-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens tariffs on China, says he may cancel upcoming meeting with President Xi Jinping</title>
      <description>The president wrote on TruthSocial that he is unhappy about China’s “hostile” move to limit access to rare minerals used in manufacturing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe7be0e0-a5f4-11f0-a88f-0000a1ace307</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT rejects Trump administration deal for priority federal funding, the first university to publicly turn down the offer</title>
      <description>Last week, the Trump administration offered nine universities a “Compact for Academic Excellence in Higher Education,” presented as an opportunity to receive competitive advantages from the federal government. It was the latest attempt by the administration to force colleges into compliance with President Donald Trump’s ideological priorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fe24f61-a5ed-11f0-b45d-0000a1ace9c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside billionaire Peter Thiel’s private lectures: Warnings of ‘the Antichrist’ and U.S. destruction</title>
      <description>The tech investor said critics of technology are “legionnaires of the Antichrist” in recent private lectures on Christianity in San Francisco that connected government oversight of Silicon Valley to an apocalyptic future, according to recordings reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e790711-a5e2-11f0-b420-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaf90870-a5dd-11f0-982d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James. Trump and Gaza. Shutdown deadlock. Peter Thiel. Polar bears. Weekend storm. Bad Bunny. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ce6471-a5c8-11f0-a82f-000a1aced47b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Peace Prize awarded to María Corina Machado, a Venezuelan democracy crusader</title>
      <description>The Venezuelan opposition leader has become a symbol of democratic resistance against an increasingly authoritarian regime, even as she has been forced into hiding and barred from holding public office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56f5e120-a5ba-11f0-ac92-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s cabinet approves Gaza ceasefire deal, triggering countdown for Hamas to release remaining hostages</title>
      <description>Cabinet approval sets in motion a sequence expected to bring about the release of some 48 Israeli hostages, living and dead, in exchange for hundreds of Palestinians held in Israeli prisons as well as a halt to Israel’s bombardment of the Gaza Strip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9afa6b0-a568-11f0-a182-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump from deploying troops in Illinois for now</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Chicago on Thursday temporarily halted the administration’s push to dispatch the National Guard in and around the country’s third-largest city. The administration is almost certain to appeal the decision, which is the second time in a week that a judge has rejected President Donald Trump’s efforts to place troops in a major city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01d4a3e0-a568-11f0-925c-000a1ace827b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sports wager with terrible odds that bettors can’t stop making</title>
      <description>Parlays offer long odds and big potential payouts by combining individual bets into one with multiple “legs.” As betting booms, they are accounting for an increasing share of the money wagered on sports, according to a Washington Post analysis of state data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cf7a9a0-a565-11f0-94ad-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department indicts N.Y. Attorney General Letitia James in mortgage fraud case</title>
      <description>She becomes the latest of President Donald Trump’s foes charged in a case that career prosecutors had turned down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac004170-a550-11f0-9dbc-0000a1ace491</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse can’t drive anymore and expects to be driven on demand</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse can’t drive anymore and expects to be driven on demand</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78bbabe0-a52a-11f0-8304-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/10/09/carolyn-hax-spouse-demand-personal-driver/</title>
      <description>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/10/09/carolyn-hax-spouse-demand-personal-driver/</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1572df0-a529-11f0-80f8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nobel Prize in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c255feb0-a514-11f0-8eed-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unorthodox deal-making helped reach a Gaza peace deal that might actually hold, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>"If the deal holds, Trump can legitimately bolster his claim to be a peacemaker."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764ff00-a510-11f0-855c-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She left the medical mainstream and rose to be RFK Jr.’s surgeon general pick</title>
      <description>Casey Means has criticized the medical establishment. She could be put in a position to change it if confirmed, as expected, to one of the nation’s most recognizable and trusted medical posts. Several medical and scientific experts expressed concern that she could amplify policy recommendations that are not grounded in evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d07200-a50c-11f0-8eed-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in literature awarded to Hungarian author László Krasznahorkai, renowned for his ‘apocalyptic’ epics</title>
      <description>The Swedish Academy honored the writer, whom critic Susan Sontag once called the “master of the apocalypse” for “his compelling and visionary oeuvre.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9402b0c1-a501-11f0-a3f3-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza breakthrough. Troops in Chicago. Charlie Kirk. Data scramble. Wildfire arrest. Prime Day. Dolly Parton. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134155b0-a4ff-11f0-824b-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan measure to block Trump’s lethal strikes against alleged Venezuelan drug smugglers fails in Senate</title>
      <description>Democrats called the administration’s strikes unconstitutional but were unable to persuade enough Republicans to vote for a restraining measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbe9b440-a4a9-11f0-bb6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hamas agree to peace deal to begin ending war in Gaza, Trump says</title>
      <description>The president’s announcement says the agreement includes the release of hostages by Hamas and the withdrawal of Israeli troops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87895330-a49d-11f0-8d85-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best restaurants in and around D.C.</title>
      <description>Washington Post food critic Tom Sietsema celebrates, one last time, some of the many places that make D.C. one of the best food cities in the country — starting with a Top 5 list. His restaurant of the year: Albi, the Levantine jewel that just keeps getting better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a610ff0-a492-11f0-9099-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 22:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s sprawling hunt for Charlie Kirk critics spans nearly 300 investigations</title>
      <description>The inquiry, resulting in a smattering of disciplinary action so far, follows an extraordinary Pentagon directive aimed at silencing criticism of the slain activist and Trump supporter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4f02f0-a47d-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quarter of FBI agents have been assigned to immigration enforcement, internal data shows</title>
      <description>The intense focus on immigration has raised alarm among current and former FBI agents who say morale is low across the bureau as agents have less time to dedicate to national security, white-collar crime and complex cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">409d6b40-a476-11f0-8e3e-0000a1ace64f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for allegedly starting L.A.-area Palisades Fire that killed 12 people in January, officials say</title>
      <description>Jonathan Rinderknecht, a 29-year-old from Florida, was charged with destruction of property by means of fire, authorities said at a news conference. The fire burned more than 23,000 acres in the area before being contained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f71bac0-a462-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ffb8a0-a460-11f0-b1d0-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</title>
      <description>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">774763d2-a458-11f0-b9fa-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James Comey makes first court appearance and pleads not guilty in case roiling Justice Department</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has opened several criminal investigations into President Donald Trump’s perceived foes in what legal experts and retired judges have described as an unprecedented attack on the rule of law. Comey is the first former senior government official to be charged as part of Trump’s efforts, but the case against him has been fraught for years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd71e9e1-a452-11f0-81ef-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
