<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 18:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the era of Trump trad</title>
      <description>This president’s aesthetic combines classical architecture and cartoonish virility with WWE alternative reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4730bfb0-e703-11ef-b032-0000a1aceb3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Four big Super Bowl LIX predictions — including who will win</title>
      <description>From Kansas City’s defense to the Eagles’ A.J. Brown to Chiefs tight end Travis Kelce, The Washington Post’s Adam Kilgore provides the Super Bowl’s most important factors to watch, plus a final score pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f021e3a0-e6fa-11ef-8b15-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df50bfe1-e6f2-11ef-88a6-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In chaotic Washington blitz, Elon Musk’s ultimate goal becomes clear</title>
      <description>In one federal agency after another, Musk and a coterie of aides are moving to control, automate — and substantially diminish — hundreds if not thousands of public functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ee51910-e66c-11ef-8979-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 22:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 underrated destinations to add to your travel wish list</title>
      <description>Our picks for where to go without crowds this year include the forests of Transylvania, a “mini New Orleans” in another southern state, a tranquil Brazilian beach and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1abbc90-e652-11ef-a473-0000a1ace055</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Cleavage’: A single word can have so many meanings. So can life.</title>
      <description>It’s what linguists call a “contronym,” a word with two opposite meanings. It also describes my life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab163d90-e648-11ef-b8d7-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only Super Bowl recipe roundup you need — including wings, dips, chili and pizza</title>
      <description>For the many millions of people without a rooting interest in the Kansas City Chiefs’ dynastic aspirations or the Philadelphia Eagles’ run to redemption, the main event will play out on a coffee table rather than the football field. Peruse our top recipes, broken down by “food group,” and supplement with store-bought essentials as needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1bcb170-e643-11ef-8676-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration cut billions in biomedical funding. Researchers say it imperils work on cancer and other illnesses.</title>
      <description>The NIH said that, effective immediately, it will cut more than $4 billion in what it calls overhead expenses, and it singled out large universities. Researchers say that will hurt small and large facilities alike that work on medical issues such as cancer research and heart disease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e18dc1-e63e-11ef-b248-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74dd4300-e629-11ef-865e-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Musk’s DOGE from access to Treasury Department material</title>
      <description>A federal judge temporarily blocked Elon Musk’s Department of Government Efficiency early Saturday from accessing sensitive Treasury Department information for millions of Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">243e0210-e5f0-11ef-b806-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will fire Kennedy Center board members, appoint himself chairman</title>
      <description>President Trump did not say which board members he plans to terminate. It is unclear whether the president has the power to make such changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f86c190-e5ae-11ef-a4f0-0000a1ace6d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director nominee Kash Patel was paid $25,000 by Russian filmmaker tied to Kremlin, documents show</title>
      <description>Patel received the money from Global Tree Pictures, a Los Angeles-based company run by Igor Lopatonok, who holds both Russian and U.S. citizenship. Lopatonok’s previous projects include a pro-Russia influence campaign that received money from a fund created by Russian President Vladimir Putin, the documents show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">232ef3f0-e5ac-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 23:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE’s access to Treasury payments marked an ‘insider threat,’ an intelligence contractor warned the department</title>
      <description>The warning, delivered by a contractor that runs a threat intelligence center for the U.S. Treasury Department, said access by Elon Musk's U.S. DOGE Service to the sensitive payment network marked an “unprecedented insider threat risk” and should be “immediately” suspended, according to correspondence reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aab51cf1-e5a7-11ef-bb07-0000a1acef49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 23:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Trump administration from putting more than 2,000 USAID workers on leave</title>
      <description>The decision is a legal setback to the effort by President Trump and his allies, led by billionaire Elon Musk, to freeze foreign aid programs, sideline or fire nearly all staff at the U.S. Agency for International Development, and shut the agency down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d426a5e0-e5a2-11ef-9952-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 22:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers flooded with thousands of calls per hour as constituents demand answers about Elon Musk</title>
      <description>Sen. Lisa Murkowski (R-Alaska) said the Senate’s phones were receiving 1,600 calls each minute, compared with the usual 40 calls per minute. The outpouring of complaints and confusion has put pressure on lawmakers to find out more about Musk’s project, heightening tensions between the billionaire tech mogul and the government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8480070-e59a-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 21:29:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump drops U.S. government’s opposition to Tennessee’s ban on transgender teen care in case pending at Supreme Court</title>
      <description>The Biden administration, along with transgender teens, their families and a medical provider, challenged Tennessee’s law banning hormone treatments and puberty blockers for transgender minors. “The government’s previously stated views no longer represent the United States’ position," the solicitor general’s office said in a letter to the court. The case can continue, with a ruling expected by summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1aef3f0-e594-11ef-948f-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 20:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. area faces icy weather Saturday and a chance of snow Tuesday</title>
      <description>A wintry mix could cause slippery travel across the area on Saturday, prompting winter weather advisories from the National Weather Service. A more significant winter storm is possible on Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10497980-e580-11ef-bd7b-0000a1ace95f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 18:19:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We left the family vacation rather than sleep on couches with our kids: Carolyn Hax takes questions</title>
      <description>We left the family vacation rather than sleep on couches with our kids: Carolyn Hax takes questions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc88941-e57b-11ef-8fdd-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 17:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Elon Musk doing? It isn’t slashing the budget. Matt Bai looks at the panic DOGE has ignited in Washington.</title>
      <description>DOGE isn’t getting anywhere near $2 trillion in spending cuts. Here’s a plan that would.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e92211-e577-11ef-981b-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 17:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret U.K. order demands Apple allow access to all cloud content from users worldwide</title>
      <description>The British government’s undisclosed order, issued last month, requires blanket capability to view fully encrypted material, not merely assistance in cracking a specific account, people familiar with the matter told The Post. There is no known precedent for an order like this in major democracies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90457d00-e567-11ef-8e98-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 15:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9903290-e55f-11ef-98ac-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 14:29:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 143,000 jobs in January, beginning the year with slower but solid gains for the labor market</title>
      <description>The January report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics adds evidence that the labor market is solid, despite the fires in California that weighed on parts of the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c3cce81-e558-11ef-a57a-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 13:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s cuts. Project 2025. Transgender athletes. Missing plane. Jobs report. Super Bowl. Drifting iceberg. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ebcb210-e54b-11ef-98e7-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders QB Jayden Daniels is named NFL’s offensive rookie of the year</title>
      <description>Daniels led Washington to a 12-5 record in the regular season, setting rookie records for rushing yards by a quarterback and passing accuracy. Though voting was conducted before the playoffs, Daniels bolstered his résumé further, leading the franchise to the NFC championship game for the first time in 33 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f248dc0-e4f9-11ef-b806-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms Russell Vought, who helped to craft Project 2025, as White House budget director</title>
      <description>Vought has endorsed deep spending cuts and radical changes to the federal workforce. Democrats opposed his nomination to lead the Office of Management and Budget, citing his calls for an expansion in presidential powers to override Congress on spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34c0a570-e4ec-11ef-8b81-0000a1ace0d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE aims to slash $2 trillion in federal spending. Try it for yourself by choosing what to cut — and see just how hard it is.</title>
      <description>It’s not clear whether all of Elon Musk’s efforts are legal. But even if they are, such deep cuts are not likely to be easy. Balance trade-offs, such as preventing payments to dead Americans or eliminating foreign aid, and see how much you can reduce the United States’ annual spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb5b0b80-e4e5-11ef-8240-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 23:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCAA bans transgender athletes from women’s sports after Trump order</title>
      <description>The new policy, which the organization announced Thursday and is effective immediately, limits competition in women’s sports exclusively to athletes assigned female at birth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ef28e0-e4e2-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 23:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials plan to close EPA’s Office of Environmental Justice and External Civil Rights, putting nearly 170 workers on leave</title>
      <description>In addition to eliminating the division, which aims to tackle the pollution that disproportionately burdens poor and minority communities, the administration plans to fire roughly 20 employees in the Justice Department’s Environment and Natural Resources Division.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379471d0-e4df-11ef-b5a7-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 23:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani’s former interpreter sentenced to 57 months in prison after stealing millions from MLB star</title>
      <description>Ippei Mizuhara agreed to a plea deal in May after he was charged with bank fraud and subscribing to a false tax return, following what authorities described as a years-long scheme to steal almost $17 million from Ohtani to pay off gambling debts and purchase personal items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6c57ea0-e4dc-11ef-a9bf-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 22:51:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syria’s new government may allow Russia to keep its air and naval bases there, defense minister says in Post interview</title>
      <description>In a wide-ranging Washington Post interview in Damascus this week, Syrian Defense Minister Murhaf Abu Qasra said the new government was open to letting Russia keep its military installations if a deal with the Kremlin served Syria’s interests. He also discussed efforts to negotiate with U.S.-backed Kurdish forces and ambitious plans to bring the country’s armed factions under the control of a unified command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2e2cc31-e4c1-11ef-a7d4-0000a1ace629</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:38:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge pauses Thursday deadline for Trump administration’s buyout program as labor groups sue to block it</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Massachusetts temporarily paused the Trump administration’s buyout program’s deadline, which had been set for 11:59 p.m. Thursday, and set a new hearing for Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa345840-e4b7-11ef-866e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:24:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Post reporters answer your questions about buyouts and layoffs under Trump</title>
      <description>Washington Post personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary and reporters Lisa Rein and Emily Davies are helping you understand the future of the federal workforce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b2fc10-e4b5-11ef-a9bf-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 18:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s DOGE team is feeding sensitive federal data into AI via Microsoft's cloud to target spending cuts</title>
      <description>Musk’s representatives from the Department of Government Efficiency have fed data from across the Education Department — including personally identifiable information for people who manage grants and sensitive internal financial data — into artificial intelligence software to probe the agency’s programs and spending, according to two people with knowledge of the actions.

This use of AI, which has not previously been reported, shows how Musk’s group, which includes former employees from his tech empire, is tapping the favorite tool of Silicon Valley as part of its mission to drastically slash the size and functions of the federal government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5264e31-e4ae-11ef-b658-0000a1ace6d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 17:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration sues Illinois and Chicago, accusing them of blocking immigration enforcement efforts</title>
      <description>The lawsuit appears to be the first the Justice Department has filed after vowing to investigate state and local officials who impede President Donald Trump’s immigration crackdown. It seeks a court order to bar protections for undocumented immigrants that exist at the state and local level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f26c7ed0-e4a8-11ef-8b81-0000a1ace0d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 16:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Washington reels, Trump voters like what they see</title>
      <description>Most who spoke to The Washington Post in Pennsylvania were in favor of President Donald Trump’s efforts to scale back the federal workforce, stand by his controversial Cabinet nominees and slash foreign aid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cfa5f60-e49f-11ef-9eac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariff whiplash: Six writers try to make sense of the twists and turns</title>
      <description>On Feb. 1, President Donald Trump announced tariffs on Canada, Mexico and China. By Feb. 3, the tariffs threatened on Mexico and Canada were deferred for a month, while those on China stayed in place.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76a0acc1-e49b-11ef-a9ad-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 15:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ‘infinite sea’ of these animals in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b385ff80-e498-11ef-9f7c-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 14:43:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s DOGE agents have accessed sensitive personnel data at the Office of Personnel Management, alarming security officials</title>
      <description>The highly restricted data includes personally identifiable information — including addresses, demographic profiles, salary details and disciplinary histories — for millions of federal employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84c4d7c0-e489-11ef-b7a7-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 12:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal workers. Trump and Gaza. Transgender athletes. Bird flu. Tech layoffs. Store closures. Egg heist. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3fe4260-e481-11ef-a10c-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Countries are preparing for the worst after Trump's comments on Gaza, David Ignatius reports</title>
      <description>To a region still recovering from the trauma of war, Trump’s proposed takeover of Gaza was incendiary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac74e060-e41d-11ef-9738-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our personal finance columnist reviewed the ‘deferred resignation’ contract with a law professor. Her verdict: Don’t sign.</title>
      <description>Our personal finance columnist reviewed the ‘deferred resignation’ contract with a law professor. Her verdict: Don’t sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e69b691-e419-11ef-b3a4-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive order that aims to ban trans student-athletes from competing on girls’ and women’s teams</title>
      <description>The new order threatens to deny federal funds for schools that allow transgender athletes to compete in K-12 and college sports. It’s the latest salvo in President Donald Trump’s attack on transgender rights, another that will ricochet through schools across the country, as the president delivers on another contentious culture war promise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9920c3a1-e407-11ef-b1fb-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will not send funds to Gaza and hasn’t committed to sending troops, White House says, after his proposal to displace Gazans</title>
      <description>White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters Wednesday that the United States “is not going to pay for the rebuilding of Gaza.” She also said President Donald Trump “has not committed” to putting boots on the ground there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24d435e0-e3f3-11ef-85ee-0000a1ace36f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China considers pulling the plug on TikTok in the U.S. as it waits for a ‘grand deal’ on trade with Trump</title>
      <description>TikTok’s Chinese owner appears to be slow-rolling negotiations for a sale while waiting for a green light from the Chinese government, even as corporate allies of President Donald Trump race to broker a deal to sell the app to an American bidder, according to three people familiar with the talks, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private business transactions.

But Beijing is increasingly likely to take a hard-line approach, letting TikTok’s U.S. operations die rather than approving a sale as it holds out for a “grand deal” with the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">824e24f1-e3e5-11ef-b464-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge indefinitely blocks Trump’s order to end birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>Maryland U.S. District Judge Deborah L. Boardman issued the preliminary injunction on Wednesday in response to a lawsuit brought by civil rights groups. The injunction applies nationally and will remain in place as the case is adjudicated. The Trump administration is expected to appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3a9151-e3dc-11ef-a046-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NWSL must create $5 million fund to compensate women’s soccer players abused by coaches and officials, new settlement states</title>
      <description>The deal involves the attorneys general from Washington, D.C., Illinois and New York, and the NWSL Players Association. It was reached more than three years after allegations of harassment, emotional abuse and sexual misconduct sparked a crisis that rocked the league and sport, led to investigations and prompted a series of changes by the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1e1e950-e3d0-11ef-aba1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ‘everlasting’ musical instrument in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abf7da10-e3ce-11ef-bf97-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS resumes accepting packages from China and Hong Kong hours after blocking them in effort to comply with Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Rather than refusing packages from China and Hong Kong entirely, the U.S. Postal Service says it will work with Customs and Border Protection on a way to collect new tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7298a501-e3ca-11ef-9bb5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Gaza proposal. Elon Musk. Tariff impacts. Sweden shooting. Abortion pills. Winter storms. Expensive violin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ca7ba2-e3b8-11ef-b59e-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most USAID workers to be put on leave as all overseas staff are recalled, Trump administration says</title>
      <description>The move is the latest action in a jarring broadside against America’s foreign aid architecture that has followed President Donald Trump’s return to the White House. In the weeks since his inauguration, the new administration has announced a broad freeze on foreign aid programs — unleashing upheaval across the aid sector and financial crises for groups reliant on USAID funding — and fired, furloughed or put on leave the bulk of AID employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec82e010-e37a-11ef-b770-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
