<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 06:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>President Trump is expected to announce a trade agreement with the United Kingdom on Thursday</title>
      <description>It wasn’t immediately clear whether the agreement would be detailed or simply serve as the framework for further talks. The agreement was a victory for British Prime Minister Keir Starmer, who visited the White House in February armed with charm and a signed invitation to a royal audience with King Charles III. British leaders have long sought to bolster economic ties to the United States to make up for the trade losses of their 2020 departure from the European Union.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fc97620-2bc1-11f0-ab2d-0000a1acedb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 04:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I’d like to see changes in my church that I am not optimistic will happen’: Four columnists on what the next pope should do</title>
      <description>As the world waits on the fabled white smoke from the Vatican City’s Sistine Chapel announcing a new pope has been chosen, we asked four Post columnists what the next leader of the Roman Catholic Church should do. Here are their thoughts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f9f7940-2b95-11f0-9793-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area</title>
      <description>Post food critic Tom Sietsema's top newcomers to the ever-evolving D.C. dining scene include a Middle Eastern gem, Mission-style burritos, a pair of New York imports and an ode to Afro-Caribbean cuisine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9536d20-2b8f-11f0-974c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread ICE visits leave D.C. restaurant owners, workers rattled and bracing for more uncertainty</title>
      <description>At least seven D.C. restaurants confirmed that Department of Homeland Security agents visited Tuesday and asked for I-9 forms to verify staff employment eligibility. "It's incredibly scary," one restaurant owner said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b087e670-2b80-11f0-a0ac-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds three former Memphis police officers not guilty in 2023 murder of Tyre Nichols</title>
      <description>Nichols was beaten to death after fleeing from a traffic stop in 2023. His case helped galvanize support for police reform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bb4f0a0-2b78-11f0-bcc3-0000a1ace8d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black smoke over Vatican signals no pope chosen on first day of conclave</title>
      <description>Cardinals did not select a new pope in their first secret ballot, a result indicated by billowing black smoke from the world's most watched chimney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">186cbc81-2b76-11f0-b810-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pushes nations to approve Elon Musk’s Starlink internet business amid tariff talks</title>
      <description>State Department documents indicate that some countries are turning to Musk’s company in hopes of striking a better deal on trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">526e6230-2b71-11f0-bd65-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve leaves interest rates unchanged amid growing concerns about Trump’s tariffs clouding the economic outlook</title>
      <description>While inflation has been falling, higher tariffs could drive up prices and dampen economic growth, which complicates the Fed's interest rate policy. Fed Chair Jerome H. Powell is expected talk about the economy’s path in a news conference at 2:30 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12fc0ab0-2b6e-11f0-a581-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice of America will carry programming from One America News, which is known for its right-wing slant</title>
      <description>Staffers at the government-funded broadcaster VOA condemned the announcement from Kari Lake, who is a senior adviser to the agency that oversees it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17f92710-2b5e-11f0-bf3b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants son’s partner to remove piercings for ‘fancy’ event</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants son’s partner to remove piercings for ‘fancy’ event</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9048c880-2b5c-11f0-9859-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conclave to elect the new pope has begun. Go inside with this guide to its ancient traditions and secretive rituals.</title>
      <description>Beneath the domes and walls of Vatican City, a quiet drama is unfolding. Cardinals from around the world will vote in the Sistine Chapel until one candidate wins a two-thirds majority to become the next leader of the Catholic Church.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a05436d0-2b5a-11f0-874a-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican ends challenge to N.C. Supreme Court race, clearing the way for the Democrat to be sworn in six months after she won</title>
      <description>The announcement ends a six-month legal saga and preserves the current makeup of the state Supreme Court, where Republicans hold a 5-2 advantage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b70ecb0-2b59-11f0-bc45-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Food critic Tom Sietsema just named the 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area. Ask him about his picks.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Food critic Tom Sietsema just named the 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area. Ask him about his picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c54bc5d0-2b54-11f0-8244-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hanging up for good in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea0ae3e1-2b47-11f0-ab1f-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 13:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India and Pakistan. Papal conclave. Canadian prime minister. DOGE database. Transgender troops. Real ID. Antivenom. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a6b9543-2b32-11f0-b6d2-0000a1acef65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and China plan to hold high-level trade talks in Switzerland this weekend</title>
      <description>Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and Trade Representative Jamieson Greer will sit down with Chinese counterparts in Geneva to discuss easing trade tensions. This comes after both sides, feeling the impact of sky-high tariffs, have softened their rhetoric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">242ea840-2ada-11f0-bc2f-000a1ace64c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 00:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump’s urging, USPS expected to name former Waste Management CEO David Steiner as next postmaster general, officials say</title>
      <description>Steiner is a board member of Postal Service competitor FedEx. He would replace Louis DeJoy, whom President Donald Trump forced out earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3b0b4d-2acf-11f0-9e15-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 23:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spyware maker NSO ordered to pay $167 million for hacking WhatsApp</title>
      <description>A federal jury in California dealt the Israeli maker of blacklisted Pegasus spyware a record-setting blow after six years of litigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc43a590-2ac1-11f0-84a5-0000a1ace1fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India strikes Pakistan in retaliation for Kashmir militant attack last month, raising fears of war</title>
      <description>The strikes were the first carried out by India inside Pakistan since 2019, bringing the nuclear-armed archrivals to the brink of direct conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6463e821-2abd-11f0-a583-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 21:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration urged Ukraine to accept U.S. deportees from other countries amid its war with Russia, documents show</title>
      <description>The extraordinary request, outlined in documents reviewed by The Washington Post, illustrates the administration’s aggressive bid to identify willing partners who will accept people expelled by the U.S. as President Donald Trump attempts to dramatically expand deportations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1d3290-2ab4-11f0-ac0d-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 19:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Supreme Court rules Trump can ban transgender troops from the military while litigation continues</title>
      <description>A lower court had put President Donald Trump's executive order banning transgender troops from military service on hold in response to a lawsuit that said the ban was unconstitutional and a threat to national security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57cde8f0-2aa8-11f0-84a6-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky Derby winner Sovereignty to skip Preakness, ending Triple Crown bid</title>
      <description>The 3-year-old won at Churchill Downs on a sloppy track Saturday, but the horse's Hall of Fame trainer, Bill Mott, indicated the morning after the race that it wasn’t a sure thing Sovereignty would run again May 17 in Baltimore.
Sovereignty is the fourth Derby winner in the past seven Triple Crown seasons to skip the Preakness after all 22 Derby winners from 1997 to 2018 entered the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95ec5f51-2aa2-11f0-ac8c-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 17:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA plans to eliminate popular Energy Star program, which certifies efficiency of home appliances</title>
      <description>The Trump administration informed Environmental Protection Agency staffers of the decision Monday, according to two people briefed on the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The move is likely to draw pushback on Capitol Hill, where Energy Star has historically enjoyed bipartisan support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baa81010-2a97-11f0-9b1e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Aunt’s vicious jab at funeral tarnishes a late mother’s gift</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Aunt’s vicious jab at funeral tarnishes a late mother’s gift</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">682ca200-2a93-11f0-98db-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 16:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friedrich Merz is named German chancellor in second parliamentary vote, after a destabilizing setback in the first round</title>
      <description>Merz, the center-right party leader, prevailed in the Bundestag on Tuesday after he earlier became the first chancellor-designate in Germany’s postwar history to fail to secure an absolute majority. He assumes office amid fraying European ties with the Trump administration and as allies, from Paris to Warsaw, look to Berlin to anchor a robust security strategy without the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d526a10-2a86-11f0-83b2-000a1ace79b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best looks from the Met Gala</title>
      <description>Menswear, for once, didn’t steal the show — it was the show. See our favorite looks from an evening of dignified, grown-up glamour at this year’s fete celebrating the museum’s exhibit “Superfine: Tailoring Black Style.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19f9d7f0-2a80-11f0-a583-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A facility that’s been closed since 1963 is in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5252cf50-2a7e-11f0-b34e-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-deportation. Hollywood tariff. Gaza occupation. Mike Pence. Texas colleges. Meta AI. Met Gala. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">416bc580-2a69-11f0-86dc-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Service ends air-quality monitoring at all national parks</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has ordered the end to the air-quality monitoring program at national parks across the country, according to two people familiar with the matter and an internal email obtained by The Post. The program collects data on the levels of air pollutants at the 63 national parks in the United States. Federal officials consult this data when deciding whether to grant a permit to a nearby industrial facility, such as a power plant or an oil refinery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a10fa1-2a05-11f0-8dc3-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The stars are arriving on the Met Gala red carpet. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Who best captured this year's Black dandy theme? Watch along with Washington Post reporters as we discuss all the eye-catching looks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2621dce0-2a02-11f0-a4bc-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. region until midnight</title>
      <description>Storms, some containing torrential rain, hail and strong winds, will sweep through the D.C. area from south to north. Follow Capital Weather Gang's live updates for the latest on the storms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d400a51-2a00-11f0-a97c-0000a1ace97d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Post wins Pulitzers for breaking news and political cartoons; ProPublica wins journalism’s top award in public service category</title>
      <description>The Washington Post was recognized with two Pulitzer Prizes on Monday, including a win in the breaking news reporting category for coverage of the attempted assassination of Donald Trump in July. Ann Telnaes, until recently a political cartoonist for The Post’s Opinions page, was awarded her second win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a72e29d0-29e7-11f0-ae09-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT maker OpenAI scraps plan to restructure into a for-profit company after pressure from Elon Musk</title>
      <description>OpenAI aimed to separate from its nonprofit board but reversed course after former employees and a lawsuit from Musk alleged it would loosen oversight of its powerful artificial intelligence technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55c640e0-29de-11f0-8796-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders owner joins Bowser and Trump to announce 2027 NFL draft on the National Mall, envisioning 1 million fans in D.C.</title>
      <description>Washington Commanders owner Josh Harris, NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell and Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) joined President Donald Trump in the Oval Office for Monday afternoon’s formal announcement about the 2027 NFL draft. Harris told The Washington Post on Monday he hopes to draw 1 million visitors to the District for the annual event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7887aea1-29db-11f0-b927-0000a1ace41d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Choosing that baecation over meeting first grandbaby, explained</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Choosing that baecation over meeting first grandbaby, explained</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c7a9d1-29ca-11f0-b616-0000a1ace652</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The velocity of unladen swallows in today’s On The Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3967e6f1-29b7-11f0-9f19-0000a1ace563</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump interview. Reopening Alcatraz. Australia election. Gaza war. Viral fundraiser. Downpours. Cosmic gold. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19445460-29a0-11f0-8c71-0000a1ace45f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeons attempt a medical first: Removing a spinal tumor through the patient’s eye</title>
      <description>Karla Flores had a tumor strangling her spinal cord near the base of her skull. Her doctors decided to try a risky procedure that had never been performed on a living patient.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bfaa170-292f-11f0-838f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s 48-hour scramble to fly migrants to a Salvadoran megaprison</title>
      <description>The administration rounded up some Venezuelans two days before the flights to El Salvador took off, pressing forward even as Venezuela agreed to accept deportation flights. A Washington Post investigation found that at least two men who had flown to the United States as vetted refugees were among those believed to have been sent to the prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">982baca0-2910-11f0-9f7d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90a44970-2900-11f0-9a73-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 35 definitive rules of train travel</title>
      <description>Whether you’re hopping up the Northeast corridor or just taking in-town public transit, you should treat your fellow passengers with the courtesy they deserve. Share this guide with the seat sprawlers and cafe car squatters in your life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d952d450-28f8-11f0-bd23-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05a5f300-28ec-11f0-bb79-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says ‘I don’t know’ when asked whether he is required to uphold the Constitution in NBC interview</title>
      <description>In a wide-ranging interview, President Donald Trump also did not rule out the use of military force to take Greenland but said it’s “highly unlikely” he’d do so with Canada. He downplayed fears of a recession and spoke of both Vice President JD Vance and Secretary of State Marco Rubio as his potential successors, saying that running for a third term “is not something I’m looking to do.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9378b310-28e8-11f0-baf9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sovereignty wins the 151st Kentucky Derby, the first leg of horse racing’s Triple Crown</title>
      <description>Sovereignty won the Run for the Roses on Saturday at Churchill Downs in Louisville.
The next leg of the Triple Crown is the Preakness Stakes, to be held May 17 in Baltimore, followed by the Belmont Stakes on June 7 in Saratoga Springs, New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3aea8f0-2873-11f0-81d9-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, brown rice is healthier than white rice — except in some limited cases</title>
      <description>Recent concerns over the health risks of eating brown rice are mostly overblown, studies show. Experts contend that the nutritional benefits outweigh any concerns about arsenic in a varied diet. A caveat is that some groups, such as infants and toddlers, may be more vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43423a0-2861-11f0-8d45-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett to step down as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway by year’s end after leading the conglomerate for decades</title>
      <description>Buffett, 94, announced his retirement intention at Berkshire Hathaway’s annual meeting in Omaha. He said he would recommend Greg Abel, whom Buffett has previously said would succeed him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ddedf20-284f-11f0-b290-0000a1ace80d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">165261b0-2839-11f0-81de-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At a Kentucky farm, star racehorses help people fight a monster: Addiction</title>
      <description>The Stable Recovery program at Taylor Made Farm changes lives with the remarkable healing power of animals. Men in the program live on the farm and learn how to care for the elite racehorses, giving them a sense of structure and purpose many of them had struggled to find.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">475fa5b0-282f-11f0-993b-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 14:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd25c8d0-2822-11f0-b3ae-0000a1aceb64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted national security adviser Michael Waltz had angered Trump by coordinating privately with Israel over plans to attack Iran</title>
      <description>Waltz appeared to have engaged in intense coordination with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu about military options against Iran ahead of an Oval Office meeting last month between the Israeli leader and President Donald Trump, two people with knowledge of the episode said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b62b4940-2820-11f0-98d4-0000a1ace003</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
