<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 13:10:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Air Force One. China tariffs. Trump and Putin. Hostage release. Pope Leo. Pap smear. Lullabies. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40f14ce0-2f20-11f0-988d-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., China agree to suspend most tariffs for 90 days as trade negotiations continue</title>
      <description>Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and U.S. Trade Representative Jamieson Greer said U.S. tariffs on Chinese goods would be reduced from 145 to 30 percent. China said it would cut its blanket tariffs from 125 to 10 percent starting Wednesday.
The agreement provides a temporary reprieve in a trade war that threatens to cause a global recession and deepen a widening rift between the world’s two largest economies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cc3eb30-2f04-11f0-8a1b-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the last U.S. pencil factories is divided over Trump’s tariffs: ‘We are not too sure about making America great this way’</title>
      <description>At Musgrave Pencil Company in Shelbyville, Tennessee, politics rarely came up before this year. President Donald Trump’s policies have changed that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21823020-2eaf-11f0-858c-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 21:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-vaccine uproar over Trump's new surgeon general pick exposes MAHA divisions</title>
      <description>The nominee, Casey Means, a nutrition advocate and ally of Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., faces criticism for not opposing vaccines enough. The division highlights a tension between prioritizing food or vaccination in the Make America Healthy Again movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52909bb0-2e9c-11f0-ba7b-0000a1ace123</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 19:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar is discussing donating an aircraft to the U.S. government for Trump to use, two people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>While the deal is not final, ethics experts are raising concerns about the possible donation from a foreign government, which they say is unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da929650-2e95-11f0-8897-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 18:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0935f550-2e83-11f0-92ab-0000a1ace4f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 16:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judges are receiving unsolicited pizza deliveries they say are meant to intimidate them</title>
      <description>Many of the deliveries, judges say, have gone to those presiding over lawsuits challenging the Trump administration’s policies. Deliveries began in February and may number in the hundreds across at least seven states, prompting increased security concerns and a demand for a Justice Department investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb4c96f1-2e74-11f0-92ab-0000a1ace4f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 14:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9f305b1-2e6d-11f0-b9d5-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mayor Bowser’s approval rating recovers as Trump worries emerge, poll finds</title>
      <description>D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser’s approval rating has rebounded from last year’s decade-low marks, a Washington Post-Schar School poll finds, as residents’ concerns about crime decline — and worries about President Donald Trump and a GOP-controlled Congress’s incursions on the city’s autonomy emerge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a8a440-2e66-11f0-b866-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 12:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land is sinking under America’s largest cities. See whether yours is affected.</title>
      <description>The 28 most populous U.S. cities are sinking to some degree, threatening buildings, roads and rail lines, according to a new study.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">246a2730-2de6-11f0-9b38-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 21:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Buzzkill.’ ‘Frustrated.’ Five small-business leaders explain what Trump’s tariffs really mean for you.</title>
      <description>Makers of clothes, beer and more on what tariffs really mean for you</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">291d4ba1-2dbd-11f0-992f-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 16:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korea’s aging extreme divers could hold the key to treating chronic disease</title>
      <description>For generations, Jeju Island women have been diving to gather food from depths of up to 60 feet using only the bodies that genes and conditioning have given them. Now, an international team of researchers has found evidence of natural selection at work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49266641-2db1-11f0-bfd8-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 15:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2062cb31-2da3-11f0-9e3f-000a1ace0f27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 13:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces ‘immediate’ India-Pakistan ceasefire after four nights of escalating violence between the nuclear-armed neighbors</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said in a post online that an agreement was reached “after a long night of talks mediated by the United States.” The ceasefire was confirmed by Pakistan’s foreign minister and by Indian officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad3c6a0-2d9a-11f0-a9af-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 12:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan says it has struck military targets inside India, bringing the nuclear-armed rivals nearer to war</title>
      <description>Pakistan said early Saturday it had hit several Indian military sites, days after India launched its largest strikes inside Pakistan in decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a02d2940-2d3b-11f0-845d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 01:10:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress should raise debt limit by July to avoid default while lawmakers are away in August, Bessent says</title>
      <description>The warning from the treasury secretary gives Republicans a clear deadline for passing President Donald Trump's budget and tax bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61ed40a0-2d1f-11f0-a99b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 21:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 60 White South Africans expected to arrive at Dulles Airport next week as refugees under Trump executive order</title>
      <description>The Afrikaners are expected to arrive on a State Department-chartered plane Monday, with federal and Virginia officials preparing to receive them in a ceremonial news conference, according to documents and emails obtained by The Washington Post, as well as three government officials familiar with the preparations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e67a3460-2cfa-11f0-8e90-0000a1ace9d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 17:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My cheating ex wants to be involved in my pregnancy</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My cheating ex wants to be involved in my pregnancy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0707a70-2cf2-11f0-a6a1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 16:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.-area economy appears headed toward economic slump, experts warn</title>
      <description>Rising unemployment and a drop in spending are among several signs of a downturn in the region on par with the one that occurred during the pandemic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea6604a0-2ce6-11f0-b0ff-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 15:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neo-monarchist blogger Curtis Yarvin helped inspire DOGE. Now he scorns it.</title>
      <description>Silicon Valley's pro-authoritarian muse has influenced the likes of JD Vance and Peter Thiel. But he has come to think that Elon Musk's bureaucracy slashers have lost their way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9289a9f0-2cdf-11f0-a94c-0000a1ace4f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 14:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31e8dd90-2cdb-11f0-89ff-000a1ace99f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Supreme Court justice David Souter dies at 85. He favored judicial restraint during his time on the court.</title>
      <description>On the high court from 1990 to 2009, he saw his role as one of quiet resistance against excess and dramatic change. He supplied a key vote to uphold abortion rights in his early years on the court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">925cb540-2cd9-11f0-abaa-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 13:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Leo XIV. Trump taxes. Jeanine Pirro. India and Pakistan. El Salvador. Disaster tracker. Secret apartment. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c111b260-2cc4-11f0-bfde-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Fox News host Jeanine Pirro to replace Ed Martin as interim D.C. U.S. attorney</title>
      <description>Pirro served as a judge and district attorney in Westchester County, New York. She joined Fox News as a legal analyst in 2006 and currently is a co-host of the conservative-leaning talk show “The Five.” Pirro will replace Martin as interim U.S. attorney after GOP senators balked at his nomination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fd38470-2c60-11f0-9ee3-0000a1ace774</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 23:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department is investigating New York Attorney General Letitia James, who has targeted Trump</title>
      <description>The probe of mortgage records for a home that James and her niece purchased in Norfolk, Virginia, is the first known criminal investigation by the Trump administration of a law enforcement official who has taken action against the president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dc51bd0-2c50-11f0-880a-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 21:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acting FEMA head removed by Trump administration a day after saying the agency should not be abolished</title>
      <description>The administration replaced Cameron Hamilton as acting administrator of the embattled disaster response agency. President Donald Trump and Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem have publicly expressed they would like to eliminate FEMA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">835b37f1-2c4e-11f0-8fc6-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 20:53:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tells Republican lawmakers to raise taxes on the rich in ‘big, beautiful bill,’ rattling GOP amid delicate negotiations</title>
      <description>Congress is trying to extend 2017 tax cuts set to expire this year. President Donald Trump told House Speaker Mike Johnson this week to raise some tax rates, two people familiar with his position said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaed2fa0-2c42-11f0-97d1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 19:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Prevost, the first American pope, is ‘right out of Francis’s playbook.’ Here’s what to know about the Chicago native.</title>
      <description>The “Latin Yankee,” as he is known in Rome, fell so in love with Peru in the decades he spent there that he became a naturalized citizen. His predecessor, Francis, turned to him on repeated occasions. In picking the 69-year-old Prevost, the conclave looked past allegations that he had mishandled or failed to act on several sexual abuse cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c541000-2c38-11f0-b01e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Prevost becomes the first American pope. He will be known as Leo XIV.</title>
      <description>The conclave’s choice to succeed Pope Francis will lead more than a billion Catholics around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">298a1421-2c31-11f0-b158-0000a1acec85</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 17:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new pope has been chosen, white smoke over the Vatican proclaims. Follow our live coverage as we learn who was named.</title>
      <description>Cheers erupted and suspense built in the Vatican’s St. Peter’s Square as cardinals announced with clamor and smoke that a successor to Pope Francis had been named. The world will learn their choice when he appears on a balcony overlooking the square.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">594387f0-2c27-11f0-a35b-0000a1ace42c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will withdraw nomination of controversial D.C. U.S. attorney pick Ed Martin</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s decision to pull the nomination comes after Senate Republicans criticized Martin’s support for Jan. 6, 2021, riot defendants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d71b6a0-2c26-11f0-be70-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-time Trump meme coin buyers have seen their investments collapse</title>
      <description>Most of the nearly 67,000 novice investors who bought the president’s $TRUMP coin have seen their holdings tank, a Washington Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d782a50-2c22-11f0-888a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: What are the top 3 credit cards for travel? The ‘Points Guy’ and our reporter are taking your questions.</title>
      <description>The Points Guy founder Brian Kelly is answering your questions live with Washington Post reporter Natalie B. Compton just in time for the busy — and expensive — summer travel season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b9da8f0-2c1e-11f0-b00a-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 15:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘A classic misdirection’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebc069c1-2c10-11f0-9745-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most D.C. residents favor using city funds on a new NFL stadium, poll finds</title>
      <description>As the D.C. Council mulls a $3.7 billion plan to build a new Washington Commanders stadium and adjoining development on the banks of the Anacostia River, most D.C. residents are in favor of using city funds for the project, a stark change from opinions three years ago. A 55 percent majority of D.C. residents favor using District money to help finance the project on the RFK Stadium site, while 39 percent oppose the idea, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d93738f1-2c0c-11f0-a2b8-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 13:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ed Martin’s sinking prospects of becoming D.C. U.S. attorney echo his past setbacks, including public spats, lawsuits and fines</title>
      <description>Martin’s headlong style both fueled his rise through conservative politics and burned him, costing him jobs, tens of thousands of dollars in fines and court contempt citations. For now, he lacks enough support to win Senate confirmation because of his stances on the Jan. 6, 2021, riot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5776a840-2c08-11f0-bf02-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 12:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. trade deal. Deportation standoff. Conclave. Tyre Nichols. Columbia protests. Sinking cities. Candy shop drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9877a952-2bfb-11f0-9cf3-000a1ace685f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Trump is expected to announce a trade agreement with the United Kingdom on Thursday</title>
      <description>It wasn’t immediately clear whether the agreement would be detailed or simply serve as the framework for further talks. The agreement was a victory for British Prime Minister Keir Starmer, who visited the White House in February armed with charm and a signed invitation to a royal audience with King Charles III. British leaders have long sought to bolster economic ties to the United States to make up for the trade losses of their 2020 departure from the European Union.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fc97620-2bc1-11f0-ab2d-0000a1acedb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 04:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I’d like to see changes in my church that I am not optimistic will happen’: Four columnists on what the next pope should do</title>
      <description>As the world waits on the fabled white smoke from the Vatican City’s Sistine Chapel announcing a new pope has been chosen, we asked four Post columnists what the next leader of the Roman Catholic Church should do. Here are their thoughts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f9f7940-2b95-11f0-9793-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area</title>
      <description>Post food critic Tom Sietsema's top newcomers to the ever-evolving D.C. dining scene include a Middle Eastern gem, Mission-style burritos, a pair of New York imports and an ode to Afro-Caribbean cuisine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9536d20-2b8f-11f0-974c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 22:07:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread ICE visits leave D.C. restaurant owners, workers rattled and bracing for more uncertainty</title>
      <description>At least seven D.C. restaurants confirmed that Department of Homeland Security agents visited Tuesday and asked for I-9 forms to verify staff employment eligibility. "It's incredibly scary," one restaurant owner said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b087e670-2b80-11f0-a0ac-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 20:20:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds three former Memphis police officers not guilty in 2023 murder of Tyre Nichols</title>
      <description>Nichols was beaten to death after fleeing from a traffic stop in 2023. His case helped galvanize support for police reform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bb4f0a0-2b78-11f0-bcc3-0000a1ace8d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black smoke over Vatican signals no pope chosen on first day of conclave</title>
      <description>Cardinals did not select a new pope in their first secret ballot, a result indicated by billowing black smoke from the world's most watched chimney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">186cbc81-2b76-11f0-b810-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 19:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pushes nations to approve Elon Musk’s Starlink internet business amid tariff talks</title>
      <description>State Department documents indicate that some countries are turning to Musk’s company in hopes of striking a better deal on trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">526e6230-2b71-11f0-bd65-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Federal Reserve leaves interest rates unchanged amid growing concerns about Trump’s tariffs clouding the economic outlook</title>
      <description>While inflation has been falling, higher tariffs could drive up prices and dampen economic growth, which complicates the Fed's interest rate policy. Fed Chair Jerome H. Powell is expected talk about the economy’s path in a news conference at 2:30 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12fc0ab0-2b6e-11f0-a581-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice of America will carry programming from One America News, which is known for its right-wing slant</title>
      <description>Staffers at the government-funded broadcaster VOA condemned the announcement from Kari Lake, who is a senior adviser to the agency that oversees it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17f92710-2b5e-11f0-bf3b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants son’s partner to remove piercings for ‘fancy’ event</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants son’s partner to remove piercings for ‘fancy’ event</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9048c880-2b5c-11f0-9859-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 16:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conclave to elect the new pope has begun. Go inside with this guide to its ancient traditions and secretive rituals.</title>
      <description>Beneath the domes and walls of Vatican City, a quiet drama is unfolding. Cardinals from around the world will vote in the Sistine Chapel until one candidate wins a two-thirds majority to become the next leader of the Catholic Church.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a05436d0-2b5a-11f0-874a-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:47:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican ends challenge to N.C. Supreme Court race, clearing the way for the Democrat to be sworn in six months after she won</title>
      <description>The announcement ends a six-month legal saga and preserves the current makeup of the state Supreme Court, where Republicans hold a 5-2 advantage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b70ecb0-2b59-11f0-bc45-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Food critic Tom Sietsema just named the 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area. Ask him about his picks.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Food critic Tom Sietsema just named the 20 best new restaurants in the D.C. area. Ask him about his picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c54bc5d0-2b54-11f0-8244-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 15:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
