<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 14:02:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Coming out of retirement in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70372f30-84b0-11ef-bb2e-0000a1acec54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies threaten Deloitte contracts after employee shares JD Vance chats</title>
      <description>Republicans backing Donald Trump are threatening Deloitte, a consulting firm that is one of the federal government’s largest business partners, with the loss of billions of dollars in contracts because an employee shared messages from 2020 in which Vance, now the GOP vice-presidential nominee, criticized the then-president’s record. 

Ethics experts said the episode is a potentially ominous preview of how a second Trump administration might use the enormous power the federal government wields over private industry to punish political acts by individual workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f55d430-84a8-11ef-aec5-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oct. 7 anniversary. JD Vance. Supreme Court. Hurricane threat. Overdose deaths. AI videos. Better AC. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d153ed0-849b-11ef-b698-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine awarded to Victor Ambros and Gary Ruvkun for discovery of microRNA</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Monday for the discovery of microRNA, which play an important role in gene regulation and how organisms develop and function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78ff05a0-8494-11ef-91bc-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world needs a better AC. These researchers think they’ve found one.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post traveled to India to see how prototypes tackle some of the hottest, most humid conditions on Earth — and to gauge how much they could shrink air conditioning’s rapidly growing emissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0f7f6c0-842b-11ef-ba23-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 21:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c27bc80-83fc-11ef-8098-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 16:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Democrat is running a campaign she’s sure to lose. That’s the point.</title>
      <description>Kate Barr is waging a sure-to-lose campaign for a seat in the North Carolina legislature as a protest over gerrymandering, which has made elections uncompetitive in states nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fccbf010-83f3-11ef-88ff-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d880ef60-83e6-11ef-96b8-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 13:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanderbilt stuns top-ranked Alabama in an upset that shakes up the college football season</title>
      <description>The Commodores upset the Crimson Tide, 40-35, on Saturday in Nashville. It was their first victory in the series since 1984.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">782b2340-8375-11ef-a302-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 23:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel’s penetration of Hezbollah and Mossad’s lethal pager operation</title>
      <description>The devices that killed or maimed as many as 3,000 Hezbollah operatives on Sept. 17 were designed by the Israeli intelligence service and assembled in Israel. A two-step de-encryption procedure built into the pagers ensured that most users would be holding them with both hands when they detonated, according to officials familiar with the operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24e5fd90-8366-11ef-b3f6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump stages a dramatic return to the site of the Pa. assassination attempt with a rally featuring survivors and first responders</title>
      <description>The rally in Butler, Pa., will also include billionaire supporter Elon Musk and notably heavy security measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8665730-8351-11ef-a302-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 19:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A young doctor was struggling. His last words hold a warning about his profession: ‘There are other people at real risk here.’</title>
      <description>William Ballantyne West Jr., 33, died by suicide in his third year of ophthalmology surgical training at George Washington University. He left a note that his family sees as a call to action. Despite some progress, barriers persist in residency programs that keep doctors from seeking mental health care during a time when many need it most.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c9dc090-8344-11ef-a71c-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 18:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Mother-in-law hides her gay son’s husband from the extended family</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Mother-in-law hides her gay son’s husband from the extended family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69270a10-833b-11ef-a689-000a1ace2058</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desperate to find Grandma after Helene, a North Carolina family hit the road with bikes and chain saws</title>
      <description>After the storm tore through the state, Beth Holmes couldn’t get in touch with her grandmother. So she and her family set off on an expedition to find her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aca02d80-8322-11ef-9bba-0000a1ace647</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 14:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00561100-831f-11ef-a17e-0000a1ace321</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 13:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for two of Biden’s most ambitious efforts to address climate change and reduce pollution</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court on Friday refused to block new Biden administration rules requiring fossil-fuel-fired power plants to slash emissions of mercury and other toxic substances and oil and gas firms to curb methane, a potent greenhouse gas, from their operations.
The issues were two of three playing out on the Supreme Court’s emergency docket over a suite of Biden administration plans to clamp down on fossil fuels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04a52ed0-827a-11ef-bcbc-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 17:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: She got dressed up, but her mother said she looked ‘awful’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: She got dressed up, but her mother said she looked ‘awful’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef744551-826f-11ef-aaa4-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 16:44:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b20599f1-8254-11ef-b4f9-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 13:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 254,000 jobs in September, reflecting surprising growth in the labor market as consumers kept spending this summer</title>
      <description>The September report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics adds more evidence that the labor market is healthy enough to allow the Federal Reserve to lower interest rates more gradually.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27b39d30-824d-11ef-994e-0000a1ace637</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 12:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama. Tyre Nichols. Port strike. Israel. School shooting suspect. Helene damage. Plastic-eating bacteria. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb51ed0-823f-11ef-89aa-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.U.’s top court rules that member states must recognize legal changes to gender identity</title>
      <description>The European Court of Justice sided with Arian Mirzarafie-Ahi, a transgender man who sued his home country of Romania for refusing to accept the name and gender identity changes he initiated in Britain when it was part of the E.U.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb5b91f0-8231-11ef-a5c4-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 09:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tried to temper Israel’s impulses and keep a lid on the Gaza war. But at every turn, he’s been foiled.</title>
      <description>A conflict the White House once hoped to moderate has gone from “over the top” to out of control. And now the Middle East is on the verge of all-out war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b525ec30-81e5-11ef-8eb1-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2024 00:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A tiny fraction of the homes in places hit hardest by Helene had national flood insurance, according to a Washington Post analysis</title>
      <description>In the inland counties affected by the devastating storm, which has killed at least 213 people overall, only 0.8 percent of homes had national flood insurance as of Oct. 1. By contrast, 21 percent of homes in the coastal counties of the seven affected states had coverage, according to The Post’s analysis of data from the National Flood Insurance Program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00df2230-81e2-11ef-b5bc-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 23:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longshoremen agree to suspend strike until January, reopen East Coast and Gulf ports</title>
      <description>The union representing 45,000 dockworkers from Maine to Texas agreed to suspend their strike to allow negotiations to continue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c10aad1-81db-11ef-ba4b-000a1acebf35</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former officer convicted of violating Tyre Nichols’s civil rights in fatal beating; he and 2 others guilty of witness tampering</title>
      <description>During the three-week federal trial, jurors repeatedly watched video of the January 2023 beating captured on a surveillance camera and the officers’ body cameras. Five ex-officers were charged with civil rights violations and faced state murder charges; two of them earlier pleaded guilty in the federal case and testified for the prosecution at trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">763ea230-81d8-11ef-8a5f-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 22:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband has been lying for entire marriage about wanting kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband has been lying for entire marriage about wanting kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6d09c50-81a0-11ef-b9ff-000a1ace72d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 16:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The making of an alleged school shooter: Family interviews and private texts reveal years of missed warnings and neglect</title>
      <description>The spiraling path of the 14-year-old suspect in last month’s shooting at Apalachee High School in Georgia offers an extraordinary case study on the making of yet another young man accused of gunning down students in their classrooms and hallways. A Washington Post investigation reveals how, over three years, institutions charged with protecting children and the wider public encountered the suspect and his family in times of crisis but did not prevent the violence that would follow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab6fc3f0-819a-11ef-91a7-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 15:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Trump made a telling comment two months before Jan. 6, and 4 other takeaways from special counsel Jack Smith’s filing</title>
      <description>The filing includes more detailed evidence that Donald Trump knew his election fraud claims were baseless but that it didn’t matter. That reminder comes with the next election just weeks away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43269de1-8191-11ef-99e0-0000a1acef89</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 14:10:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A milestone birthday in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ba510b0-818c-11ef-bfc9-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 13:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Mile Island’s owner is seeking a federal loan guarantee to reopen the shuttered nuclear plant for its Microsoft AI deal</title>
      <description>The taxpayer-backed $1.6 billion loan could give Microsoft and Three Mile Island owner Constellation Energy a major boost in their unprecedented bid to steer all the power from a U.S. nuclear plant to a single company.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3e2b4b0-8186-11ef-891a-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 12:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump evidence. Campaign fact check. Beirut strike. Helene toll. Judge shooting. Extreme heat. Fruit fly brain. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8fb72f1-8176-11ef-a536-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. is a notoriously bleak city for dating. Netflix’s ‘Love Is Blind’ swiped right on it anyway.</title>
      <description>The hit reality show’s creator and its head of casting tell us what to expect from the seventh season, which premiered today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3477c30-8109-11ef-9ec1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 22:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith lays out new evidence to show Trump acted as a private citizen to try to block Biden’s 2020 victory</title>
      <description>The lengthy, much-anticipated filing unsealed Wednesday details President Donald Trump’s private interactions with Vice President Mike Pence, attorney Rudy Giuliani and other senior White House and GOP officials. It is a key part of Smith’s attempt to show that Trump can still face trial after the Supreme Court ruled he was immune from prosecution for official acts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bdc2f90-80ff-11ef-a2c6-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 20:43:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our post-debate chat is happening now: Why wasn’t there more live fact-checking? Ask our reporters your 2024 questions.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters Yvonne Wingett Sanchez and Cleve Wootson are answering your questions about the vice-presidential debate between Sen. JD Vance (R-Ohio) and Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz (D). Send in your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28d461b2-80e8-11ef-849a-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 18:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI, maker of ChatGPT, receives new funding that values the company at $157 billion</title>
      <description>OpenAI became one of the most valuable start-ups ever after investors committed $6.6 billion in new investment funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">619b8100-80e2-11ef-a821-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s ahead in the polls now? Our Post Pulse polling model provides daily updates with interactive charts and state-specific data.</title>
      <description>See who’s polling ahead in key swing states that could decide the election. Add this page to your saved stories for easy access now through Election Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b83c050-80e0-11ef-baa8-0000a1ace850</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 17:03:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Do you really need to cook ground beef in oil? Our food writers respond and answer your questions.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Do you really need to cook ground beef in oil? Our food writers respond and answer your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b845d00-80db-11ef-8844-0000a1acebfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend still ‘obsessed’ with ex — emotionally and financially</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend still ‘obsessed’ with ex — emotionally and financially</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f3b100-80d7-11ef-a1ad-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 16:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The average U.S. hurricane leads to more than 10,000 indirect deaths in the years after it makes landfall, study finds</title>
      <description>An analysis of U.S. hurricane data released Wednesday found that the average tropical cyclone leads to thousands of excess fatalities for more than a decade after it makes landfall. The finding — which is hundreds of times higher than official death estimates — highlights how communities are left poorer, sicker and more isolated years after the floodwaters recede.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a15bc4b0-80d5-11ef-849a-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reporter keeps asking about Caitlin Clark. Players want her banned.</title>
      <description>WNBA players have called for Christine Brennan, a USA Today columnist who is writing a book about Clark, to lose her playoff credentials. The dispute comes at a thrilling but tense moment for the league, as Black players report increased harassment from fans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">050f5050-80cf-11ef-85f5-0000a1ace225</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fiercely defended Ukrainian town falls to Russian forces as Ukraine’s east buckles under improved tactics, superior firepower</title>
      <description>In an arc of villages south of Pokrovsk, including the now-vanquished Vuhledar, battlefields that have been stagnant for two and a half years are showing more movement than ever — in Russia’s favor.|</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">095ceea0-80c6-11ef-84b7-000a1ace755c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re ‘trying hard not to suck’ at today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeb11c51-80c2-11ef-8d28-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 13:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who won the VP debate? Voters weigh in on how Vance and Walz performed.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post asked a group of uncommitted, swing-state voters in real time about their reactions to Tuesday’s debate. Regardless of how they plan to vote in November, they thought Sen. JD Vance (R-Ohio) performed better than Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz (D).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9e52810-80b7-11ef-aad3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 12:15:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vance-Walz debate. Trump campaign. Iran attacks Israel. Helene. Sean Combs lawsuits. John Amos. Fat Bear Week. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dbc88a0-80ad-11ef-b513-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: It was a remarkably civil affair, and other takeaways from the vice-presidential debate</title>
      <description>Gov. Tim Walz ended strong over Jan. 6 but struggled early, while Sen. J.D. Vance appeared confident and tried to blunt the GOP position on abortion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62813aa0-8075-11ef-85cc-0000a1ace421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 04:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More policy, fewer zingers: Vance, Walz spar on Middle East, border and more in debate. Follow our coverage for the second half.</title>
      <description>Republican JD Vance and Democrat Tim Walz introduce themselves on the national stage in the early-goings of the vice-presidential debate, while also having more in-depth discussions on Israel's war in Gaza and with Iran, climate change, immigration at the U.S. southern border, taxes and the economy than voters saw during presidential debates between Donald Trump and Joe Biden and Kamala Harris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a95f00-8061-11ef-a2ae-0000a1ace495</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'That is pure demagoguery': Follow along as 11 columnists discuss the VP debate</title>
      <description>'That is pure demagoguery': Follow along as 11 columnists discuss the VP debate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76e82af0-805f-11ef-8627-0000a1aceb7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance and Tim Walz to face off tonight in the only planned vice-presidential debate. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters provide news and analysis as Donald Trump and Kamala Harris’s running mates take the stage in New York for what could be the final big event ahead of November’s presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47087a31-8058-11ef-99ad-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding help to get sober is hard. In deep-red Kentucky, it’s even harder as a mom.</title>
      <description>The state is rocked by the opioid crisis and has imposed a near-total ban on abortion, meaning residents who become pregnant while grappling with addiction have few options.

With substance use factoring into half of the state’s maternal deaths, help extends only so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09d570e0-8040-11ef-8d0f-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 21:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Amos dies at 84. The ‘Good Times’ and ‘Roots’ actor risked his career to protest demeaning portrayals of Black characters.</title>
      <description>Amos, a running back turned actor, appeared in scores of TV shows, including as Gordy the weatherman on “The Mary Tyler Moore Show” and the adult Kunta Kinte on “Roots,” the landmark ABC miniseries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd092e31-8024-11ef-b41e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
