<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 07:03:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>California voters approve congressional map that boosts Democrats’ chances of winning as many as five more House seats, AP projects</title>
      <description>Voters approved a ballot measure pushed by Gov. Gavin Newsom (D), offsetting Texas’s move to redraw its own map in the GOP’s favor at President Donald Trump’s urging. The dueling moves are part of a national fight over redistricting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86024c00-b9fc-11f0-8080-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 04:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Jay Jones wins Virginia attorney general seat, AP projects, overcoming his text message scandal</title>
      <description>Jones, a former state delegate who vowed to fight Trump administration policies, won despite a scandal over violent text messages he sent in 2022 about a former GOP House speaker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4584d50-b9f4-11f0-985c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 03:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic socialist Zohran Mamdani wins New York mayoral race, defeating former governor Andrew Cuomo, AP projects</title>
      <description>Mamdani, 34, will be the first Muslim mayor of the nation’s largest city. He campaigned on tackling the city’s affordability crisis and has clashed with President Donald Trump and some fellow Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bd49970-b9f0-11f0-8080-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Mikie Sherrill wins New Jersey governor’s race, AP projects</title>
      <description>The congresswoman beat Republican Jack Ciattarelli in a closely watched election. New Jersey leans blue but shifted to the right last year and often has competitive contests for governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e79e1f60-b9ee-11f0-9b6f-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 02:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Ghazala Hashmi wins Virginia lieutenant governor seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>Hashmi, a state senator, will be the first Muslim and first South Asian to hold a statewide office in Virginia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">420e6931-b9e7-11f0-bb97-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Abigail Spanberger to become Virginia’s first female governor, AP projects</title>
      <description>The former congresswoman and ex-CIA officer has been a centrist Democrat, focusing on pragmatic issues — such as the economy and health care — during her campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0134fd10-b9e3-11f0-b97a-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 01:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow live: Races to decide New York mayor, Virginia and New Jersey governors, California redistricting and more are on the line</title>
      <description>The contests offer a snapshot of voter attitudes one year after President Donald Trump was elected to return to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05e99a90-b9da-11f0-8964-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPS plane crashes after takeoff at Louisville airport with three on board</title>
      <description>Video of the incident shows UPS Flight 2976 ablaze and flying at a low altitude shortly before crashing, producing a fiery explosion that sent a plume of black smoke into the air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81a2fe74-b9d9-11f0-9fc3-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 23:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Messages sent from the Trump administration suggest that furloughed workers may not be paid after the shutdown ends</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is sending notifications to federal staff suggesting only those who are working during the government shutdown will be paid when it ends, despite a 2019 law that guarantees pay to furloughed employees, too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96ad84c0-b9a2-11f0-a06f-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:20:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How long should you date someone who’s only ‘good on paper’?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How long should you date someone who’s only ‘good on paper’?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31143840-b9a0-11f0-9941-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real truth about the Tudor succession comes to light. Literally.</title>
      <description>The transition to the Stuart dynasty after Elizabeth I’s death was neither smooth nor peaceful.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9e9c90-b99e-11f0-b20f-0000a1ace732</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secretive donor circle that lifted JD Vance is now re-writing MAGA’s future</title>
      <description>Chris Buskirk put tech elites at the center of power in President Donald Trump’s Washington. His efforts are grounded in a controversial theory — an “aristocracy” is needed to move the country forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82d98570-b993-11f0-b1f7-0000a1ace987</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:32:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Election Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f13c1b10-b991-11f0-a2cd-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:21:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election Day. Dick Cheney. Inflation blame. Billionaire network. Israeli leak. Step count. Pokémon thefts. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4fdeeb1-b976-11f0-9ce1-0000a1aceff3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 12:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Cheney dies at 84. As vice president from 2001-2009, he set the nation’s course as none in his role had done before.</title>
      <description>After the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks, Republican Richard B. “Dick” Cheney  became chief architect of a “war on terrorism” that involved bypassing restrictions against torture and domestic espionage.

In his later years, he spoke out against the abuse of presidential power by Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">287b15c0-b976-11f0-8391-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 12:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What it’s like to cross an ocean on the only remaining passenger ship of its kind</title>
      <description>The Queen Mary 2 keeps a romantic age of transatlantic sailing alive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d77ba050-b924-11f0-9a94-000a1acec277</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 02:20:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest careers that have now vanished, by the numbers</title>
      <description>The Department of Data started spelunking through archaic occupations in search of disappearing jobs — but it turns out the best answer is more obvious than you think.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43567aa0-b918-11f0-ad2d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:50:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer, a far-right political activist, is now credentialed to cover the Pentagon</title>
      <description>The former congressional candidate has frustrated some in the Trump administration with her close ties to the president and her public criticism of high-ranking defense and national security officials she argues are disloyal — some of whom were dismissed soon after her rebukes. She joins a new cohort of right-wing media that have agreed to the Pentagon’s new press policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d31de62-b912-11f0-bfdc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diane Ladd, the Oscar-nominated, multifaceted character actress, dies at 89</title>
      <description>She received the highest praise for her performances in “Alice Doesn’t Live Here Anymore,” “Wild at Heart” and “Rambling Rose.” Her daughter Laura Dern followed her into acting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd6fa990-b8f7-11f0-8e2a-0000a1acedbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration says it is paying out half of November’s SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>The administration said that it will release enough funds to pay for a half-month’s worth of food assistance benefits in November, days after two courts ordered the U.S. Department of Agriculture to release the money to avoid forcing nearly 42 million Americans into food insecurity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f9c8fb0-b8df-11f0-8a0a-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She can’t unsee it now — she’s always wrong in her husband’s eyes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She can’t unsee it now — she’s always wrong in her husband’s eyes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b7de90-b8d7-11f0-9c1c-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani’s success is a warning, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>How did a socialist with almost no governing experience become New York’s mayoral frontrunner?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">364a5a80-b8d6-11f0-90a3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sales are down in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">720aec11-b8c2-11f0-8a0a-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change is supercharging extreme rainfall. See if you live in a hotspot.</title>
      <description>A Post investigation reveals where hidden rivers in the sky are making rainfall more dangerous worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c41be740-b8c0-11f0-99f1-0000a1ace309</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump polls. Zohran Mamdani. Shutdown impacts. Heavy rainfall. Melatonin study. Disappearing jobs. Pickleball noise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97ebbce0-b8ac-11f0-bf44-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickleball noise is annoying. We’ve figured out why — and how to fix it.</title>
      <description>The racket from some 70,000 pickleball courts across the United States has generated bitter fights. If we understand the sound, can we learn to ignore it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2282070-b83f-11f0-86ca-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters broadly disapprove of Trump, poll finds, but Democrats may not benefit</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll finds that most Americans disapprove of President Trump's handling of top issues, and a majority say he has gone too far in exercising his powers. But a year out from the 2026 midterm elections, there is little evidence that these negative impressions have accrued to the benefit of the Democratic Party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59ff5571-b822-11f0-9ed4-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb2adf00-b80d-11f0-b710-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dials up pressure on the Justice Department over the 2020 election</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is escalating demands to freshly scrutinize ballots from the 2020 election, raising tensions with administration officials who think their time is better spent examining voter lists for future elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0070c6a1-b80a-11f0-8caf-000a1ace96c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a43960-b7f8-11f0-9faf-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a young Thomas Jefferson’s plea to the King helped ignite America’s fight for independence</title>
      <description>In the summer of 1774, Jefferson retreated to Monticello and wrote a secret plea meant to avert disputes with the British — a document that instead helped set America on the path to independence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">addf4840-b7f4-11f0-9f35-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Los Angeles Dodgers win the World Series, beating the Toronto Blue Jays in Game 7 to repeat as champions</title>
      <description>The Dodgers were heavy favorites entering the series but were pushed to the limit by the Blue Jays. Los Angeles is the first team to win the World Series in consecutive seasons since the New York Yankees won three straight from 1998 to 2000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8011fc60-b7a3-11f0-aa2f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 04:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. mayor imposes citywide youth curfew after multiple teens arrested in Navy Yard on Halloween</title>
      <description>The incident was one of several in which large groups of teens caused disturbances in the city, the mayor said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7866bc50-b779-11f0-8ae8-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration tells Congress war law doesn’t apply to strikes against alleged drug traffickers in Latin America</title>
      <description>The Office of Legal Counsel told lawmakers that the War Powers Resolution, which requires Congress's approval for ongoing military conflict, does not apply here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42b0be50-b763-11f0-a73a-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After two years and eight doctors, the reason for her face twitching was surprisingly simple</title>
      <description>Doctors couldn’t explain why the right side of a Minnesota woman’s face kept twitching, as the convulsions turned the outgoing woman into a recluse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3894b80-b737-11f0-8868-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edf6c501-b729-11f0-aefd-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE and Border Patrol’s use of tear gas to disperse protesters injures, sickens and tests the law</title>
      <description>Federal immigration agents say chemical agents are needed to disperse violent protesters. But videos also show officers directly firing at people in aggressive and “unorthodox” ways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c21a2920-b726-11f0-befb-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to release billions in backup funds for SNAP, relied on by 42 million Americans</title>
      <description>In an oral ruling, Judge Jack McConnell said the Agriculture Department must distribute $5.5 billion in the contingency funds “timely, or as soon as possible, for the November 1 payments to be made.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab2b1eb0-b689-11f0-ba3a-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1f0f20-b67b-11f0-b765-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela pleads with Moscow for help as U.S. ramps up the pressure</title>
      <description>Documents show Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro drafted a letter asking Russia for missiles, radar and upgraded aircraft as U.S. forces amass in the Caribbean.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13aef4e0-b674-11f0-a3fa-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Police seek hundreds more officers amid Trump’s crime crackdown</title>
      <description>A hiring spree in the nation’s capital is part of a plan to become “the premier law enforcement agency in D.C.,” according to documents obtained by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de76f0c0-b66e-11f0-9bc0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio approves new congressional map giving Republicans a leg up in two more House seats</title>
      <description>The new map received rare bipartisan agreement because Republicans who control the state legislature did not want to risk a challenge from Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">587bbc40-b66d-11f0-8531-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My family emigrated from Vietnam. Halloween in America astonished me.</title>
      <description>Coming from a communist-run nation, I was baffled by glimpses of life in my new home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bbdbe20-b663-11f0-9319-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c3d8ec0-b65e-11f0-925f-0000a1ace1f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center ticket sales have plummeted since Trump takeover</title>
      <description>Nearly nine months into the president’s oversight, sales for orchestra, theater and dance performances are the worst they’ve been since the pandemic, according to a Washington Post analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f131e2f1-b651-11f0-8c36-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s actions. Shutdown impacts. Kennedy Center. National Guard. Former prince Andrew. Autism study. Fall back. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70712c0-b648-11f0-8c1a-0000a1ace1bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of science’s biggest dinosaur debates may finally be settled</title>
      <description>For decades, paleontologists debated whether fossils were of a young T. rex or a species called nanotyrannus. A new study settles it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4641a1-b5e8-11f0-a63b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid in pregnancy tied to autism and developmental issues, study says</title>
      <description>A study published in the journal Obstetrics and Gynecology analyzed more than 18,100 births in Massachusetts of children born to women who contracted the virus starting in the early months of the pandemic through some of 2021, before vaccines were widely available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56201510-b5d5-11f0-87e9-000a1ace2f48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified U.S. report finds hundreds of possible Israeli human rights violations</title>
      <description>The State Department’s watchdog says it will take years to review credible allegations against Israeli military units in Gaza, according to officials, raising doubts about future accountability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e581e0-b5ce-11f0-9dfb-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Charles III strips brother Andrew of prince title and orders him to vacate his home at Royal Lodge over Epstein scandal</title>
      <description>The move marks the latest setback for the embattled royal as the scandal over his ties to the convicted American sex offender Jeffrey Epstein continues to cast a long shadow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00223b34-b5ca-11f0-bccd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
