<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 02:14:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>They bought homes for under $1 million. Here’s what they learned.</title>
      <description>Last year, just over 4 million existing homes sold in the United States — the lowest number in nearly three decades, according to the National Association of Realtors. Nine households that bought real estate in the past year share how they navigated the buying process during these tumultuous times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9881be00-04eb-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among the 18 Trump allies indicted in Arizona this week: A senior counsel to the RNC’s election integrity team</title>
      <description>When conservative lawyer and media personality Christina Bobb became the latest member of Donald Trump’s inner circle to be charged for her alleged role in the effort to reverse the 2020 presidential election results, it became immediately clear she would not have to give up her day job with the Republican National Committee. Bobb’s indictment solidifies her identity as a dedicated Trump loyalist and potentially elevates her role within the RNC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb4b0850-04cb-11ef-8e47-0000a1acec20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A vegan cheese beat dairy in a big competition. Then the plot curdled.</title>
      <description>When Climax Foods’ plant-based blue cheese was named as a finalist in the Good Food awards, traditionalists were shaken. Its status was revoked as controversy fomented.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036318c0-04c1-11ef-b672-0000a1ace1b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for something to watch? These are the best new TV shows and series in 2024 so far.</title>
      <description>“Ripley,” “The Sympathizer,” “Shogun,” “Fallout,” “Elsbeth,” “Constellation” and “The Girls on the Bus” all make our critics’ evolving list of the year’s best TV shows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2fc4c20-04b7-11ef-af7a-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Elaine: After a traumatic birth, new mom can’t let go of debilitating fears</title>
      <description>Ask Elaine: After a traumatic birth, new mom can’t let go of debilitating fears</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e395adc0-04af-11ef-8376-0000a1acec1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to a man who threatened Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.): ‘You spread hatred, and you’re gonna pay for it’</title>
      <description>In a time of rising political anger, one man going through a mental health crisis threatened the congresswoman after seeing one of her political ads. Then came the consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1245b2c0-04a4-11ef-be41-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">433cd6b0-049a-11ef-a79b-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoring sight is now possible with gene therapy</title>
      <description>Several companies are experimenting with optogenetics to create a “bionic eye” that can restore sight in visually impaired people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53bbfa60-0414-11ef-bfdb-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia’s next war could be triggered by a rusting warship on a disputed reef</title>
      <description>In the South China Sea, tensions over competing claims by China and countries in Southeast Asia have grown more intense than at any time in recent years. The risk of armed confrontation increasingly hinges on China’s efforts to block the Philippines from resupplying the crew aboard a dilapidated navy ship intentionally grounded on a contested reef to establish it as a military outpost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7888a7a1-03f4-11ef-a7ba-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret meetings, social chatter: How the Columbia protest started a nationwide student revolt</title>
      <description>The day after dozens of pro-Palestinian protesters were arrested at Columbia, hundreds of students nationwide joined a Zoom to learn how they could start their own encampments. The coordination has led to what historians now call one of the most consequential student uprisings in recent times. Here’s how it unfolded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">501f8140-03e9-11ef-a36b-0000a1ace835</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most lopsided first round in NFL draft history made it clear: Offense rules, our analyst says</title>
      <description>When the NFL draft began Thursday night, the first 14 picks were offensive players. The 23 offensive players chosen in the first round shattered the previous mark of 19. The draft’s biggest takeaway: Even after a season in which scoring dropped, the NFL is doubling down on this era’s skew toward offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd3880b1-03de-11ef-b2da-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety regulators launch new review of whether Tesla did enough to fix Autopilot</title>
      <description>Tesla recalled 2 million cars with Autopilot in December to add warnings. Federal regulators are now questioning whether the remedy goes far enough. Autopilot can still be activated on roads with cross traffic or no center median, where The Post found at least eight serious or fatal crashes have occurred.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4612ea0-03d9-11ef-8ce6-0000a1ace289</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e37510-03d0-11ef-930f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump immunity. Student protests. Harvey Weinstein. Kenya flooding. NFL draft. Disinfectant. Loud cicadas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2229bb71-03bc-11ef-8033-0000a1ace586</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL draft: Chicago Bears select QB Caleb Williams first overall; Washington Commanders take QB Jayden Daniels. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The first two players chosen were both former Heisman Trophy-winning quarterbacks — Williams at USC and Daniels at LSU — and more quarterbacks are expected to follow. Follow our live coverage of the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">011f34d0-0364-11ef-9135-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Southern California cancels main commencement ceremony, citing new safety measure amid protests over Israel-Gaza war</title>
      <description>The university has also faced criticism after announcing earlier this month that it would not include a speech by its valedictorian, who is Muslim and pro-Palestinian, at the ceremony because of safety concerns. This week, more than 90 protesters were arrested after officers struggled to break up a demonstration on campus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40d58810-0344-11ef-9b78-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC restores net neutrality regulations that were repealed during the Trump administration</title>
      <description>The Federal Communications Commission voted 3-2 to reimpose rules first adopted in 2015 during the Obama administration. But the internet is different now, and some telecom executives are arguing that the advent of 5G requires additional exemptions, while others call such exemptions a loophole.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9292df0-032a-11ef-80b9-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems poised to reject Trump’s immunity claim in 2020 election case, in a way that further delays his D.C. trial</title>
      <description>During nearly three hours of oral argument, a majority of Supreme Court justices seemed to be looking for a way to provide narrow protections for a president’s core constitutional duties. But all seemed to agree a president is not shielded from prosecution for private conduct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80889511-0326-11ef-87c3-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why not get rid of email at work? Daniel Pink is answering your questions live.</title>
      <description>Daniel Pink is fielding your ‘Why Not?’ ideas and answering your questions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c154440-031f-11ef-bb2e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Can one spouse tell another to stop traveling so much for work?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Can one spouse tell another to stop traveling so much for work?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4794a0-031d-11ef-8fb8-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitian Prime Minister Ariel Henry resigns, a crucial step for new elections and U.N.-approved police deployment amid gang violence</title>
      <description>A transitional presidential council was sworn in on Thursday, and a government decree said Michel Patrick Boisvert would serve as interim prime minister. Boisvert has been leading the government since Henry left the country on a diplomatic trip in February.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">037301c0-0315-11ef-a94b-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.Y. court overturns Harvey Weinstein’s 2020 rape conviction and orders new trial — a shocking twist in a pivotal #MeToo case</title>
      <description>The New York Court of Appeals ruled the judge in Weinstein’s trial improperly allowed testimony about allegations that weren’t part of the case, according to the Associated Press. The former movie mogul will remain in prison on his 2022 California rape conviction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4a7c90-0309-11ef-a8ac-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court weighs if Trump is immune from prosecution on charges of trying to subvert the 2020 election. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The oral argument in Washington comes as Donald Trump is on trial in New York in the hush money case. The justices’ ruling on immunity will have a major impact in shaping presidential power and accountability for future occupants of the White House — and whether Trump will be tried on federal charges in D.C. before this year's election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14eaab40-0308-11ef-98c4-0000a1ace4c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Sucks to be you’ if you’re not on the train they're building in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">950589f0-0306-11ef-a0af-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100 pro-Palestinian protesters arrested near Emerson College in Boston; campus protests in Texas, California also broken up</title>
      <description>Protests spread at colleges across the country, with dozens of arrests at the University of Southern California and the University of Texas at Austin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e10d321-0305-11ef-9a82-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy grew at a 1.6% annualized rate in the first quarter, as consumer spending slowed</title>
      <description>New data from the U.S. Bureau of Economic Analysis shows gross domestic product remained solid, although consumer spending slowed as higher prices weighed on the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1da1ac41-0301-11ef-8a05-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New federal rules will slash air, water and climate pollution from U.S. power plants. Red states are certain to sue.</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency finalized an ambitious set of rules that will cut air pollution, water pollution and planet-warming emissions spewing from power plants across the country. The rules will crack down on releases of mercury, greenhouse emissions and other pollutants from power plants' smokestacks, waste dumps and wastewater discharges. Republican attorneys general are likely to challenge some or all of the regulations in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bdb6f30-02fc-11ef-8f1d-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 election charges. Abortion case. College arrests. Bird flu. Plastic polluters. NFL draft. Flight refunds. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f65b3b50-02f2-11ef-8b17-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Meadows, Rudy Giuliani, pro-Trump electors and other allies charged in Arizona 2020 election interference probe</title>
      <description>The indictments cap a year-long investigation by Arizona Attorney General Kris Mayes (D) into the unsuccessful attempt to keep Donald Trump in the White House after he lost the 2020 presidential election by trying to award Arizona’s electoral votes to Trump instead of Joe Biden, who won the state. Arizona is the fourth state, following Michigan, Georgia and Nevada, to seek charges against those who formed an alternate slate of presidential electors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ebc4380-0291-11ef-b16f-0000a1ace203</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen, preparing to take the stand against his ex-boss, says he’s reformed. Will America buy it?</title>
      <description>After years as Donald Trump’s bruising personal attorney, Cohen is a man on a quest for redemption. But as he prepares to serve as a linchpin in the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal case against the former president, America’s most famous ex-fixer remains a divisive figure — even among partisans on the Trump-loathing left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db0f1450-0281-11ef-a142-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-controlled Arizona House votes to repeal Civil War-era abortion ban. The measure now heads to the state Senate.</title>
      <description>Soon after Roe v. Wade was overturned, the 1864 law briefly took effect in the state, only to be blocked by the courts. Earlier this month, the Arizona Supreme Court revived it, inciting a national uproar and political panic among Republicans as 2024 elections loom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d38b20-0270-11ef-8445-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court conservatives seem skeptical that federal law can require hospitals to perform emergency abortions in states with bans</title>
      <description>The Biden administration has invoked the Emergency Medical Treatment and Labor Act to argue that the federal government can penalize hospitals that fail to provide emergency abortions in states with strict abortion bans. But conservative justices appeared skeptical the 40-year-old federal law — which requires hospitals that receive federal funds to stabilize or transfer all emergency patients regardless of their ability to pay — could be used to require abortions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd683fa1-0258-11ef-a199-0000a1acefff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd2a21c0-0257-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc16e20-0253-11ef-8cd8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have a radical democracy. Robert Kagan asks: Will Trump voters destroy it?</title>
      <description>We have a radical democracy. Will Trump voters destroy it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90ccc480-0251-11ef-8e5f-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. announces $1 billion Ukraine weapons package after Senate approves massive foreign aid bill</title>
      <description>The weapons package of artillery, ammunition and air-defense missiles restarts an expansive U.S. effort to sustain Ukraine’s embattled military as the war with Russia bleeds into its third year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9e35510-024c-11ef-b3dc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reggie Bush gets his Heisman Trophy back, more than a decade after the former USC running back was stripped of it</title>
      <description>Bush won the trophy in 2005 but forfeited it in 2010 after an NCAA investigation found he and his family had received gifts from a sports agent, and most of his college statistics were vacated. “We considered the enormous changes in college athletics over the last several years in deciding that now is the right time to reinstate the trophy for Reggie,” the Heisman Trust announced Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688c4280-024b-11ef-98d8-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court is hearing arguments on whether hospitals must provide emergency abortions in states with bans. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>At issue is a nearly 40-year-old federal law that requires hospitals that receive federal funds to stabilize or transfer all emergency patients, regardless of their ability to pay. The Biden administration invoked the Emergency Medical Treatment and Labor Act to argue that the federal government has the power to penalize hospitals that fail to provide emergency abortions even in states with strict bans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6030fe70-0244-11ef-a00b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘next-level’ find in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to even your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5f7cef1-023e-11ef-9f64-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid. Trump witness. Abortion case. Campus protests. Larry Nassar. Air pollution. Bionic eyes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce069fb0-0229-11ef-8521-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress passes bill that forces a sale or a ban of TikTok, the most significant threat yet to the app’s U.S. operations</title>
      <description>The legislation delivers a historic rebuke of the video-sharing platform’s Chinese ownership, culminating years of failed attempts to tackle the app’s alleged national security risks.

The Senate approved the measure as part of a sprawling funding package sending $95 billion in aid to Ukraine, some of which is structured as a loan, as well as help for Israel, Taiwan and humanitarian assistance.

President Biden is expected to sign the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff8d2340-01db-11ef-9ff1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA finds evidence of bird flu virus in grocery store milk but expresses confidence in safety of dairy supply</title>
      <description>The findings by the Food and Drug Administration do not necessarily suggest a threat to human health but indicate the avian flu virus is more widespread among dairy herds than previously thought. The agency is conducting further testing to definitively confirm that milk remains safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">577f4521-01bd-11ef-aaf2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump has become angrier and more isolated on Truth Social</title>
      <description>On his company’s social network, Donald Trump is offering followers an intimate view of what his second term could look like: isolated, vitriolic and vengeful. His following is diminished, but his posting has accelerated. He has traded combative tweets for even more belligerent screeds. And above all, he persists in spreading lies about his 2020 election loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c85c470-01ba-11ef-9a04-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla earnings sharply declined in first quarter, casting doubt on its recovery after weak sales, layoffs and recalls</title>
      <description>Tesla has fallen far from its days as a darling of Wall Street and is now battling a complex array of challenges that threaten its business outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce8d4730-01ad-11ef-9ff1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee passes bill to let teachers carry guns on campuses, a year after Nashville school shooting left six people dead</title>
      <description>The bill, approved by the state's GOP supermajority over protests by students and parents, is one of the most expansive pro-gun steps taken by the state since the Covenant School shooting in March 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95977af1-01ac-11ef-9d9f-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC bans noncompete agreements that restrict workers from switching employers within their industry</title>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission approved a rule that will bar employers from enforcing the clauses, which have been signed by millions of Americans. The rule is supposed to take effect after 180 days, though business groups have promised to challenge it in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6bab090-01a5-11ef-8df6-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. reaches $138.7M settlement with victims of former USA Gymnastics doctor Larry Nassar over FBI misconduct claims</title>
      <description>The agreement settles 139 claims brought over the department’s failure to investigate allegations that could have brought Nassar to justice sooner and prevented dozens of assaults. The settlement brings to a close the last major legal case over Nassar’s prolific abuses. Nassar, 60, is serving an effective life sentence for federal convictions relating to possession of child pornography, as well as state convictions for sexual assaults of patients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fb07790-0192-11ef-9cd1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent worries ‘beautiful’ 4-year-old hears too much about looks</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent worries ‘beautiful’ 4-year-old hears too much about looks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">976c3360-018a-11ef-b385-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 130 Israel-Gaza war protesters were arrested at NYU, police say. Columbia is offering hybrid classes amid demonstrations.</title>
      <description>Anti-war protests on college campuses are growing and continue to be met by police across the nation. More than 100 demonstrators were arrested at Columbia last week, and about 50 were arrested at Yale on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b7f2410-0185-11ef-a677-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s that buzzing in today’s On the Record?</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb5d080-0175-11ef-9b9c-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
