<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 01:28:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Worried about a recession? Here’s what to do with your 401(k), our personal finance columnist writes.</title>
      <description>If you’ve looked at your retirement portfolio lately, it’s likely you’re a bit seasick, Michelle Singletary writes. Don’t risk taking action that’s not in your best interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b21fb40-ff8d-11ef-a55b-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 22:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA moves to roll back dozens of Biden's environmental rules for electric vehicles, power plants, clean water and more</title>
      <description>EPA Administrator Lee Zeldin said the agency will begin the process of repealing and rewriting the regulations, including limits on greenhouse gas emissions from cars and coal plants. The announcement heralds a seismic shift in U.S. environmental policy, although the rulemaking processes could take months or even years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95843450-ff84-11ef-aced-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate pushes closer to government shutdown after Democrats spurn funding bill</title>
      <description>Senate Democrats say they are prepared to vote against the Republicans’ bill if lawmakers do not strike a deal by midnight Friday. Not enough Democrats support the bill to clear the 60-vote threshold needed to overcome a filibuster, Senate Minority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-New York) said on the Senate floor Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">186725f0-ff7e-11ef-b50d-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A document prepared for the Kremlin and reviewed by The Post lays out a hard-line negotiating position on Ukraine</title>
      <description>The document was written in February by an influential Moscow-based think tank close to Russia’s Federal Security Service and was obtained by a Western intelligence service. It says Russia should insist on recognition of its sovereignty over land it has occupied and calls for a further carve-up of Ukrainian territory through the creation of buffer zones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a448771-ff76-11ef-80f2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 19:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Effort to deport Columbia University student activist rests on Rubio’s decision, document shows, citing no other evidence</title>
      <description>A government document that details the civil charges against Mahmoud Khalil, an Algerian citizen and a prominent pro-Palestinian activist, does not include additional evidence from immigration officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61590f50-ff5e-11ef-be85-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security, under pressure from DOGE, weighs big cuts to phone services that 73 million rely on to access earned benefits</title>
      <description>The Social Security Administration is considering ending a phone program that helps with claims processing and is used by millions of elderly and disabled Americans. The change would disrupt the agency’s internal operations and threaten its ability to serve the public, current and former officials warned, just as DOGE is targeting the agency for across-the-board staff cuts of more than 12 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc4968c0-ff5b-11ef-942b-0000a1acef5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings were close till niece chose to spend Christmas with aunt</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings were close till niece chose to spend Christmas with aunt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">322495e0-ff5b-11ef-be85-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Is it okay to ask for changes on a chef’s tasting menu?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Is it okay to ask for changes on a chef’s tasting menu?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fee0400-ff53-11ef-aced-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 15:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Jeanne Shaheen (D-New Hampshire) won’t seek reelection in 2026, complicating Democrats’ path to retake control of the Senate</title>
      <description>Democrats, who lost control of the Senate in last year’s elections, will almost certainly need to prevail in New Hampshire to retake the chamber next year. Former Republican governor Chris Sununu is among those eyeing the competitive race to succeed Shaheen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8eb6060-ff4b-11ef-98b8-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 14:12:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling a senator a ‘traitor’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5009ae20-ff46-11ef-b132-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 13:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased more than expected in February as some prices declined ahead of new tariffs</title>
      <description>The February consumer price index report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics comes as a new round of tariffs take hold on steel and aluminum imports, which economists say could raise prices more, threatening to slow the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">873c5cb1-ff3e-11ef-9e21-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 12:35:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Ukraine deal. Federal job cuts. Shutdown bill. Measles outbreak. Southwest Airlines. S’mores. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b286fd1-ff31-11ef-9321-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.U. retaliates against Trump’s tariffs with its own, covering about $28 billion in U.S. products, as trade war escalates</title>
      <description>The European Union announced tariffs starting next month on U.S. exports, including on bourbon and motorcycles, and warned of further retaliation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf9abe30-ff2f-11ef-9e21-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 10:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department cuts nearly half of its workforce</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is reducing staff at the Education Department by nearly half, laying off more than 1,300 employees after nearly 600 accepted offers to leave voluntarily. The move advanced President Donald Trump's goal of diminishing — and eventually eliminating — the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e52a8ca0-fec8-11ef-b2dc-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 22:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill to avert government shutdown, sending it to Senate as 12:01 a.m. Saturday deadline nears</title>
      <description>The White House pushed Republicans to vote for the measure, helping to overcome lingering GOP concerns over the legislation. It will need Democratic votes to pass the Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3251cb0-fec2-11ef-bd03-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 21:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration slashes division in charge of 26,000 U.S. artworks</title>
      <description>The fate of holdings dating to before the Civil War is uncertain after the dismissal of most workers in the General Services Administration’s fine arts and preservation units.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83347c62-feb7-11ef-8d79-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 20:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTSB recommends ban on some helicopter flights near National Airport, citing ‘intolerable risk to aviation safety’</title>
      <description>The National Transportation Safety Board’s preliminary investigation into January’s midair collision of a helicopter and an American Airlines regional jet that killed 67 people led to an urgent recommendation that the helicopter flight corridor southeast of the airport be closed when the nearby runway is in use.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ab7f10-feac-11ef-8131-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 19:07:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to lift pause on Ukraine aid as Kyiv agrees to 30-day ceasefire proposal</title>
      <description>After hours of talks on Tuesday, officials from Washington and Kyiv issued a joint statement backing a 30-day pause in fighting. It was not immediately clear whether the offer would be acceptable to Moscow. But the mere fact that U.S. and Ukrainian officials were able to agree on the statement marked a significant improvement in relations following the row between the two nations’ presidents in the Oval Office and the abrupt suspension of U.S military support for Kyiv.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">818d1db0-fea6-11ef-a90c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend refuses to lock dead bolt, saying he ‘won’t live in fear</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend refuses to lock dead bolt, saying he ‘won’t live in fear</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fe08b80-fe93-11ef-a90c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 16:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Trump administration is reshaping reality by hiding data</title>
      <description>Sweeping statistical purges are part of a broader attempt to reinvent “truth.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8584f150-fe91-11ef-9230-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ordered a doubling of tariffs for Canadian steel and aluminum to 50 percent</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said in a Truth Social post on Tuesday that he wanted to increase steel and aluminum tariffs by another 25 percent specifically on Canada, in addition to the already planned 25 percent tariffs slated to go into effect for all steel and aluminum imports. The move is in response to Ontario Premier Doug Ford’s imposition of a new tax on electricity supplied to three U.S. states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3d01d60-fe87-11ef-b1db-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A midnight ride in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">205652b0-fe7d-11ef-9512-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 13:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock slump. Ukraine aid. Vaccine research. Rodrigo Duterte. Protester arrest. Wild weather. Dog freak-outs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d98ad2-fe67-11ef-8774-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Philippine president Rodrigo Duterte arrested on an International Criminal Court warrant accusing him of crimes against humanity</title>
      <description>Duterte is accused of the extrajudicial killings of thousands of people during his war on drugs. He served as president between 2016 and 2022, a period in which he openly advocated for executing alleged criminals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35338aa1-fe4a-11ef-8774-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 07:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Department moves to relax rules that held companies liable for killing birds, sparking alarm from conservationists</title>
      <description>The department’s acting chief lawyer suspended every legal opinion issued by the Biden administration, including one that subjected companies to penalties for accidentally killing birds through activities such as oil and gas drilling, wind energy production, mining or construction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9addd470-fe07-11ef-aaa2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 23:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms Lori Chavez-DeRemer as Labor Secretary with Democratic support. The Teamsters union lobbied for her selection.</title>
      <description>Chavez-DeRemer, a moderate conservative and a former Oregon congresswoman, is known for co-sponsoring the PRO Act, sweeping pro-union legislation associated with Democrats that aimed to make it easier for workers to unionize.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c06d24b0-fe03-11ef-b083-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 23:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH to terminate or limit grants related to vaccine hesitancy and acceptance</title>
      <description>The National Institutes of Health will cancel or cut back dozens of grants for research on why some people are reluctant to be vaccinated and how to increase acceptance of vaccines, according to an internal email obtained by The Post. The order covers more than 40 awards to researchers around the country seeking to understand why vaccine acceptance has declined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bcae700-fdf5-11ef-8c0d-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 21:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow, S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq sustain heavy losses a day after Trump declines to rule out possibility of recession</title>
      <description>The president said Sunday that it will take “a little time” before Americans see a payoff from his policies. His comments come as Wall Street has grown increasingly concerned that the Trump administration’s tariff policies could disrupt economic growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ad133f0-fdeb-11ef-9f8e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 20:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s ‘innately sour outlook on life’ weighs on his spouse</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s ‘innately sour outlook on life’ weighs on his spouse</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3671dba1-fdc9-11ef-9f50-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 16:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A decline for this insect in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">759da120-fdb4-11ef-8888-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 13:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. DOGE backlash. Mark Carney. Shutdown watch. Gaza war. Warm weather. Paul Revere. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2b45b30-fd9e-11ef-b1aa-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada’s Liberals pick former central banker Mark Carney to replace Prime Minister Justin Trudeau and counter Trump threats</title>
      <description>Carney, the former governor of the Bank of Canada and Bank of England, steered countries on both sides of the Atlantic through the turmoil of the global financial crisis and Britain’s break from the European Union. He takes over as Canada faces economic warfare and threats to its sovereignty from U.S. President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0350c80-fd39-11ef-a5e5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 22:56:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’ve sent a lot of Trump push notifications. Here’s what they signify about his efforts to reshape the country.</title>
      <description>In the six weeks after President Donald Trump’s inauguration, his administration put forward more than 80 executive orders. Here are the biggest executive actions from those weeks, as captured in Washington Post news alerts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e32df410-fd2d-11ef-8774-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 21:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declines to rule out a recession amid tariff impacts, after previously touting his trade policies</title>
      <description>Speaking to Maria Bartiromo on Fox News on Sunday, President Donald Trump acknowledged turbulence in the U.S. economy — a reversal from previously cheering that his policies would deliver quick victories to voters and businesses. It also stood in contrast to reassurances from his own advisers that no recession was in sight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83828e90-fd05-11ef-b51a-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 16:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cb3030-fd02-11ef-a9b7-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 16:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A breakthrough in age-reversal research could soon make the jump to human trials</title>
      <description>Cellular reprogramming is hailed by its supporters as the most promising scientific approach to improving human health spans and lifespans. But there have been serious side effects during experiments on animals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d9f3770-fcf4-11ef-9581-0000a1acef58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 14:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa5d581-fceb-11ef-aae9-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger at Elon Musk turns violent with molotov cocktails and gunfire at Tesla lots</title>
      <description>More than a dozen violent or destructive acts have been directed at Tesla facilities since President Donald Trump’s inauguration, according to court documents, surveillance photographs, police records and local media reports reviewed by The Washington Post. As Elon Musk has rocketed to prominence as Trump’s best-known supporter, his electric vehicle company has faltered. Its stock has fallen by more than 35 percent since the inauguration on Jan. 20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e561081-fc6e-11ef-8409-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DOGE Service gains access to sensitive income database maintained by child support agency</title>
      <description>A federal official told The Post that the group sought read-only access to the system “to reduce waste, fraud and abuse.” The government database — created to help enforce child support payments — contains substantial amounts of personal income data linked to nearly all U.S. workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3831a471-fc52-11ef-8ef0-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department removes key national security staff as part of purge</title>
      <description>At least three officials from the National Security Division were transferred, amounting to a gutting of leadership in the highly sensitive section, which is charged with working with the FBI and other intelligence agencies to protect the nation from threats. Their removal is part of a bigger culling of senior career officials at the Justice Department under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82d584c0-fc4c-11ef-bd5f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 18:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans unveil another extension to avert government shutdown until Sept. 30, but it’s not clear if they have the votes</title>
      <description>The continuing resolution unveiled Saturday would stave off a politically costly shutdown. But it would also mean that Republicans, who control both chambers of Congress and the White House, would largely keep funding set by President Joe Biden last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b797d51-fc48-11ef-bd5f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I love my partner, but I also want to focus on my dreams</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I love my partner, but I also want to focus on my dreams</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">602117b0-fc41-11ef-a2e0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 17:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you remember the first week of the pandemic? Kate Cohen takes us into covid’s great forgetting.</title>
      <description>In coronavirus, we have discovered a memory-resistant strain of pandemics, Cohen writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1e946e0-fc3b-11ef-a062-0000a1ace277</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock forgot one of its wildest front men. He’s got a story to tell.</title>
      <description>Peter Wolf befriended music legends, married a movie star and led the J. Geils Band. His new memoir reminds us: He was there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2de8b50-fc32-11ef-93cb-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 15:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a8491a0-fc2a-11ef-9d04-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 14:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Justice Department drops landmark case against a synthetic rubber facility Biden said was an ‘imminent’ health threat</title>
      <description>The lawsuit, filed under the Biden administration, accused a plant in LaPlace, Louisiana, of releasing unsafe levels of the likely carcinogen chloroprene. Republicans say the plant provides critical jobs and that the pollution concerns are overblown, but environmental and public health advocates say residents face elevated cancer risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b829d10-fbb6-11ef-852d-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 00:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina carries out nation’s first firing squad execution in 15 years</title>
      <description>Brad Sigmon, who was convicted in a 2001 double murder, chose the firing squad method after autopsies from previous executions raised concerns over the state’s supply of lethal injection drug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45c63180-fbaf-11ef-824f-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A top arms firm made at least $120 million from what the U.N. calls the world’s worst humanitarian catastrophe, records reveal</title>
      <description>A trove of documents, phone intercepts and other communications provided to The Post show how Turkey’s largest defense company funneled $120 million worth of drones and munitions to the Sudanese army engulfed in a brutal civil war despite a web of international sanctions — providing a rare window into the murky world of wartime dealmaking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa719c90-fba6-11ef-8a38-0000a1acec82</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Hackman likely died of a cardiovascular issue days after his wife died of a rare virus, officials said</title>
      <description>Hackman, 95, probably died from a combination of high blood pressure and extensive heart disease, and Betsy Arakawa, 65, seems to have died of hantavirus pulmonary syndrome, a virus that infects the lungs and is usually contracted from rodent excrement, officials said Friday at a news conference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44aaad30-fba0-11ef-93cb-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Army Corps of Engineers knew Trump order would waste California reservoir water, memo shows</title>
      <description>A memo obtained by The Post shows federal officials rushed ahead with a plan to discharge Central Valley irrigation water in January, following a White House directive in the wake of catastrophic wildfires in Los Angeles. An Army Corps colonel wrote that officials knew the water was unlikely to reach Southern California, as President Donald Trump had promised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8760f1a0-fb8e-11ef-85c0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
