<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:02:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will pay $24.5 million to settle Trump lawsuit over company’s decision in 2021 to remove his account after Jan. 6 attack</title>
      <description>The agreement says that President Donald Trump has directed YouTube to contribute $22 million of the settlement to help construct the new White House ballroom. The rest of the money will go to a handful of other plaintiffs who accused YouTube of censoring them. The settlement follows similar deals earlier this year with social platforms Meta and X, which also suspended or blocked Trump’s accounts after the Jan. 6, 2021, attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b74cbe00-9d80-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu agrees to Trump peace deal. If Hamas refuses, Trump offers Israel full support to keep fighting.</title>
      <description>The plan, which is subject to approval by Hamas, would require an immediate ceasefire as well as the release of all remaining Israeli hostages within 72 hours of both sides agreeing to the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82d0ab0-9d66-11f0-a9a2-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding for federal agencies expires tomorrow night. Here's how this potential shutdown may differ from previous ones.</title>
      <description>Broad swaths of the federal government — from national parks to small business loans to taxpayer services — could go offline this week unless lawmakers and President Donald Trump strike a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c70b8830-9d58-11f0-9a38-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26144d41-9d4e-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7d13c70-9d48-11f0-af6a-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing work from this platform in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4352b60-9d38-11f0-a4a3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church shooting. Government shutdown. Military meeting. Portland troops. Gaza plan. Tropical Storm. Bad Bunny. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71504eb0-9d23-11f0-a9d5-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe retains the Ryder Cup, holding off the United States at Bethpage Black</title>
      <description>The European team secured the trophy Sunday on Long Island, claiming the Ryder Cup on U.S. soil for the first time since 2012. The Americans fell into a massive hole Friday and Saturday and could not recover despite a strong Sunday surge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7f1f530-9cb0-11f0-a752-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Mayor Eric Adams says he is ending his reelection bid</title>
      <description>The incumbent has faced pressure — particularly from the Trump administration — to quit his bid and coalesce more support around former New York governor Andrew M. Cuomo. Cuomo is running as an independent candidate against the Republican nominee Curtis Sliwa and the Democratic nominee and front-runner Zohran Mamdani.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cc9fe72-9c95-11f0-9a95-0000a1ace037</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 person killed, several injured in shooting at Mormon church in Michigan, police say. The suspect is also dead.</title>
      <description>A local police chief said a man rammed a vehicle through the front doors of a Mormon church in Grand Blanc, Michigan, before opening fire. Officials did not identify the suspect by name or describe a motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c594620-9c92-11f0-8d94-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59aef620-9c84-11f0-9563-0000a1aceff4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to attend gathering of top generals, upending last-minute plans</title>
      <description>Hundreds of top military officers and staff have been summoned to Virginia on short notice for a speech by Pete Hegseth. President Donald Trump decided this weekend to attend the meeting, adding new security concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f047600-9c78-11f0-a2ec-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4a7b5a0-9c6f-11f0-9f1d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considers funding advantage for colleges that align with Trump policies</title>
      <description>The proposal could transform the government’s vast research funding operation, which has long awarded university grants based on scientific merit. Officials hope to launch it within a few months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f762110-9c6c-11f0-a86a-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration's 21-point proposal leaves door open for a Palestinian state</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's 21-point plan, which was obtained by The Washington Post, outlines an agreement for Hamas disarmament, an international security force and a “Trump development plan” to rebuild the shattered enclave. But Israel might balk at some proposals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fe95050-9c06-11f0-a056-0000a1ace1f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump deploys troops to Portland, authorizing ‘full force’ if necessary</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump announced Saturday that he was sending troops to Portland, Oregon, and to immigration detention facilities around the country, escalating a campaign to use the U.S. military against Americans that has little modern precedent. It was not immediately clear whether Trump was ordering solely a National Guard deployment or a broader military operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f817c80-9bb3-11f0-9063-0000a1aced1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service at ‘breaking point’ as storm approaches</title>
      <description>Staffing cuts under the Trump administration mean forecasters are struggling to maintain normal operations just as wildfires ramp up in the West and the Atlantic hurricane season peaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd261980-9baf-11f0-8bee-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18331fa0-9ba8-11f0-916b-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“I went nose-to-nose with a mountain lion. It was scary — and magical,” Post columnist writes.</title>
      <description>Mountain lions used to range across the entire continental U.S., but now they are limited to the west coast. Returning these carnivores east of the Mississippi could help maintain entire ecosystems by keeping animals lower down the food chain in check, limiting invasive species, reducing fire danger, boosting biodiversity and even potentially combating climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3054c1e0-9b2d-11f0-b3ee-000a1ace5879</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexstar stations will join Sinclair in broadcasting Jimmy Kimmel again, bringing him back to his former full audience</title>
      <description>Kimmel's show was pulled off the air by ABC following comments the late-night host made on the killing of Charlie Kirk, but was restored on Tuesday, while Nexstar and Sinclair stations continued to boycott the program until today. The reinstating of Kimmel's show to Nexstar and Sinclair stations brings him back to his former audience following the controversy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29fa65a0-9b20-11f0-9fb7-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for Trump administration to freeze billions in foreign aid for now</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a preliminary injunction from a federal judge who found the president had usurped Congress’s power of the purse by refusing to spend roughly $4 billion it had budgeted for food, medicine and development around the world. The ruling is a victory for the president’s push to exert greater control over federal spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad18eec1-9b1b-11f0-a3c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinclair will bring Jimmy Kimmel back to its ABC affiliate stations, ending boycott that began after his Charlie Kirk comments</title>
      <description>Sinclair Broadcast Group will end its boycott of the late-night talk show this evening in roughly 30 markets, including D.C. This move comes more than a week after Kimmel’s comments about the shooting of Kirk angered supporters of the conservative activist and following ABC reinstating the program Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed9a78e0-9b09-11f0-9d7f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details emerge about Pete Hegseth’s unusual order to gather top generals and admirals for ‘warrior ethos’ speech</title>
      <description>The defense secretary has summoned hundreds of top military brass to fly in from around the world for what is planned as a short address on the “warrior ethos,” according to multiple people familiar with the order to gather in-person at the Quantico Marine Corps base in Virginia on Tuesday. The Pentagon has refused to comment on the nature of the meeting, alarming and confusing top military officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbb3a660-9b02-11f0-b748-000a1acef2b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: We visited my in-laws. Their ‘lousy hosting’ was insulting.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: We visited my in-laws. Their ‘lousy hosting’ was insulting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e2feab0-9afa-11f0-aca1-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Barnett dies at 79. The Washington lawyer was a consummate political insider, with clients on both sides of the aisle.</title>
      <description>Barnett, a partner at Williams &amp; Connolly, represented corporations as well as public officials, many of whom he helped transition into the private sector.

He served as Hillary Clinton’s personal attorney beginning in 1992 and represented clients including Washington Post journalist Bob Woodward, former vice president Dan Quayle and Democratic strategist James Carville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56b8fa0-9aee-11f0-9fb7-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager. It’s your weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73189221-9adf-11f0-b3c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After U.S. strikes, Iran is increasing work at a mysterious underground site, according to a Post review of satellite imagery</title>
      <description>The work is at a site known as Pickaxe Mountain, where since 2020, Iranian engineers have been tunneling deep into the Zagros mountain range — about a mile south of the nuclear complex at Natanz, which was a target of U.S. bombing strikes in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5ad39e0-9ad0-11f0-b955-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Comey. New tariffs. Pete Hegseth. Iran nuclear site. Amazon refund. Tropical Storm Humberto. Ancient human. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e80bca1-9ac8-11f0-be6e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces new tariffs on trucks, furniture and pharmaceuticals</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said pharmaceutical products may face tariff rates of up to 100 percent, upholstered furniture 30 percent and heavy trucks 25 percent starting Oct. 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c82f0e0-9a79-11f0-a898-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 01:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James Comey indicted amid Trump push to prosecute foes</title>
      <description>Comey is charged with making a false statement to Congress and with obstructing Congress.
A federal grand jury declined to indict him on a third count sought by prosecutors. The charges involve the FBI's investigation of Russia's efforts to interfere with the 2016 election and his testimony before the Senate Judiciary Committee in September 2020.  He has denied wrongdoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f11a11b6-9a64-11f0-91d0-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 must-watch movies, 7 bingeable shows and more works of art that define D.C.</title>
      <description>Writers at The Washington Post spent months collecting the essential cultural artifacts of D.C., both the federal city and the place where people actually live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cde6f761-9a5c-11f0-9b5b-0000a1ace06c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 22:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs order advancing TikTok deal to create U.S. spinoff, pushing app into hands of some of his wealthiest allies</title>
      <description>The deal will allow TikTok to stay online in the United States after Congress passed a law demanding that its owner, the Chinese tech giant ByteDance, sell the popular video app or have it banned nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ea0f5f0-9a52-11f0-9965-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooter in Dallas attack intended to harm ICE agents and planned attack for months, officials say, citing notes left behind</title>
      <description>Notes found at the shooter’s home indicated he acted alone and “wanted to cause terror,” authorities said. The attack killed one detainee and critically wounded two others before the gunman fatally shot himself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88147410-9a48-11f0-9e7b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon will refund $1.5 billion to Prime subscribers as part of $2.5 billion settlement of FTC’s claims that it tricked users</title>
      <description>The refunds are part of a settlement with the Federal Trade Commission over allegations that Amazon tricked people into signing up for the shipping service and made it difficult to cancel. The e-commerce giant must also pay a $1 billion fine, making the total $2.5 billion settlement one of the largest in U.S. history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb1c54c0-9a2c-11f0-abe9-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unemployed husband and his yard projects are both in the weeds</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unemployed husband and his yard projects are both in the weeds</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a407e0-9a28-11f0-9709-0000a1ace520</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth orders rare, urgent meeting of hundreds of generals and admirals in Virginia without a stated reason, sowing alarm</title>
      <description>The Pentagon has summoned military officials from around the world for a gathering in Virginia. Even top generals and their staffs don’t know the reason for the meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8680c010-9a19-11f0-8756-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:11:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A price hike in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your daily points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">086eade0-9a14-11f0-9b99-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House budget office instructs agencies to prep for mass layoffs if the government shuts down</title>
      <description>The memo directs agencies to consider firing employees working on any program that is not funded by another law, such as Republicans’ One Big Beautiful Bill Act, and which does not align with the president’s priorities.

Government funding will run out next week if Congress doesn't act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f6a4441-9a02-11f0-b176-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Comey. ICE shooting. Tylenol pushback. FEMA delay. Kamala Harris. Huntington’s disease. Space weather. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6aaa360-99fe-11f0-8fda-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She shattered her elbow and ended up with a $97,000 bill</title>
      <description>Deborah Buttgereit struggled to afford health coverage after her husband’s death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">786c8090-999c-11f0-b7aa-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump should fix the U.N., not just grandstand, John Bolton writes</title>
      <description>Rhetorical digs won’t improve an institution in need of serious repair, Bolton writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35d40e10-9992-11f0-94e7-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department will seek to indict former FBI director James B. Comey, fulfilling a demand from Trump</title>
      <description>After the U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Virginia resigned under pressure, President Donald Trump replaced him with a White House aide and demanded that Attorney General Pam Bondi seek criminal charges against Comey. Virginia prosecutors plan to ask a grand jury in Richmond to indict him on allegations that he lied to Congress, people familiar with the matter say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5436060-998a-11f0-ae86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, the world’s largest greenhouse gas emitter, pledges its first-ever reduction target</title>
      <description>China committed to reducing its greenhouse gas emissions by 7 percent to 10 percent over the next decade. Climate experts widely described China’s commitment as insufficient and said they hoped the country would out-perform its new target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c9f05a0-9981-11f0-b9e5-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationals to name Paul Toboni as head of baseball operations, tasking him with Washington’s teetering rebuild</title>
      <description>Toboni, 35, arrives in D.C. from the Boston Red Sox, where he helped oversee a stellar draft and player development system. The decision, confirmed by two people familiar with the situation, comes after the Nationals fired longtime general manager Mike Rizzo and manager Dave Martinez in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed726650-997b-11f0-8a51-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Texas flooded, key staff say FEMA’s leader could not be reached — part of a broader pattern of inaccessibility</title>
      <description>After the deadly July floods in Texas, key Federal Emergency Management Agency staff members say they could not reach acting administrator David Richardson for a period of roughly 24 hours as they scrambled to coordinate a response. The Washington Post reviewed internal records that support current and former FEMA officials’ claims that Richardson is frequently inaccessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2922d801-9978-11f0-8187-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Kimmel and the upside of ignoring big-government coercion</title>
      <description>Trump, Kimmel and the upside of ignoring big-government coercion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8205e130-9967-11f0-8fc6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Planner is told to ‘chill’ when family’s lateness ruins plans</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Planner is told to ‘chill’ when family’s lateness ruins plans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb7c490-995f-11f0-a976-0000a1ace7dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-ICE messaging was found on rounds in Dallas ICE facility shooting that killed 1 person and injured 2, officials say</title>
      <description>No Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers were injured in the shooting, an ICE official said at a news conference. The shooter is also dead, officials say. The FBI is investigating the attack as an “act of targeted violence,” a Dallas special agent said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40da88b0-995c-11f0-8749-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not allowing a ‘shopping spree’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d3d09f0-994b-11f0-acfb-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark, hoping to reconcile, will apologize to Greenland over forced contraception</title>
      <description>Danish Prime Minister Mette Frederiksen is scheduled to formally apologize for forced contraception in Greenland. The public apology in Greenland’s capital comes as Denmark aims to repair colonial wounds amid attention from U.S. President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">798bb760-9948-11f0-83e6-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
