<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 05:22:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>At 82, he’s as fit as a 20-year-old. His body holds clues to healthy aging.</title>
      <description>Scientists are studying Juan López García, a world-record-holding ultramarathoner, to learn how we can stay healthy as we age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bac71da0-021b-11f1-b053-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 22:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for California voting map that bolsters Democrats</title>
      <description>The ruling is a major victory for the party as it seeks to offset a nationwide push by Republicans and Trump to redraw congressional maps to gain an advantage in this year’s midterm elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1af5040-0201-11f1-8c8f-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 19:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An album of the year winner in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47879940-01ea-11f1-8c8f-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 16:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border czar Tom Homan says 700 ICE and CBP officers are leaving Minneapolis</title>
      <description>The withdrawal decreases the federal footprint from about 3,000 agents to 2,300 — a significant scaling back but still much higher than the 80 who were in the Minneapolis area before Operation Metro Surge began Dec. 1, according to court records. The reduction in officers is effective immediately, he said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">482c2990-01dd-11f1-af87-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 15:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown reprieve. Iranian drone. Columbus statue. Renée Good. Housing crisis. Super-ager. Best in show. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00d17940-01c1-11f1-b4a8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 6 of America’s oldest restaurants have lived on for over a century</title>
      <description>At a time of great change in the restaurant industry — the world, actually — Tom Sietsema wanted to learn not just how these places have survived, but also how they thrive. As different as these six restaurants are, and despite their hardships, they share common threads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cec00f0-0154-11f1-91f9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 22:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to end government shutdown, buy time for ICE talks</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security will be funded through Feb. 13 to allow for bipartisan negotiations over immigration enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">242cf7d0-0134-11f1-9396-0000a1ace22c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 19:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. shoots down suspected Iranian drone that approached aircraft carrier USS Abraham Lincoln</title>
      <description>White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt said the drone was “acting aggressively” when it approached the carrier, prompting commanders to order it shot down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69ec86d0-0131-11f1-ac6a-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 18:51:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon warns Scouts to restore ‘core values’ or lose military support</title>
      <description>The relationship dates back decades, but Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has criticized the organization for allowing girls to join and changing its name from Boy Scouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e4dbf00-0127-11f1-9690-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Drop ‘snarky’ colleague from trip, or will the fallout be worse?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Drop ‘snarky’ colleague from trip, or will the fallout be worse?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e545641-0122-11f1-a75e-000a1ace03d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 17:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How millions of everyday investors are getting a tax break</title>
      <description>A watershed change by the SEC offers American savers a way to dodge the mutual fund surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9172b1f1-0115-11f1-ac34-0000a1ace8c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 15:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new location in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0b68031-010f-11f1-baa2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney announces Josh D’Amaro to succeed Bob Iger as CEO</title>
      <description>Iger returned in 2022 for a second stint as chief executive. D'Amaro currently leads Disney’s parks and resorts division.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cea4800-010c-11f1-aadd-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 14:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security is targeting Americans with a secretive legal weapon</title>
      <description>Under President Donald Trump, the Department of Homeland Security has weaponized administrative subpoenas to attack free speech, according to privacy and civil rights groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15c85950-0102-11f1-8111-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 13:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election powers. Epstein files. Measles cases. Kennedy Center. Iran talks. AI social network. Stair climbing. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94e1050-00f7-11f1-a748-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 11:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A bishop issued an edict to stand during Communion. The backlash speaks to a broader fight among U.S. Catholics.</title>
      <description>Charlotte’s bishop, Michael Martin, decreed parishioners could no longer use kneelers and altar rails during the sacrament. Then 31 of the diocese’s 147 active priests sent a letter to the Vatican questioning their boss’s authority on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e450050-009b-11f1-b980-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2026 00:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President says he's not ripping down the building, but some board members were blindsided by his proposal</title>
      <description>When asked Monday by reporters whether he would demolish the building, President Donald Trump said, “I’m not ripping it down. I’ll be using the steel. ... We’re using some of the marble and some of the marble comes down.” The center’s staff learned of the planned closure Sunday through Trump's social media post. They received no official communication until the center’s president, Richard Grenell, later sent a copy of Trump’s Truth Social announcement to all employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c302b0-0090-11f1-9a3f-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 23:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brendan Banfield found guilty of murdering wife in plot with au pair</title>
      <description>The Virginia man accused of plotting with the family’s au pair to frame a stranger as his wife’s killer was found guilty of aggravated murder in the 2023 killings of Christine Banfield and Joseph Ryan. He was the last witness to testify in his own double murder trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e3f1d20-0084-11f1-9551-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 22:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department demotes Ed Martin, stripping Trump ally of most authority</title>
      <description>Top Justice Department officials have stripped Martin of the bulk of his expansive responsibilities, leaving him on the sidelines of many of the controversial investigations he has championed, according to two people familiar with the personnel move. Martin will continue to serve as the department’s pardon attorney but will no longer work at its headquarters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">075b1140-006d-11f1-9551-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and India seal trade deal, Trump says, after months of tensions</title>
      <description>The agreement calls for Washington to lower its 25 percent tariff on goods imported from India to 18 percent, with India reducing its tariffs on U.S. goods to zero, according to President Donald Trump. It is unclear if the additional 25 percent tariff Trump levied on New Delhi for its purchases of Russian oil in August will remain, though the president said Prime Minister Narendra Modi has also agreed to to stop “buying Russian Oil.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88c2eab1-005d-11f1-85e5-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:35:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Caring for mom with dementia dredges up memories of childhood abuse</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Caring for mom with dementia dredges up memories of childhood abuse</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0fd9300-0059-11f1-b644-0000a1ace740</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 17:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Democratic win in Texas was shocking, except for this</title>
      <description>The midterm implications for Republicans could be less dire than they appear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d21289d1-0050-11f1-9de2-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 16:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insiders sounded alarms about Elon Musk’s Grok. Then the chatbot exploded with sexual content.</title>
      <description>Under pressure to boost its popularity, Musk’s artificial intelligence start-up xAI loosened its guardrails and relaxed controls on sexual content, setting off internal concern.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c2eb210-0048-11f1-a430-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 15:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new addition to the National Film Registry in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c33eaef1-0043-11f1-8e21-0000a1ace599</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 14:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most important sound at this year’s Grammys? It was free speech, our critic writes.</title>
      <description>With trophies in hand, Bad Bunny, Billie Eilish and SZA spoke out against ICE during an awards show where the musical performances felt secondary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">100297d0-0038-11f1-b03e-000a1aced031</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center. Government shutdown. ICE detentions. Dollar value. Epstein files. Grammys. Longevity tip. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf562e0-002e-11f1-a8b5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bad Bunny wins album of the year at the Grammy Awards while Kendrick Lamar, Billie Eilish and Olivia Dean notch big wins</title>
      <description>The ceremony occasionally verged into politics, with several artists criticizing the Trump administration’s actions against immigrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1de7b110-fff1-11f0-9b9d-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 04:39:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will the Grammys belong to Kendrick Lamar, Lady Gaga or KPop Demon Hunters? Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Sabrina Carpenter, Bad Bunny, Leon Bridges also lead in nominations on music's biggest night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40c7b50-ffd1-11f0-97b5-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to close Kennedy Center for about two years in July for construction</title>
      <description>The president’s proposal calls for the center to undergo a full rebrand. It comes amid a series of cancellations and internal upheaval since he took over the storied institution nearly a year ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5532cc0-ffca-11f0-9c1a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the bird that can fly 8,000 miles without stopping</title>
      <description>B6, a bar-tailed godwit, offers puffed-up humans a lesson in humility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2929c430-ffb2-11f0-8cf7-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 21:08:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I’ve held onto from knowing David Foster Wallace</title>
      <description>On the 30th anniversary of “Infinite Jest,” a former assistant to the author’s editor looks back on a complicated mind and relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4bc8db0-ffac-11f0-b8d0-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 20:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fab10c0-ff95-11f0-a2e4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 17:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you know Black history? Test your knowledge with this quiz.</title>
      <description>Museums and other institutions continue to face pushback from the Trump administration over DEI, and states have passed laws limiting how teachers can discuss Black history in the classroom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb889150-ff88-11f0-b31f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 16:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mysterious delay in the Supreme Court tariffs case</title>
      <description>The Trump administration, though the underdog, will find each passing week an encouraging sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">816a4440-ff7f-11f0-825b-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 15:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6e0aac1-ff7a-11f0-91c0-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 14:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where to go in 2026, without crowds</title>
      <description>12 destinations to add to your travel wish list, from a Mexican mountain town to an accessible Greek island.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06652ef2-ff01-11f0-b931-0000a1ace986</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2026 00:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of 5-year-old detained by ICE in Minneapolis</title>
      <description>Liam Conejo Ramos and his father were ordered released by a federal judge. The pair were detained in their driveway in Minnesota last week, sparking protests at the family detention center in Dilley, Texas, where they have been held.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4519c8a0-feec-11f0-8b2c-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 21:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding this much exercise to your daily routine may boost longevity</title>
      <description>Using activity tracker data, researchers found that just a bit more exercise could save one in 10 people from an earlier death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acc13270-fedf-11f0-b991-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 20:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge won’t scale back Trump’s immigration surge in Minnesota for now</title>
      <description>Minnesota officials had said the immigration crackdown was endangering public safety in their state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6acf671-fec4-11f0-9e15-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:49:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f956e90-fec0-11f0-8c01-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Melania’ documentary promises to take us behind the scenes. There’s nothing to see, our critic writes.</title>
      <description>The new film about the elusive first lady mostly underscores her impenetrability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c55b9ed0-febf-11f0-bd52-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 16:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to build a 250-foot-tall arch, dwarfing the Lincoln Memorial</title>
      <description>The president is eying a plot of land near Memorial Bridge. The art critic who proposed the idea called for a smaller arch or for Trump to pick a new site.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b5eb2e0-feaa-11f0-b2a1-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 13:41:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes funding deal, but short-term shutdown still expected</title>
      <description>A temporary funding lapse will start Saturday before the House returns to consider the agreement early next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e2c3550-fe36-11f0-8895-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 23:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine O’Hara dies at 71. The Canadian-born actress starred in ‘Schitt’s Creek’ and ‘Home Alone.’</title>
      <description>O’Hara partnered with Christopher Guest for a series of beloved mockumentaries and gained a new generation of fans as a vain former soap-opera star on “Schitt’s Creek.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">feef7780-fe0a-11f0-a7f3-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband is a liar and a thief. I don’t want to tell my family.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband is a liar and a thief. I don’t want to tell my family.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78ebb780-fe09-11f0-aecc-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 18:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department says it opened civil rights investigation into Alex Pretti’s shooting</title>
      <description>Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche’s announcement signals an apparent shift from its handling so far of shootings involving agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e01d250-fe01-11f0-8895-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione won’t face death penalty in case of UnitedHealthcare CEO’s killing</title>
      <description>Mangione will not face the death penalty on charges of stalking and killing UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson in late 2024, a federal judge ruled Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cd257f0-fdf2-11f0-bb8a-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 15:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don Lemon arrested by federal officials over church protest</title>
      <description>The former CNN host was taken into custody in Los Angeles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f599200-fde5-11f0-8b87-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taps Fed critic Kevin Warsh to succeed Jerome Powell as chairman</title>
      <description>The Wall Street veteran once held hawkish views on interest rates but has recently signaled a stance more in line with President Trump’s public demands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">961ed5f0-fdd5-11f0-818c-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 12:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. Anger in Minnesota. ICE warehouses. Tulsi Gabbard. ‘Melania’ premiere. Nor’easter. Slower aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cf7a7c0-fdd3-11f0-9d36-000a1ace88dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
