<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>This startup is selling an EV that charges in five minutes. Scientists have doubts.</title>
      <description>The high-end electric motorcycle maker Verge Motorcycles and its spin-off motor company Donut Lab say they’re selling the world’s first EV powered by a “solid-state” battery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb276101-f497-11f0-aa2a-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35e20c00-f490-11f0-83da-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 17:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b7224c1-f47a-11f0-9fba-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She brought her political dissent to Stephen Miller’s home. Now police are investigating.</title>
      <description>Barbara Wien, 66-year-old retired peace studies professor, says she was taking a stand against the Trump administration’s policies. To Katie Miller, married to one of the president’s most powerful aides, Wien’s actions appeared to be a threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcae6050-f476-11f0-ac5b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon readies 1,500 soldiers to possibly deploy to Minnesota, officials say</title>
      <description>Though no decisions have been announced, soldiers with the Army’s 11th Airborne Division in Alaska have been placed at the ready following Trump’s Insurrection Act threat, according to defense officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5568d4b0-f42b-11f0-a741-0000a1acecf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 05:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These prophets of economic doom are worried about another collapse</title>
      <description>They called the dot-com and housing bubbles. Now they're worried about the AI investment boom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ceef311-f3ff-11f0-a741-0000a1acecf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 23:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind Trump's decision to back away from striking Iran</title>
      <description>The president confronted the limits of U.S. military power as costs loomed and Mideast allies lobbied for restraint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9951ade1-f3e6-11f0-9be5-0000a1ace03b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 20:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dan Bongino stoked ‘deep state’ conspiracy theories. Now they’re coming back to haunt him.</title>
      <description>Bongino’s stint as the FBI’s deputy director has alienated some of his online followers as he relaunches his podcast career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">462e4100-f3d7-11f0-89a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abigail Spanberger sworn in as Virginia’s first female governor</title>
      <description>Spanberger, a former Democratic member of Congress and undercover operative for the CIA, became Virginia’s first female governor Saturday. She takes office after a landslide victory and a centrist message focused on affordability and defending the commonwealth from President Trump’s policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">454d2640-f3cb-11f0-9f01-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces tariffs on European countries opposing Greenland takeover</title>
      <description>The move escalates tensions between the U.S. and longtime allies that have been sending Trump a message that the territory of Denmark is not for sale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8394d61-f3c9-11f0-a7b3-0000a1ace1d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 17:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37428fd0-f3b3-11f0-8c18-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The definitive ranking of the best sitcom neighbors in TV history</title>
      <description>They’re intrusive. They’re perceptive. They’re infuriating. And they’ve nearly vanished.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a811ae10-f3b0-11f0-b6f8-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 14:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge bars DHS agents in Minneapolis from arresting or retaliating against peaceful protesters</title>
      <description>The order comes in response to a lawsuit from local residents alleging that federal agents violated their constitutional rights while they were observing or protesting immigration raids.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6a72700-f34d-11f0-847b-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 02:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Young men are finding happiness in their parents’ homes — and they’re not going anywhere</title>
      <description>During a time of acute anxiety and curiosity about young men in America, more of them are embracing the living-with-parents lifestyle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acb4a151-f344-11f0-83a1-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 01:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U-Va. board leaders resign, attorneys at two other Virginia colleges are dismissed as Spanberger and Democrats take power</title>
      <description>The departures come as Democrats push to unwind some changes made at Virginia colleges and universities during the administration of Republican Gov. Glenn Youngkin. Some schools have also faced intense scrutiny from the Trump administration and other conservatives over diversity, equity and inclusion policies, the response to antisemitism, and the provision of gender transition care, among other topics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23eb5580-f33f-11f0-a336-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 00:54:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department issues subpoenas for Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz and Minneapolis Mayor Jacob Frey as part of criminal investigation</title>
      <description>The subpoenas, which are without recent precedent, escalate an already bitter political battle between the Trump administration and Democratic state officials following the fatal shooting of a woman in Minneapolis by an immigration officer last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ebcb630-f332-11f0-97d7-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials extend National Guard’s D.C. mission through 2026, two defense officials familiar with plan say</title>
      <description>The domestic military mission, which is the subject of an ongoing court challenge, was due to expire at the end of February. The National Guard headquarters overseeing the mission said that 2,673 troops were assigned to the mission as of Friday morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ad63b80-f331-11f0-b703-0000a1ace588</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 23:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yulia Navalnaya, Alexei Navalny’s widow: Dictators are coming for the lawyers</title>
      <description>"The persecution of my husband’s lawyers shows how authoritarian power eliminates dissent at its source," Navalnaya writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2cfce20-f32a-11f0-87a5-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 22:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump installs loyalists on panel to review White House ballroom to secure rapid approval</title>
      <description>The Commission of Fine Arts will discuss the controversial project next week. Officials hope to win approval in two months, while some past White House projects have taken years to green light.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5638710-f325-11f0-bc81-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 21:54:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of man shot in the leg by ICE in Minneapolis disputes key aspects of DHS account</title>
      <description>Relatives say the non-fatal shooting occurred at the door of the house, not out in the street during a scuffle. They also say the victim was not the man a federal officer tried to arrest in a traffic stop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f4f5b41-f31c-11f0-813e-0000a1aceb9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 20:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My spouse yelled at my sister. Now she doesn't feel safe with him.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My spouse yelled at my sister. Now she doesn't feel safe with him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">128cf571-f301-11f0-9cb1-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington National Opera announces new venues after split with Kennedy Center</title>
      <description>The company has lined up Lisner Auditorium at George Washington University for two upcoming operas, and has also seen a spike in donations since it announced last week that it was leaving the Kennedy Center, which has been transformed under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8563471-f2ef-11f0-823b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s most elusive founder has lessons for today</title>
      <description>With “Common Sense,” published 250 years ago this month, Thomas Paine was just getting started.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f996e410-f2ea-11f0-ad7f-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57203b70-f2e8-11f0-afa5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insurrection Act. Detainee death. Nobel Prize. Outraged judge. Political violence. Psychiatric disorders. Terrapin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbbf80e0-f2d2-11f0-95e5-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 ways travel has changed so far this century</title>
      <description>Cruise ships used to be about sailing and the sea. If you wanted to rent a room, you went to a hotel. Those were such quaint times. Our staff discussed the biggest travel moments and advances that took place between 2000 and 2025, and we asked industry stalwarts for theirs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59965d40-f274-11f0-8720-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical examiner believes death of man at ICE detention center in Texas was homicide, recording says</title>
      <description>A fellow detainee says he witnessed Geraldo Lunas Campos, a 55-year-old Cuban immigrant, being choked to death by guards on Jan. 3.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7aa90a90-f266-11f0-bf3d-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 23:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon said it plans to overhaul the newspaper, calling it ‘woke.’ Its top editor pledged to defend its independence.</title>
      <description>The Pentagon will “modernize” the publication and “refocus its content away from woke distractions that syphon morale, and adapt it to serve a new generation of service members,” chief Pentagon spokesperson Sean Parnell wrote on X. A spokesperson for the Defense Department did not answer questions about how the changes would comply with the newspaper’s long-standing editorial independence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc22c971-f251-11f0-9a53-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 20:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of bettors and players fixed NCAA and Chinese Basketball Association games, prosecutors say</title>
      <description>Sports bettors worked with players across NCAA men’s basketball to rig the outcome of at least 29 games, federal prosecutors alleged in an indictment unsealed Thursday. The athletes played for schools across the country, including Tulane, St. Louis University, DePaul, Fordham and others, according to the U.S. Attorney’s Office for the Eastern District of Pennsylvania.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1638770-f22d-11f0-8ea4-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who used the Maduro raid to earn $400K? The pool of suspects is alarming.</title>
      <description>A bet on government action by a government actor is always a bet against the public interest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5daaa640-f222-11f0-a01c-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These workers are striking in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf36ddb0-f21e-11f0-8d75-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens to invoke Insurrection Act in Minnesota to quell ICE protests</title>
      <description>The Insurrection Act enables a president to deploy the military on U.S. soil in extraordinary circumstances: to quell an insurrection, civil disorder or armed rebellion. It empowers the military to make arrests and perform searches domestically.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd0c8040-f21c-11f0-a401-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 14:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First renderings of the Commanders’ new stadium show plenty of callbacks to RFK Stadium</title>
      <description>The most striking features include a translucent roof, a grand colonnade and main entryways on the same axis as the Washington Monument and the U.S. Capitol.
While the design process is ongoing, the renderings reflect the major design principles agreed upon by the team and the lead architects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07e20d0-f216-11f0-9518-0000a1ace74f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 13:34:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis tensions. Iran protests. Greenland talks. FBI search. Missing jobs. Cancer treatment. Microplastics. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af4ecd50-f209-11f0-8a8e-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agent shoots person in leg as Minneapolis protests flare</title>
      <description>In a statement, Department of Homeland Security alleged that an individual attempted to evade arrest by driving their vehicle away from federal law enforcement officers, crashing it into a parked car and then running away on foot. Both the officer and the person shot were being treated at a hospital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9db290-f1c5-11f0-8040-0000a1ace31b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 03:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She made a Facebook comment about her mayor. Then the police arrived.</title>
      <description>Raquel Pacheco says she was asserting her right to free speech. Miami Beach police said they dispatched officers to assess whether there was a safety threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8215b81-f1ad-11f0-a252-000a1ace8848</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 01:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks Venezuela war powers bill after Vance breaks deadlock</title>
      <description>The vote failed after two Republicans withdrew their previous support under intense pressure from the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">625df590-f1a8-11f0-af5e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland meeting between U.S. and Danish officials ends in standstill: ‘We didn’t manage to change the American position’</title>
      <description>Diplomats from Denmark and Greenland agreed to set up a “high-level working group” after meeting with Vice President JD Vance and Secretary of State Marco Rubio at the White House, but they said there was little agreement so far about the future of the Arctic territory.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">123f81c0-f18d-11f0-89c5-0000a1acef3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Iran secretly reassured each other via a Russian mediator that they would not preemptively attack</title>
      <description>The communications between Israel and Iran last month — and the role played by Russia as the intermediary — were unusual given the hostility between the two Middle Eastern rivals, which engaged in a 12-day war in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a49dd60-f185-11f0-8760-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 20:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration indefinitely pauses immigrant visa processing for 75 nations, including Brazil, Iran, Russia and Somalia</title>
      <description>The State Department has ramped up efforts in recent months to restrict migration, particularly from nations President Donald Trump has deemed a threat to national security. The visa order takes effect Jan. 21, and a full list of the countries on the administration’s list has not been released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5459ab10-f16c-11f0-92c5-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Husband’s new car obsession burns their couple time’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘Husband’s new car obsession burns their couple time’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce39fea1-f16a-11f0-a9bd-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:02:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why are more restaurants plating fish skin side up?</title>
      <description>Why are more restaurants plating fish skin side up?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">137f22f0-f167-11f0-86e8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. withdraws some forces from key Qatar base as Trump weighs Iran strikes, echoing moves before summer attack on nuclear sites</title>
      <description>The Pentagon’s partial withdrawal from al-Udeid Air Base occurs as President Donald Trump broadcasts his administration’s support for Iranian civilians protesting the country’s leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">383c8bf0-f15d-11f0-92c5-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 15:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unlikely phone call in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6bc2e30-f155-11f0-8c91-0000a1ace750</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI executes search warrant at Washington Post reporter’s home amid investigation into government contractor</title>
      <description>The reporter, Hannah Natanson, was at her home in Virginia at the time of the search on Wednesday. The warrant said that law enforcement was investigating Aurelio Perez-Lugones, a system administrator in Maryland who has a top secret security clearance and has been accused of accessing and taking home classified intelligence reports, according to an FBI affidavit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fffdb01-f151-11f0-b3d7-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 14:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump reiterates Greenland’s importance before meeting Vance will host with officials from Denmark and the self-governing territory</title>
      <description>Visiting officials appeared unnerved by the vice president’s planned involvement in today’s talks after they had sought a meeting with Secretary of State Marco Rubio.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aad137b0-f149-11f0-9a0d-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran protests. ICE shooting. Trump’s obscene gesture. ‘Anti-vaxxer.’ Earnings calls. Polar vortex. Red meat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85cad970-f140-11f0-a01f-000a1ace6293</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saks Global — parent company of Saks Fifth Avenue, Neiman Marcus and Bergdorf Goodman — files for bankruptcy</title>
      <description>Saks Global has faced declining sales and crushing debt. The holding company commenced voluntary Chapter 11 cases in the U.S. Bankruptcy Court for the Southern District of Texas, it said in a news release. Its stores remain open, it added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5e9c8d1-f115-11f0-a099-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 06:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New RFK Jr. pick for advisory panel: ‘I was not anti-vaccine. I am now.’</title>
      <description>Two OB/GYNs appointed to the influential Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices have criticized vaccination during pregnancy and more broadly. One called the vaccine industry “disgusting.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">636aec10-f0d4-11f0-a3dd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claudette Colvin dies at 86. She refused to give up her seat on a segregated Alabama bus 9 months before Rosa Parks made history.</title>
      <description>Colvin’s arrest in 1955 inaugurated what the Rev. Martin Luther King Jr. described as a pivotal period for Black people in Montgomery. She became a star witness in a civil rights case that reached the Supreme Court, which ordered an end to bus segregation in 1956.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a387a7a0-f0c7-11f0-98d0-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 21:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
