<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza’s Health Ministry says 40,000 Palestinians have been killed in Israel’s war against Hamas. A full count is elusive.</title>
      <description>The Gaza Health Ministry does not distinguish between civilians and combatants but says the majority of the dead are women and children. Aid workers say the 40,000 figure is likely to be an undercount that excludes thousands of bodies believed to be buried under rubble. About 1,200 people in Israel were killed in Hamas’s Oct. 7 attack, and more than 300 Israeli soldiers have died in combat since late October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">071e6210-5aef-11ef-bfc6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gena Rowlands dies at 94. The actress starred in ‘A Woman Under the Influence’ and ‘The Notebook.’</title>
      <description>Over seven decades, Rowlands worked sparingly in mainstream fare but managed to attract a cascade of superlatives and an honorary Academy Award for career achievement in 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d8c1590-5aa3-11ef-91f9-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia President Minouche Shafik resigns after drawing ire over response to pro-Palestinian protests</title>
      <description>The resignation ends a short and turbulent tenure marred by controversy and backlash over how she handled an outbreak of protests on campus last spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43bdf51-5a9e-11ef-92f2-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. tried to meet with Kamala Harris to discuss endorsing her in exchange for a Cabinet job</title>
      <description>Harris has rebuffed the outreach, while Kennedy has had conversations with Republican nominee Donald Trump about a role in his administration as well. Kennedy is exploring multiple options for the future of his presidential effort, which has seen a decline in national polling since President Joe Biden dropped out of the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d899a6b2-5a95-11ef-9843-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stonehenge mystery has (maybe) been solved, but the revelation raises tantalizing new questions</title>
      <description>Researchers on Wednesday revealed that the long-mysterious “Altar Stone” at the heart of Stonehenge came from faraway Scotland, leading scientists to question how — and why — a six-ton slab of sandstone made its way from north to south 5,000 years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cc53ed0-5a84-11ef-9d32-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harris magnifies America’s generational and cultural divides</title>
      <description>“Make America Great Again” versus “We are not going back.” Lee Greenwood’s music versus Beyoncé’s. The two candidates, their rallies and their movements are showcasing two sides of the country split by demographics and cultural touchstones — not just party and policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6f59a31-5a74-11ef-9cc0-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO declares a global health emergency as a new form of mpox spreads rapidly in Africa</title>
      <description>Cases in Africa have already surpassed 15,000 this year, exceeding the toll for all of 2023. Two years ago, mpox emerged as a threat in the United States as cases surged mainly among gay men.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c3130a0-5a67-11ef-9f26-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to ditch sister’s ‘insufferable’ guy without hurting feelings</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to ditch sister’s ‘insufferable’ guy without hurting feelings</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bb7f540-5a56-11ef-b381-0000a1acec34</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Our food critic is telling the story of the time he judged Tim Walz’s hot dish</title>
      <description>Happening now: Our food critic is telling the story of the time he judged Tim Walz’s hot dish</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">340d8701-5a50-11ef-8925-0000a1ace047</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress declined to create a national monument to recognize the 1908 Springfield race riot. Now Biden will do it on his own.</title>
      <description>The president will make the designation during a Friday event with civil rights leaders and Illinois lawmakers, the White House confirmed to The Washington Post on Wednesday. More than a century after the 1908 race riot sparked the founding of the NAACP, Springfield is reeling from the fatal shooting of Sonya Massey, an unarmed Black woman, by an Illinois sheriff’s deputy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">575b9370-5a44-11ef-bff6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Today’s On the Record is inspired by a kangaroo</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aad2f1e0-5a41-11ef-b3d6-0000a1acec42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The annual inflation rate dropped in July, probably keeping the Fed on track to cut interest rates next month</title>
      <description>A string of encouraging reports on prices have bolstered the central bank’s confidence that it can take some pressure off the economy before it slows down too much.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79b2ee60-5a39-11ef-a82d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 12:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz. Primary results. Weapons to Israel. Ohio murder. Tropical storm. Parvovirus. Message in a bottle. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57a27461-5a2c-11ef-90ce-000a1ace50b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Fumio Kishida, mired in record-low approval ratings, says he will stand down next month</title>
      <description>Kishida, who has ramped up Japan's defense spending and hewn closely with the United States on security matters, will not seek reelection as head of the ruling Liberal Democratic Party next month, bringing to an end his three-year tenure as prime minister.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28a3fa80-59e6-11ef-b2d9-0000a1aceb29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 02:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-police chief who led raid on Kansas newspaper faces felony charge of obstruction of justice amid investigation of his department</title>
      <description>Gideon Cody allegedly tampered with an investigation into his force’s raid of the Marion County Record newsroom and its publisher’s home in a case that sparked national outrage from press freedom advocates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68f9f050-599e-11ef-b5c3-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 18:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Israeli raid deep inside Gaza rescued four hostages but killed scores of Palestinians. A review of videos shows how it happened.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post video investigation of the June 8 raid in Nuseirat shows the Israeli military employed heavy airstrikes for nearly four hours in the dense residential area where Hamas was holding the captives. The raid, which left 274 people dead according to Palestinian authorities, was the most successful hostage-rescue operation of the war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e49140-5990-11ef-b1b4-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:26:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: When his partner gets sick, boyfriend makes a show of being sicker</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: When his partner gets sick, boyfriend makes a show of being sicker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6810d890-598d-11ef-9034-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This oil tycoon brings in tens of millions for Trump, and he’s telling Trump what the industry wants</title>
      <description>Harold Hamm has become the former president’s point person in raising money from oil industry donors. He is also relaying to Trump what the industry is seeking: less environmental regulation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b2d9c00-597f-11ef-bb8b-0000a1ace976</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 14:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Near, far, wherever you are, I believe that it’s time for today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37bb63f0-5978-11ef-aa04-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack investigation. Musk and Trump. Ukraine. Abortion lawsuit. Greece fire. Disputed bronze medal. Spinning iceberg. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e57f1c0-5963-11ef-802b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s interview with Elon Musk on X delayed by technical difficulties</title>
      <description>The former president’s interview was scheduled to begin at 8 p.m. Eastern time, but has been delayed by at least 20 minutes due to unknown technical difficulties. Musk previously interviewed Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis on X when DeSantis announced his primary challenge to Trump, and the website faced similar issues that prevented people from being able to join the call between the two men. Musk blamed a “massive” denial of service attack on the website for the problems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bfc7a01-590b-11ef-a81b-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 00:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden-Harris campaign advisers and a Trump ally were allegedly targeted by Iranian hackers, FBI probe finds</title>
      <description>The FBI investigation began in June after Roger Stone's email was allegedly compromised and hackers attempted to break into the accounts of Democratic presidential campaign advisers, people familiar with the matter say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5a00980-58f9-11ef-88de-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran, wary of war, weighs retaliation against Israel for the assassination of Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh</title>
      <description>In public, Iranian officials are continuing to warn of a “tough” reprisal to “punish” Israel. But in private meetings with the leaders of its armed proxies, according to those familiar with the conversations, Iran has called for caution — seeking to balance any show of force with the desire to avoid an all-out war in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70e6aea1-58f6-11ef-8162-0000a1ace36b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 22:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says it is investigating the alleged hack of sensitive Trump campaign materials</title>
      <description>The GOP campaign claimed this weekend that it had been hacked by Iran, in an echo of past battles over foreign nations’ interference in U.S. presidential elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4b74311-58ec-11ef-8d1e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 20:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Surprise half-siblings are living reminders of father’s infidelity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Surprise half-siblings are living reminders of father’s infidelity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c6dd8d1-58c4-11ef-ab41-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Painting a zoo in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33e9dbe0-58af-11ef-bc60-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hack. Rally crowds. Gaza strike. Uvalde videos. Boeing woes. Allergy spray. Tom Cruise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03375320-589a-11ef-9a14-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Olympics needed a reset. Merci to Paris for providing it, columnist Barry Svrluga writes.</title>
      <description>After lackluster Olympics in Tokyo and Beijing and disappointing hosts even before the coronavirus pandemic, these Summer Games were exactly what the whole enterprise needed and in a style no other city could provide, Svrluga writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143365a1-582d-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After two years of far-right rule in a Michigan county, the opposition had one chance to change it</title>
      <description>Divisive, Trump-style politics came to Ottawa County. Then moderate Republicans and some Democrats mobilized and fought back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5df105a0-581c-11ef-bb78-000a1ace1b0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s plan to upend the federal workforce could rattle the DMV economy</title>
      <description>The Republican presidential nominee’s Agenda47 policy manifesto and his party platform seek to “shatter the Deep State” with actions such as moving up to 100,000 federal positions out of D.C., which experts say could be devastating to the area’s economy. Virginia, Maryland and D.C. are among the top four jurisdictions nationwide for federal civilian employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1869f40-580b-11ef-a3ac-0000a1ace14b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 highlights from Paris Olympics: Team USA wraps up Games tied with China in gold medals and atop total medal count</title>
      <description>Sunday’s win over France in the women’s basketball final gave the United States a 40th gold, enough to finish the competition even with China. Team USA’s 126 medals overall easily topped China’s 91. American gymnast Jordan Chiles must return her bronze medal from the women’s floor exercise. And Dutch distance runner Sifan Hassan won the women’s marathon in Olympic record time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">757edca0-57ff-11ef-a7af-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 16:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d37140-57fa-11ef-8c2c-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s basketball team, trailing in second half, comes back to beat host France and capture eighth straight Olympic gold</title>
      <description>One of the Olympics’ greatest dynasties was tested Sunday. But the United States survived and has now won 10 of 13 Olympic women’s basketball tournaments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4db86e0-57f5-11ef-8936-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you reduce your risk of cancer? Here’s what an oncologist with a family history of diagnoses does.</title>
      <description>Taking sun protection seriously is one of this doctor’s five tips to prevent a cancer diagnosis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7b5c5a0-57f2-11ef-8201-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. women’s basketball team takes on host France for its eighth straight Olympic gold. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Team USA, the heavy favorite, is on a 60-game winning streak in the Olympics and looking to make it back-to-back wins for American men’s and women’s basketball over the French. This is France’s second appearance in a gold medal game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f840fa70-57e5-11ef-b4a7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 13:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e939ab0-57e2-11ef-a16b-0000a1ace146</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gymnast Jordan Chiles must return her Olympic bronze medal for floor after court ruling</title>
      <description>Chiles won her medal Monday after a coach’s inquiry lifted her over Romania’s Ana Barbosu, but the Court of Arbitration for Sport ruled Saturday that the inquiry that benefited Chiles was filed after the one-minute deadline. The International Olympic Committee confirmed Sunday morning that the medal would be reallocated to Barbosu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae66aeb0-57ca-11ef-acb9-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign says it is the victim of a foreign hack after the leak of a report on Vance</title>
      <description>Microsoft discovered evidence that Iranian hackers compromised the email account of a former Trump campaign adviser, a person familiar with the matter says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90ce24b0-576f-11ef-adfa-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 23:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 15 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. track and field stands out behind stars Sydney McLaughlin-Levrone, Gabby Thomas and Rai Benjamin</title>
      <description>Benjamin's huge anchor leg ensured the men's 4x400 team the victory. On the women's side, McLaughlin-Levrone ran away from everyone on the second leg, and Thomas followed suit en route to an easy win. Also on the track, American Masai Russell brought home gold in the women's 100-meter hurdles. And elsewhere, the U.S. women's soccer and men's basketball teams added golds of their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6139cd70-576b-11ef-9ab4-0000a1ace6f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 22:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. men’s basketball team beats host France, capturing gold for the fifth straight Olympics</title>
      <description>Led by aging stars LeBron James, Steph Curry and Kevin Durant, the Americans went 6-0 in the Paris Games and captured gold in front of rabid French fans in central Paris. The Americans last failed to win gold in 2004.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">198e1920-575e-11ef-9942-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 21:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. men take on Victor Wembanyama and host nation France in a battle for Olympic hoops gold. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Team USA was the tournament’s favorite. Backed by rabid fans, France has notched multiple upsets along the way. Now the teams will battle for gold in Paris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bac7fc0-574c-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 19:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s soccer team beats Brazil, 1-0, to capture its first Olympic gold medal since 2012</title>
      <description>Mallory Swanson scored the winning goal in the 57th minute. With a new coach and new-look roster, the Americans stormed through the Olympic tournament undefeated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e448ca30-573a-11ef-97e4-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I feel pressured by my family’s hopes for my future partner</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I feel pressured by my family’s hopes for my future partner</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff4192c0-5737-11ef-9e1d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 16:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. women’s soccer team, seeking its first Olympic gold since 2012, is set to take on Brazil in Paris. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Led by a new cohort of young stars, the Americans have stormed through the tournament undefeated after a disappointing World Cup last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d8c7f80-5727-11ef-92d9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 14:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pastor claimed his pro-Trump prophecies came from God. His brother called him a fake.</title>
      <description>Jeremiah Johnson found religious fame after leaning into politics. His brother, also a preacher, worried he was twisting the Lord’s word for money and power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c24b27d0-5720-11ef-9928-0000a1acecdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 13:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d2a7fc0-571c-11ef-aeba-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Zappa’s kids are still grappling with his legacy — and each other</title>
      <description>Dweezil no longer speaks to his siblings. Moon has spent decades reassessing the family dynamic — emotional labor that lies thick on the pages of her new memoir.

Ahmet and Diva, meanwhile, seem dazed still by the force of their siblings’ anger — siblings with whom they share not just a fraught business partnership but also a one-of-a-kind childhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8834b451-56a6-11ef-9400-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 highlights from Paris Olympics: American Rai Benjamin rules the track; U.S. women’s basketball will play for gold</title>
      <description>Benjamin breezed to a gold medal in the men's 400-meter hurdles and helped erase the foibles of the U.S. men's 4x100 relay team, which finished seventh and was eventually disqualified because of a bad first baton exchange. Elsewhere, the U.S. women smothered Australia on the basketball court, ensuring a trip to their eighth straight gold medal game, where they will meet France on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bca4e0-56a0-11ef-b28e-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA rejects first psychedelic to treat PTSD, marking a setback and calling for more study of ecstasy-based drug</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration declined to approve MDMA to treat post-traumatic stress disorder, instead calling for another large study that could take years to complete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e97cc591-569c-11ef-845e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imane Khelif, female boxer who was a target of online attacks over ‘gender eligibility’ test, wins Olympic gold</title>
      <description>The Algerian fighter faced online hate after a Russia-linked boxing organization disqualified her from last year's world championships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3843df31-5696-11ef-9e61-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
