<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 05:02:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs order directing government to sue states that attempt to regulate AI — despite growing bipartisan opposition</title>
      <description>The executive order comes as an increasing number of Republicans are speaking out against the president’s support of the tech industry’s ambitions for artificial intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b1fc060-d6f8-11f0-bc9b-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is expected to dramatically loosen federal restrictions on marijuana, according to six people familiar with the discussions</title>
      <description>An executive order would direct agencies to classify marijuana as a Schedule III drug, similar to some common prescription painkillers. Rescheduling marijuana would not legalize or decriminalize cannabis, but it would ease barriers to research and boost the bottom lines of legal businesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0abd7d80-d6e9-11f0-82ff-0000a1ace3c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana redistricting effort fails as GOP lawmakers deliver rare rebuke of Trump</title>
      <description>Some GOP state senators, who hold the majority, sided with Democrats to kill a plan to alter Indiana’s voting map, delivering President Donald Trump the biggest blow yet in his nationwide effort to create safer Republican congressional districts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc4fd20-d6da-11f0-86f6-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury again declines to indict New York Attorney General Letitia James, a prominent Trump foe, in mortgage fraud case</title>
      <description>The decision marked another loss for the Trump administration as its officials attempt to charge James in a case that career prosecutors have long viewed as weak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65869ae1-d6cf-11f0-9f9d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks Democrats’ bill to extend ACA subsidies, all but ensuring they will expire at the end of the year</title>
      <description>The vote was the culmination of Democrats’ months-long push to extend the subsidies and prevent premiums from rising for millions of Americans — a campaign that helped trigger the longest federal government shutdown in history. Republicans promised to hold the vote as part of a deal to end the shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5352820-d6be-11f0-ba02-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings at odds over funeral arrangements for abusive mother</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings at odds over funeral arrangements for abusive mother</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09ac6b30-d6b3-11f0-9c5d-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was there when ‘Napalm Girl’ was photographed. This is what I saw.</title>
      <description>“The Stringer” does nothing to shake my strong belief that Nick Ut captured the famous image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b44f12e0-d6ae-11f0-a1db-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders ‘immediate release’ of Kilmar Abrego García from ICE custody</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Paula Xinis said she ordered his release in part to ensure that he had a fair immigration process after the Justice Department and an Immigration and Customs Enforcement witness last month said immigration officers had no other option but to deport him to the African nation of Liberia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd716a90-d6a7-11f0-9d7c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem is expected to face tough questions on immigration at a House panel hearing</title>
      <description>Noem’s appearance before the House Homeland Security Committee today is billed as a discussion about global threats the United States faces, but much of the focus is expected to be on her role in the Trump administration’s controversial immigration policies. Follow our live coverage and reporter insights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c7b3230-d6a4-11f0-8f2b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A retail giant stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f914a7f0-d69f-11f0-aa58-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds quarantined as South Carolina outbreak accelerates in the wake of Thanksgiving travel and a lack of vaccinations</title>
      <description>Authorities traced a sizable outbreak to a church in the state’s northwest. Of the 111 measles cases recorded in that area, 105 involved people who were unvaccinated while three involved those who were partially vaccinated, state epidemiologist Linda Bell said at a news briefing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ed82b00-d69d-11f0-a65f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a top U.S. commander decided to kill two boat strike survivors</title>
      <description>The order given by Adm. Frank Bradley is under scrutiny from Congress. People who have viewed or been briefed on a classified video of the operation shed light on the most consequential deliberation of his career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2377b670-d693-11f0-91aa-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 13:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil tanker. ICE planes. Trump’s billionaires. Interest rates. ChatGPT lawsuit. Font choice. Ancient fire. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3275f30-d688-11f0-b805-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene’s boyfriend has had a weird month</title>
      <description>Brian Glenn is trying not to get caught in the middle of the breakup between his partner and his president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b780b0-d628-11f0-ae5e-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 00:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes Pentagon bill pressuring Hegseth to release boat strike evidence</title>
      <description>The Senate could approve the measure in coming days and lawmakers are confident President Donald Trump will sign it into law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6afd85f0-d621-11f0-b534-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 23:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan fires football coach Sherrone Moore, citing an ‘inappropriate relationship’ with staff member</title>
      <description>The abrupt announcement brings a stunning end to Moore’s tenure as the Wolverines’ coach after two full seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c550090-d617-11f0-8d3f-0000a1ace481</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. seizes oil tanker off Venezuelan coast, Trump says, a significant escalation in the U.S. pressure campaign against Maduro</title>
      <description>The seizure adds a new tactic to the Trump administration’s military campaign in waters near oil-dependent Venezuela. Since September, U.S. forces have launched strikes against more than 20 boats it alleges were carrying drugs to the United States, killing at least 87 people, while massing troops, warships and aircraft in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10c9d620-d60c-11f0-89f7-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 21:06:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland mom ruled fit for trial 11 years after her young children vanished</title>
      <description>Catherine Hoggle faces two counts of murder in the deaths of Jacob, 2, and Sarah, 3. She had long been considered too mentally unstable to stand before a jury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be8e6c60-d609-11f0-970d-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 20:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve cuts rates by a quarter of a percentage point and signals at least one more cut next year</title>
      <description>Wednesday’s widely expected move lowers the Fed’s benchmark rate to a range of 3.5 percent to 3.75 percent, the lowest level in about three years. But officials remain sharply divided over how to respond to an economy sending mixed signals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b4057b0-d5fb-11f0-88fa-0000a1ace170</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘My boyfriend never tells me I’m beautiful’: Hax readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘My boyfriend never tells me I’m beautiful’: Hax readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36d15f40-d5ea-11f0-a3d1-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This sci-fi writer predicted the future. Is he right again?</title>
      <description>Host Megan McArdle talks to Neal Stephenson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97ef8810-d5e5-11f0-8c9b-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our new food critic, Elazar Sontag, is taking your questions. Ask him why he’s ditching anonymity, bringing back stars and more.</title>
      <description>Our new food critic, Elazar Sontag, is taking your questions. Ask him why he’s ditching anonymity, bringing back stars and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c2d2060-d5e1-11f0-9714-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security inks contract to create its own fleet of Boeing 737s for deportations</title>
      <description>U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement has long relied on charter planes to carry out deportation flights, but two officials familiar with the contract and records reviewed by The Washington Post indicate ICE has broader plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">821bab00-d5df-11f0-882f-000a1ace0934</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:47:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second judge orders release of Epstein files, covering materials related to his 2019 indictment on sex-trafficking charge</title>
      <description>Richard M. Berman, a federal judge in New York, ruled that public access is required by a law Congress passed last month. On Tuesday, another federal judge made a similar ruling covering documents involved in the prosecution of Jeffrey Epstein’s accomplice, Ghislaine Maxwell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba29d332-d5dc-11f0-95db-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The color of the year in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc49b151-d5d4-11f0-aae4-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 14:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tour. Miami mayor. Boat strike probe. Vaccine safety. Weird weather. TikTok map. Talented octopus. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8fa8120-d5bf-11f0-8b71-0000a1aceb85</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miami elects Eileen Higgins, who is set to become the city’s first Democratic mayor in nearly 30 years</title>
      <description>Higgins will become the first female mayor in the history of Miami. The contest attracted attention from President Donald Trump and national Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e070fe00-d565-11f0-a3fb-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 01:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best TV shows of the year, rated by our critic</title>
      <description>It’s been a tricky year for an embattled industry, but at least we got to watch Diego Luna, Michelle Williams, Jason Momoa and Nathan Fielder. Did your favorite show make the cut?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c410670-d559-11f0-b6a9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 23:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA to probe whether adult deaths are linked to coronavirus vaccine</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration’s investigation is part of a probe that has alleged children died as a result of the shots, federal health officials said. Previous reviews have found that vaccines to fight covid are generally safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f65e7931-d54d-11f0-94ed-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:25:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silver prices smash a new record, outpacing gold</title>
      <description>The precious metal has more than doubled in value since the start of the year, rising above $60 per troy ounce on New York’s Commodity Exchange on Tuesday for the first time ever.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb86410-d52e-11f0-9e71-0000a1ace076</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 18:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Father-in-law isn’t subtle about hating his grandkid’s name</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Father-in-law isn’t subtle about hating his grandkid’s name</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a74c9890-d520-11f0-a022-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Study shows how your brain changes at four key ages: 9, 32, 66 and 83</title>
      <description>In a study published in the journal Nature Communications, researchers looked at about 4,000 scans from healthy people ages 0 to 90. They found four major times when the brain underwent developmental changes, dividing the lifespan into five distinct epochs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a920ae0-d519-11f0-a892-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 16:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A marriage gap is growing — and it could spell disaster</title>
      <description>The “war on boys” could be resulting in some women shunning marriage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f66ba00-d517-11f0-82f0-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of ‘voluminous’ records in Ghislaine Maxwell case</title>
      <description>Before releasing the records, the Justice Department must redact information that could identify victims of Jeffrey Epstein, the wealthy sex trafficker whom Maxwell was convicted of assisting, the judge wrote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c251be30-d512-11f0-89f9-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 15:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new peace prize in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba78c980-d50b-11f0-a6a6-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia and Ukraine. Trump’s power. Nancy Mace. Netflix bid. Forever chemicals. Golden Globes. Brain aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d976d00-d4f6-11f0-8286-0000a1acecd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the most common zodiac sign? What about the most common birthday?</title>
      <description>Are some signs and birthdays more widespread? And why does it seem like all of my colleagues (or neighbors) have the same sign? The Department of Data is on the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14758d41-d491-11f0-aac1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 23:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth’s ‘who cares?’ doctrine is finally taking heat, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>In U.S. history, war crimes have been rare. Accountability is needed to keep them that way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8f07e80-d478-11f0-a577-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine will not surrender territory to Russia, Zelensky says, which could mark collapse of Trump’s plan to end war</title>
      <description>The unequivocal declaration that Ukraine would not cede its land could spur the breakdown of President Donald Trump’s latest proposal to end the war, which critics have condemned as fulfilling Russian President Vladimir Putin’s wish list. Some Ukrainian officials held out hope that the negotiations could still bear fruit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aebf6590-d470-11f0-8683-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alina Habba, Trump’s embattled pick for top New Jersey prosecutor, resigns after appeals court ruled she was serving unlawfully</title>
      <description>Habba announced the decision in a statement posted to social media and said she intends to continue serving as a senior Justice Department adviser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">665b1600-d46b-11f0-88a0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems poised to expand Trump’s power over independent agencies by allowing him to fire an FTC commissioner</title>
      <description>The justices seem likely to allow the president to fire a member of the Federal Trade Commission, a ruling that could limit or overturn a nine-decade-old precedent that insulated some agencies from political influence by the executive branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d72ed40-d462-11f0-8e10-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest surprises (and snubs) from the 2026 Golden Globe nominations</title>
      <description>“One Battle After Another” dominated, as expected, while a surging “Sentimental Value” poured water all over “Wicked: For Good.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b1eaf00-d45f-11f0-8a0d-0000a1ace773</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mom of White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt’s nephew is set free on bond as she fights potential deportation</title>
      <description>The release of Bruna Ferreira, 33, who shares custody of an 11-year-old son with her former fiancé, Leavitt’s brother Michael, comes nearly a month after immigration officers detained her in Massachusetts while she was on her way to pick up their son from school and sent her to the South Louisiana ICE Processing Center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef66ef0-d45a-11f0-a611-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unemployment and health issues add up to ‘feeling inadequate’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unemployment and health issues add up to ‘feeling inadequate’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">819208c0-d457-11f0-99e3-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to announce $12 billion tariff relief for farmers</title>
      <description>Farmers, a key segment of President Donald Trump’s base, faced fallout from his tariff policies. The assistance package is expected to particularly help soybean farmers, who have seen a precipitous drop in sales this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0cd6830-d44e-11f0-8b84-000a1ace30bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was a red state governor. What I saw at Harvard surprised me.</title>
      <description>The spirit of association remains alive in unexpected places.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1447b81-d44a-11f0-a2ed-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paramount launches hostile bid for Warner Bros. Discovery, challenging Netflix’s $83 billion deal</title>
      <description>The David Ellison-run company is promising Warner Bros. Discovery shareholders a deal it says is more lucrative and easier for the Trump administration to approve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7653a2f1-d445-11f0-a5c4-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 14:52:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has pardoned or commuted nearly 100 people for drug crimes, despite his anti-drug rhetoric</title>
      <description>A Chicago gang leader, a Baltimore kingpin and a former Honduran president accused of leading a vast “narco-state” are among those who have been granted clemency during the president’s two terms, a Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4365eee1-d43e-11f0-9ed7-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Police Chief Pamela Smith steps down, Bowser says</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser praised Smith for her service but did not offer a reason for her departure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abcc62f1-d431-11f0-b36b-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration crackdown. Kennedy Center. Venezuela. Child deaths. Aging study. College football. Lanternfly honey. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">639b62f0-d42d-11f0-b36b-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
