<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 03:10:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he would ‘fire’ special counsel Jack Smith in ‘two seconds’ if elected president</title>
      <description>In a radio interview, former president Donald Trump made clear he would seek the removal of Smith, who is pursuing federal cases on behalf of the Justice Department against Trump for allegedly conspiring to overturn the 2020 election and illegally hoarding classified documents. The latter case has been dismissed, but Smith is appealing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d81310-920f-11ef-b0c2-000a1aceb08d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'monumental' arrest of the former head of this company in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f78dba0-920c-11ef-bfe8-0000a1ace1d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alsobrooks has a clear lead over Hogan in Maryland U.S. Senate race, Post-UMD poll finds</title>
      <description>Democrat Angela D. Alsobrooks maintains her lead over Republican Larry Hogan in Maryland’s closely watched U.S. Senate race, fueled in large part by voters' preference for Democrats to control the chamber, according to a Washington Post-University of Maryland poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0815990-9207-11ef-82d5-0000a1ace919</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New EPA rule declares any amount of lead dust detected in homes as hazardous, establishing an aggressive standard for cleanup</title>
      <description>Tens of millions of homes across the country still contain lead-based paint, which is especially dangerous for children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54a576c0-9200-11ef-a688-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris town hall. Russian misinformation. North Korea. Boeing. Infant mortality. Prime number. White House tour. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b775610-91f7-11ef-9270-0000a1ace081</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing workers vote down company’s latest contract offer, prolonging strike</title>
      <description>The rejection leaves the aerospace giant unable to resume production of most commercial airliners as its financial woes deepen with a $6.2 billion loss in the third quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42541b40-91ae-11ef-b6fb-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 02:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris says in CNN town hall she agrees Trump is a fascist following remarks from his former chief of staff</title>
      <description>“He himself has said he would terminate the Constitution of the United States,” Vice President Kamala Harris said after saying she agreed he was a fascist.

Her reaction came in response to a question about Donald Trump’s former chief of staff, John F. Kelly, who said this week that the former president fits the definition of being a fascist. Harris is increasingly focusing on what she and her allies portray as Trump’s authoritarian impulses, including threats to turn the military on his enemies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3ee5910-91a8-11ef-84a0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An American in Moscow who is creating deepfakes targeting the Harris campaign works with Russian intelligence, documents show</title>
      <description>John Mark Dougan, a former deputy Palm Beach County sheriff who has become one of Russia’s most prolific propagandists, was provided funding for his misinformation campaigns by an officer from the GRU, the country’s military intelligence service, according to Russian documents obtained by a European intelligence service and reviewed by The Washington Post. Dougan had long claimed to be working independently of the Russian government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ffc0170-9188-11ef-8b34-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Is iodized salt needed in your diet? Our food writers are answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Is iodized salt needed in your diet? Our food writers are answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66c2d230-915b-11ef-a748-0000a1ace13f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A caregiver’s body is failing, but family’s needs persist</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A caregiver’s body is failing, but family’s needs persist</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fe111f0-9158-11ef-a4e5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Mystics let go of general manager Mike Thibault and coach Eric Thibault in an unexpected move</title>
      <description>Mike Thibault, who led the Mystics to their first WNBA title in 2019, had a long tenure with the organization, for years serving as coach and general manager before stepping away from his coaching role, while retaining his GM duties, in November 2022. His son, Eric, took over as coach and directed the Mystics to a 33-47 record over two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f2e15d0-9156-11ef-8915-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Terrorist attack’ on Turkish defense and aerospace company kills at least 3 and injures 14, interior minister says</title>
      <description>Interior Minister Ali Yerlikaya confirmed the attack on the headquarters of Turkish Aerospace Industries near Ankara, the capital. No group immediately claimed responsibility. Apparent footage of the attack, broadcast on Turkish television and shared on social media but which has not been independently verified, shows gun-wielding assailants opening fire and smoke from an explosion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc823ac0-9151-11ef-a886-000a1ace9371</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How U.S. sanctions work, illustrated by a Russian oligarch’s $90 million yacht</title>
      <description>Following the yacht’s path to its seizure in Mallorca offers a step-by-step look at economic sanctions — and what happens to assets the U.S. wants to freeze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07a4a4a1-914b-11ef-8b0f-000a1ace74d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $20 delay in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f77abd60-9142-11ef-a7c1-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 13:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early voting. Walz video. Intelligence leak. E. coli outbreak. College enrollment. Bronny James. Buried treasure. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2541fd0-912d-11ef-8049-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin confirms U.S. seeing North Korean troops inside Russia</title>
      <description>Austin said it would be a “very, very serious issue” if the intention of the troops was to participate in the war in Ukraine. South Korea and Ukraine have accused Russia of training thousands of North Korean troops to participate in the ongoing war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26f14f10-9129-11ef-99ab-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 10:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia Supreme Court declines to reinstate election rules approved by Trump-allied board that critics warned could cause chaos</title>
      <description>The decision is yet another legal setback for the state election board, which sought to implement an array of changes in the weeks and months before the November vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43497470-90c1-11ef-8c6c-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 22:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E. coli outbreak linked to McDonald’s Quarter Pounders, CDC says</title>
      <description>The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is investigating an E. coli outbreak that has sickened 49 people in 10 states, including one person who has died. McDonald’s has stopped using fresh slivered onions and quarter-pound beef patties in several states while the investigation continues into which food ingredient is contaminated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d3eb6b0-90bf-11ef-b054-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 21:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antetokounmpo, Doncic or Jokic? See who’s No. 1 on our list of the top 100 NBA players as a new season tips off.</title>
      <description>The 2024-25 NBA season starts tonight. Here’s our annual look at the league’s best players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf3a090-90b8-11ef-8db6-0000a1ace793</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 21:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Republicans appear to be voting early after Trump pivots to encourage it</title>
      <description>GOP participation seems to at least partially reflect former president Donald Trump’s change of heart on early voting, which he slammed without evidence in 2020 as riddled with fraud but has heavily promoted this campaign season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">736bc7c0-90ad-11ef-81f6-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 19:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: Are the Commanders legitimate contenders? Post sportswriters are answering readers’ questions now.</title>
      <description>With a 5-2 record, Washington has been one of the top teams in the NFL this season, but it received a scare Sunday when rookie QB Jayden Daniels exited a victory with a rib injury. Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier are answering fans’ questions ahead of this weekend’s matchup against No. 1 pick Caleb Williams and the Chicago Bears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59b13ed0-90a0-11ef-ba6a-0000a1ace9d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 18:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How good are you at spotting misinformation online? Test yourself with these 8 questions.</title>
      <description>Misinformation is everywhere this election. See how well you can identify falsehoods — and how you stack up against other readers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c6c2bc0-9096-11ef-9d27-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters prefer Harris’s agenda to Trump’s. They just don’t realize it. Take this quiz to see how well you align with each candidate.</title>
      <description>Try our interactive quiz to see how well you (and other voters) align with each candidate’s agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5da2d410-908f-11ef-9e81-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Anxious mother-in-law is seriously ill. Doesn’t positivity help?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Anxious mother-in-law is seriously ill. Doesn’t positivity help?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5213ba0-908e-11ef-843e-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-CEO of Abercrombie &amp; Fitch arrested on sex trafficking charges</title>
      <description>Former Abercrombie &amp; Fitch chief executive Mike Jeffries was arrested Tuesday along with his romantic partner, Matt Smith, and another man, Jim Jacobson, in connection with a criminal sex trafficking investigation, according to two people familiar with the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0293ce0-907f-11ef-95f7-000a1ace3954</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 14:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A title for this team —  but not without controversy — in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4053800-9079-11ef-a7c1-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 13:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged leak of U.S. intel on Israel’s potential Iran attack plan is under investigation by the FBI</title>
      <description>The FBI said it is working with the Defense Department and intelligence agencies to probe the possible leak of classified material. Over the weekend, multiple news organizations reported that the documents contained information about Israel’s potential plans for a retaliatory attack on Iran, which sent a barrage of missiles into Israel on Oct. 1.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4606d140-9075-11ef-a7c1-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 12:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris campaign. Central Park Five. Washington state shooting. Israeli strike. Consent law. Student loans. NBA. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8f69fb0-9064-11ef-95c6-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 13-year-old gave birth. Idaho’s parental consent law snagged her care.</title>
      <description>The state’s new law requires parental permission for nearly all health care a minor receives. A young teen’s pregnancy got caught up in the consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca228a10-8ff7-11ef-8222-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 21:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A viral attack on Tim Walz features video of a man using a former student’s name to make false claims</title>
      <description>The real former student, a Hawaii man who attended a school where the vice-presidential candidate formerly taught, told The Washington Post that they never met and that he was dismayed to see the video. Millions of people have viewed social media posts containing the video since it was published last week on X.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e82d4b1-8fe9-11ef-8513-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This type of home could reinvent the American Dream and help fix the housing crisis</title>
      <description>Americans are desperate for more affordable and low-maintenance housing options</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">789aaaf0-8fcb-11ef-a0c9-0000a1aced6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Teen son is nasty to his parents, polite to the rest of the world</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Teen son is nasty to his parents, polite to the rest of the world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164cc040-8fc6-11ef-9cdb-000a1ace008d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trans youth who received gender-affirming care were largely satisfied with the treatments, survey finds</title>
      <description>A survey of more than 200 transgender and nonbinary youth who received gender-affirming medical care, such as puberty blockers and hormones, shows they were largely satisfied with the treatments they received, according to a study published Monday in JAMA Pediatrics, with only 4 percent — nine respondents — expressing some form of regret.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7521b930-8fbd-11ef-937e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 15:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College athletes are finally getting paid. A Post analysis reveals the winners and losers of this hidden economy.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post obtained and analyzed public records from power conference schools to reveal how boosters and corporations are doling out “name, image and likeness” money to college athletes — and how this hidden economy is fueling disparities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfcda1e0-8fb4-11ef-9e2e-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 14:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking into this archive in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d1227e0-8fb4-11ef-91e0-0000a1ace0b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 13:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris and Trump locked in dead heat in seven battleground states, Washington Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>The survey of more than 5,000 registered voters finds former president Donald Trump strongest in Arizona while Vice President Kamala Harris shows strength in Georgia. With two weeks to the election, some voters are still deciding, with more 18-to-25-year-olds uncommitted than those in other age groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26c92660-8fa4-11ef-af10-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential polls. Birth control. Israeli strike. Historic rainfall. Home prices. WNBA Finals. Pyramid dog. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cdf2fb0-8f9b-11ef-aecd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Dodgers win the National League pennant, setting up a star-studded World Series with the New York Yankees</title>
      <description>The Dodgers finished off the New York Mets in six games Sunday night and will face the Yankees in the best-of-seven World Series beginning Friday in Los Angeles. The high-profile matchup pits Shohei Ohtani, Mookie Betts and the Dodgers against Aaron Judge, Juan Soto and the Yankees for Major League Baseball's championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34b3b350-8f5c-11ef-a1ab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 03:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Liberty wins WNBA championship, defeating Minnesota Lynx in five games</title>
      <description>The Liberty prevailed in overtime in the winner-take-all Game 5 on Sunday night in Brooklyn to capture its first league title in its sixth trip to the Finals. After falling in last year's championship series, New York had the best record in the WNBA this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb2549f0-8f55-11ef-9395-0000a1ace147</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 02:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quarterback Jayden Daniels exits Commanders' game with apparent rib injury</title>
      <description>The star rookie, who guided Washington to a 4-2 record entering Sunday, left in the first quarter against the Carolina Panthers. The severity of his injury is not yet clear. The Commanders lead the Panthers 27-0 at halftime. Follow our live file for updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1290cd20-8f2b-11ef-ae73-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 21:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters in must-win Pennsylvania are full of doubt, anger and unease</title>
      <description>The Post drove 1,000 miles talking to voters in the most critical battleground state and found worries about Kamala Harris, fears about Donald Trump and uncertainty all over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7430eb0-8f24-11ef-ac49-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 20:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3c5fd0-8efc-11ef-9758-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The whistleblower who triggered Trump’s first impeachment asks: Was it worth it?</title>
      <description>The CIA analyst’s lonely stand upended his career and put his life at risk. Now he’s speaking about it for the first time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9731c010-8ef0-11ef-8080-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a068d870-8ee7-11ef-8513-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 13:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeowners love rooftop solar panels. But there’s a problem.</title>
      <description>As more and more homeowners turn to solar, thanks in part to more generous government incentives, it could become more expensive for the United States to meet its overall climate goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89885580-8e61-11ef-9c29-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 21:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would you be fooled by deepfakes of Trump and Harris? Test yourself.</title>
      <description>Artificial intelligence has made it easy to copy someone’s voice, allowing thousands of audio impersonations to flood the internet this election year.  Here’s how to tell what’s real.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5039e820-8e43-11ef-ba0f-0000a1acef7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 17:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m a manager with no real power. How do I support my employees?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m a manager with no real power. How do I support my employees?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86a8f560-8e37-11ef-9efc-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 16:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing and union leaders reach tentative deal to end machinists’ strike with a proposal that calls for a 35 percent pay hike</title>
      <description>The 33,000 machinists on strike will vote Wednesday on whether to approve the deal brokered with the help of acting Labor Secretary Julie Su. The work stoppage has halted production of some of the company’s top-selling jets and led the company to furlough thousands of employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b2ebb0-8e30-11ef-9033-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 15:44:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Putin-backed strongman who threw the Paris Games into chaos with a boxing ‘gender controversy’</title>
      <description>Banned from the Games, Russia wanted to upend the Olympics. Enter Umar Kremlev and a fierce battle over "gender tests" allegedly failed by two women boxers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd5fcc30-8e26-11ef-b8db-0000a1ace906</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 14:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f5ff0f0-8e1e-11ef-9033-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 13:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
