<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 09:03:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>President Joe Biden pardons his son Hunter</title>
      <description>The president said Sunday he had pardoned his son Hunter, who was found guilty of gun-related charges in Delaware and pleaded guilty to tax evasion in California. He said “raw politics has infected this process and it led to a miscarriage of justice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fc24e80-b047-11ef-94b3-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mar-a-Lago becomes a magnet for foreign leaders, haunting Biden’s final acts</title>
      <description>Declarations by President-elect Donald Trump that may or may not become policy have set some foreign governments on edge, while delighting others. Traditions to ensure a smooth transfer of power have been ignored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04389950-b038-11ef-a2be-0000a1ace2dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 23:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They didn’t thank you for your gift. Our personal finance columnist suggests ways to talk it out.</title>
      <description>They didn’t thank you for your gift. Our personal finance columnist suggests ways to talk it out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">effb5610-b016-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 19:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world fails to deliver a treaty on cleaning up plastic after marathon U.N. negotiations fall flat</title>
      <description>Delegates from more than 170 countries meeting in South Korea failed to agree on how to curb plastic pollution. A broad coalition of nations pushed for manufacturing cuts, but oil-rich countries balked at the idea of limiting future plastics production. Negotiators said they hoped to continue the talks next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afa32180-b00a-11ef-97ac-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb6b99c0-b006-11ef-b964-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4d48360-aff1-11ef-b09f-0000a1ace935</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 14:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Kash Patel as his choice to lead the FBI, an agency he has repeatedly criticized</title>
      <description>FBI directors serve 10-year terms, so Donald Trump would have to fire Christopher Wray, or Wray would have to resign before his term is up in 2027. Patel has publicly mused about targeting journalists and government officials, and he published a list of “deep state” names in a book last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036f3210-af78-11ef-a273-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best books of 2024, according to The Post’s Book World staff</title>
      <description>Expertly shaped fiction, brisk and original nonfiction: We've collected the year’s standouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2738dc20-af35-11ef-830b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 16:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">072ee081-af28-11ef-a273-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59 gifts to surprise everyone on your list</title>
      <description>From maximalist dog accessories to candles too pretty to burn, these gifts were selected for their quality, idiosyncrasy and charm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f61b2f90-ae9d-11ef-8fbc-0000a1ace0dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 22:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s inability to stand up to parents isn’t okay anymore</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s inability to stand up to parents isn’t okay anymore</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b7570-ae73-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 recipes to give your Thanksgiving leftovers new life</title>
      <description>15 recipes to give your Thanksgiving leftovers new life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a5d9520-ae6c-11ef-b047-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you know more about civics than an eighth-grader? Take our quiz.</title>
      <description>Like millions of Americans, you probably have strong feelings about how the president should lead, what Congress should do and how the courts should rule, but do you know what gives them those powers in the first place? Test your knowledge to see if you know as much about government as a middle-schooler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f482bc1-ae67-11ef-ac1c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 15:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. lawmakers back bill to legalize assisted dying in England and Wales, as more countries consider legalization</title>
      <description>The bill, modeled after Oregon’s law, would apply to terminally ill patients and could usher in one of the most dramatic social changes Britain has seen in years.

The bill still faces months of further scrutiny and procedural hurdles, but there’s a good chance of it becoming law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bdeb7e0-ae61-11ef-afed-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ce15e0-ae5e-11ef-9f50-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame’s post-fire restoration is unveiled with a grand tour led by France’s Macron. See the first photos.</title>
      <description>The tour is the first in-depth look inside since a 2019 fire gutted the cathedral. The tour celebrates the stonecutters, carpenters, sculptors and engineers who helped repair Notre Dame after French President Emmanuel Macron promised it would be rebuilt in five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b48d8081-ae4a-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 12:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s plans. Hostages in Gaza. Missing hiker found. Snow. Black Friday. Ancient footprints. Orcas vs. sharks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c0b4be2-ae49-11ef-ac1c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: X is Elon Musk’s MAGA World. Threads is a mess. Is Bluesky any better?</title>
      <description>Underneath the leadership of Musk, many people left X (formerly Twitter) with the digital equivalent of only the clothes on their back — abandoning their followings and taking only their usernames. Now the virtual town square is fragmented as people flee to bluer pastures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20f0f8f0-add4-11ef-86a1-0000a1ace902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: New job took care of the burnout. So why doesn’t it feel better?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: New job took care of the burnout. So why doesn’t it feel better?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56b5c2a0-adab-11ef-bc83-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercising to lose weight? Science says it rarely works.</title>
      <description>A metabolism researcher dispels myths about how we burn calories and how this changes as we age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc1f34e0-ada0-11ef-a6d2-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving! Play today's On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Turkey Day points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db9608b1-ad95-11ef-ba18-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to roast a turkey: Times and temperatures to count on</title>
      <description>How to roast a turkey: Times and temperatures to count on</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a33cbd0-ad90-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bomb threats. Middle East. Prisoner swap. Thanksgiving forecast. NFL schedule. Weight loss. Stem cells. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">448041d0-ad80-11ef-b94d-000a1ace27fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are America’s most fulfilling jobs, according to our Department of Data. One triumphed in a landslide.</title>
      <description>What jobs give you the most satisfaction in life? Which ones make you feel like you're contributing to the community? Which make you proud of your employer? We looked at the data!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e8ec5c0-ad13-11ef-9150-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 23:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our best Thanksgiving dessert recipes</title>
      <description>Our best Thanksgiving dessert recipes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47c29272-acfa-11ef-81f3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 20:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it better to roast a 20-pound turkey whole or cut it into parts? We’re answering your Thanksgiving cooking questions now.</title>
      <description>Is it better to roast a 20-pound turkey whole or cut it into parts? We’re answering your Thanksgiving cooking questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">279fd520-ace1-11ef-9b4a-000a1acec311</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 17:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diamonds are forever, but this lab grows them in weeks</title>
      <description>Lab-grown diamonds cost less and are more popular than ever. This is how they’re made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2653d150-acda-11ef-b9da-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 16:10:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Americans imprisoned in China have been released in a prisoner swap, according to U.S. officials</title>
      <description>The three U.S. citizens — John Leung, Kai Li and Mark Swidan — will be reunited with their families soon, according to a White House statement. They had been wrongfully detained in China for years. It was not immediately clear who else was part of the trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1376151-accf-11ef-93ce-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Thanksgiving myth in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ecf1420-accd-11ef-be0e-0000a1aceb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 14:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-Hezbollah cease-fire. Trump’s tariffs. Captured fugitive. Organ donors. Vaccines. Cold weather. Orca video. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fe86012-acb7-11ef-813a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For a low-stress Thanksgiving, get a head start on cooking with these make-ahead recipes for every part of your feast</title>
      <description>Preparing the Thanksgiving feast can feel like a whirlwind. Lighten the load with our menu of make-ahead dishes, including green beans, mashed and sweet potatoes, mac and cheese, stuffing and, yes, even the turkey. Everything can be made ahead, if you want to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75946320-ac43-11ef-ad4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hezbollah have agreed to cease-fire deal, Biden says</title>
      <description>The agreement, which passed a vote 10-1 in Israel's cabinet, takes effect on Wednesday at 4 a.m. local time and will pause a year-long conflict that has escalated in recent weeks, said U.S. and Israeli officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22eedc00-ac38-11ef-b98e-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We crowdsourced D.C. winter snowfall forecasts. Here's what they say.</title>
      <description>The hundreds of forecasts we gathered from readers, experts and our own Capital Weather Gang meteorologists project somewhat less snow than normal for the upcoming winter. Most people expect about a foot of snow compared to the normal amount, which is closer to 14 inches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfeb6420-ac31-11ef-97a0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A columnist’s first 50 years: George F. Will looks back on five decades of writing</title>
      <description>One secret of column-writing: Offer platoons of facts that give readers the delight of discovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94194530-ac2b-11ef-b67e-0000a1ace5d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to reduce Thanksgiving food waste? Give yourself permission to cook less.</title>
      <description>Want to reduce Thanksgiving food waste? Give yourself permission to cook less.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31b812e1-ac21-11ef-b2c4-000a1aced357</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Manners: We host 2 holiday parties to accommodate all our friends</title>
      <description>Miss Manners: We host 2 holiday parties to accommodate all our friends</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">668e0230-ac18-11ef-8e7d-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These batteries could harness the wind and sun to replace coal and gas</title>
      <description>New, hulking batteries can store enough renewable energy to replace polluting fossil fuel plants and power thousands of homes. Japan’s northernmost island, Hokkaido, is experimenting with technology that could help it power itself and export clean electricity to the rest of the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbfd79a1-ac0d-11ef-ae9a-0000a1acec73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A not-so-jolly holiday season for this retailer</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a78a4520-ac07-11ef-af6d-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Jack Smith. Cease-fire talks. Macy’s expenses. Weight-loss drugs. Big batteries. Thanksgiving snow. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7c2c3b0-abed-11ef-8cd3-0000a1ace849</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration proposes Medicare coverage of weight-loss drugs for millions of people, teeing up potential clash with RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>The plan to pay for the popular anti-obesity medications for 7.5 million Medicare and Medicaid beneficiaries would cost the federal government tens of billions of dollars. But the incoming Trump administration could block the plan, and Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the president-elect’s choice for secretary of Health and Human Services, is an avowed enemy of the drugs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15f528e0-abea-11ef-a38a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he’ll impose new tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China, citing illegal immigration and drug smuggling</title>
      <description>In a post on his social media site, the president-elect said he’d issue executive orders on his first day back in office, setting tariffs of 25 percent on imports from Mexico and Canada and 10 percent on imports from China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7e35360-ab92-11ef-9a66-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk and Ramaswamy race to build a ‘DOGE’ team for war with Washington</title>
      <description>Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy were tapped by President-elect Donald Trump to lead an advisory panel to find “drastic” cuts to the federal government. The two billionaire “Department of Government Efficiency” leaders have spent the past week in Washington and at Mar-a-Lago, seeking staff and interviewing seasoned political operators, legal specialists and top tech leaders, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c00edf01-ab78-11ef-8542-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One game, endless fun. Introducing Wridges, our new word game. You’ll be hooked from the first letter.</title>
      <description>One game, endless fun. Introducing Wridges, our new word game. You’ll be hooked from the first letter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87e89590-ab68-11ef-9d4b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Smith seeks to drop Trump from appeal of classified documents ruling but continue case against his two co-defendants</title>
      <description>The motion, coming an hour after Smith moved to drop the Jan. 6 election obstruction case against Donald Trump, would allow the Justice Department to continue appealing Judge Aileen Cannon’s ruling that Smith was unlawfully appointed as special counsel. Smith is seeking to preserve what he can of the criminal cases, while acknowledging that federal policy prohibits prosecuting a sitting president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78bc0f30-ab62-11ef-a126-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith asks to dismiss Trump’s 2020 election obstruction case but allows case to be revived in future</title>
      <description>The motion to dismiss charges without prejudice could put President-elect Donald Trump in the position of having to pardon himself before he leaves office to avoid future legal jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6178780-ab59-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A cheater’s new fiancée wants to hear his ex’s side of the story</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A cheater’s new fiancée wants to hear his ex’s side of the story</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f00eb830-ab4e-11ef-a168-0000a1ace71f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of your body start aging earlier than others, new research shows</title>
      <description>Scientists call this new area of research “organ aging,” and it’s redefining how we think about getting older.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72d73640-ab43-11ef-a126-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A TikTok take on a classic vegetable in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3153fcf0-ab3c-11ef-a249-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Taylor Bradford dies at 91. Her novels, mostly about resilient and wealthy women, have sold more than 90 million copies.</title>
      <description>Bradford, a British-American novelist who debuted in 1979 with “A Woman of Substance,” a rags-to-riches tale that she followed with more than 30 bestsellers, died Sunday. Ten of her books were made into TV miniseries and films.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea8e38a2-ab2a-11ef-b77f-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks. Israeli strike. Climate deal. Raw milk. Student death. ‘Glicked’ box office. Look-alike contest. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdf78da0-ab24-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
