<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>‘Particularly dangerous situation’ warning for confirmed tornado in Montgomery County</title>
      <description>Authorities advised people in the path of the storm to seek immediate shelter, and that there was a confirmed tornado near Poolesville and headed east.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97feeb60-2395-11ef-8bb9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 23:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Justice Alito’s account of the upside-down flag at his home doesn’t fully add up: A look at the major discrepancies</title>
      <description>Supreme Court Justice Samuel A. Alito Jr. has said that it was his wife who flew the banners, not him, and that she flew one of them after a neighborhood dispute. But his successive explanations have raised additional questions and, in some cases, conflicted with known facts, police records and accounts of neighbors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b1f5bd0-2388-11ef-aa50-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia appeals court pauses lower-court proceedings in Trump election case</title>
      <description>The order means the case against the former president and eight of his co-defendants, accusing them of a criminal conspiracy to overturn his defeat in the state, will almost certainly not be scheduled for trial before the fall election or even the new year. The appeals court is reviewing a request from the defendants to disqualify Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b55531-237e-11ef-9ca4-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birth control access could be threatened as conservatives mischaracterize IUDs and emergency contraception as causing abortions</title>
      <description>Since the Supreme Court overturned the right to abortion two years ago, far-right conservatives have been trying to curtail birth-control access by sowing misinformation about how various methods work to prevent pregnancy, even as Republican leaders scramble to reassure voters they have no intention of restricting the right to contraception, which polls show the vast majority of Americans favor.

Democrats are seeking to capitalize on the moment, with the Senate scheduled to hold a vote Wednesday on the federal right to contraception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29302410-2363-11ef-a74c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: The garden’s overrun with basil. What are some really good recipes using it? Our food writers are taking your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: The garden’s overrun with basil. What are some really good recipes using it? Our food writers are taking your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9654f8a0-2358-11ef-89d1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth’s record heat streak has now lasted an entire year, pushing the planet closer to a dangerous climate threshold</title>
      <description>Scientists announced that it was the hottest May on record, marking an entire year of uninterrupted record warmth. It is now highly likely that there will be a year in which temperatures exceed the global target of limiting global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) by 2028, the World Meteorological Organization said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b11abc0-2357-11ef-a579-0000a1aceb57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Ex offered son a loan — with strings that could trip up the family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Ex offered son a loan — with strings that could trip up the family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d480ca90-2354-11ef-8dfa-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing’s Starliner has entered orbit. Its first successful launch with astronauts on board came after years of setbacks.</title>
      <description>After multiple delays, the Atlas V rocket carrying Sunita “Suni” Williams and Barry “Butch” Wilmore entered orbit for an expected eight-day mission to the International Space Station.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eac0300-2350-11ef-89d1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing is making a third attempt to send Starliner into space for its first flight with astronauts aboard. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>If successful, the mission would mark the first time Boeing’s Starliner spacecraft has flown people, a key milestone for the company and for NASA, which is relying on the commercial sector to ferry its astronauts to space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6325de0-2349-11ef-b643-000a1acefb8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin says he’ll end Virginia’s participation in standards that zero-emission vehicles make up all new auto sales by 2035</title>
      <description>The standards were set by California and adopted by multiple other states. This marks at least the second time Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) has circumvented environmental standards passed by Democratic majorities in the Virginia legislature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ae2e352-2346-11ef-84c0-0000a1ace503</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular, mysterious soda is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13dba10-233f-11ef-a103-0000a1acecf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India’s election. Primary results. MDMA. Birth control. AI warning. Sinking city. Dr Pepper. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1321c21-232a-11ef-a5e6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incumbent Trayon White Sr. projected to win Democratic primary for D.C. Council Ward 8 seat</title>
      <description>The race pitted White, who was first elected in 2016, against two challengers who argued that the ward’s lingering troubles call for new leadership. White surmounted a financial disadvantage, including fines that his previous campaign committees owe to the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10fe4620-22d6-11ef-b2b0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls have closed in the D.C. Democratic primary. Follow our coverage to see results in Wards 7, 8 and more.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post is bringing you live coverage of election results, analysis and more as votes are tallied in several City Council races — including the open Ward 7 race, where 10 candidates are seeking to succeed former Mayor Vincent C. Gray.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c005fd00-22ce-11ef-af39-0000a1ace164</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 00:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Lawmakers expensed millions in 2023 under a new program that doesn’t require receipts. An earlier alert incorrectly said Rep. Gaetz was the top spender.</title>
      <description>he program, which kicked off last year after a House panel passed it with bipartisan support, was intended to make it easier for lawmakers to cover the cost of maintaining separate residences in D.C. and their home districts. But critics argue that its reliance on the honor system and lack of transparent record-keeping makes it ripe for abuse.

An earlier version of this article incorrectly said Rep. Matt Gaetz (R-Fla.) was the reimbursement program’s top spender in 2023. That analysis was based on data released by the House as of last week. But additional data The Post reviewed Tuesday showed that Rep. Jack Bergman (R-Mich.) was reimbursed for more than Gaetz was. This article has been updated and alert corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f6e1500-22c9-11ef-b0e7-0000a1acef7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 23:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr Pepper has joined Pepsi as the second-best-selling soda in the U.S. It’s still shrouded in mystery.</title>
      <description>Dr Pepper has joined Pepsi as the second-best-selling soda in the U.S. It’s still shrouded in mystery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f70da825-22bf-11ef-a64c-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 22:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA panel recommends against approving MDMA to treat PTSD. It’s unclear whether the agency will authorize the novel treatment.</title>
      <description>Committee members said there is not enough evidence that use of the drug, also known as ecstasy, can be used safely and effectively. But the Food and Drug Administration sometimes sets aside recommendations of its advisory panels, so there’s still a chance the agency will approve the first-of-its kind application for a psychedelic drug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15480720-22bd-11ef-b2b0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 21:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers expensed millions in 2023 under a new program that doesn’t require receipts. Rep. Matt Gaetz was the top spender.</title>
      <description>The program, which kicked off last year after a House panel passed it with bipartisan support, was intended to make it easier for lawmakers to cover the cost of maintaining separate homes in D.C. and their home districts. But critics argue that its reliance on the honor system and lack of transparent record-keeping makes it ripe for abuse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae890151-22a4-11ef-91b0-0000a1aced5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI firm employees write open letter warning of the technology’s grave risks to humanity</title>
      <description>Current and former workers with ties to OpenAI, Anthropic and Google’s DeepMind called on companies to provide greater transparency and whistleblower protections in a Tuesday letter. The letter was endorsed by AI luminaries including Yoshua Bengio and Geoffrey Hinton, considered the technology’s “godfathers,” and renowned computer scientist Stuart Russell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b38b5200-228d-11ef-8444-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it worth proposing with a simple, ‘subpar’ engagement ring?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it worth proposing with a simple, ‘subpar’ engagement ring?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932bbb50-228b-11ef-9683-0000a1ace928</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novak Djokovic, world No. 1 and defending champion, withdraws from French Open with knee injury</title>
      <description>Djokovic, a three-time champion at Roland Garros, tweaked his already-injured right knee during his five-set victory Monday over Argentina’s Francisco Cerundolo. Djokovic had been set to face Casper Ruud of Norway in the quarterfinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">759297a0-2289-11ef-90ea-0000a1ace129</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB issues lifetime ban to Padres infielder Tucupita Marcano for sports betting violations and disciplines 4 other players</title>
      <description>The league on Tuesday announced that Marcano, a 24-year-old from Venezuela who played for the San Diego Padres, had been “declared permanently ineligible.” Four other players — Michael Kelly, Jay Groome, José Rodríguez and Andrew Saalfrank — were suspended for a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e864c50-2283-11ef-a50b-0000a1ace061</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 15:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Trump attorney Kenneth Chesebro and other aides charged in Wisconsin over 2020 elector plot</title>
      <description>Chesebro is among three who were charged in connection with the former president’s attempt to overturn the election. The charges are the first in Wisconsin related to the effort, following charges in Arizona, Michigan, Nevada and Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b526c570-2280-11ef-affc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 14:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A colorful bird is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967d8af0-2276-11ef-9d0b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Early election returns in India indicate Prime Minister Narendra Modi’s party will struggle to win an outright majority</title>
      <description>The early results showed tepid support for Modi’s Bharatiya Janata Party, piercing the air of invincibility around the most dominant Indian politician in decades. Modi and his supporters had entered the election predicting a landslide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76b242d0-2265-11ef-beae-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:27:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Border rules. Hunter Biden. Anthony Fauci. Affirmative action. Maternal deaths. Giant hail. GameStop. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">974db8c1-2261-11ef-91b0-0000a1aced5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s left to decide on the Supreme Court docket? A lot. Here’s our guide to the major rulings to come.</title>
      <description>From gun rights to Donald Trump’s immunity claim, we are tracking major cases until the Supreme Court’s term wraps at the end of this month. The Court is expected to announce more opinions Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71dd1e10-21f7-11ef-a5b7-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 22:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The jury has been selected for Hunter Biden’s gun trial in Delaware. Opening statements are expected tomorrow.</title>
      <description>The president’s son faces three felony counts for allegedly lying about his drug use on a gun purchase form and then illegally possessing the gun while also using drugs. As Hunter Biden, his wife, first lady Jill Biden and others looked on, dozens of potential jurors from Wilmington, Del., were asked Monday whether they thought politics played a role in the judicial system and whether they could judge Hunter Biden impartially.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ed5380-21e7-11ef-8444-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 20:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plans to sign executive order that returns migrants to Mexico when illegal crossings exceed daily limit, officials say</title>
      <description>President Biden is expected to issue an order Tuesday that would shut off access to the U.S. asylum system when illegal border crossings exceed a daily threshold, according to four administration officials and people with knowledge of the plans.

Migrants would be ineligible for asylum consideration once the limit is surpassed, according to the officials, who spoke on the condition of anonymity because they were not authorized to discuss a pending White House order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3853b140-21de-11ef-bceb-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 19:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to relate to others without making it about you</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to relate to others without making it about you</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aa90ac0-21c3-11ef-9926-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 16:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During the coronavirus pandemic, we were told to stay 6 feet apart. There’s no science to support that.</title>
      <description>Physicians at the forefront of the country’s response to the health crisis, including infectious-disease expert Anthony S. Fauci, have acknowledged the six-foot rule “wasn’t based on data.” It remains clear that social distancing measures saved lives, but the reasons for telling people to maintain six feet of separation in public — compared with the World Health Organization’s recommendation of about three feet — are not clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0f6420-21c0-11ef-a39c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 15:49:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The record books are updated in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3c322d0-21ad-11ef-a953-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 13:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia co-opts far-right politicians in Europe with cash to promote anti-Ukraine agenda, officials say</title>
      <description>A front organization masquerading as a news website was used to funnel hundreds of thousands of euros to far-right politicians in more than five countries to plant Kremlin propaganda in Western media and bolster the position of pro-Russian candidates in this week’s European Parliament elections, according to interviews with a dozen European intelligence officials from five countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b2f4640-21a5-11ef-9deb-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 12:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. announces largest income tax settlement in city history</title>
      <description>Billionaire bitcoin investor Michael Saylor and the software company he founded have agreed to pay $40 million to settle a lawsuit by D.C.’s attorney general alleging he defrauded the city of millions in taxes by falsely claiming he lived in Virginia or Florida. Under the agreement, Saylor and MicroStrategy deny they violated District law and admitted no wrongdoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b617e270-219f-11ef-89ac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico election. Hunter Biden. Gaza cease-fire talks. Anthony Fauci. Religious schools. Simone Biles. Moon mission. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e8e7470-2198-11ef-a5e8-0000a1acec35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claudia Sheinbaum wins the Mexican presidency, becoming the first woman to lead the nation</title>
      <description>The victory by the 61-year-old scientist and former Mexico City mayor, a protégé of outgoing President Andrés Manuel López Obrador, consolidates the power of the leftist Morena movement. Morena has transformed Mexican politics in six years and focused attention on the poor, but opponents say it’s weakened democratic institutions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0937710-216e-11ef-bf16-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 06:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sally Buzbee steps down as editor of The Washington Post</title>
      <description>Publisher and CEO William Lewis announced on Sunday that she will be replaced temporarily by Matt Murray, the former editor of the Wall Street Journal. After the presidential election in November, Robert Winnett, of Telegraph Media Group, will take over.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd138670-2145-11ef-a151-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 01:09:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simone Biles wins ninth national all-around title at U.S. gymnastics championships</title>
      <description>Biles, 27, dominated the field in Fort Worth, extending her record for most all-around titles by an American gymnast. The next event for U.S. women's gymnasts is the Olympic trials, which begin June 28. The top finisher at the trials will automatically earn a spot on the team for the Paris Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5f25320-2144-11ef-9cb5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 01:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why restaurants are so loud, how it affects our health and what science says we can do about it</title>
      <description>Washington Post food critic Tom Sietsema began recording and publishing decibel levels in his reviews in response to reader feedback. Noise was the most cited complaint in Zagat’s last Dining Trends Survey in 2018, and it continues to dominate the conversation in online restaurant reviews. Experts are advocating standards that would not only alleviate customer complaints, but also protect the health of patrons and staff members. Learn about how sound behaves in restaurants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9aeb021-2123-11ef-af66-0000a1aceb32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 21:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a dramatic spat between Hunter Biden and his brother’s widow led to tomorrow’s trial</title>
      <description>When Hallie Biden found a newly purchased Colt Cobra .38 handgun in Hunter Biden’s truck, she put it in a shopping bag and drove to a high-end grocery store, where she tossed it in a trash can. That set off a chain of events that would trigger frantic text messages, launch another dark chapter in a doomed romance — and lead to Hunter Biden’s federal trial beginning Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7decf070-2113-11ef-8c7d-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 19:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>28 books to read this summer</title>
      <description>It’s going to be a busy travel season, and you’ll need books for all those trains, planes and automobiles. Our picks would make good company, from absorbing histories to funny fiction and everything in between.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf1e0630-2101-11ef-8243-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 17:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b252e70-20f9-11ef-b31b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 16:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s best decade, according to our Department of Data</title>
      <description>Pollsters asked Americans when the United States had the best economy, most moral society and best music. One variable best predicted their answers — and it wasn’t race, gender or politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec402720-20ed-11ef-8e92-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 14:39:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71162ba0-20e6-11ef-9cd5-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 13:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another beach house in North Carolina’s scenic Outer Banks just fell into the ocean. Others may follow.</title>
      <description>Rising seas and eroding shorelines have now claimed a half-dozen houses along the Cape Hatteras National Seashore in the past four years. Some property owners have been forced to take drastic measures to retreat from the oceanfront.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93606f00-205e-11ef-baa0-000a1acedb86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 21:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Listen to our columnists react to Donald Trump’s guilty verdict, the quality of his defense and consequences moving forward.</title>
      <description>Three Post Opinions columnists got together right after the Trump verdict was announced Thursday to talk through what just happened. This excerpt of their conversation has been edited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2c8cf50-204a-11ef-9d84-000a1acec3b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 19:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They took the children: The United States’ hidden legacy of using Indian boarding schools to destroy tribal culture and seize land</title>
      <description>For 150 years, the U.S. government ordered Native American children to be removed from their families and sent them to remote boarding schools to eradicate their cultures, assimilate them into White society and seize tribal land.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59bc7651-203a-11ef-a45c-0000a1ace09b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 17:14:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s guilty verdict sharpens the two big questions of this election, The Post’s chief correspondent writes</title>
      <description>Trump’s conviction on 34 felony counts is a precedent-breaking outcome that has sharpened the competition between him and President Biden to define the stakes and the choices for voters in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4431fb20-2030-11ef-afc6-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 16:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing is gearing up to send Starliner into space with two NASA astronauts on board. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The mission — a test flight for the space agency — comes after years of delays and setbacks for the company’s spacecraft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f18e621-202a-11ef-afc6-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 15:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new national spelling bee champion was crowned after knowing how to spell ‘abseil.’ How good of a speller are you? Take our quiz.</title>
      <description>Students compete in the Scripps National Spelling Bee by spelling words that could make one’s head spin. But there are dozens of everyday words that are regularly misspelled. Think you can find them all?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8e1f720-2020-11ef-bc5b-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 14:11:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
