<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 16:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes scaled-back platform that softens language on abortion, same-sex marriage</title>
      <description>The document, which is set to be discussed and voted on ahead of the GOP national convention in Milwaukee, hews to former president Donald Trump’s current position on abortion being an issue that should be decided by states — a departure from previous years when the party called for a nationwide restriction. It also affirms GOP support for deporting millions of undocumented immigrants, embracing tariffs and ending the Education Department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2088b221-3d42-11ef-a08d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No one had ever charged a school shooter’s parents with homicide. She did it anyway.</title>
      <description>A Post reporter embedded with Michigan prosecutor Karen McDonald as she pursued involuntary manslaughter charges against Jennifer and James Crumbley, whose 15-year-old son killed four students at Oxford High School. Go behind the scenes to see what it took for McDonald and her team to make legal history in a case few believed they could win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c144890-3d3d-11ef-80f4-0000a1ace8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 15:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s described as ‘boring’ but ‘sensible’ in today’s On the Record?</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d34c61-3d2e-11ef-8c94-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Beryl. France election. Biden concerns. Boeing plea deal. Russian troops. Coco Gauff. Koala cuddles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4148edf1-3d19-11ef-8fab-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beryl makes landfall near Matagorda, Tex., as a Category 1 hurricane</title>
      <description>Beryl came ashore at 4 a.m. Central time with peak winds of 80 mph. The storm is forecast to produce a “life-threatening” ocean surge and damaging hurricane-force winds. It is the first Atlantic hurricane to make landfall in the United States this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7a983b0-3d09-11ef-84a2-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 09:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing agrees to plead guilty to conspiring to defraud the government in a case linked to two jet crashes that killed 346 people</title>
      <description>Prosecutors alleged two Boeing pilots concealed key information from the government about a new automated control system aboard the 737 Max aircraft that was implicated in two fatal crashes in 2018 and 2019.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c80a8180-3cdf-11ef-9e05-000a1acef361</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 04:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Four senior House Democrats, in private leadership call, say Biden should step aside</title>
      <description>Those who made the case for the president to drop his reelection bid were Reps. Jerry Nadler (N.Y.), Joseph Morelle (N.Y.), Mark Takano (Calif.) and Adam Smith (Wash.), according to three people on the call who spoke on the condition of anonymity.

&lt;i&gt; A previous news alert incorrectly said that Rep. Ted Lieu (Calif.) was among the House Democrats who said on a private call Sunday that they wanted President Biden to end his reelection campaign. Lieu was on the call but said he did not speak. This alert has been corrected. &lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e764d50-3cc8-11ef-80f6-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 01:19:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five senior House Democrats, in private leadership call, say Biden should step aside</title>
      <description>Those who forcefully made the case for the president to drop his reelection bid were Reps. Jerry Nadler (N.Y.), Joseph Morelle (N.Y.), Ted Lieu (Calif.), Mark Takano (Calif.) and Adam Smith (Wash.), according to three people on the call who were granted anonymity to discuss a private meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">548e5a97-3cb4-11ef-96f0-0000a1ace027</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Amy Coney Barrett is charting her own path, with piercing questions and a willingness to break ranks with conservatives</title>
      <description>Barrett, 52, is still close to the right-leaning center of the Supreme Court and most often aligned with Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. and Justice Brett M. Kavanaugh. But she has called for a pragmatic, incremental approach to some cases in which her colleagues wanted to move more aggressively.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49b67dc0-3cad-11ef-be2d-000a1acec4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 22:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French election projections put a leftist alliance in the lead, as far right performs far below expectations. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The populist, anti-immigration National Rally party had been hoping to install France’s first far-right government since World War II, with 28-year-old Jordan Bardella as prime minister. A left-wing party alliance and candidates from President Emmanuel Macron’s centrist movement have been trying to block them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7761150-3c8b-11ef-a5c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 18:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is what it’s like to survive measles. One of the most contagious diseases once defeated in the U.S. is surging again.</title>
      <description>Vaccination had largely eliminated the scourge from the United States in 2000. But amid falling domestic vaccination rates, measles is back, with more cases this year than each of the past two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">943f3f51-3c83-11ef-9b6d-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 17:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dab06cd-3c7c-11ef-88c7-000a1ace4c77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 16:16:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do you like your hot dog? Explore our highly subjective guide to America’s best regional styles.</title>
      <description>How do you like your hot dog? Explore our highly subjective guide to America’s best regional styles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a184700-3c78-11ef-be2d-000a1acec4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 15:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most religious, and religiously diverse, places in America</title>
      <description>The Post’s Department of Data mined the U.S. Religious Census, a decennial count of America’s faithful, for insights into the geography of religious devotion, including claims on church attendance and actual behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">177d51a0-3c6f-11ef-a47c-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 14:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e30acf21-3c63-11ef-9f3f-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 13:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He decided to run on every street in Washington — and finished his 1,838th street on Friday. Here’s his big takeaway.</title>
      <description>Although there were some exceptions, like no highways and no streets banned by the Secret Service, Dion Thompson-Davoli's 1,400-mile labor of love left a lasting impression: “It’s magnificent,” he said of the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b07c470-3be6-11ef-90f5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 22:21:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL rookie and Maryland native Khyree Jackson was killed in a car crash along with two high school teammates in Prince George’s County</title>
      <description>Jackson, 24, was drafted by the Vikings in the fourth round of this year’s NFL draft. Jackson and his former teammates were killed early Saturday in a three-vehicle crash after their car was struck by another car and veered off the road in Upper Marlboro, according to Maryland State Police.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceba8b70-3bc6-11ef-80e9-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 18:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women’s No. 1 seed Iga Swiatek knocked out of Wimbledon in the third round by Yulia Putintseva of Kazakhstan</title>
      <description>Swiatek, the world’s top ranked player, dropped the second and third sets at the All England Club to Putintseva, who is ranked No. 27 in the world. Swiatek, of Poland, is a five-time Grand Slam tournament winner but has yet to advance past the quarterfinals at Wimbledon in her career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b214000-3bbd-11ef-a4f4-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 17:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer was missing holiday songs — so Alexandra Petri made 8. Listen to ‘Sunscreen (In My Eye),’ ‘Hot Dog 76’ and more.</title>
      <description>Everyone knows such beloved, definitely real hits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4c5a050-3bb3-11ef-bd11-000a1ace8644</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 16:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden relies on a little-known White House doctor who has never ordered a cognitive test for the president</title>
      <description>President Biden’s prime-time debate performance — where he mumbled, repeatedly misspoke and sometimes appeared confused — has put new scrutiny on the man that the president simply calls “Doc” and on his handling of the president’s health. Kevin O’Connor, the physician to the president, has grown extraordinarily close to Biden since becoming his personal doctor in 2009 but has kept a low profile in the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fedf680-3bad-11ef-b218-0000a1ace759</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 15:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We mapped weather forecast accuracy across the U.S. Look up your city.</title>
      <description>Everyone complains about the weather forecast, but some people have more cause to grumble than others. Find out how accurate the forecast is where you live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3a13ba0-3ba0-11ef-99e0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 14:05:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfd9fe70-3b9b-11ef-be0a-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reformist Masoud Pezeshkian will be Iran’s next president</title>
      <description>A heart surgeon and relative unknown, Pezeshkian campaigned on engaging with the West to help free the country’s economy from crippling sanctions. He prevailed in the second round of snap elections Friday organized after the death of President Ebrahim Raisi in a May helicopter crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f67a240-3b54-11ef-a889-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 04:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This natural gas exporter is building a fortress on sinking land. Can its 26-foot-high wall protect it from sea level rise?</title>
      <description>In a part of Louisiana threatened by hurricanes and storm surge, a company has built a massive sea wall around its gas export plant.
That raises a question: How far will the fossil fuel industry go to protect itself from climate impacts it helped cause?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a783b5b0-3b1a-11ef-9c74-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Warner (D-Va.) is seeking to assemble a group of senators to ask Biden to exit the presidential race</title>
      <description>Warner is telling Democratic senators that Biden can no longer stay in the election in the wake of his faltering debate performance, according to two people familiar with private conversations who spoke on the condition of anonymity to talk freely.
As the chair of the Senate Intelligence Committee, the Virginia Democrat is viewed as a serious voice privately advocating for the president to step aside. He represents a state that Democrats must win in November to maintain their hold on the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed43c9a1-3b06-11ef-b109-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has displayed signs of accelerated aging with lapses appearing more common, those who have interacted with him say</title>
      <description>Aides, foreign leaders, donors and members of Congress say Biden has seemed slower and more often loses his train of thought in recent months, though close aides insist he remains mentally sharp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12807af0-3ae0-11ef-9f63-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Supreme Court clears way for ballot drop boxes, reversing an earlier decision by a conservative-controlled court</title>
      <description>Liberals on the Wisconsin Supreme Court on Friday overturned a decision that banned absentee ballot drop boxes made by conservatives when they controlled the court two years ago. The 4-3 ruling came a year after liberals took a majority on the top court in a crucial swing state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2199b020-3ad5-11ef-8c52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager. It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager. It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4472cf20-3ad3-11ef-9a2d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican excommunicates Carlo Maria Viganò, former ambassador to the U.S., for refusing to recognize the pope</title>
      <description>In a rare trial, the Vatican took action against one of Pope Francis’s most vociferous internal critics. Viganò, who was loyal to the previous pope, Benedict XVI, had called on the pope to resign, be arrested, and excoriated him in harsh terms, including calling him “a servant of Satan.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3546a171-3ace-11ef-8c52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy adds 206,000 jobs in June, as the resilient labor market continues to grow despite some headwinds</title>
      <description>The labor market notched another month of growth in June, according to data released Friday from the Bureau of Labor Statistics. Even as interest rates remain high, weighing on some parts of the economy, the labor market continues to buoy workers, wages and consumer spending, preventing a broader downturn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5bddf50-3aca-11ef-a88f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keir Starmer becomes Britain’s next prime minister, ushering in a new era after 14 years of Conservative rule</title>
      <description>King Charles III invited the Labour Party leader to form a government, after Conservative Prime Minister Rishi Sunak tendered his resignation at Buckingham Palace. It marks a huge reversal for Britain’s top parties, with a new government dominated by the center left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78b626f0-3ac0-11ef-9471-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election. Biden interview. Hurricane Beryl. Jobs market. Threads. Wimbledon. Hot dogs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b93e42f0-3abd-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election exit poll projects big win for Labour, ending 14 years of Conservative Party rule</title>
      <description>In an election that was more about mood than policy, voters appear to have conveyed their frustration with the incumbent Conservative Party and a willingness to give a chance to a renewed Labour Party, purged of its hard-left elements and socialist rhetoric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff1112a1-3a48-11ef-a4de-0000a1ace5dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new men’s hot-dog eating champion is crowned: Patrick Bertoletti ate 58. Miki Sudo downed a record 51 to win the women’s contest.</title>
      <description>Bertoletti won for the first time, while 10-time champion Sudo defended her title at this year's Nathan's Famous International Hot Dog Eating Contest, held at Coney Island in New York City. It was the first time since 2004 that Joey Chestnut, the 16-time champion who had won the previous eight contests, was missing from the competition. He was banned last month after signing a sponsorship agreement with Nathan's rival Impossible Foods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbbfe0a0-3a27-11ef-ae5c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Guy who berated spouse over butter would like his second chance now</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Guy who berated spouse over butter would like his second chance now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2de9221-3a1e-11ef-94ab-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We spoke to dozens of Biden’s delegates. Some are having doubts.</title>
      <description>In interviews with more than three dozen delegates to next month’s Chicago convention, most expressed support. But some were candid about their preference for another option, perhaps Vice President Harris. All said they will vote for President Biden — unless he bows out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e81bc730-3a1a-11ef-b633-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands will celebrate Independence Day by becoming U.S. citizens — after taking a civics test. Try our quiz to see if you’d pass.</title>
      <description>Before taking part in naturalization ceremonies, all aspiring U.S. citizens must prove their knowledge of civics in an oral exam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a456ff20-3a0f-11ef-9c18-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 14:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Fourth! Celebrate with today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Enjoy the holiday!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43b5a40-3a09-11ef-9ea3-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boil-water advisory lifted for D.C. and Arlington; utility says it confirmed that water quality ‘never deviated' from EPA standards</title>
      <description>The warnings were issued because of clarity issues, which can interfere with disinfection or indicate the presence of bacteria, viruses and parasites, according to D.C. Water.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc0303c1-3a04-11ef-aced-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign crisis. Hurricane Beryl. U.K. election. Wildfire. Banned additive. Longer workweek. Ant surgery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8502ee60-39f4-11ef-9051-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. and Arlington issue boil-water advisories</title>
      <description>The District and Arlington County advised residents to boil their water because of clarity issues in local water sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26bd5511-39b9-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and aides concede he needs to quickly demonstrate his fitness for office or face pressure to step aside</title>
      <description>Growing concern from Capitol Hill, top donors and senior party strategists, including some of his own advisers, prompted Biden to start contacting allies in recent days to admit that he is in a tough moment and that he has to prove to voters he is up for the job.
His critics have been shaken by his relative inaction over the previous six days to directly address the panic ignited by his halting debate performance last Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bab15b0-3989-11ef-914d-0000a1ace264</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 22:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat advisory issued for D.C. area on the Fourth of July with strong storms also possible</title>
      <description>Factoring in humidity, it could feel as hot as 100 to 105 Thursday afternoon, prompting a heat advisory from the National Weather Service for areas near the Interstate 95 corridor. The heat and humidity could also fuel some strong late-day thunderstorms with dangerous lightning, strong winds and heavy rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a34ade30-397e-11ef-ac86-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If not Biden, who? Five columnists rate the potential field of replacements for the Democratic presidential nominee.</title>
      <description>If President Biden were to decide not to run for reelection, who should replace him? That would be a question for the 4,000-plus delegates in August at the Democratic National Convention in Chicago, but before then, it’s a question for five Post Opinions columnists, who kicked the tires on the options over email this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f68b7fc0-397c-11ef-904b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents of teen dad wonder if they’re the ones making mistakes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents of teen dad wonder if they’re the ones making mistakes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b084e40-3955-11ef-a9fb-0000a1aced20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why are some restaurants switching to fixed-price menus? Our food critic is answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why are some restaurants switching to fixed-price menus? Our food critic is answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe04030-394f-11ef-9a8d-0000a1ace241</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who are America’s best leaders? How can we make more of them? Garrett Graff explores what makes a good leader in his first column.</title>
      <description>Great leaders are scarce. How do we increase the supply?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e29d21d0-3945-11ef-a7bc-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A duo that ‘could be magical’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67b54d89-3940-11ef-9b24-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sentencing delay. Biden crisis. Alzheimer’s drug. India stampede. Wildfires. Covid cases. Frog saunas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62770940-392b-11ef-a2ee-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. would pursue Donald Trump's criminal cases past Election Day, even if he wins</title>
      <description>Prosecutors believe a Justice Dept. ban on charging or prosecuting sitting presidents applies to Inauguration Day, not Election Day, according to people familiar with internal deliberations. That means Trump could face court hearings or even trials until Jan. 20, 2025, if he is elected in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b750f171-38c6-11ef-9301-0000a1ace642</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
