<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 20:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans challenge legitimacy of overseas votes, including military ballots, as legal fight expands</title>
      <description>A Pennsylvania lawsuit opens a new front in GOP efforts to raise questions about the validity of mail-in ballots, targeting a group once seen as off-limits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52147f71-873b-11ef-baab-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 19:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the damage caused by Hurricane Milton in photos, videos and maps of Florida</title>
      <description>Milton’s quadruple impact of deadly tornadoes, heavy rain, hurricane-force wind and storm surge left debris in Florida from coast to coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58b763f0-8728-11ef-9947-0000a1ace499</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Just found out once-close brother is getting married today</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Just found out once-close brother is getting married today</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca4d6df1-8720-11ef-9011-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 16:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ethel Kennedy dies at 96. The widow of Sen. Robert F. Kennedy kept her family grounded through decades of tragedy.</title>
      <description>After Sen. Kennedy’s assassination in 1968, his wife — once labeled "America's most admired woman" — remained fiercely loyal to his memory and saw it as her life’s work to further his commitment to social justice and to anchor his ideas forever in American culture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95e1ec20-871c-11ef-b611-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Woodward and Carl Bernstein's 1989 interview with Trump was lost in storage for over 30 years. Woodward finally found the tape.</title>
      <description>The yet-to-be-president holds forth on strength, friendship, dealmaking, public service and building violations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a15a0190-8718-11ef-b723-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 15:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio voters dismiss false claims about Haitians, but Trump has slight lead, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>Most Ohio voters don’t believe former president Donald Trump’s debunked claim that Haitian immigrants in Springfield are “eating people’s pets,” and agree with Gov. Mike DeWine’s defense of Haitians as hard workers who are in the United States legally, a Washington Post poll finds.

But the former president holds a six percentage point edge over Kamala Harris among likely voters in the Buckeye State – 51 percent to 45 percent – similar to his eight-point winning margin four years ago. And a must-win Senate election for Democrats to keep control of the chamber is essentially tied, with 48 percent supporting Democratic Sen. Sherrod Brown and 47 percent supporting Republican Bernie Moreno, well within the poll’s margin of error of plus or minus 3.5 percentage points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ff7ddd0-8710-11ef-bd86-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rat Pack-era spot goes down in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3dbc480-870b-11ef-9f80-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased further in September in last consumer price index report before Americans vote with the economy a top concern</title>
      <description>Price increases have slowed significantly this year, but they continue to weigh on Americans’ minds, as they head to the polls to vote in the November presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f3b5d0-8703-11ef-9069-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 12:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton leaves trail of damage, flooding across Florida. More than 3 million are without power. Follow live updates.</title>
      <description>Heavy rains and winds continued to lash parts of Florida. Milton, which made landfall as a Category 3 storm on Wednesday night, is now Category 1 and moving off the state's east coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c53f9840-86fa-11ef-85e7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 11:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in literature awarded to South Korean writer Han Kang</title>
      <description>Kang is best known in the U.S. for her novel “The Vegetarian.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bacdde00-86f8-11ef-8093-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 11:13:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton. Harris campaign. Abortion ad. Boeing strike. Climate warning. Rafael Nadal. Northern lights. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9277da0-86f6-11ef-a3fd-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rafael Nadal to retire. Tennis legend won 22 Grand Slam tournaments.</title>
      <description>The Spanish star, plagued by a series of injuries, said in a video posted on social media that he will retire after playing in the Davis Cup Finals in November in Malaga, Spain. "The reality is that it has been some difficult years, these last two especially. I don't think I have been able to play without limitations."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66365570-86ee-11ef-b919-000a1ace3f7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 09:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton has made landfall sooner than expected in Florida, south of Tampa Bay</title>
      <description>Milton, now the fifth hurricane to strike the Gulf Coast this year, swept ashore near Sarasota around 8:30 p.m. eastern time. It's expected to continue barreling through the Florida Peninsula and could produce life-threatening storm surge and devastating hurricane-force winds, as well as potentially catastrophic flooding from heavy rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f0c3a30-86a0-11ef-9641-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 00:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wildlife populations plummeted by three-quarters in the past 50 years, new analysis shows</title>
      <description>The new World Wildlife Fund report, which draws upon the Living Planet Index managed by the group and the Zoological Society of London, assesses the state of 5,495 species of amphibians, birds, fish, mammals and reptiles around the world. It shows the extent to which human activity is decimating wildlife through habitat destruction, overexploitation and other causes. The worst average declines were in Latin America and the Caribbean, at 95 percent, followed by Africa at 76 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86657d00-8692-11ef-9641-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 23:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where things stand in the fight for the House and Senate as Election Day nears</title>
      <description>With less than four weeks to go, Republicans appear poised to win the Senate, which is currently controlled by the Democrats. The Democrats, meanwhile, seem to have a slight edge in the race for the Republican-controlled House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de319e50-8689-11ef-b31c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton is expected to make landfall tonight as tornadoes ravage Florida. Check forecasts and updates before it closes in.</title>
      <description>The storm is expected to make landfall between Tampa and Sarasota, most likely between 10 p.m. and midnight Eastern time. But within the next few hours, conditions will begin to deteriorate as the storm approaches land.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7524f70-8682-11ef-b141-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) stokes fear of vast noncitizen voting. But records don’t back up his claim.</title>
      <description>Youngkin has boasted about purging 6,303 noncitizens from the state’s voter rolls. But a review of state court records and interviews with elections officials found no evidence that any noncitizens have tried to vote during his term in Virginia, and that most of the 6,303 he purged actually stemmed from errors on paperwork at the Department of Motor Vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">844cb220-8671-11ef-b0b4-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 19:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton is closing in on Florida as the state braces for serious impact. Get live updates and see a city-by-city forecast.</title>
      <description>The storm remains an extremely dangerous Category 4 storm and is set to make landfall within a couple of hours of midnight, probably between Tampa and Sarasota. Dangerous hurricane-force winds and life-threatening storm surge are expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe446ad0-865a-11ef-ac1b-0000a1ace960</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:24:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé’s family complains often about the other ‘in-law women’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé’s family complains often about the other ‘in-law women’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba5f9e01-8657-11ef-9641-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists have said we can cool the planet back down. Now they’re not so sure.</title>
      <description>Scientists have long said that we can reverse global warming if the planet passes 1.5 degrees Celsius above pre-industrial levels. But a new study shows that the damage from that so-called “overshoot” — including massive sea level rise — could last for centuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">855fa460-8653-11ef-9641-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sietsema just shared his 40 favorite D.C. restaurants. Ask him all about his picks in his live chat.</title>
      <description>Tom Sietsema just shared his 40 favorite D.C. restaurants. Ask him all about his picks in his live chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82d1ca60-864f-11ef-a1c8-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 15:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A billionaire is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adf4cd80-8642-11ef-bfcc-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best restaurants in the D.C. area, including longtime classics and dazzling newcomers, as picked by food critic Tom Sietsema</title>
      <description>In his 25th annual fall dining guide, The Post’s food critic is serving up dining destinations for every taste. Among the highlights: groundbreaking Indian off H Street NE, a Greek oasis in North Bethesda, an emerging Ethiopian eatery in Alexandria, and Tom’s Restaurant of the Year, featuring irresistible Mexican street food on 14th Street NW.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">531a0da0-8640-11ef-a950-0000a1ace37b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 13:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton. Election 2024. Bob Woodward’s book. Gaza death toll. Ghost guns. TikTok lawsuits. Bitcoin mystery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a647d330-862d-11ef-ac1b-0000a1ace960</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in chemistry awarded to David Baker, Demis Hassabis and John M. Jumper for work on proteins</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Wednesday by the Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences for research that cracked the code of proteins. Baker built entirely new kinds of proteins. Hassabis and Jumper used an AI model to predict proteins’ complex structures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8550f7d0-8626-11ef-bf12-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 10:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. frantically tried to stop the threat of Russian nuclear use, and 4 other key revelations from Bob Woodward’s new book</title>
      <description>Woodward’s “War,” set to be released next week, is the fourth book by the author and Washington Post associate editor since Donald Trump’s upset victory in 2016. It reveals how a years-long political contest between Trump and Joe Biden — and now Trump and Kamala Harris — has unfolded against the backdrop of cascading global crises.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">532ba2a0-85b8-11ef-a67c-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does it take to digitize 13 billion records? Sarah Vowell brings us into the agency undertaking the monumental task.</title>
      <description>Sarah Vowell on the National Archives</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ff07240-85ad-11ef-b1ec-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 19:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton could be one of Florida’s worst storms in a century. See the city-by-city forecast as it nears.</title>
      <description>After probably making landfall within 100 miles of Tampa on Thursday morning, Milton is expected to track eastward across central Florida as it spreads strong winds, heavy rain and the potential for tornadoes in much of the state. Here are the forecasts for six Florida cities in or near Milton’s path.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13b076b0-85a3-11ef-8ed0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 18:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to allow Biden administration’s regulation of nearly untraceable firearms known as ghost guns</title>
      <description>A majority of justices on the Supreme Court seemed poised during oral arguments to uphold a major gun regulation imposed by the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives. The rule requires background checks, serial numbers and sales records for ghost guns, which are assembled from kits and have been used in a growing number of crimes over the last decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dda88e80-8594-11ef-991d-0000a1ace557</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 16:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In landmark move, EPA requires removal of all U.S. lead pipes within a decade</title>
      <description>Nearly 40 years after lead pipes were banned in new construction, the Environmental Protection Agency finalized a rule Tuesday requiring water utilities to replace all existing pipes within 10 years. The initiative, which would eliminate a toxic threat to American children, is projected to cost tens of billions of dollars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55880a00-8588-11ef-8f8f-0000a1ace9d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 15:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Jets fire coach Robert Saleh after a disappointing 2-3 start. He is the first NFL coach to be fired this season.</title>
      <description>Saleh, 45, was in his fourth season as the Jets' head coach and had a record of 20-36. The team's offense struggled this fall, despite the return of quarterback Aaron Rodgers from injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a35ad00-8582-11ef-991d-0000a1ace557</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than a dozen states sue TikTok, alleging its addictive features hook and harm children</title>
      <description>The states are filing lawsuits Tuesday accusing TikTok of harming the well-being of children, in a bipartisan salvo that amplifies the company’s legal perils as it tries to stave off a federal ban.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92607330-857f-11ef-99eb-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 14:14:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spending on election ads in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ca2dd40-8579-11ef-884a-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump secretly sent coronavirus tests to Putin during 2020 shortage, new Bob Woodward book says</title>
      <description>“War,” by Woodward, traces how Presidents Donald Trump and Joe Biden responded to an international crisis and concludes that Trump is worse than Richard M. Nixon, the president exiled by the Watergate scandal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72dccc50-8577-11ef-94f5-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 13:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 key moments from the Kamala Harris ‘60 Minutes’ interview</title>
      <description>The vice president talked about owning a gun, her economic plan and immigration during the “60 Minutes” election special, a long-standing tradition for major-party presidential candidates.

Her rival, Donald Trump, backed out of the appearance, CBS said. Trump campaign manager Steven Cheung took aim at the program last week, saying the interview had not been scheduled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">150fafd0-8567-11ef-bf6a-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Milton. “60 Minutes.” Supreme Court. Lebanon. Lead pipes. Cissy Houston. Lost cities. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e61e9a0-8564-11ef-a7f8-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 11:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in physics awarded to John Hopfield and Geoffrey Hinton for discoveries that enable artificial neural networks</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Tuesday by the Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences for research that used tools from physics to help “lay the foundation for today’s powerful machine learning.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62470910-855d-11ef-80c3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 10:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who uses public libraries the most? There’s a divide by religion — and politics — our Department of Data found.</title>
      <description>The top library users all have one thing in common. But the Americans least likely to use libraries fall into two groups, each of which share some surprising traits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84cf8060-84f5-11ef-9168-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 21:45:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milton rapidly intensifies to a Category 5 hurricane and is predicted to hit Florida as a large, powerful storm. See the forecast.</title>
      <description>While Milton is forecast to weaken modestly before striking Florida’s west coast Wednesday, it could hit flood-prone Tampa with a devastating ocean surge over 10 feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00855b40-84c8-11ef-9011-0000a1aceb05</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Late 20s and facing societal pressures to settle down</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Late 20s and facing societal pressures to settle down</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60992e10-84c5-11ef-8d8d-0000a1aced44</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 16:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming out of retirement in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70372f30-84b0-11ef-bb2e-0000a1acec54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allies threaten Deloitte contracts after employee shares JD Vance chats</title>
      <description>Republicans backing Donald Trump are threatening Deloitte, a consulting firm that is one of the federal government’s largest business partners, with the loss of billions of dollars in contracts because an employee shared messages from 2020 in which Vance, now the GOP vice-presidential nominee, criticized the then-president’s record. 

Ethics experts said the episode is a potentially ominous preview of how a second Trump administration might use the enormous power the federal government wields over private industry to punish political acts by individual workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f55d430-84a8-11ef-aec5-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 12:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oct. 7 anniversary. JD Vance. Supreme Court. Hurricane threat. Overdose deaths. AI videos. Better AC. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d153ed0-849b-11ef-b698-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in physiology or medicine awarded to Victor Ambros and Gary Ruvkun for discovery of microRNA</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Monday for the discovery of microRNA, which play an important role in gene regulation and how organisms develop and function.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78ff05a0-8494-11ef-91bc-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 10:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world needs a better AC. These researchers think they’ve found one.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post traveled to India to see how prototypes tackle some of the hottest, most humid conditions on Earth — and to gauge how much they could shrink air conditioning’s rapidly growing emissions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0f7f6c0-842b-11ef-ba23-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 21:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c27bc80-83fc-11ef-8098-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 16:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Democrat is running a campaign she’s sure to lose. That’s the point.</title>
      <description>Kate Barr is waging a sure-to-lose campaign for a seat in the North Carolina legislature as a protest over gerrymandering, which has made elections uncompetitive in states nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fccbf010-83f3-11ef-88ff-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 15:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d880ef60-83e6-11ef-96b8-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2024 13:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vanderbilt stuns top-ranked Alabama in an upset that shakes up the college football season</title>
      <description>The Commodores upset the Crimson Tide, 40-35, on Saturday in Nashville. It was their first victory in the series since 1984.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">782b2340-8375-11ef-a302-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 23:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel’s penetration of Hezbollah and Mossad’s lethal pager operation</title>
      <description>The devices that killed or maimed as many as 3,000 Hezbollah operatives on Sept. 17 were designed by the Israeli intelligence service and assembled in Israel. A two-step de-encryption procedure built into the pagers ensured that most users would be holding them with both hands when they detonated, according to officials familiar with the operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24e5fd90-8366-11ef-b3f6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
