<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard rejects Trump administration demands for oversight, putting nearly $9 billion of the school’s federal funding at risk</title>
      <description>Harvard University officials on Monday rejected the Trump administration’s demands for changes at the school, saying the government’s directives amount to overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc10550-1956-11f0-ae10-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department’s budget would be slashed by nearly half under Trump plan, internal memo says</title>
      <description>The document, reviewed by The Washington Post, targets spending on humanitarian assistance, global health and international organizations such as the United Nations and NATO. The blueprint represents a decline of $27 billion from funding levels approved by Congress for 2025, though it is unclear whether lawmakers would approve such steep cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58a52a30-1951-11f0-b851-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador’s president says he won’t return wrongly deported Maryland man to U.S.: ‘Of course I’m not going to do it’</title>
      <description>Salvadoran President Nayib Bukele said Monday during a meeting with President Donald Trump that he did not plan to return Kilmar Abrego García to the United States. Abrego García is at the center of an ongoing court battle after the U.S. government wrongly deported him to El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f64b80-194b-11f0-8bf2-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family annoyed that golden goose is conscious of credit card debt</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family annoyed that golden goose is conscious of credit card debt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9909fe0-1949-11f0-8674-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which home energy upgrades will save you money? We did the math.</title>
      <description>Going green at home can reduce emissions — but may also raise your utility bills, even with tax credits. The Washington Post asked experts to analyze a real-life scenario for a fairly typical American home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41ce6470-193d-11f0-9273-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new award in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77c22a61-1935-11f0-9060-0000a1ace86c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with attempted murder and terrorism in fire at Pennsylvania governor’s home. He told police of his hatred for Shapiro.</title>
      <description>According to a police affidavit, Cody Balmer told police that he set the fire and that he would have attacked the Gov. Josh Shapiro with a hammer if he’d found him on the property.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcbcc741-1928-11f0-ad12-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff confusion. Arson attack. Wrongly deported man. Detained student. Home prices. Car pollution. Masters drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a13d11e1-191f-11f0-be09-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Vargas Llosa dies at 89. The Nobel Prize-winning author from Peru probed authoritarian rule in Latin America in his novels.</title>
      <description>He helped lead the Latin American “boom” of literary fiction in the 1960s, which produced some of the era’s most-acclaimed novels. He also sought to remedy social ills — as he insisted intellectuals must — with a quixotic run for the presidency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e489d650-18d3-11f0-a183-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration official who oversaw dismantling of USAID leaves State Department</title>
      <description>During his three months at the agency, Pete Marocco worked closely with tech billionaire Elon Musk, with both recommending severe cuts to USAID and State Department programs, according to U.S. officials familiar with the situation who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss personnel matters. It was not immediately clear why Marocco stepped down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f80b9190-18cf-11f0-8567-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A State Department memo said the Trump administration produced no evidence that a Tufts student supported antisemitism or terrorism</title>
      <description>The internal memo, prepared days before Rumeysa Ozturk was detained by ICE agents, raises doubts about the Trump administration’s public claims that the doctoral student engaged in activities “in support of Hamas.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b125c880-18c6-11f0-8d24-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rory McIlroy wins the Masters in a playoff over Justin Rose, completing the career Grand Slam with his fifth major championship</title>
      <description>McIlroy began Sunday with a two-shot lead but needed to survive some late misadventures that left him tied with Rose, who started the day seven shots behind. It's the first green jacket for McIlroy, who becomes just the sixth man to complete the career Grand Slam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5613ad1-18bd-11f0-8bec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38-year-old man in custody after arson attack on Gov. Josh Shapiro's mansion, Pennsylvania police say</title>
      <description>Cody Balmer of Harrisburg was taken into custody Sunday in connection with what Shapiro (D) described as a “targeted” attack hours after he and his family celebrated the Jewish holiday of Passover at the governor’s mansion. Officials said they did not yet know a motive and charges haven't been filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79dadd30-18b1-11f0-8bec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris said au revoir to cars. Air pollution maps reveal a dramatic change.</title>
      <description>The shift in pollution levels shows how ambitious policymaking can directly improve health in large cities. Air pollution is often described by health experts as a silent killer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab32cc81-18ac-11f0-ae10-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro’s home was set on fire in an act of arson that caused ‘significant’ damage, state police say</title>
      <description>Shapiro and his family awoke to police banging on their door as they responded to the fire at the governor’s mansion in Harrisburg. The family was safely evacuated with no injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77922250-1888-11f0-9c58-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 16:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81b5c820-1880-11f0-addb-0000a1ace9d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood’s intimacy coordinator field faces growing pains as A-list stars decline coaching</title>
      <description>Gwyneth Paltrow and Mikey Madison are among the stars who have opted to work without sex scene advisers. Those in the emerging profession defend their role on sets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff86e970-1874-11f0-8382-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 14:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f54fa450-186b-11f0-a82c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when 3,000 heavy metal fans take a Caribbean cruise</title>
      <description>On the 70,000 Tons of Metal cruise, metalheads from around the world sail from Miami to Jamaica with bands playing on a pool deck stage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b64c87a0-17df-11f0-8978-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials have the private goal of deporting at least 1 million immigrants this year. Analysts say that's unrealistic.</title>
      <description>Deporting 1 million immigrants in one year would surpass previous statistics, as the highest number was more than 400,000 a year when Barack Obama was president. But there’s a reason that goal remains a private one, and immigration officers and analysts are increasingly skeptical that officials can meet that target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0098ef0-17ce-11f0-b565-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa442280-17c9-11f0-b2ae-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was torn from her birth mother 30 years ago. Then they found each other.</title>
      <description>Korean adoptees can remind the world that these are deeply personal losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5cfe460-17bb-11f0-99f5-0000a1ace11d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones and other electronics will be exempted from reciprocal tariffs, Trump administration says, including Chinese imports</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's exemptions on electronic components coming out of China was announced late Friday. Beijing placed a 125 percent tariff on all U.S. goods earlier in the day, saying it would “fight to the end.” The exemptions on electronic components will likely be welcomed by tech companies like Apple, which produces the bulk of its iPhones in China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82a3770-17ae-11f0-bab4-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 15:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87d9bce0-17a2-11f0-b02b-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration overrode Social Security staff to falsely list immigrants as dead, people familiar say</title>
      <description>The plan spearheaded by DOGE and the Department of Homeland Security aims to eliminate the ability of thousands of immigrants to legally earn wages. Many agency officials say the practice is illegal and risks wrongly labeling other people as dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e6b1050-179e-11f0-9d5d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE takes over federal grants website, wresting control of billions</title>
      <description>A DOGE engineer removed federal officials’ permissions to post to Grants.gov without telling them, according to four people with knowledge of the move. Now decisions affecting billions of dollars in grant opportunities are set to flow through a DOGE-controlled mailbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29b7e290-1743-11f0-a78b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles judge allows Menendez brothers to seek early release, bringing them closer to potentially reducing their life sentences</title>
      <description>The Menendez family has in recent years made a push for the brothers’ release, maintaining that Erik and Lyle Menendez killed their parents in self-defense after suffering physical and sexual abuse at the hands of their father. During their trial, however, prosecutors said the brothers murdered their parents for financial gain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34ca9cf0-1733-11f0-a664-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence reveals a disturbing narrative in the deaths of 14 emergency workers in Gaza</title>
      <description>Israel says the first responders were fired on for moving “suspiciously.” Dispatcher records, witness testimony, and video and audio evidence contradict Israel’s account in key regards, including the proximity of the gunfire to the victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa60ebc0-1726-11f0-9d67-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plan would eliminate NOAA climate research, slash agency budget</title>
      <description>A Trump budget proposal would make deep cuts to National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration research on weather, climate and oceans, eliminating labs and reducing its budget by 27 percent. The proposal, obtained by The Washington Post, said the programs were "misaligned" with the "will of the American people." Democrats and science advocates said the cuts would devastate global climate science and make weather forecasts less accurate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e321580-171b-11f0-b9a7-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 21:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana judge rules Columbia student Mahmoud Khalil is eligible for deportation, his lawyers say</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had accused the legal permanent resident of being a threat to U.S. foreign policy for his involvement in pro-Palestinian activism. Khalil has been detained since he was arrested at his New York City apartment last month and stripped of his green-card status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79f8e61-1711-11f0-adf1-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 20:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. doesn't comply with judge’s deadline for plan to return man wrongly deported, saying it needs more time</title>
      <description>Kilmar Abrego García, a Salvadoran immigrant married to a U.S. citizen, was among more than 200 people expelled to El Salvador on March 15 — despite a court ruling prohibiting his removal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8e80841-16f5-11f0-88c1-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m tired of my husband using me as Google</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m tired of my husband using me as Google</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8c7d9d0-16f3-11f0-8878-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cuts to NASA science proposed in early White House budget plan, people familiar say, potentially impacting future missions</title>
      <description>NASA’s science budget, which supports space telescopes and interplanetary robotic missions, could be cut nearly in half under an early version of a Trump administration budget proposal to Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3592b311-16df-11f0-a25a-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51e5bbd0-16d9-11f0-8281-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While a majority of U.S. manufacturing workers who voted in 2024 backed Trump, most say tariffs would hurt them, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>The Washington Post asked more than 500 workers in manufacturing jobs across the country what they think about President Donald Trump’s tariffs. Most completed the survey before Trump announced he would pull back some tariffs but maintain a 10 percent levy on most foreign goods and raise tariffs on China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e57b700-16d5-11f0-b9e0-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. China. Supreme Court. Helicopter crash. Mass grave. Funding freeze. Extreme heat. Birthday tradition. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b818700-16c4-11f0-8878-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China raises tariffs on U.S. goods to 125 percent as trade war deepens between the world's two largest economies</title>
      <description>Beijing hit back in response to the Trump administration’s move to raise tariffs on Chinese goods to 145 percent, saying it would “firmly retaliate and fight to the end.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc7aee70-16b2-11f0-9683-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6,000 living immigrants added to Social Security death database as part of Trump's crackdown</title>
      <description>The classification makes it hard for immigrants to work or receive benefits in the United States as administration officials put pressure on undocumented immigrants to leave the country. Some current and former Social Security officials question the legality of the practice. A White House official said the targets have criminal histories or terrorist ties but did not provide evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29af9fe0-166c-11f0-a795-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI and other law enforcement agencies drafted to do welfare checks on migrant children and young people, alarming advocates</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security has enlisted several other law enforcement agencies in recent weeks to conduct welfare checks on children and young people who came to the United States without their parents. These checks have gained some attention on social media, prompting questions and alarm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">007ec310-1669-11f0-a181-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds order directing Trump officials to return wrongly deported man from Salvadoran prison</title>
      <description>The court on Thursday upheld a lower-court order requiring the Trump administration to “facilitate” the return of a Maryland man who was mistakenly deported last month to a mega-prison in El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba8b2cc1-1660-11f0-a71d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 23:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter crash in Hudson River kills all 6 on board, including 3 children, New York officials say</title>
      <description>All six people who were on board a Bell 206 helicopter that plunged into the Hudson River on Thursday afternoon have been declared dead, authorities said. The helicopter belonged to a tour company, city officials said, and carried one pilot, two adults and three children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27c96ad0-1658-11f0-8139-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff cuts begin at the National Endowment for the Humanities, threatening programs across the U.S.</title>
      <description>The employee union said almost 75 percent of NEH staff members should prepare for reductions in their workforce, roughly a week after the agency's grants were canceled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2120b590-164d-11f0-b25e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets closed down, reversing about a third of yesterday's gains, after White House clarified tariffs are 145% of Chinese imports</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P fell by more than 3 percent and the Nasdaq was down more than 4 percent, with banks and tech stocks driving some losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56b18910-1647-11f0-b25e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From George F. Will: This is 10-thumbed, fumbling, overconfident governmental progressivism</title>
      <description>This is 10-thumbed, fumbling, overconfident governmental progressivism</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80216120-163e-11f0-8b09-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Will the IRS notice if you don’t file taxes? Columnist Michelle Singletary takes your questions ahead of Tax Day.</title>
      <description>With the April 15 deadline closing in, our personal finance columnist is answering your questions with tax expert Eric Bronnenkant. Send in your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e8ab300-1627-11f0-b17c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A decade after he broke engagement, ‘I act like I don’t know him’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A decade after he broke engagement, ‘I act like I don’t know him’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe57dc50-1624-11f0-8a08-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pick to oversee Bureau of Land Management withdraws after her criticism of Jan. 6 riot surfaces</title>
      <description>Kathleen Sgamma, whom the president nominated to head the agency, wrote in 2021 that she was “disgusted” by the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, according to a document obtained by the investigative group Documented. Sgamma leads a Denver-based oil and gas industry trade group, the Western Energy Alliance, and was set to have her nomination hearing Thursday morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7f74f70-1620-11f0-ae2d-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jittery markets open lower after a record-breaking day as tariff hikes on Chinese imports fan fears of a U.S.-China trade war</title>
      <description>Major stock indexes have been volatile all week as Wall Street reacts to a stream of tariff news. After the United States and the European Union paused plans to impose tariffs on each other, some investors Thursday turned to the impact of a potential U.S.-China trade war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1781f20-1611-11f0-9ac4-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This state’s flower is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb62aa0-160f-11f0-af4d-0000a1ace7f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased more than expected in March, before most of Trump’s tariffs took effect</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed a slower pace of growth for inflation in March in good news for the economy, according to new data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10371480-1608-11f0-a2b7-0000a1ace126</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
