<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 01:30:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>No daylight saving time? See how early or late you would be in the dark.</title>
      <description>Would you be okay if the sun rose before 4 a.m., or after 10? Not changing clocks is a popular idea, but we’d have to live with the extremes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7d19550-b817-11ef-a128-0000a1ace85c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 23:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Belichick finalizing deal to become University of North Carolina football coach a year after leaving New England Patriots</title>
      <description>Belichick, who turns 73 in April, won six Super Bowls in 24 seasons with New England. He was passed over in the last NFL hiring cycle after departing from the Patriots in January. Belichick has never coached at the college level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b49396d0-b815-11ef-878c-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 23:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report commissioned by D.C. Council finds ‘substantial evidence’ that indicted Ward 8 Democrat Trayon White Sr. violated its rules</title>
      <description>A law firm the council hired to investigate White found “substantial evidence” that he violated council rules and used his office for personal financial gain. The report was prompted by White’s arrest on a federal bribery charge, to which he has pleaded not guilty. The council is scheduled to meet Monday to determine whether to punish White and could vote to expel him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cecb990-b80b-11ef-bb49-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 22:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes massive Pentagon policy bill after a heated debate over medical care for troops’ transgender children</title>
      <description>Democrats and some Republicans expressed frustration with Speaker Mike Johnson (R-Louisiana), whose provision targeting the specialized treatment eroded the $895 billion bill’s bipartisan support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77fab430-b809-11ef-b28a-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq index breaks 20,000 for the first time as Big Tech carries the benchmark</title>
      <description>The Nasdaq composite index is now up more than 33 percent for the year. Prominent technology stocks led Wednesday’s rally, with Amazon, Alphabet, Meta and Tesla all closing higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fb616f0-b804-11ef-9022-0000a1ace199</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Director Christopher A. Wray to resign before President-elect Trump, who vowed to replace him, takes office</title>
      <description>Donald Trump announced last month that he would nominate loyalist Kash Patel to serve as FBI director, sending a message to Wray that he should either resign in the middle of his 10-year term or prepare to be fired. The incoming president and his allies have long criticized the FBI for investigations of Trump and of possible ties between his campaign and Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4526ab00-b7f4-11ef-9d6a-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Aunt resents 20-something nieces’ ‘massive’ salaries</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Aunt resents 20-something nieces’ ‘massive’ salaries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">843feb31-b7e5-11ef-8a04-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Skyglow’ sounds pretty, but it’s causing major problems. Here’s how we can reduce it.</title>
      <description>All the light we would rather not see</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a9d5a1-b7e1-11ef-87fd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: A restaurant offered a diner $200 to change an online review. Is that bribery? Our food critic takes your questions.</title>
      <description>Happening now: A restaurant offered a diner $200 to change an online review. Is that bribery? Our food critic takes your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d767cc0-b7db-11ef-bb71-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albertsons calls off merger and sues Kroger, saying it did not do its best to get regulatory approval for the grocery megadeal</title>
      <description>Albertsons said Wednesday it is seeking “billions of dollars in damages” from Kroger for its “self-serving conduct.” The lawsuit comes the day after a federal judge issued an injunction blocking Kroger’s proposed $24.6 billion acquisition of Albertsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b44de140-b7d3-11ef-8ef0-000a1ace72d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An undefeated team in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a840dfd0-b7cc-11ef-bf3e-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation increased in November, as prices appear stuck after progress all year</title>
      <description>Overall inflation has proved stubborn and hasn't come down as quickly as in the beginning of the year, because of rising housing costs and insurance premiums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">947826f1-b7c4-11ef-a67a-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione. Trump’s team. Israeli strikes. Malibu fire. The Onion. Butterfly threat. Daylight saving. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75bc5631-b7b7-11ef-9b59-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects sale of Alex Jones’s Infowars to the Onion</title>
      <description>Jones had challenged the Onion’s winning bid in an auction for the site he founded. The conspiracy theorist was ordered to auction Infowars to pay the roughly $1.5 billion in damages he owes for claiming the Sandy Hook school shooting was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a72d9780-b77e-11ef-8e13-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The suspect in the slaying of a health-care CEO ‘had so much to offer,’ friends say. Now, he sits in prison, charged with murder.</title>
      <description>Luigi Mangione, a son of a prominent Baltimore family and an Ivy League graduate, had seemingly lost his way. Brian Thompson, a son of small-town Iowa who ascended to become CEO of UnitedHealthcare, appeared to be reaching new heights. Their paths allegedly intersected on a Midtown Manhattan sidewalk, ending in tragedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e54240-b75d-11ef-a6ef-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 01:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals win MLB draft lottery, will pick first in July</title>
      <description>The Nationals had the fourth-best odds — 10.2 percent — to land the top pick, but they won the draft lottery Tuesday night and will do just that. They last picked first in 2009 and 2010, landing franchise icons Stephen Strasburg and Bryce Harper with those selections. Among the candidates to go No. 1 in 2025: Oklahoma high school shortstop Ethan Holliday, brother of the Baltimore Orioles' Jackson Holliday and son of former MLB slugger Matt Holliday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a23829a1-b749-11ef-9c75-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 22:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts Kroger-Albertsons deal for now, putting merger of two supermarket giants at risk</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Adrienne Nelson sided with the Federal Trade Commission and several state attorneys general who oppose Kroger’s proposed $24.6 billion acquisition of Albertsons. Although the block is temporary, Kroger attorney Matt Wolf said during the hearing that an injunction would effectively end the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2ab6d90-b738-11ef-aa57-0000a1ace07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 20:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iconic monarch butterfly could soon join the endangered species list as U.S. moves to protect it</title>
      <description>The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service’s proposal to designate the orange butterfly as threatened with extinction could have enormous consequences for landowners across its huge range, which extends across much of the Lower 48. The monarch makes an epic annual flight from the mountains of Mexico through the United States and into Canada.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ca34b0-b729-11ef-ae53-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Keeping drama at bay at a family wedding without plus-one support</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Keeping drama at bay at a family wedding without plus-one support</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8362fcf0-b71a-11ef-80ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsealed criminal complaint alleges details of UnitedHealthcare CEO’s killing, including ‘written admissions’ and footage</title>
      <description>Police allege Luigi Mangione, 26, is the person who killed Brian Thompson based on evidence that includes “written admissions about the crime” and surveillance footage, the complaint says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f2a151-b716-11ef-8ab5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 16:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was suicidal and needed help. Online predators pushed him to take his life on camera.</title>
      <description>The death of a Minnesota man offers a case study into how the sadistic online group known as 764 has used the messaging app Discord to find and torment vulnerable people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8263e4d0-b70c-11ef-9e15-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pair of $28 million slippers in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28fea030-b705-11ef-859f-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione. Pete Hegseth. Syria. Daniel Penny. Murdoch drama. AI videos. Golden Globes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4860f480-b6ee-11ef-bfe0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione charged with murder in UnitedHealthcare shooting</title>
      <description>A five-day manhunt sparked by the fatal shooting of health insurance executive Brian Thompson in Manhattan ended in central Pennsylvania with the arrest of Mangione, 26. Warrant details on the New York state courts website list charges of murder, illegal gun possession and possessing a forged instrument. The criminal complaint remains sealed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06c38c00-b6b1-11ef-ba09-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 04:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione, person of interest in killing of UnitedHealthcare CEO, arrested in Pennsylvania on gun charges</title>
      <description>Mangione, 26, faces five counts including carrying a firearm without a license, possessing instruments of a crime and providing law enforcement with false identification, according to a criminal complaint filed in Altoona, Pennsylvania. He was arraigned at the Blair County courthouse on Monday evening and denied bail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c754980-b68d-11ef-952b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police identify Luigi Mangione, 26, as man being held in connection with fatal shooting of UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson</title>
      <description>Thompson, chief executive of the Minnesota-based insurance giant, was shot and killed on Wednesday morning outside a hotel in Midtown Manhattan where he was scheduled to attend an investor conference. Police said they believed the 50-year-old was targeted. The shooting sparked a manhunt that spread beyond New York after police found evidence the shooter left the city on a bus shortly after the killing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b5238c0-b65e-11ef-ae47-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 18:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband vents his road rage onto his spouse in the car</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband vents his road rage onto his spouse in the car</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28543c30-b651-11ef-909c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Penny is found not guilty after his chokehold killed Jordan Neely on a New York City subway last year</title>
      <description>Penny became a celebrity for conservatives, who praised the Marine Corps veteran for intervening while Neely shouted at and threatened passengers in May 2023. Neely’s family has said he was suffering from mental health problems and needed help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81712e30-b64d-11ef-a24e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 16:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA bans two cancer-causing chemicals used in everyday products</title>
      <description>The two chemicals — perc, an industrial solvent commonly used in dry cleaning, and TCE, a substance found in consumer and manufacturing products including degreasing agents — are known carcinogens. TCE is associated with numerous cancers including non-Hodgkin’s lymphoma, leukemia, and kidney and liver cancer. The new rules underscore President Joe Biden’s efforts to enact key protections against harmful chemicals before leaving office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d1c77d0-b63f-11ef-aacd-0000a1ace291</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 15:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rooster with ‘wings of fire’ in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dcf6660-b63a-11ef-b381-0000a1ace7bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 14:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes: ‘Emilia Pérez,’ ‘Conclave’ and ‘The Brutalist’ lead with the most nominations. See our full list.</title>
      <description>In TV, “The Bear,” “Only Murders in the Building” and “Shogun” had the most nods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e6cca00-b635-11ef-8a64-0000a1ace07b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 13:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assad’s downfall. Trump’s threat. Jay-Z lawsuit. Border deaths. Walkable cities. College football. Ruby slippers. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20d9e210-b625-11ef-ae21-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juan Soto reaches 15-year, $765 million deal with the New York Mets</title>
      <description>The 26-year-old slugger was among the most coveted free agents in baseball history, and the Mets won a bidding war that included the crosstown rival New York Yankees — Soto’s former team — and the Boston Red Sox.
The move will help the Mets compete with the World Series champion Los Angeles Dodgers and other powerful clubs in the National League after a surprise run to the NLCS this past season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57bb8910-b5de-11ef-a155-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 03:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many Americans prefer sprawl to walkable neighborhoods</title>
      <description>Building more 15-minute neighborhoods would cut pollution and conserve nature. But do Americans want to live in them? See how walkable your neighborhood is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c81373f0-b5b9-11ef-9a6b-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 23:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Milk chocolate or dark? The answer could affect your risk of diabetes.</title>
      <description>A large new study found that people who regularly ate chocolate had a lower likelihood of developing Type 2 diabetes. But only dark chocolate was associated with a lower risk of developing the disease, not milk chocolate. Researchers are not sure why that is, but they had some ideas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">056cd227-b59f-11ef-b5b6-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian President Bashar al-Assad lands in Moscow, Russian state media says, as Syrians rejoice at home. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>His regime crumbled under the weight of the armed Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham this weekend. Influential neighbors called for a peaceful transition as Western leaders hailed Assad’s fall with caution and called for regional stability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77f1d431-b590-11ef-a1f3-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 18:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The College Football Playoff bracket is set. Here’s who made the cut for the inaugural 12-team field.</title>
      <description>The selection committee unveiled the teams that will play in the first expanded edition of the playoff, which will culminate in the national championship game Jan. 20 in Atlanta.

The playoff begins with four first-round games at campus sites Dec. 20 and 21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20391c30-b58b-11ef-a1dd-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 17:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec0f8562-b586-11ef-86cd-0000a1ace906</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 17:07:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scam victims often feel ashamed, but this group helps them heal. Catch up on our ‘Scammed’ series.</title>
      <description>A support group for fraud victims helped an 80-year-old woman after she lost her life savings to a sophisticated scammer. Read the final installment of personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary’s “Scammed” series and any of the other parts you may have missed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7906370-b57a-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 15:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134537d0-b571-11ef-b384-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bashar al-Assad's regime falls in Syria as rebels in Damascus claim victory on state TV</title>
      <description>The armed Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham said early Sunday it had entered Damascus, the capital. Syria’s prime minister, in a videotaped statement, vowed to “extend our hand” to the opposition. With Assad's whereabouts unknown, an anchor on state television said "Syria has regained its freedom."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fb38d40-b543-11ef-a9da-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 09:05:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Damascus residents report hearing gunfire as Syrian rebels claim to enter the capital</title>
      <description>Rebels entered the Syrian capital in a crucial stage of a lightning advance launched by the armed Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham less than two weeks ago. They say they are looking for President Bashar al-Assad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7fd3c00-b512-11ef-a3ef-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian rebels enter strategic city of Homs, threaten Damascus, as army withdraws. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The Syrian army was “repositioning itself to the outskirts” of Homs, pro-government Sham FM said Saturday, as the Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham announced its entry into the country’s third-largest city, 90 miles north of the capital. The rapid advance of HTS from the north, joined Saturday by rebels from the south, has posed the greatest threat yet to the 24-year rule of President Bashar al-Assad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae5eb770-b4e8-11ef-8203-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 22:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 definitive hotel rules that every traveler should follow</title>
      <description>Hotels are here to serve you, but best not to push it. If you want to be an upstanding guest and expert traveler, you still need to follow the main tenets of a hotel stay. These are the rules for tipping, parking, cleaning and much more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">849aa5e0-b4e6-11ef-b809-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin claimed Jordanians ‘crashed’ Quantico. Feds say it was an Amazon delivery.</title>
      <description>The Republican governor has used the arrest of two undocumented men, who misunderstood directions to stop at a check-in station, to inflame fears over illegal immigration. Federal prosecutors — who initially charged the pair with misdemeanor trespassing, but later dropped those charges — say that, while the Jordanians were in the country illegally and are in the process of being deported, they did not crash the gate or intend to do any harm at Quantico.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ccd9640-b4cc-11ef-bb57-0000a1ace659</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrects link: All-cash buyers are still snapping up homes. See where they’re buying.</title>
      <description>The share of home buyers paying all cash reached 33 percent through August this year — one of the highest rates since the years after the Great Recession. Search by Zip code to see where all-cash purchases are happening near you. A previous alert directed readers to the wrong story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2d60c00-b4b8-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-cash buyers are still snapping up homes. See where they’re buying.</title>
      <description>The share of home buyers paying all cash reached 33 percent through August this year — one of the highest rates since the years after the Great Recession. Search by Zip code to see where all-cash purchases are happening near you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6514a720-b4b4-11ef-87a8-0000a1acec23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7399cf0-b4a7-11ef-8441-0000a1ace707</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea President Yoon Suk Yeol impeachment vote fails after martial law decision</title>
      <description>The South Korean National Assembly voted on President Yoon Suk Yeol’s impeachment Saturday but failed to meet the minimum ballot threshold after a boycott by members of Yoon’s ruling People Power Party. The failed vote, watched by thousands of protesters outside, is likely to trigger further political disarray and growing demands for resignation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d414c600-b496-11ef-bf68-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 12:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has tried to move federal jobs out of D.C. before. It didn’t go as planned.</title>
      <description>As he returns to the White House, President-elect Donald Trump has said he will relocate federal workers. Here’s what happened the last time he tried to do that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4485ddd0-b428-11ef-b861-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 23:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
