<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-in solar promises an easy, cheap way to power your home. Our columnist tried it.</title>
      <description>Millions of people in the United States can’t install rooftop solar, because they are renters or live in buildings with roof limitations. But for a few hundred dollars, portable panels that hang on any sunny surface can pump free solar electricity into your home via a wall socket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcd8850-7ab3-11f0-bf86-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a871c530-7aab-11f0-bd83-0000a1ace6d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 14:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin gets a small public-relations victory, the Editorial Board writes. What happens next will be more consequential.</title>
      <description>Putin’s short-term, public-relations win is less important than the meetings that follow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08c18500-7aa8-11f0-b0fa-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump drops Ukraine war ceasefire demand, in a reversal that aligns him with Russia’s Putin, splits with European allies</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, with the backing of European leaders, has previously insisted that a ceasefire must be in place before any negotiations to end the war. Russian President Vladimir Putin has long pushed for negotiations toward a final agreement that would allow fighting to continue in the meantime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0c97150-7a8d-11f0-95f8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky says he will meet with Trump in Washington on Monday to discuss Alaska summit</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky made the announcement after a “long and substantive” telephone conversation with President Donald Trump. He said the meeting on Monday would be used to “discuss all of the details regarding ending the killing and the war.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b4223c0-7a7f-11f0-92a5-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Canada cancels hundreds of flights as a strike involving some 10,000 flight attendants takes effect</title>
      <description>The strike means most Air Canada flights will be grounded, including international flights, a union spokesperson said. More than 600 flights have been canceled, with more expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0a065b0-7a64-11f0-bb84-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Gavin Newsom and other Democrats roll out a new map to counteract a GOP plan to redraw districts in Texas and other states</title>
      <description>The new California map would add up to five more Democratic House seats, likely wiping out the gains Republicans hope to make in Texas and intensifying a brutal national redistricting fight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b59f80b0-7a35-11f0-85a2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Putin signal no concrete agreement on Ukraine, take no questions after breaking off summit early</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin emerged sober-faced from their closed-door talks, exchanging niceties but acknowledging that no final deal had been reached to achieve peace in Ukraine. Trump said he would soon be speaking to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, along with European leaders, to continue the push for agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ddba520-7a30-11f0-8cf9-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After more than three hours of private talks in Alaska, Trump and Putin prepare to take reporters' questions. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin's high-stakes talks Friday held the potential to end the Kremlin’s war in Ukraine and shape the course of security in Europe for a generation. Trump said on his way to Anchorage that he is optimistic that "something’s going to come of it."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13f0700-7a26-11f0-b01c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: D.C. police chief remains in command, but Trump can demand help on immigration</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Ana C. Reyes did not issue a ruling but got attorneys for D.C. and the Justice Department to hash out an agreement that preserves local control of the police department. The judge also said Friday that President Donald Trump likely had the legal authority to get help from local police on immigration enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf59e591-7a21-11f0-b5ba-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Witkoff and Rubio land in Anchorage for talks with Russian President Vladimir Putin, with Ukraine peace on the line</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump, who is joined by special envoy Steve Witkoff and Secretary of State Marco Rubio, has said he will know quickly whether the meeting will be productive and will end it early if warranted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d22280-7a07-11f0-9795-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan football receives array of fines and suspensions for sign-stealing operation uncovered during national championship season</title>
      <description>The NCAA’s announcement Friday marks the conclusion of a nearly two-year process that began when news broke early in the 2023 season that Connor Stalions, then a low-level member of then-coach Jim Harbaugh’s staff, allegedly coordinated an improper in-person scouting and sign-stealing operation against future Michigan opponents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd8ea700-79f0-11f0-b979-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first hurricane of the season has formed in the Atlantic. Erin could intensify into a major Category 4 storm by Monday.</title>
      <description>Erin will track close enough to the Caribbean islands to bring heavy rain, possible flooding and dangerous waves this weekend, even as the storm is expected to avoid landfall. The East Coast isn’t out of the woods for next week, with rip currents and rough surf expected. Bermuda may also see bad weather next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d29263d0-79eb-11f0-8792-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem is living for free in Coast Guard commandant's home in highly unusual arrangement</title>
      <description>Noem recently moved into Quarters 1, a spacious waterfront residence on a military base where the Coast Guard commandant typically resides and is not paying rent. Her spokesperson says the arrangement is because of concerns over the secretary's safety.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8807270-79e6-11f0-be40-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3083b7b1-79dc-11f0-9bef-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. attorney general sues Trump administration as federal government seeks to exert more control over city's police department</title>
      <description>The announcement came hours after U.S. Attorney General Pam Bondi ordered sweeping changes to law enforcement policies in the city and said a Trump official should assume all duties and responsibilities of the police chief.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d064300-79d7-11f0-b127-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Putin. ICE expansion. D.C. police. Kids’ vaccines. Looming hurricane. Alcohol poll. Hairy toothpaste. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f737f350-79c6-11f0-92ac-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bowser, D.C. attorney general reject Bondi move to name emergency police commissioner in first major pushback to federal takeover</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser and D.C. Attorney General Brian Schwalb said the order by Attorney General Pam Bondi — which also ordered sweeping changes to D.C. police polices — was unlawful and suggested they would not comply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">676e9fc0-7990-11f0-b508-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Pam Bondi orders D.C. mayor to recognize DEA chief as ‘emergency police commissioner’</title>
      <description>In a signed order, Attorney General Pam Bondi said Terrance Cole, head of the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration, should assume all powers and duties of the chief of police and that the department’s top officers “must receive approval” from him before issuing any directives. Bondi said Cole's appointment would last through President Donald Trump’s emergency declaration in the District.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4596a240-7980-11f0-bf0d-0000a1ace568</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police chief expands cooperation with ICE as federal agents ramp up immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>D.C. Police Chief Pamela A. Smith issued an order Thursday that officers may now assist federal immigration enforcement efforts by sharing information about people not in custody, including those encountered at traffic stops. They may also assist by transporting federal immigration agency employees and their detained suspects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb78d3f0-795b-11f0-8d5d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS is reviving a childhood vaccine safety task force, fulfilling a demand from anti-vaccine activists</title>
      <description>The committee is tasked with issuing recommendations to develop and refine childhood vaccines with “fewer and less serious adverse reactions.” An anti-vaccine group founded by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. funded a lawsuit against the health agency to force the revival of the task force, raising concerns from vaccine experts about the motivations of a new committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd15d2f0-793f-11f0-b09f-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP is betting Latino Trump voters will keep them in power. That’s no sure thing.</title>
      <description>The congressional maps that Texas Republicans are drawing to boost their chances of keeping control of Congress depend, to varying degrees, on preserving their gains with Hispanic voters. But that doesn’t mean they’ve locked these voters down, according to conversations with more than two dozen Latino voters, elected officials and strategists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95ae8f60-7938-11f0-b946-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who threw sandwich at law enforcement was Justice Department employee and has been fired, AG Bondi says</title>
      <description>Police allege that Sean Charles Dunn began yelling obscenities at officers in D.C., including Metro Transit Police and U.S. Customs and Border Protection officials. Dunn allegedly told one of his arresting officers: “I did it. I threw a sandwich.” Attorney General Pam Bondi said Thursday that he had been fired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6d09ee0-792a-11f0-8c3c-0000a1ace725</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b74772-7928-11f0-a609-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The two reasons Americans aren’t having babies, according to data</title>
      <description>An analysis of where Americans keep having babies reveals what works.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bcd1e80-7920-11f0-ad2c-0000a1ace1bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill in the blank in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8ad3e91-7912-11f0-8296-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift’s new album is inspired by the Eras Tour, and 4 other takeaways from her interview on Travis Kelce’s podcast</title>
      <description>During a conversation that was unprecedented in both length and tone, she talked about everything, casually, as if she were just hanging out with her family or friends — while millions of people watched. Here are five highlights from the episode of “New Heights,” the sports podcast co-hosted by her boyfriend, Kansas City Chiefs star Travis Kelce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50deaaa0-7906-11f0-bb84-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. protests. Foreign aid. Kennedy Center. Tropical storm. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Ancient teeth. Rabbit ‘tentacles.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc217890-78fd-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance becomes the latest affluent American to fall for England’s storybook vacation spot</title>
      <description>The vice president’s family is vacationing in the Cotswolds. Ellen DeGeneres has made it a home. Kourtney Kardashian recently called it a “dreamy storybook fairy tale.” For the region’s tourism industry and real estate brokers, the American market is a goldmine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34c35fb0-7888-11f0-ac65-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer changes you, but I never saw my new hair coming</title>
      <description>It’s not clear why chemotherapy gave me curls, Rachel Manteuffel writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb481381-7884-11f0-8010-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c32deb60-7862-11f0-9bac-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will host this year’s Kennedy Center Honors. The class includes Sylvester Stallone, Gloria Gaynor and Kiss.</title>
      <description>The annual production may see significant changes under President Donald Trump, who revealed the honorees during a visit to the arts complex on Wednesday. The list also includes George Strait and Michael Crawford.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f002080-785f-11f0-8b2d-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b536cf0-7857-11f0-9ac6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani’s rise could be useful for America — by exposing socialism’s many harms, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Why Mamdani’s socialism-on-the-Hudson would be useful for America</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a5f50d0-784e-11f0-97be-0000a1ace54f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $4 trillion company in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cea5ab1-784a-11f0-8490-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Tice vanished in Syria 13 years ago. The Post uncovered details and previously unreported efforts to find the journalist.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters interviewed more than 70 people who knew, met, negotiated over or investigated the disappearance of the American journalist, revealing new information about his imprisonment and the effort to free him from Syria’s brutal prison system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e64ffb1-783d-11f0-a61f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Smithsonian review. Austin Tice. DOGE data. Bursting glacier. AI therapy. Jellyfish swarm. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a22f3280-7834-11f0-b746-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeanine Pirro: I'm the U.S. attorney for D.C. These three laws are detrimental to making our capital safe.</title>
      <description>Jeanine Pirro: The fight to make D.C. safe and beautiful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56759ae0-77d6-11f0-9121-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who gets Kennedy Center Honors under Trump? George Strait, Kiss and Michael Crawford being eyed.</title>
      <description>The arts complex’s marquee awards ceremony may see significant changes as President Donald Trump continues to overhaul the institution he took over in February.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43a68010-77d5-11f0-a115-000a1ace4057</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard to deploy in D.C. tonight, White House says, a day after Trump announced federalization of city police force</title>
      <description>A White House official, speaking on the condition of anonymity under ground rules set by the administration, said the Guard is expected to “begin being on the streets starting tonight.” A small number of the about 800 National Guard members who are expected to be a part of the mission had been mobilized as of Tuesday afternoon, defense officials said, with more expected in coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3a66ea0-77d1-11f0-b09d-0000a1ace09f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House announces more aggressive review of Smithsonian museums</title>
      <description>In a letter, White House officials said they would focus "on Americanism" in a review of the Smithsonian’s exhibition text, curation, exhibition planning and collections, starting with eight museums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4d5cf0-77ba-11f0-b0b9-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Republicans say they will start second House session on congressional maps this week, pressuring absent Democrats to return</title>
      <description>Republicans said Tuesday they would begin another special legislative session Friday to redraw the state’s maps in favor of their party, aiming to force Democrats to quickly return or commit to remaining away for another month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e89057f0-779d-11f0-98e4-0000a1ace862</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC shooter expressed discontent with coronavirus vaccines before firing hundreds of bullets at headquarters Friday, officials say</title>
      <description>The assault on the Atlanta headquarters of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has left many employees angry at Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. for his criticism of the agency and false claims about vaccines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8eb287f1-7796-11f0-94ce-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to face people’s questions after twin pregnancy loss?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to face people’s questions after twin pregnancy loss?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b54c6300-7795-11f0-9e0e-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dial-up memories in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfdfa2e0-7780-11f0-a27e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation held steady in July, as the full effects of Trump’s tariffs have yet to take hold</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s tariffs are lifting consumer prices in some parts of the economy, according to new Labor Department data, but less than analysts predicted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9bfe530-7779-11f0-bd76-000a1ace887c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plan would require hundreds of National Guard members to be ready around the clock to quell civil unrest</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is evaluating plans that would establish a “Domestic Civil Disturbance Quick Reaction Force,” with 600 troops on standby at all times to deploy in as little as one hour, according to internal Pentagon documents reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e49bdb20-776f-11f0-a5f1-0000a1ace415</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s D.C. crackdown. Pentagon plan. Tariff delay. Slain journalists. CDC shooting. Tropical storm. Taylor Swift. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74aa01b0-776b-11f0-946d-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House delays sharper tariffs on Chinese imports for 90 days</title>
      <description>Trade negotiators say they want more time to work out a deal to avoid tariffs as high as 145 percent on Chinese products. The new pause would expire Nov. 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece07340-7710-11f0-9b15-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to nominate Bureau of Labor Statistics critic E.J. Antoni to run the agency after he fired its previous chief</title>
      <description>If confirmed by the Senate, Antoni, an economist at the Heritage Foundation, would replace Erika McEntarfer, whom Trump fired this month after a bleak report revised spring jobs figures downward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c98ae70-7708-11f0-9c70-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
