<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08f17790-1b79-11ef-bf85-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When open houses get weird: Real estate agents dish on the horrors they’ve seen, from the gross to the dangerous</title>
      <description>Industry experts are split on whether open houses actually help sell homes, but there seem to be two universal truths about them: The practice helps agents expand their client base, and, when you welcome large numbers of random people to view a listing, extremely strange things can happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">771b0000-1b70-11ef-b9eb-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 14:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a007f90-1b64-11ef-8396-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small tortilla shops are being shaken down as Mexican cartels create vast extortion networks, expanding their grip on the economy</title>
      <description>At least 15 percent of tortillerías in Mexico — about 20,000 storefront businesses — are regularly extorted, according to the industry trade group. A decade ago only a tiny percentage were threatened. What has happened is emblematic of the criminal penetration of industries from agriculture to construction across Mexico and Latin America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0437c1-1af5-11ef-a852-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Black rising star lost his elite orchestra job. He won’t go quietly.</title>
      <description>Josh Jones, an acclaimed young classical percussionist, thinks the Kansas City Symphony dismissed him unjustly. Now he is breaking the orchestra world’s “code of silence” about hiring, firing and promotion to share his grievances. Symphony officials deny he was unfairly treated. But other musicians say he has launched a much-needed conversation about an outdated system they believe thwarts many talented young artists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d6ed2a0-1ac5-11ef-8540-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Sister-in-law inserts herself into our kids’ playdates. Do I say something?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Sister-in-law inserts herself into our kids’ playdates. Do I say something?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12c09800-1ab1-11ef-ace5-0000a1aceff9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Milwaukee patio becomes a battleground for Black public housing tenants, some of America’s most talked-about voters</title>
      <description>College Court Apartments residents, exasperated by the problems in their building, proposed solutions to local leaders. Instead of a response, tenants awoke a few days later to find a padlock on the gate to the patio. Recent polling suggests low-income Black voters like the ones at College Court are disappointed in Joe Biden’s presidency — but he desperately needs their votes, especially in swing states such as Wisconsin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b8c2f70-1aa4-11ef-9fa7-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 14:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efff81c0-1a9a-11ef-a706-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uvalde families announce new lawsuits alleging ‘Call of Duty’ studio, Meta and gunmaker all helped ‘groom’ shooter</title>
      <description>The lawyer who won a record-breaking settlement for Sandy Hook families alleges Daniel Defense, Activision and Meta are responsible for pushing the Robb Elementary shooter to acquire the AR-15 style weapon he used in the Texas attack. Victim relatives are intensifying their quest for accountability in civil court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42b0d6b0-1a0c-11ef-ac17-0000a1ace503</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three missionaries were killed by a gang in Haiti, an Oklahoma-based group says. Two were relatives of a Missouri lawmaker.</title>
      <description>Missouri state Rep. Ben Baker identified two of the victims as his daughter Natalie and son-in-law Davy Lloyd. They were coming out of a church Thursday evening when they were ambushed by “a gang of 3 trucks full of guys,” Missions in Haiti Inc. said on its Facebook page. A U.N.-approved international police force, led by Kenya and funded and trained largely by the United States, is preparing to deploy to the Caribbean nation to help its security forces confront gangs that now control an estimated 80 percent of the capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">995ecde0-19ef-11ef-9b0a-0000a1ace636</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some high-tech U.S. weapons in Ukraine are being defeated by Russian jamming, documents obtained by The Post show</title>
      <description>The percentage of some GPS-guided munitions, including Excalibur artillery shells, successfully hitting their targets plummeted after Russian forces deployed sophisticated electronic warfare capabilities, prompting Kyiv to abandon some Western weapons altogether. Russia’s successful jamming could serve as a blueprint for other adversaries, including China and Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3c1f520-19e3-11ef-8a4b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Spurlock dies at 53. His documentary ‘Super Size Me’ skewered the fast-food industry and tackled the epidemic of obesity.</title>
      <description>Spurlock’s family confirmed the Oscar-nominated director died from cancer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c44c1f30-19db-11ef-9401-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">200feb10-19d4-11ef-8297-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.N.’s top court rules that Israel must ‘immediately halt’ its military offensive in Rafah</title>
      <description>International Court of Justice rulings are legally binding but require the U.N. Security Council to enforce them. Israel’s war to destroy Hamas in the Gaza Strip has leveled large sections of the territory, killed tens of thousands of people, mostly civilians, and brought the population to the brink of famine, according to health officials. In a preliminary response to the case filed by South Africa, the ICJ in January ordered provisional measures to prevent further harm to civilians.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c25ee10-19d1-11ef-a289-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>East Coast abortion clinics have seen a surge in traffic since a Florida law banning most abortions went into effect</title>
      <description>New survey data collected by researchers at Middlebury College offers a first-of-its-kind look at the practical impact of the Florida law that banned most abortions on May 1, showing wait times at clinics increased in multiple states though a collapse in care many had predicted before the law passed has not so far materialized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84875530-19c8-11ef-a5d1-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting map. Israel ruling. Ticketmaster lawsuit. College athletes. Hurricanes. Food prices. Holiday weekend travel. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5dfa890-19bc-11ef-a464-0000a1ace460</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges are set to pay their athletes directly after NCAA and power conferences vote to settle landmark amateurism lawsuits</title>
      <description>The NCAA’s board of governors and college athletics’ five power conferences voted to approve a settlement in the House v. NCAA case that involved former athletes suing over not being compensated for the use of their names, images and likenesses. Two related cases also would be settled under the agreement.
The terms of the settlement, which is still pending plaintiff approval and additional steps in the legal process, include a framework for revenue sharing that would lead to athletes being paid by their schools beginning in the 2025-26 school year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eca0102-1960-11ef-b637-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternate electors who tried to reverse Trump’s 2020 defeat are poised to serve as electors again in at least three states</title>
      <description>Their eagerness to serve — and encouragement to do so from their parties — reflects a widespread belief among Republicans that the electors did nothing wrong in 2020, raising the question of what they might do or say if former president Donald Trump once again loses any of those states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b8d8000-194d-11ef-bea2-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Baltimore prosecutor Marilyn Mosby sentenced to 12 months of home detention, 2 years of supervised release for fraud and perjury</title>
      <description>Mosby, who gained national prominence for charging police officers following the death of Freddie Gray, had been convicted in federal court in Maryland for lying to mortgage lenders in the process of buying two Florida vacation homes and falsely claiming financial hardship to access retirement money. Mosby has continued to deny wrongdoing, saying she was the target of a politically motivated prosecution, and has been campaigning for a presidential pardon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60fec1f0-193e-11ef-b0b1-0000a1ace832</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750f7cf1-191d-11ef-b252-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Southern to pay $310 million over last year’s toxic train derailment in Ohio, including cleanup costs and a penalty</title>
      <description>The settlement with the Justice Department resolves a lawsuit over the railroad’s discharge of toxic substances following the fiery train derailment in Ohio on Feb. 3, 2023.

Under the agreement, Norfolk Southern will pay an estimated $235 million to cover the costs of the EPA’s efforts to clean up contaminated air, water and soil in and around where the train derailed and toxic fumes were later vented.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a27fb550-1919-11ef-ac3e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA warns this could be among the worst hurricane seasons in decades</title>
      <description>Record-warm ocean waters, fueled by human-caused climate change, are a key factor in the prediction. Hurricane season officially begins on June 1 and typically peaks in August and September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75564060-1911-11ef-bebc-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows disputed South Carolina voting map that critics say excludes Black voters</title>
      <description>At issue was South Carolina’s congressional district map used in 2022, which was created by the GOP-led state legislature and moved Black voters from one district to another. The justices had to decide whether it was permitted as a way to bolster the Republican majority or was an unconstitutional effort to divvy up voters by race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32814070-190f-11ef-8695-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endless shrimp in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5aa1120-1908-11ef-8b7c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long before the Key Bridge collapse, mariners sounded alarms that a ‘ship strike’ could be catastrophic</title>
      <description>Over the past two decades, as cargo ships grew ever larger, members of a Baltimore harbor safety committee repeatedly raised the possibility that an out-of-control vessel could imperil the Key Bridge, according to previously unreported records obtained by The Washington Post. The records show no indication that the warnings spurred new physical protections for the bridge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dfe6730-18fe-11ef-8b7c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 12:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian state recognition. Nikki Haley. Stage collapse. Bird flu. Fentanyl. Blackouts. Scarlett Johansson. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c57e420-18f3-11ef-a299-000a1ace3042</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show</title>
      <description>On Monday, Johansson cast a pall over the release of improved AI voices for ChatGPT, alleging that OpenAI had copied her voice after she refused a request by CEO Sam Altman to license it. But an actress was hired to create the Sky voice months before Altman contacted Johansson, according to documents, recordings, casting directors and the actress’s agent.
The agent, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to assure the safety of her client, said the actress confirmed that neither Johansson nor the movie “Her” were ever mentioned by OpenAI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c849ec0-1892-11ef-bc67-0000a1acef43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 23:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. will soon take antitrust action against Ticketmaster parent Live Nation, according to people familiar with the matter</title>
      <description>Live Nation also operates concert venues and promotes events. Exactly what the federal government would seek in court isn't yet clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58ce71a1-188b-11ef-b29e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After mounting a primary challenge against Donald Trump, Nikki Haley says she’ll vote for him</title>
      <description>In her first public appearance since suspending her campaign in early March, the former U.N. ambassador, when asked about which candidate she would prefer on foreign policy, said, “I will be voting for Trump.”
Haley, who did not endorse Trump when she dropped out of the race, went on to say that it was incumbent upon the former president to earn the support of the people who voted for her in the primaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c521e511-1883-11ef-b8ed-000a1ace16dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans can't get anything done, so they're bullying D.C., Marc Fisher writes in his first Opinions column.</title>
      <description>Republicans in Congress have new ‘solutions’ for D.C. They’re absurd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76550ed0-1879-11ef-8a86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A severe thunderstorm watch is in effect for the D.C. area until 8 p.m. Damaging winds and hail are possible.</title>
      <description>Scattered storms are possible in the region through this evening, especially west and north of the District. A few could contain damaging winds and hail, in addition to heavy rain and lightning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8aa8caa1-1876-11ef-8a86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Michigan farm worker tested positive for bird flu, the second human case in 2 months in the U.S. The worker has since recovered.</title>
      <description>The worker suffered mild symptoms from the highly pathogenic H5N1 virus, according to state officials. Human cases of bird flu are rare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8154aad0-1873-11ef-89f4-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election is set for July 4, with a high probability of ousting the Conservative Party</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Rishi Sunak’s announcement of a summer date landed as a surprise, as some analysts thought he wouldn’t want to face voters before it was absolutely necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b026e630-1859-11ef-9109-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband hasn’t properly atoned for calling his spouse an ‘eight’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband hasn’t properly atoned for calling his spouse an ‘eight’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b7f6b1-1854-11ef-ae0f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: How should a restaurant handle a ‘loud, rude and obnoxious’ group of diners? Our food critic is answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: How should a restaurant handle a ‘loud, rude and obnoxious’ group of diners? Our food critic is answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33892150-1850-11ef-b362-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s where D.C.’s Democratic council candidates stand on crime, education, the Commanders and more. The primary is on June 4.</title>
      <description>Voters will choose a nominee for D.C. Council Wards 4, 7, 8 and at-large in this deep-blue city, where the primary often determines the winner in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70fa2ec0-184c-11ef-9f48-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The anniversary of a landmark case in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">732d7560-183f-11ef-8361-0000a1ace165</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington-area residents want the Commanders to return to D.C., Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Schar School poll finds that area residents clearly prefer the Commanders’ next stadium be built in D.C. proper as opposed to Northern Virginia or suburban Maryland, where the stadium currently is. A 51 percent majority says the stadium should be built in D.C., while 17 percent say it belongs in Maryland and 15 percent say Virginia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a0d36a0-183e-11ef-8229-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fundraising email falsely says Biden was ‘locked &amp; loaded’ to ‘take me out’ in Mar-a-Lago search, misrepresenting FBI policy</title>
      <description>Trump’s baseless accusation — an extraordinary distortion of a standard FBI policy on the use of deadly force during such operations — came as the former president faces 88 criminal charges across four indictments, and added to a long history of false and incendiary claims against his political opponents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24eca090-1837-11ef-977e-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Primary results. Deadly tornadoes. Abortion pills. Flight turbulence. Matthew Perry. Graceland. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f5f8a01-182a-11ef-977e-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland, Spain and Norway recognize Palestinian state, with several other European countries expected to follow</title>
      <description>The symbolic diplomatic moves won’t have any immediate effect on the Israel-Gaza war but they put pressure on Israel to move toward a two-state solution, which its government has rejected. Israel has said recognition for a Palestinian state amounts to support for terrorism that jeopardizes peace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b20b892-180e-11ef-b590-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin McCarthy protege wins special election to fill his California House seat, the AP projects</title>
      <description>California Assemblyman Vincent Fong (R) beat Tulare County Sheriff Mike Boudreaux (R) in the special election for California’s 20th District, the Associated Press reported. Fong was endorsed by both McCarthy and Donald Trump and will serve the remainder of McCarthy’s term. He is also a candidate for the full term in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17dc9460-17eb-11ef-97c4-0000a1acec74</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis, who brought Georgia criminal case against Trump, wins Democratic primary</title>
      <description>Willis has beat a Democratic challenger in the primary for district attorney in the Atlanta area, according to the Associated Press. In the general election, Willis is expected to face Courtney Kramer, a Republican lawyer who interned in the Trump White House and was involved in Trump’s efforts to reverse his 2020 loss in Georgia. It has been two months since an Atlanta-area judge ruled that Willis could continue prosecuting the case despite having a romantic relationship with the outside attorney she appointed to lead the investigation. The accusations have slowed the case down, making it unlikely it will get to trial before the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd700d00-17ca-11ef-a206-0000a1acec86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a place with a history of hate, an unlikely fight against GOP extremism — with a crucial test in tonight’s primary</title>
      <description>North Idaho has beaten the far right before. Now renegade Republicans are seeking to root it out of their own party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ef581-17ad-11ef-a95a-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dark new biopic starring Sebastian Stan as a young Trump is the talk of Cannes</title>
      <description>“The Apprentice” drew spots of laughter from the Cannes Film Festival audience. But by and large, it is a chilling origin story.

Former president Donald Trump’s campaign called the film “pure fiction which sensationalizes lies.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53dfb70-17a0-11ef-9aae-0000a1ace376</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11816c0-178b-11ef-b330-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe is funding the draconian practice of detaining migrants in North Africa and dumping them in the desert, investigation finds</title>
      <description>A year-long joint investigation by The Washington Post, Lighthouse Reports and a consortium of international media outlets shows how the European Union and individual European nations are supporting and financing aggressive operations to push tens of thousands of migrants to remote areas in Morocco, Mauritania and Tunisia each year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1f2640-1784-11ef-877c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will not testify in his N.Y. hush-money trial. The defense has rested, and jury deliberations will take place next week.</title>
      <description>Both sides have finished presenting evidence in Donald Trump’s trial over allegedly falsifying business records related to a payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels before the 2016 election. After the judge and the lawyers discuss jury instructions this afternoon, the trial will take a break until closing arguments, scheduled for next Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21a0da90-177f-11ef-8089-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A long-awaited film meets mixed reviews in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">295d87f1-1776-11ef-a553-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East. Trump’s trial. Campaign cash. Extreme weather. African migrants. Scarlett Johansson. Cockroaches. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47c4ef90-1761-11ef-915c-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
