<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 05:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>We pitted dairy and plant milk against each other in the ultimate test. This is how they stack up.</title>
      <description>Dairy milk is popular, but more people are embracing plant-based milks. Which one is best for you? Pick your team and see how the competition plays out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd49af90-e95c-11ee-9f8a-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Angelos dies at 94. The Baltimore lawyer was best known as the combative owner of MLB's Orioles.</title>
      <description>Peter G. Angelos won hundreds of millions of dollars for workers injured by exposure to asbestos, then became wider known to the public as the chief owner of the Baltimore Orioles for three decades. The Orioles said Angelos had been “ill for several years” in a statement announcing his death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62274f70-e946-11ee-93c3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a bankrupt bettor became the bookie at the center of the scandal surrounding Dodgers star Shohei Ohtani</title>
      <description>The Post used interviews and previously unreported law enforcement and court records to fill out the backstory of Mathew Bowyer, a gambler turned bookie who became intertwined with baseball’s biggest star, rocking the sports world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25ab23f0-e937-11ee-abe5-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They obsessed over Catherine, Princess of Wales. Now they’re hit with a sobering truth.</title>
      <description>People who mocked and speculated about Catherine during her public absence have deep regrets after learning she has cancer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ecb9600-e926-11ee-87cd-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38c28370-e919-11ee-ad07-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll from Moscow concert attack rises to at least 115 as more bodies are found, Russian authorities say</title>
      <description>Russian officials say they expect the death toll to rise further, given the number of seriously injured. The militant group ISIS has claimed responsibility for the raid, which followed U.S. government warnings this month about a “planned terrorist attack” in the Russian capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d31a08a0-e8fe-11ee-83ce-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes $1.2 trillion spending bill slightly past deadline, averting shutdown despite brief expiration of funding</title>
      <description>The House passed the legislation Friday morning. The Senate stalled over disagreements about GOP amendments before finally reaching a late-night breakthrough. The White House said President Biden would sign it into law on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65782ac0-e8db-11ee-8537-0000a1ace299</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB launches formal investigation into betting scandal involving Los Angeles Dodgers superstar Shohei Ohtani</title>
      <description>Major League Baseball said in a statement that its Department of Investigations “began their formal process investigating the matter” Friday, adding that it "has been gathering information" since learning about the allegations of theft made against Ippei Mizuhara, who had served as Ohtani's interpreter. The Dodgers fired Mizuhara earlier this week amid allegations he stole millions from Ohtani to cover gambling debts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d97988e0-e8a6-11ee-b8d4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS claims responsibility for Moscow concert attack that has killed at least 40</title>
      <description>A news agency for the terrorist group, which opposes Russia as an enemy of Muslims, said it was behind the deadliest attack in the country in over a decade. A U.S. official, speaking on the condition of anonymity, said the United States had “no reason to doubt” the claim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1648f160-e89e-11ee-befc-0000a1aced61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women allege sexual misconduct, harassment by polo champion</title>
      <description>A half-dozen young women interviewed by The Washington Post alleged that John Gobin, a polo champion who runs a school for the sport in Virginia, engaged in a pattern of sexual harassment.

The allegations — some made in a newly filed lawsuit — include inappropriate touching and demeaning comments. At the time, some of the women were teenage workers at the school. Through an attorney, Gobin said all the claims by the women are false. He has not been charged with a crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fee34b0-e897-11ee-b323-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Mike Gallagher’s departure will leave GOP with just one-vote margin in House</title>
      <description>Under Wisconsin law, Gallagher’s seat is expected to remain vacant until January, with the November general election to determine who wins. After Gallagher leaves on April 19, House Speaker Mike Johnson (La.) will only be able to spare one vote to pass any conservative legislation through the chamber on party lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3574abb0-e88f-11ee-8cac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen in camouflage attacked a popular Moscow concert venue. Dozens were wounded or killed, state media reported.</title>
      <description>Several gunmen opened fire Friday night at Crocus City Hall, a popular concert venue on the outskirts of the Russian capital, and there were reports of an explosion. The region’s governor said he was going to the scene.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba343c0-e879-11ee-9212-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine, Princess of Wales, has cancer, she says in a recorded address</title>
      <description>The announcement follows months of speculation about the health of the 42-year-old princess, who has not made an official appearance since Christmas and underwent abdominal surgery in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24dc3e70-e877-11ee-a78a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: A parent thinks their daughter’s boyfriend is charging her too much rent</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: A parent thinks their daughter’s boyfriend is charging her too much rent</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611b7c40-e86b-11ee-994d-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:43:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The liberal revolution is in danger, Fareed Zakaria writes. Here’s how to save it.</title>
      <description>We are living in an age of backlash to three decades of revolutions in different realms. Since the fall of the Berlin Wall in 1989, the world saw the liberalization of markets, the democratization of politics and the explosion of information technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4bd70c0-e867-11ee-9823-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $1.2 trillion spending bill that would avert government shutdown, sending it to Senate hours before tonight’s deadline</title>
      <description>A bipartisan majority backed the bill, as lawmakers race to fund about three-quarters of the federal government’s operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f5e3581-e863-11ee-b9be-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Media merger gets shareholder approval, providing a potential windfall to the former president</title>
      <description>Donald Trump will own about 60 percent of the company that results from the merger of Trump Media &amp; Technology Group and Digital World Acquisition, the company created to take Trump Media public. Trump’s share of the new company, whose primary business is the Truth Social platform, could potentially be worth billions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">187b9631-e859-11ee-b533-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House debates $1.2 trillion spending package to avert a partial government shutdown, hours before deadline. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Passage in the House would send the bill to the Senate for expected consideration later Friday. The bill would fund roughly three-quarters of the government for the next six months and has the support of President Biden and leaders of both parties in Congress. But the measure still has to clear significant hurdles before the midnight deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cd91d70-e852-11ee-9f80-0000a1ace8db</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:45:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e41b5140-e84f-11ee-b533-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. U.S. sues Apple. Cease-fire vote. Homeless law. Pig kidney. Royal job. Ancient village. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55743e20-e83b-11ee-8139-0000a1ace425</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women are dropping birth control amid a misinformation explosion driven by social media influencers and conservative commentators</title>
      <description>Social media algorithms feed young women a stream of videos reinforcing messages divorced from scientific evidence. Instead, many social media influencers recommend “natural” alternatives, such as timing sex to menstrual cycles — a less effective birth-control method that doctors warn could result in unwanted pregnancies in a country where abortion is now banned or restricted in nearly half the states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94e1f9d0-e7d2-11ee-97b8-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 22:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embattled Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) says he won’t run in Democratic primary as he fights federal corruption charges</title>
      <description>Menendez and his wife were charged last year with taking bribes from three business executives, including gold bars, in exchange for legislative favors. He has pleaded not guilty to the initial indictment, as well as to additional charges since then, including obstruction of justice.
The senator said in a video posted to social media on Thursday that he hopes to run for reelection as an independent if exonerated in his legal case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f0f1c40-e7ce-11ee-8ba8-0000a1ace01c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 22:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All six White former officers in Mississippi ‘Goon Squad’ case receive long prison terms for torturing two Black men</title>
      <description>The former law enforcement officers received sentences ranging from 10 years to 40 years for the assault last year in which two Black men were Tased repeatedly, sexually assaulted and subjected to a mock execution. Each had pleaded guilty. The case drew national outrage amid the ongoing push from civil rights groups for greater police accountability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ba123d0-e7bc-11ee-9391-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 19:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is the government suing Apple? Look at your iPhone’s restrictions.</title>
      <description>If you have an iPhone, you can see for yourself the heart of the federal antitrust case. The lawsuit points to several restrictions that Apple imposes on users, including the inability to send secure messages to non-iPhone users, app limitations and forced use of Apple Pay for tap-to-pay purchases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c19ef980-e7a7-11ee-b151-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it wrong to ‘confront’ a brother who resists staying in touch?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it wrong to ‘confront’ a brother who resists staying in touch?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41504c80-e79c-11ee-a64c-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani has had a relentlessly pristine MLB career. Now a stunning scandal is swirling around baseball’s biggest star.</title>
      <description>Hours after news broke that the Los Angeles Dodgers had fired Ohtani’s longtime friend and interpreter Ippei Mizuhara amid allegations that Mizuhara stole millions from Ohtani to cover gambling debts, Ohtani jogged onto a baseball field enveloped by scandal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2119ac80-e798-11ee-b20d-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department and states sue Apple, accusing the tech giant of holding a smartphone monopoly</title>
      <description>Instead of competing with rivals by offering more affordable services, federal and state enforcers claim the company has illegally wielded a monopoly over the smartphone market by cutting off developers and stifling competitors with punitive restrictions. Apple is facing mounting legal and regulatory scrutiny.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c02cb8c0-e78f-11ee-9391-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 14:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This former daytime talk show host is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40c55721-e787-11ee-ace0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Join The Post for ‘The Futurist Summit’ with tech leaders from DARPA, OpenAI, Intel and more</title>
      <description>Technology has reshaped our professional and personal lives, restructured our economy and workforce, and created new pressure points for democracies around the world. The Washington Post is hosting conversations about how these transformations are shaping our future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd89df21-e782-11ee-8764-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 13:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s cash crunch. Car emissions. ‘Goon Squad.’ Birth control. Shohei Ohtani. March Madness. Happy countries. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2adc1b20-e772-11ee-83ce-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Dodgers fire MLB star Shohei Ohtani’s interpreter as theft and gambling allegations send a shockwave through the sport</title>
      <description>The Dodgers, who are opening their season in South Korea, confirmed in a statement that they had terminated Ippei Mizuhara, Ohtani’s close friend and interpreter, but offered no further comment.

Media reports surfaced alleging Mizuhara stole millions from the MLB superstar, but the degree to which Mizuhara was involved and other details remained unclear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42fe8ea0-e721-11ee-8d60-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 01:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Very, very troubling’: Legal experts flummoxed by latest order from judge overseeing Trump classified documents case</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Aileen M. Cannon, who is overseeing Donald Trump’s pending trial on charges that he mishandled classified documents, has ordered defense lawyers and prosecutors to outline  proposed jury instructions based on two scenarios — each of which badly misstates the law and facts of the case, according to legal experts.
“In my 30 years as a trial judge, I have never seen an order like this,” said Jeremy Fogel, who served on the federal bench in California and now runs the Berkeley Judicial Institute.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0e3ffa0-e70c-11ee-9671-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service warns of dangerous conditions as brush fires bring smoke into D.C. region</title>
      <description>A series of fires in Virginia and Maryland brought a smoky haze into the D.C. region Wednesday evening, as a combination of strong winds and low humidity created conditions that the National Weather Service says could fuel more blazes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3685d30-e70a-11ee-b18f-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 22:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court gets another say on abortion. What’s at stake with the mifepristone case? Listen to our columnists discuss.</title>
      <description>When SCOTUS overturned Roe, it indicated that abortion was an issue to be relegated to the states. Instead, it has blown up American politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3edb410-e6fb-11ee-98bc-000a1ace4070</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 20:53:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed keeps interest rates steady and signals it will cut rates three times this year, as inflation simmers</title>
      <description>Central bank officials have said they want to build confidence that inflation is reliably falling to normal levels before they take pressure off the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de6dda51-e6e3-11ee-9391-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 18:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s still time to get in on that women’s March Madness pool — and our sports analytics expert has the perfect bracket</title>
      <description>Before the start of the NCAA women’s basketball tournament, The Post’s Neil Greenberg presents his annual “perfect bracket.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4c36ee0-e6e0-11ee-914c-0000a1aceb62</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 17:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate hopeful Larry Hogan (R) has double-digit lead on Democrats in deep-blue Maryland, poll finds, with control of chamber in play</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-University of Maryland poll finds the former governor ahead of potential Democratic rivals, who face each other for the open seat on May 14. In that wide-open primary contest, the poll found Rep. David Trone with a slight lead over Prince George's County Executive Angela Alsobrook, with 39 percent of primary voters undecided. While Hogan leads now, Maryland voters said by a 20-point margin they prefer Democratic control of the Senate, a position Democrats plan to exploit to weaken Hogan's popularity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">646e3ff0-e6da-11ee-b758-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Impaired mother-in-law won’t stop driving, and husband won’t step in</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Impaired mother-in-law won’t stop driving, and husband won’t step in</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e62fbc0-e6d3-11ee-ab85-0000a1ace98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden requires automakers to ramp up sales of EVs and hybrids — his biggest climate move yet. It’s likely to face legal challenges.</title>
      <description>The Biden administration finalized the toughest-ever limits on planet-warming emissions from passenger cars and light trucks Wednesday, a bid to speed up the nation’s halting transition to electric vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f85956c0-e6ce-11ee-a24b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 15:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Trump attacks Biden’s mental fitness, he’s shadowed by his own father’s dementia</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s long fixation on mental fitness followed years of watching his father’s worsening dementia — a formative period that some associates said has been a defining and little-mentioned factor in his life, and which left him with an abiding concern that he might someday inherit the condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ab29840-e6c3-11ee-a24b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 14:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A red-orange sky over this country in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03ef35c0-e6bd-11ee-a24b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 13:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration law. Primary results. Shutdown talks. Gaza strike. Abortion record. Jonathan Glazer. Olympic condoms. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd0a50f0-e6a8-11ee-ba08-000a1ace6731</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas immigration law blocked from taking effect, hours after Supreme Court gave state the go-ahead to arrest, deport migrants</title>
      <description>The surprise ruling by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the 5th Circuit came hours after the Supreme Court cleared the way for S.B. 4 to take effect during legal challenges. The law makes it a state crime for migrants to enter Texas illegally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9052ccb0-e67d-11ee-a084-0000a1ace29d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 05:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-backed candidate wins Ohio's GOP Senate primary, AP projects, setting up a competitive race against Sen. Sherrod Brown (D)</title>
      <description>Bernie Moreno, a wealthy former car dealer backed by Donald Trump, defeated state Sen. Matt Dolan (R) and Secretary of State Frank LaRose (R), the Associated Press reported. Moreno will now face Brown in what is expected to be one of the most competitive Senate contests of the 2024 election cycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56f61a60-e652-11ee-9d19-0000a1ace93c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:39:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas gets the Supreme Court’s green light to enforce a harsh immigration law, for now</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court on Tuesday cleared the way for Texas to begin enforcing a law that makes it a state crime for migrants to illegally cross the border and allows state officials to deport undocumented individuals.  Liberal justices dissented, saying the change would invite "chaos and crisis" at the border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a930aa-e61f-11ee-b8f4-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 18:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Teen sees new stepsiblings as ‘too Brady Bunch for me’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Teen sees new stepsiblings as ‘too Brady Bunch for me’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134e7911-e60c-11ee-b0c2-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage raises questions about the Israeli justification for the deadly IDF strike on Gaza journalists</title>
      <description>Footage recovered from the drone of an Al Jazeera team killed by the Israel Defense Forces in a targeted Jan. 7 missile strike raises critical questions about the Israeli justification for the attack. Hamza Dahdouh and Mustafa Thuraya are among 90 journalists and other media workers who have been killed in less than six months of fighting in Gaza, according to the Committee to Protect Journalists — the deadliest period for the profession since the group began collecting data in 1992.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bd13c60-e606-11ee-b296-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The perfect bracket to win your March Madness men’s pool</title>
      <description>Before the start of the NCAA men’s basketball tournament, The Post’s bracket expert Neil Greenberg presents his annual “perfect bracket” to help you win your office pool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d0b920-e5fa-11ee-bb25-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An enigmatic artist’s mural appears in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce0c5640-e5f4-11ee-b1d0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s finances. Supreme Court. Gaza famine. ‘Havana syndrome.’ Asbestos ban. Kate Middleton. Banksy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54d3a60-e5df-11ee-bbbc-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
