<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:01:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The names of the potential next pope are circulating. Here are some of the contenders.</title>
      <description>Ahead of the conclave to select Pope Francis’s successor, possible candidates include cardinals Bo of Myanmar, Tagle of the Philippines and Italians Pizzaballa and Parolin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f8b9560-1f0d-11f0-9127-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 35-year-old lawyer told Trump the Smithsonian needs changing. He’s ordered her to remove ‘improper ideology.’</title>
      <description>Lindsey Halligan is an attorney assigned to help deemphasize “the negative” at a premier cultural institution. She explained her role to The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bae4c350-1f04-11f0-967d-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 23:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department allows DOGE staffers to access sensitive case data for millions of immigrants</title>
      <description>Representatives for the U.S. DOGE Service have received permission to access a Justice Department system that contains information including the addresses and case histories for millions of legal and undocumented immigrants, according to documents obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">309c6380-1efd-11f0-80b5-000a1acef398</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard sues Trump administration in escalating confrontation, claiming $2.2 billion funding freeze violates Constitution</title>
      <description>The university argues that government actions, including the freeze of federal funding, violated the First Amendment, exceeded its authority and failed to follow administrative procedures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e747eef0-1ef4-11f0-a466-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 21:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadine Menendez, wife of ex-senator Bob Menendez, convicted in bribery scheme that ensnared him</title>
      <description>Prosecutors described Nadine Menendez as a liaison between then-Sen. Bob Menendez (D-New Jersey) and the contacts who paid him bribes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9a826d0-1eec-11f0-aac3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican confirms Pope Francis died of a cerebral stroke and cardiocirculatory collapse. Tributes continue to pour in.</title>
      <description>He died Monday morning at the age of 88 after a recent bout with double pneumonia. Francis had made public appearances and held private audiences before and during Easter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea947951-1edd-11f0-9047-000a1acefc15</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Expecting a girl this time, couple goes over the top celebrating</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Expecting a girl this time, couple goes over the top celebrating</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23abe3e0-1eca-11f0-b292-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘5 things’ emails for federal employees are going by the wayside as Elon Musk readies his exit from DOGE</title>
      <description>As the billionaire and presidential adviser prepares to leave his government role, his signature email initiative is failing, with more agencies now telling employees to ignore the emails. There was never a plan for how to handle employees’ replies, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd49df10-1ec0-11f0-86c5-0000a1acef64</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular franchise is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da639030-1eb4-11f0-9dc3-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Catholics mourn Pope Francis, church prepares for next steps, and names for a successor circulate. Follow our live updates.</title>
      <description>Pope Francis died at the age of 88 at 7:35 a.m. local time Monday, the Vatican said, ending a historic chapter — and setting in motion a carefully orchestrated transition aimed at ensuring the stability and continuity of the Roman Catholic Church.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f703810-1eb3-11f0-9d8f-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis. Sensitive documents. Elon Musk’s role. El Salvador. Supreme Court. Weight-loss drugs. Healthy aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3cb4f80-1e9f-11f0-bc27-000a1ace3c07</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis dies at 88. He was a transformative figure, and his openness and empathy for the disenfranchised reshaped the papacy.</title>
      <description>From his early moments as the first non-European pontiff since 741, Francis demonstrated that he would be no ordinary pope. The Argentine Jesuit’s unpretentiousness and open style changed the global conversation around Catholicism and what it meant to be a religious person in the 21st century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e739ac0-1e87-11f0-95ef-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 08:07:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. restaurants are pushed to the brink of closure in the wake of wage hikes and government layoffs</title>
      <description>Dozens of the city’s restaurants are expected to close this year. Many unemployed federal workers’ discretionary income for dining just vanished. Voters also approved a ballot initiative in 2022 to phase out the lower minimum wage for tipped workers by 2027, significantly increasing payroll costs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df1fb2c3-1e32-11f0-89d7-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 22:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensitive documents, including White House floor plans, improperly shared with federal workers during Biden and Trump years</title>
      <description>The inadvertent sharing of a Google Drive folder with the entire staff of the General Services Administration, which was described in internal records reviewed by The Post, was the latest instance of sloppy handling of sensitive documents under both the Biden and Trump administrations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85c70dc0-1e2a-11f0-a67f-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 21:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use your ancestry to get dual citizenship abroad</title>
      <description>Depending on their family tree, U.S. citizens could get a second passport — for a cost. Here’s how.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccc99a80-1e1b-11f0-99e0-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 19:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military dismisses field commander and says probe found a ‘misunderstanding’ led to killings of 15 Gaza emergency workers</title>
      <description>The inquiry concluded that the soldiers did not summarily execute any of the unarmed paramedics who were shot and killed in Rafah in March, but it left key questions about the killings unanswered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b266170-1e0c-11f0-ab35-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 17:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab8bbb21-1e00-11f0-b728-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 10-minute Sunday bedroom reset will set you up for a better week</title>
      <description>We created two Sunday routines: one that can be performed in 10 minutes or less and one that is more labor-intensive, which you can follow for a fresher, tidier bedroom in the time it takes to do a load of laundry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d82621-1df4-11f0-bd57-0000a1ace09b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 14:32:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">acf012a0-1deb-11f0-bfb0-0000a1aced2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 13:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance meets with Pope Francis on Easter Sunday amid tension over immigration and foreign aid</title>
      <description>The meeting between Francis and the vice president, a recent convert to Catholicism, comes as the Trump administration and the Vatican have diverged on immigration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5e6b681-1dd0-11f0-9abf-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 10:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where does hurricane debris end up? We tracked a scooter, an office chair and other waste with Air Tags to find out.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters obtained permission to track 10 junk items from people who threw out their belongings after Hurricanes Helene and Milton. We then monitored the items as they traversed southwest Florida to gain a better understanding of post-storm cleanup efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbc6490-1d68-11f0-b728-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 21:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a baseball cap contributed to a Maryland man’s wrongful deportation</title>
      <description>A police department gang unit survey from six years ago is the source of allegations against Kilmar Abrego García. The survey and the database it fed into are no longer used after complaints of racial profiling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e68d4e41-1d43-11f0-aa65-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 17:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘No one hands you the bible of fatherhood when you become one’: Kevin Merida on LeBron James, the father</title>
      <description>As his incomparable career enters another transition, King James places fatherhood front and center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c275f50-1d38-11f0-855f-0000a1ace71c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 16:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My mom always wants more from me. I finally cut her off.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My mom always wants more from me. I finally cut her off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94d26ab0-1d37-11f0-8b80-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 16:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 340-mile race on foot is unsanctioned, dangerous and not exactly legal. For those who land a coveted invite, it’s everything.</title>
      <description>The “Speed Project” race from Los Angeles to Las Vegas has grown over the past decade to include 83 teams of runners from more than 30 countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efb0ae00-1d2e-11f0-a0a9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 14:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2c31bb0-1d22-11f0-a1a5-000a1acecbcc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egg prices are so high that people are dyeing potatoes for Easter. We tried it.</title>
      <description>Egg prices are so high that people are dyeing potatoes for Easter. We tried it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89731390-1d1e-11f0-939c-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 13:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court blocks Alien Enemies Act deportation of alleged Venezuelan gang members</title>
      <description>The Trump administration was planning to deport a group of at least 30 Venezuelan men under a rarely invoked wartime statute before the Supreme Court ruled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6be7c270-1ce3-11f0-8113-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 05:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 festive recipes for an Easter brunch or dinner, including ham, lamb, salads and quiche</title>
      <description>15 festive recipes for an Easter brunch or dinner, including ham, lamb, salads and quiche</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56fd9d30-1c9d-11f0-bb10-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 21:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of immigrants prove they are alive, forcing Social Security to undo death label</title>
      <description>Social Security Administration staff reinstated nearly three dozen people over the past week, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.

The immigrants are among the roughly 6,100 who were falsely added to a deaths database by DHS and the U.S. DOGE Service in a bid to pressure them to leave the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32e08920-1c76-11f0-8d0f-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The American experiment launched 250 years ago — with the sound of gunshots</title>
      <description>The American semiquincentennial begins now. It’s an opportunity for both celebration and reflection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c7cb42-1c6e-11f0-acda-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 16:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef7c700-1c59-11f0-84ce-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 13:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilmar Abrego García. Trade deals. FSU shooting. Health cuts. Russia-Ukraine. Severe weather. Fyre Festival. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54aa82e0-1c44-11f0-ac28-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is ready to ‘move on’ from peace talks between Ukraine and Russia if there is no progress ‘within days,’ Rubio says</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio did not specify what the Trump administration “moving on” would mean for continued military support for Ukraine or sanctions on Russia. If the United States were to just end its support for peace talks, it would mark a significant win for the Kremlin, which currently has the momentum on the battlefield.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b84dd0f0-1c34-11f0-b13b-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 09:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senator from Maryland says he met with wrongly deported man in El Salvador</title>
      <description>Sen. Chris Van Hollen (D-Maryland) shared a photo of himself with Kilmar Abrego García on social media and said he’d met with him Thursday. His office confirmed the authenticity of the photo and message. The senator had said Wednesday he’d been denied access to the man at the center of an escalating standoff between the Trump administration and the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae3742c0-1bf5-11f0-ae96-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Apr 2025 01:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB Commissioner Rob Manfred met with President Trump amid Pete Rose discourse</title>
      <description>The specifics of their discussion at the White House on Wednesday were not immediately clear, but the previously unreported meeting comes after Trump criticized MLB for keeping Rose, the all-time hits leader who died last year at 83, ineligible for induction into the Hall of Fame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">195d2c51-1be6-11f0-8e9b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret U.S. intelligence assessment contradicts Trump’s justification for mass deportations without due process</title>
      <description>The determination, reached early this month by the National Intelligence Council and drawing on the acumen of all 18 U.S. intelligence agencies, is the most comprehensive assessment to date, undercutting Trump's rationale for deporting suspected gang members from Venezuela.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98b74880-1be3-11f0-8d12-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 23:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two dead, at least five injured in Florida State shooting; suspect is son of a law enforcement officer, authorities say</title>
      <description>The suspected shooter is the son of a local sheriff’s deputy, authorities said at a news conference. The suspect is believed to be a current student at the university, campus police chief Jason Trumbower said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02412790-1bcf-11f0-ba18-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 21:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Mahmoud Khalil: A letter from an ICE detention facility</title>
      <description>Mahmoud Khalil: What does my detention by ICE say about America?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd1df5e0-1bc7-11f0-9741-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 20:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A suspect is in custody after Florida State shooting leaves at least six injured, authorities say</title>
      <description>At least one person was in critical condition and five others were in serious condition after a shooting at the Tallahassee campus. A suspect is in custody, a police spokesperson confirmed. The university said law enforcement had control of the scene as of 3:20 p.m.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43165650-1bc5-11f0-85de-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 19:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court will review Trump’s attempt to ban birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>The justices scheduled a special court argument in May to consider President Donald Trump's proposal to deny U.S. citizenship to babies born in the country if neither parent is a U.S. citizen or legal permanent resident. The administration is seeking to narrow nationwide court orders blocking Trump's action, which Democratic-led states and immigrant advocacy organizations say is at odds with the nation’s history, past court rulings and the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53d89d11-1bb9-11f0-8ea5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida State University students told to shelter in place after reports of a campus shooting</title>
      <description>Tallahassee Memorial Hospital said in a statement that it was receiving patients from an incident at Florida State.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">684451e0-1baf-11f0-9af3-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 17:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After divorce, second-guessing ability to make big decisions</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After divorce, second-guessing ability to make big decisions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8657cc20-1ba5-11f0-9f7e-0000a1acec56</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:03:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s adtech unit is an illegal monopoly, court rules. The tech giant may be forced to sell the profitable division.</title>
      <description>The case, brought by the Justice Department in a federal court in Virginia, revolved around the major role that Google plays in brokering the sale of online advertisements to news outlets and other website operators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23ab6330-1b9f-11f0-ba18-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 15:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world’s heaviest known invertebrate in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1750bb20-1b91-11f0-8b37-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health cuts. El Salvador. Trump vs. Harvard. Puerto Rico outages. Lying chatbots. Storm waste. Sign of alien life. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9f56c0-1b7b-11f0-9aa0-0000a1ace0fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE, DOGE seek sensitive Medicare data as Trump administration's immigration crackdown intensifies</title>
      <description>The targeted database, which is managed by the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services and includes health and personal information, contains home addresses sought by Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials, according to a person familiar with the matter and documents reviewed by The Post. Current and former health officials said they were deeply concerned by what appears to be an unprecedented use of the Medicare database as part of immigration enforcement efforts, and they were uncertain if the process was legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">364ffac1-1b20-11f0-bd00-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks IRS to revoke Harvard’s tax-exempt status</title>
      <description>The directive to the Internal Revenue Service escalates President Donald Trump’s feud with Harvard University, other Ivy League institutions and nonprofit groups his administration views as "woke."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c96c051-1b0b-11f0-b5a1-0000a1ace075</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House seeks to cut $40 billion in funding for the Department of Health and Human Services, internal document shows</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's proposed reductions would be about one-third of the agency's discretionary budget. Public health experts warned that the move would be catastrophic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81f8991-1b04-11f0-b563-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials say destroying endangered species’ habitats isn’t ‘harm’</title>
      <description>A proposed rule would narrow the definition of harm under the Endangered Species Act and could open the door to more mining, construction and other activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5999510-1af6-11f0-b52f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
