<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Harris’s whirlwind, high-pressure VP vetting process: Who rose to the top and what ultimately sold her on Walz</title>
      <description>Kamala Harris interviewed three final candidates on Sunday. Her team had reservations about one of them, then another expressed doubts about leaving his current job. That paved the way for Tuesday’s announcement of Tim Walz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce119e40-5451-11ef-b9b9-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. men's basketball rolls and a Cuban wrestler makes history</title>
      <description>Devin Booker led the U.S. men's basketball team to a blowout of Brazil, setting up a semifinal against Nikola Jokic and Serbia. Elsewhere, Gabby Thomas and Cole Hocker won track gold, the U.S. women's soccer team topped Germany in a tense semifinal, and Cuban wrestler Mijaín López made history with a gold medal in his fifth straight Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">652a4b20-5442-11ef-91d1-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris makes first appearance with running mate Gov. Tim Walz at Pa. rally before multistate tour. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Walz is expected to share his and Harris’s biographies of longtime public service, according to shared excerpts of his speech. And he will distinguish their ticket from Donald Trump, whom he will portray as selfish.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94b04eb0-543f-11ef-8f35-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz made ‘weird’ happen, Karen Tumulty writes. He offers the ticket much more than that.</title>
      <description>Walz has a genuine feel for the concerns of people in conservative corners of the country, Tumulty writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb63a20-543a-11ef-984a-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: With Walz, Harris aims for broad appeal over swing-state potential, and 4 other takeaways from her VP pick</title>
      <description>Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz won out with his “weird” audition and brings a folksiness to the ticket with his recent left-leaning record. Here are takeaways from his selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b88a190-5433-11ef-aac7-000a1ace8d94</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American runner Gabby Thomas cruises to Olympic gold in women’s 200 meters</title>
      <description>Three years after taking bronze at the Tokyo Games, Thomas left no doubt that gold was on her mind in Paris. She thumped the field in the women's 200 meters, posting a time of 21.83 seconds, a full 0.25 seconds ahead of silver medalist Julien Alfred. Fellow American Brittany Brown won bronze with a time of 22.20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83f5cbc0-542d-11ef-8e01-0000a1aceb3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. runner Cole Hocker wins gold in thrilling men’s 1,500-meter race</title>
      <description>One of the most anticipated races of the Olympic track and field meet yielded one of the most stunning champions. Hocker, a long-haired Indiana native by way of the University of Oregon, broke an Olympic record in the men's 1,500 meters, spoiled the heated rivalry between Jakob Ingebrigtsen and Josh Kerr and ran into American track history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03072680-5428-11ef-9766-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Bangladeshi officials meet student demand to name Nobel laureate Muhammad Yunus as transitional leader</title>
      <description>The announcement came after a six-hour meeting between the president, security chiefs and leaders of a student movement that forced Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina from office earlier this week. The appointment of Yunus, who was a pioneer of microfinance and a critic of the former government, would be an initial step to restoring order after mass protests, which left 400 people dead in the past month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc744b1-5424-11ef-bd22-0000a1ace06d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s soccer team beats Germany, 1-0, in extra time, setting up gold medal matchup with Brazil-Spain winner</title>
      <description>With a new coach and revamped roster, the U.S. women remain undefeated in the Olympic tournament after an extra-time goal by Sophia Smith delivered the narrow win. The United States will face the winner of Tuesday’s Brazil-Spain matchup in the gold medal game on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6e66b30-5422-11ef-8ee0-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Nosy bridesmaid learns best friend’s groom was cheating. Now what?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Nosy bridesmaid learns best friend’s groom was cheating. Now what?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">521b65d0-540d-11ef-b4a8-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 16:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For first time in 40 years, EPA issues an emergency order to stop use of a pesticide known to harm fetuses</title>
      <description>The order applies to dimethyl tetrachloroterephthalate, also known as DCPA or Dacthal, an herbicide used on crops such as broccoli, Brussels sprouts, cabbage and onions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">259d3a20-5407-11ef-99c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 15:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A resignation on the world stage in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08ee41a0-5400-11ef-8b9b-0000a1ace569</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 14:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris has told allies that Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz is her VP pick. The military veteran has a record of wins on conservative terrain.</title>
      <description>The presumptive Democratic nominee selected the former congressman and military veteran as her running mate. Walz, 60, is not well known nationally but has gained more attention in recent weeks after giving television interviews in which he criticized Donald Trump and Republicans as “weird.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc102a61-53f3-11ef-b972-0000a1acef82</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial markets. Harris tour. Google ruling. Iraq attack. Tropical Storm Debby. HBCU gift. Olympics. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06851000-53e3-11ef-9d3f-0000a1ace55f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many Arizona schools are refusing to host polling places, fearing threats and chaos as elections come under attack</title>
      <description>For generations, public school gymnasiums, classrooms and cafeterias have been fundamental to American elections. But when voters in Maricopa County — home to Phoenix and more than half of this swing state’s registered voters — show up to make their voices heard in November, chances are it won’t be at a school.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cdd6901-537e-11ef-942d-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 23:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 10 highlights from Paris Olympics: Mondo Duplantis raises the bar and Simone Biles ends her Games with silver</title>
      <description>Duplantis, a Louisiana-born pole vaulter who competes for Sweden, capped his performance with a world record leap. After concluding her Olympics with a silver medal on floor, Biles created an instantly iconic image with U.S. teammate Jordan Chiles when the duo bowed to Brazilian winner Rebeca Andrade. Elsewhere, American star Noah Lyles advanced in the 200 meters, compatriot Valarie Allman defended her women’s discus title, and the U.S. women's three-on-three basketball team claimed bronze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9299030-537a-11ef-a277-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 22:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several U.S. service members injured in suspected rocket attack at Iraqi air base, officials say</title>
      <description>The incident occurred at Al Asad air base, an installation in western Iraq, U.S. defense officials said in a statement. It was not immediately clear how many American personnel were wounded or the extent of their injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df760460-5374-11ef-937b-000a1ace2638</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 21:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. stock markets close with some of the worst losses in nearly two years. But economists say there’s no reason to panic.</title>
      <description>Two major stock indexes dropped more than three percentage points Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67d6afe0-5365-11ef-9b42-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 20:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google is an illegal monopoly, federal court rules — a landmark antitrust win for the Justice Department</title>
      <description>The case has been closely watched in antitrust law circles as the first of a string of cases by federal prosecutors against high-tech giants, as Washington enforcers argue that Big Tech has gotten too powerful and doesn’t serve the public interest. Lawsuits have also been filed against Amazon, Meta and Apple.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c542c2a0-535f-11ef-8ee0-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 19:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it unfair to want to be an at-home mom after agreeing to work?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it unfair to want to be an at-home mom after agreeing to work?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5b826e0-5343-11ef-ab29-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simone Biles wins silver for her floor routine after a fall on beam earlier in the day. She will leave Paris with 3 gold medals.</title>
      <description>Brazil’s Rebeca Andrade, Biles’s top rival at these Games, won gold. Biles, 27, said this week that while she is “getting really old,” she hasn’t ruled out competing in Los Angeles in 2028.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9177cb1-5330-11ef-9cf0-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:44:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow slides more than 1,000 points at open as fears of a U.S. economic downturn sparked a global selloff</title>
      <description>Japan’s Nikkei 225 index plunged more than 4,400 points, or 12 percent, in its biggest single-day drop on record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e373af0-532f-11ef-8cf8-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 13:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debby makes landfall as Category 1 hurricane in Florida’s Big Bend; ‘catastrophic flooding’ feared as storm moves inland</title>
      <description>After producing a “life-threatening” storm surge, heavy rain and damaging winds to Florida's west coast, the storm is forecast to bring "potentially historic heavy rainfall" across southeast Georgia and eastern South Carolina into midweek.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88daf201-531a-11ef-aedd-0000a1ace809</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris’s VP search. Hurricane Debby. Israeli strikes. Bangladesh protests. U.K. violence. Noah Lyles. Asteroid. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de67ff21-5319-11ef-8d4c-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bangladesh’s Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina resigns in wake of deadly anti-government protests, army chief says</title>
      <description>Hasina’s resignation, announced in a televised address by army chief Gen. Waker-Uz-Zaman, comes after a month of violent clashes between Bangladeshi security forces and anti-government protesters that led to the death of hundreds and culminated on Monday with crowds storming into Hasina’s official residence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e45fc40-5314-11ef-bb58-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 10:19:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro lost Venezuela’s election, a Post review of voting receipts collected by Venezuela’s opposition shows</title>
      <description>Challenger Edmundo González likely beat President Nicolás Maduro in the July 28 election by millions of votes, according to data pulled from more than 23,000 precinct-level tally sheets. Maduro’s electoral council last week declared him the winner; the United States and other governments have rejected the claim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">571f79d0-52ba-11ef-989b-0000a1ace08f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 9 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. swimmers finish on top; Scheffler wins golf gold; a medal surprise in cycling</title>
      <description>The Americans won the final event of the Olympic swimming meet, the women’s 4x100-meter medley relay, to overtake the Australians atop the gold medal standings with eight. Scottie Scheffler, the world’s top-ranked golfer, staged a spectacular comeback to claim gold. U.S. cyclist Kristen Faulkner pulled a major upset in the women’s road race, becoming the first American to win the event since 1984. Elsewhere, Noah Lyles stole the show on the track in the photo-finish final of the men’s 100 meters and the U.S. women’s basketball team cruised into the knockout round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4094b693-52b9-11ef-8027-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 23:28:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘My place was down in the dungeons, where the dragons lived’: Five writers on how their lives were shaped by an iconic game</title>
      <description>For Dungeons &amp; Dragons, the magic is in the memories</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8894b80-52aa-11ef-aaeb-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who killed MLB pitcher Tyler Skaggs?</title>
      <description>After the Los Angeles Angels pitcher overdosed in 2019, blame fell on one team employee. Five years later, records suggest the truth is more complicated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">616319d0-52a9-11ef-aaeb-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 21:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. sprinter Noah Lyles wins Olympic gold in the 100-meter dash, cementing status as fastest man alive</title>
      <description>It’s the first Olympic gold medal for the 27-year-old from Alexandria, Va. After a public battle with mental health issues, Lyles has emerged as the world’s top sprinter, winning three golds at last year’s world championships. He will go for two more in Paris — in the 200-meter dash and the 4x100-meter relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f63c2500-529b-11ef-84da-0000a1ace8f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 19:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American women set world record to win gold in 4x100-meter medley swimming relay</title>
      <description>The squad of Regan Smith (backstroke), Lilly King (breaststroke), Gretchen Walsh (butterfly) and Torri Huske (freestyle) crushed the field, setting the mark in 3 minutes 49.63 seconds, more than 3½ seconds ahead of their rivals from Australia.

Their win gave the Americans their eighth gold medal of the meet, against seven for Australia, keeping alive their streak of topping the gold medal chart in swimming at every Olympics since 1992.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6f84711-528a-11ef-b3ec-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American swimmer Bobby Finke sets world record to win gold in men’s 1,500-meter freestyle at Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>Finke defended his gold medal in the event from the Tokyo Games, finishing Sunday’s race in 14 minutes 30.67 seconds, besting China’s Sun Yang’s previous mark from 2012.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e9b760-5284-11ef-b3ec-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When online patient portals reveal scary health news such as cancer and other grim test results before doctors can</title>
      <description>Americans are entitled to immediate access of medical tests and scan results, from routine bloodwork to MRIs, lifting the veil on records that were once difficult to access. The new medical landscape resulting from a bipartisan law promoting transparency has exposed fault lines in a stressed health-care system where the promises of technological advancements are undercut by the heavy workloads foisted on medical professionals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f64e360-5283-11ef-acbc-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbaab7b1-527a-11ef-b034-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serbia’s Novak Djokovic wins his first Olympic tennis gold medal over Spain’s Carlos Alcaraz in Paris</title>
      <description>A bronze medalist in 2008, Djokovic won his first Olympic gold and avenged a loss to Alcaraz in the Wimbledon final last month. The win makes him the fifth player to capture the golden slam: singles titles in the four majors and the Olympic gold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63ab44a0-5273-11ef-b3ec-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 15:08:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rent prices are actually falling in some areas. Check to see if yours is one of them.</title>
      <description>Rents nationally have climbed about 19 percent since 2019, though prices increased only about 1 percent in the past year, according to a Washington Post analysis. That pace is down considerably from the steep price growth seen in 2021 and 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b156f82-526e-11ef-bb67-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e85bf590-5265-11ef-8320-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 13:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 8 highlights from Paris Olympics: Simone Biles wins gold on vault and Sha’Carri Richardson takes silver in 100 meters</title>
      <description>Biles on Saturday won her third gold medal at the Paris Games, holding off Brazil's Rebeca Andrade in the vault final. Richardson, who was kept out of the Tokyo Games, competed in her first Olympic final and earned silver, behind Saint Lucia's Julien Alfred. In the pool, Katie Ledecky made more history with her ninth Olympic gold and the Americans set a world record in the mixed 4x100-meter relay. Elsewhere, Trinity Rodman lifted the U.S. women into the soccer semifinals and Anthony Edwards powered the U.S. men to a win in their final game of basketball group play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04facd70-51e9-11ef-a697-0000a1ace43c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 22:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Ledecky wins gold in 800-meter freestyle, making Olympic history with fourth straight win in a single event</title>
      <description>In her last event of the Paris Games, Ledecky became the first woman to win the same swimming event in four straight Olympics. It was her fourth medal and second gold of these Games, bringing her to nine career golds, more than any female swimmer in history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41721e21-51d0-11ef-86cf-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:40:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches in effect for the D.C. area into Saturday evening</title>
      <description>Numerous storms are expected to pass through the Washington region between 9 p.m. and 10 p.m. A few could produce damaging wind gusts and flooding downpours in addition to dangerous lightning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57917230-51cd-11ef-b404-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 19:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American gymnast Stephen Nedoroscik wins bronze in pommel horse, his second medal of the Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>Nedoroscik, whose routine on pommel horse earlier this week clinched the first U.S. men’s gymnastics team medal since the 2008 Beijing Games and transformed him into an internet sensation, put forth another big performance Saturday in his specialty event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">879ac6a0-51b6-11ef-b984-0000a1aceb50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 16:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s soccer team tops Japan to advance to Olympic semifinals on Trinity Rodman’s extra-time goal</title>
      <description>The United States beat Japan, 1-0, in Paris on Saturday, overcoming a sluggish start to stay alive at the Summer Games. The Americans, led by new coach Emma Hayes, will next face either Canada, the defending gold medalist, or Germany.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8072ab60-51af-11ef-8ce5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims he struck a new deal to debate Harris. But the vice president says that’s untrue and urges sticking to existing date.</title>
      <description>Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump claimed late Friday night to have struck a deal for a new debate with Vice President Harris, the presumptive Democratic nominee. But the Harris campaign said Saturday that she never agreed to such a deal, urging Trump to keep the debate date he agreed to with President Biden before Biden withdrew from the race last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a02fc7e0-51ae-11ef-81e5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 15:39:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40550d0-519c-11ef-ad2d-0000a1ace047</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 13:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We lost sight of him’: Local police radio traffic shows failed search for Trump rally shooter</title>
      <description>The Washington Post obtained a transcript of encrypted radio communications by local police that, along with interviews, provides the clearest picture yet of the minute-by-minute hunt for Thomas Matthew Crooks. The examination also shows that communication between Secret Service and the local police was disjointed and time-consuming, helping to explain why Secret Service agents closest to Trump were taken by surprise when gunfire erupted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a661e90-5196-11ef-a0a1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 12:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense secretary revokes deals with accused 9/11 plotters that would have blocked the death penalty</title>
      <description>In a Friday night memo, Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin withdrew the agreements with Khalid Sheikh Mohammed and two others charged in the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks that would have allowed them to avoid the death penalty. He also took direct oversight of the case from retired Brig. Gen. Susan K. Escallier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84fc0481-5135-11ef-8890-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2024 01:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military moves additional forces toward Israel as Iran threatens to attack</title>
      <description>The Pentagon has ordered the deployment of Navy destroyers and cruisers, both with offensive and defensive ballistic missile capabilities, and an additional squadron of fighter jets to the Middle East as Tehran vows to avenge the killing of militant leaders, officials said Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83e64544-5129-11ef-bd5d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 23:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 7 highlights from Paris Olympics: Richardson back on track; Marchand a four-time gold medalist; an unlikely U.S. medal</title>
      <description>Sha’Carri Richardson easily won her heat in the 100 meters and is a favorite to take gold in that event three years after being suspended for the Tokyo Games. In the pool, Leon Marchand, the hometown hero, cruised to his fourth gold of these Games in the 200-meter individual medley, while American star Caeleb Dressel failed to advance to Saturday's 100-meter butterfly final and Regan Smith grabbed her second silver of the week for the United States. And back at the track, Grant Fisher used a strong finishing kick to capture the first U.S. medal in the men's 10,000 since Galen Rupp’s silver in 2012 — and only the second since 1964.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0eeef780-5120-11ef-8e1d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 22:39:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As markets slump, Nasdaq closes in correction territory, weeks after setting a record high</title>
      <description>Markets have started August on a two-day down note, with the three major indexes accelerating their slide Friday. The Nasdaq composite index fell into correction territory — down about 10 percent from the record it set less than a month ago — following disappointing quarterly reports from Big Tech firms such as Amazon, Intel and Microsoft.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b540a450-510a-11ef-bac2-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 20:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian opposition figure Ilya Yashin says he demanded not to be freed in prisoner swap, was taken out of Russia against his will</title>
      <description>Yashin, a longtime friend and colleague of the late opposition leader Alexei Navalny, said at a news conference in Germany on Friday that he had submitted a document to Russian prison officials declaring that he did not want to be freed as part of any prisoner exchange: “I insist on my legal right to remain in the country where I was born.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">765351c0-50fb-11ef-ba4a-0000a1ace1c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 18:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
