<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 08:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Giuffre dies at 41. She was the public face of women who said they were sexually abused and trafficked by Jeffrey Epstein.</title>
      <description>In court papers, lawsuits and interviews spanning nearly a decade, Giuffre recounted coming under Epstein’s control as a 16-year-old and being “passed around like a platter of fruit” to his influential friends, including Britain's Prince Andrew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18fe1d40-2245-11f0-a186-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 02:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former congressman George Santos sentenced to more than 7 years in prison after pleading guilty to financial misconduct</title>
      <description>Santos’s attorneys had asked for him to face two years in prison, saying that he had accepted responsibility for his actions and writing in court filings that his actions “stemmed largely from a misguided desperation related to his political campaign, rather than inherent malice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c318db0-21f5-11f0-a30d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: We were on a date. And then his estranged wife showed up.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: We were on a date. And then his estranged wife showed up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05ab5750-21f3-11f0-914f-0000a1ace74d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 16:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director says Wisconsin judge has been arrested, accused of shielding an immigrant in her courthouse from being detained by ICE</title>
      <description>The arrest of Milwaukee County Circuit Judge Hannah Dugan was announced on X by FBI Director Kash Patel. The tweet was later deleted. It would be the first publicly known instance of the Justice Department charging a local official with allegedly interfering with immigration enforcement since President Donald Trump returned to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e44dd0-21e9-11f0-af3c-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 15:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bfe9ce0-21d9-11f0-a940-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A baby-faced GM swooped in for Travis Hunter and rocked the NFL draft. Here’s what we learned in the first round.</title>
      <description>As the NFL draft began Thursday night, the Jacksonville Jaguars executed one of the boldest trades in draft history to secure the Heisman Trophy winner, the Cleveland Browns gave themselves multiple options to draft a quarterback, and the New York Giants traded up for Mississippi quarterback Jaxson Dart, leaving Colorado’s Shedeur Sanders still available at the close of a fascinating night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a44d9070-21d6-11f0-abc2-0000a1ace67b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 13:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Majority of Americans now disapprove of Trump’s handling of immigration, a change from earlier this year, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Fifty-three percent of Americans say they disapprove of President Donald Trump’s handling of immigration, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll this month. In February, 48 percent said they disapproved and 50 percent approved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a0dbc60-21cc-11f0-a69c-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s approval ratings. Pete Hegseth. Pope’s funeral. Measles warning. College pact. NFL draft. Cicada invasion. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750c4390-21c4-11f0-a46f-0000a1ace12c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tells Justice Dept to probe Democrats’ core fundraising platform</title>
      <description>The president’s directive to his attorney general to investigate fundraising infrastructure, such as ActBlue, escalates his efforts to target political opponents — in this case, the central machinery of the opposition party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3c2341-217a-11f0-a46f-0000a1ace12c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 02:11:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans pick quarterback Cam Ward, Jaguars take Heisman Trophy winner Travis Hunter to start NFL draft. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The NFL's annual draft is underway in Green Bay, Wisconsin, with the Jaguars making an early splash by trading up to No. 2 to take Hunter. All 32 teams began the day with a first-round pick, something that had never happened in the NFL's modern era, according to the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f553c310-216b-11f0-b10d-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 00:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top donors to Trump’s $239 million inauguration fund include more than a dozen administration nominees</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump raised a record sum for his 2025 inauguration celebrations, propelled by contributions from corporations and ultra-wealthy individuals. The donors who gave at least $1 million to the fund include crypto companies and a poultry giant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">205eb1b1-215c-11f0-a2a8-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 22:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to return second migrant sent to megaprison in El Salvador</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Stephanie Gallagher in Maryland ruled Wednesday that the man should be returned because he was deported despite being part of a class action settlement that should have protected him from removal. The case marks the second time a federal judge has ordered the Trump administration to return a migrant sent to El Salvador’s Terrorism Confinement Center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55a09b50-2129-11f0-a047-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Forceful friend invites herself to all your plans</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Forceful friend invites herself to all your plans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33641930-2125-11f0-9d92-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 16:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. could face millions of measles cases over the next 25 years if vaccination rates drop 10 percent, according to new research</title>
      <description>At current state vaccination rates, measles could become commonplace in the U.S. with hundreds of thousands of cases over the same period, according to results from a model published Thursday in the medical journal JAMA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c79bbaa0-211f-11f0-a46f-0000a1ace12c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 15:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk had the government in his grasp. Then it unraveled as he clashed with Trump’s Cabinet.</title>
      <description>A showdown last week with Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent was the billionaire’s latest confrontation with a top Trump appointee in a controversial three-month stint as head of the U.S. DOGE Service. But Musk sparred with other secretaries and aides well before he announced he would soon head back to Tesla.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b25060c1-2114-11f0-811a-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 14:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The likely top pick in the NFL draft in today‘s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70fc1f50-2110-11f0-97df-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 13:31:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump aides consider opening up at least six national monuments for mining, oil drilling</title>
      <description>Trump officials are analyzing whether to scale back the extent of national monuments spanning millions of acres out West, according to two people familiar with the matter and an internal Interior Department document. Redrawing the boundaries would set up a potential legal battle pitting pro-development conservatives against environmentalists and tribes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed3eab01-20fc-11f0-8f5e-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 11:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth. Elon Musk blowup. Russian strikes. Shrinking monuments. Wildfire smoke. NFL draft. Shakespeare’s wife. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ad2910-20fb-11f0-b632-0000a1ace605</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth had Signal chat app installed on a computer in his Pentagon office</title>
      <description>Hegseth directed the installation of Signal, a commercially available messaging platform, on a desktop computer, said three people familiar with the matter, illustrating the extent to which he has integrated use of the unclassified communications tool with the highly secure systems the U.S. government relies on to safeguard military plans and other sensitive information.
The move was intended to circumvent a lack of cellphone service in much of the Pentagon and enable easier communication with the White House and other Trump officials, these people said, speaking on the condition of anonymity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7aaad3f0-209f-11f0-ace0-0000a1acefbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s fury over a Tesla Autopilot crash investigation foreshadowed his war on Washington</title>
      <description>“Hubris Maximus: The Shattering of Elon Musk,” by Washington Post technology reporter Faiz Siddiqui, details the CEO’s abrasive tactics and contempt for regulators charged with overseeing his companies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3821cbc0-208a-11f0-9c93-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 21:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. and the rise of ‘MAHA moms’: Three columnists discuss health in Trump’s America</title>
      <description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr.'s tenure as HHS secretary has been every bit as troubling as many feared.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dada1cd0-2082-11f0-9f0a-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:38:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-trans posts pass muster under Meta’s new hate-speech rules</title>
      <description>The social media giant's advisory board approves videos containing disparaging remarks about trans people, in a first test of looser content rules introduced in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">996ddc00-207d-11f0-9d35-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grandma tired of hearing the grandkids are ‘too busy’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grandma tired of hearing the grandkids are ‘too busy’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49fd0a20-205e-11f0-984c-000a1ace2658</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Durbin, Senate’s No. 2 Democrat, announces his retirement, saying ‘it’s time to pass the torch’</title>
      <description>The Illinois senator, first elected to the chamber in 1996, said he won’t seek reelection next year, opening up a senior leadership position and a seat in a deep-blue state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5baacd0-205b-11f0-9ba3-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: European Central Bank President Christine Lagarde joins David Ignatius on The ’Ship, The Post’s new leadership series</title>
      <description>Lagarde talks with our Opinions columnist about her stewardship of the ECB at a pivotal moment for the global economic order. Watch live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8de3450-2057-11f0-a620-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World’s largest bleaching event on record has harmed 84 percent of coral reefs, scientists say</title>
      <description>As sea temperatures rise, coral reefs around the world are losing their color at an unprecedented scale, federal marine scientists announced this week, with 84 percent of reefs exposed to bleaching levels of heat since 2023. The National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration’s new assessment comes amid the planet’s fourth global coral bleaching event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a336a8b0-2056-11f0-86dd-0000a1ace0f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 15:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top economic advisers urged Trump to back off attacks on Fed chief after stock markets slid, people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick were among officials warning the president of financial market disruption, according to three people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45fbe020-2051-11f0-b7b4-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 14:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A franchise that's ‘long been tied to real-world politics’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">485ebae0-2047-11f0-beb9-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 13:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth under pressure. Tesla slump. Trump’s economy. Vaccine poll. Sarah Palin. Tree-friendly cities. Boozy chimps. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a4f1790-2032-11f0-bf64-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s inner circle is weighing whether the White House should back raising taxes on incomes over $1 million</title>
      <description>Some allies, including Vice President JD Vance, have expressed openness to the idea, people familiar with the talks say. But Republicans in Congress and many outside advisers are sharply opposed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8ab5271-1fbe-11f0-b32d-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla earnings plunge 71 percent, first-quarter report shows, as Elon Musk fuels firestorm of controversy</title>
      <description>The electric vehicle manufacturer announced quarterly earnings were down from a year earlier, amid tariff threats and protests over the CEO’s role in pushing government cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bc771c0-1fb9-11f0-8342-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 20:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. proposes recognizing Russian annexation of Crimea as part of Ukraine deal, according to people familiar with talks</title>
      <description>Recognition of Crimea and eventual lifting of sanctions would come in exchange for Russia agreeing to halt hostilities. Ukraine’s European partners are expected to push for security guarantees, as well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd2eaf80-1fa3-11f0-a75b-0000a1ace34c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems to support letting religious parents pull their children from public school story time with LGBTQ books</title>
      <description>In a case that has implications for public schools nationwide, the justices appeared to back the idea that parents can opt their children out of lessons featuring stories about gay characters or same-sex marriage if those books conflict with their religious beliefs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a4b5f30-1f9d-11f0-83f7-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 17:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She asks for their flight info; daughter-in-law suggests therapy</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She asks for their flight info; daughter-in-law suggests therapy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f6ef73-1f93-11f0-a4f6-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 16:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio’s proposal to shake up State Department targets programs focused on human rights, war crimes and democracy, documents show</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio’s envisioned overhaul of America’s primary foreign policy institution comes as the Trump administration continues to reorient the United States on the world stage while dramatically cutting costs and downsizing staff in a bid for efficiency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cb8ccd0-1f89-11f0-90bf-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 14:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mayoral election in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd9eef30-1f7d-11f0-b4d8-0000a1acef88</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMF predicts Trump’s tariffs will cause ‘significant slowdown’ in the world economy and hamper progress in bringing down inflation</title>
      <description>Global growth will slow to an annual rate of 2.8 percent, half a percentage point lower than projected in January, the International Monetary Fund said Tuesday. The slowdown will be particularly sharp for the U.S. economy, which will grow this year at an annual rate of 1.8 percent, one third lower than its January estimate and a full percentage point below last year’s mark, the IMF said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9cf34a0-1f79-11f0-ba65-0000a1ace70b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 13:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope contenders. Pete Hegseth. DOGE data grab. Trump vs. Harvard. Food dyes. Thunderstorms. Meteor shower. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f14dc130-1f68-11f0-8c3e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis’s funeral will be held on Saturday</title>
      <description>The pope’s body will rest in an open coffin for public viewing, the Vatican said, in a ceremony that Francis called for to be simplified a year ago. Francis, 88, died Monday of a cerebral stroke and cardiocirculatory collapse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dadcd80-1f5c-11f0-b84a-0000a1acef69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 09:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The names of the potential next pope are circulating. Here are some of the contenders.</title>
      <description>Ahead of the conclave to select Pope Francis’s successor, possible candidates include cardinals Bo of Myanmar, Tagle of the Philippines and Italians Pizzaballa and Parolin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f8b9560-1f0d-11f0-9127-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 35-year-old lawyer told Trump the Smithsonian needs changing. He’s ordered her to remove ‘improper ideology.’</title>
      <description>Lindsey Halligan is an attorney assigned to help deemphasize “the negative” at a premier cultural institution. She explained her role to The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bae4c350-1f04-11f0-967d-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 23:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department allows DOGE staffers to access sensitive case data for millions of immigrants</title>
      <description>Representatives for the U.S. DOGE Service have received permission to access a Justice Department system that contains information including the addresses and case histories for millions of legal and undocumented immigrants, according to documents obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">309c6380-1efd-11f0-80b5-000a1acef398</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard sues Trump administration in escalating confrontation, claiming $2.2 billion funding freeze violates Constitution</title>
      <description>The university argues that government actions, including the freeze of federal funding, violated the First Amendment, exceeded its authority and failed to follow administrative procedures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e747eef0-1ef4-11f0-a466-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 21:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nadine Menendez, wife of ex-senator Bob Menendez, convicted in bribery scheme that ensnared him</title>
      <description>Prosecutors described Nadine Menendez as a liaison between then-Sen. Bob Menendez (D-New Jersey) and the contacts who paid him bribes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9a826d0-1eec-11f0-aac3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 20:10:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican confirms Pope Francis died of a cerebral stroke and cardiocirculatory collapse. Tributes continue to pour in.</title>
      <description>He died Monday morning at the age of 88 after a recent bout with double pneumonia. Francis had made public appearances and held private audiences before and during Easter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea947951-1edd-11f0-9047-000a1acefc15</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Expecting a girl this time, couple goes over the top celebrating</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Expecting a girl this time, couple goes over the top celebrating</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23abe3e0-1eca-11f0-b292-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 16:03:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘5 things’ emails for federal employees are going by the wayside as Elon Musk readies his exit from DOGE</title>
      <description>As the billionaire and presidential adviser prepares to leave his government role, his signature email initiative is failing, with more agencies now telling employees to ignore the emails. There was never a plan for how to handle employees’ replies, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd49df10-1ec0-11f0-86c5-0000a1acef64</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 14:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular franchise is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da639030-1eb4-11f0-9dc3-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Catholics mourn Pope Francis, church prepares for next steps, and names for a successor circulate. Follow our live updates.</title>
      <description>Pope Francis died at the age of 88 at 7:35 a.m. local time Monday, the Vatican said, ending a historic chapter — and setting in motion a carefully orchestrated transition aimed at ensuring the stability and continuity of the Roman Catholic Church.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f703810-1eb3-11f0-9d8f-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis. Sensitive documents. Elon Musk’s role. El Salvador. Supreme Court. Weight-loss drugs. Healthy aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3cb4f80-1e9f-11f0-bc27-000a1ace3c07</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
