<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 10:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>President Joe Biden and Hillary Clinton headline Night 1 of the Democratic National Convention. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>As his party gathers to rally around a new nominee, the president, who withdrew from the race last month, will speak on the first day of the convention. He then plans to leave for a family vacation as a jubilant convention goes on without him.
And while he had hoped this week would be about rallying the party around his vision for a second term, he has now reoriented himself around bolstering Vice President Kamala Harris, a recognition that his legacy is deeply tied to whether she can win in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">126c7510-5e7f-11ef-b6cf-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 23:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI and intelligence agencies conclude Iran was behind attempted hacks of Trump campaign and Democratic presidential campaign</title>
      <description>In a joint statement, the agencies say they are confident "the Iranians have through social engineering and other efforts sought access to individuals with direct access to the Presidential campaigns of both political parties." It is unclear what information — if any — was obtained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6114aa20-5e7a-11ef-9638-0000a1acef6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 22:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under new deal, Afghan refugees will be temporarily relocated to Philippines as part of a pathway to U.S. resettlement</title>
      <description>Tens of thousands of Afghans eligible for relocation to the United States remain scattered across the globe in the wake of the chaotic evacuation from Kabul in 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a348b780-5e6e-11ef-809a-0000a1ace068</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 21:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former GOP congressman George Santos pleads guilty to identity theft and wire fraud</title>
      <description>Santos (R), who lied about his credentials and life story during his 2022 campaign, was charged with defrauding donors by taking their money for his personal use and using their credit cards without authorization, wrongfully claiming unemployment benefits, and lying on his congressional financial disclosure statements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44e3ce30-5e66-11ef-9b3a-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrystul Kizer, child sex-trafficking victim who killed her abuser, is sentenced to 11 years in prison</title>
      <description>Kizer was 17 when she shot Randall Volar III, who’d filmed his abuse of her. Rather than risk a life sentence, Kizer, now 24, pleaded guilty in May to a reduced charge of second-degree reckless homicide with use of a dangerous weapon, leaving her fate to a Wisconsin circuit court judge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ef078f0-5e51-11ef-b4c2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 17:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council member Trayon White Sr. charged with bribery and accused of taking cash to help companies secure government funds</title>
      <description>White, a Democrat who represents Ward 8 in Southeast Washington, is accused of taking cash in exchange for assisting businesses with securing government contracts or grants worth millions, according to court documents. He is expected to appear in federal court in D.C. this afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83f5c090-5e45-11ef-ac73-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband constantly interrupts spouse’s night of alone time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband constantly interrupts spouse’s night of alone time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96571050-5e44-11ef-be6b-0000a1ace576</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 16:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phil Donahue dies at 88. The long-reigning king of daytime TV tackled tough issues but pioneered a breezy show format.</title>
      <description>“Phil Donahue Show” audience members asked questions and offered opinions — a format that opened the door to successors and rivals including Oprah Winfrey. Over the years, Donahue interviewed late-night host Johnny Carson, pop star Elton John and boxer Muhammad Ali. Some of his more controversial guests included novelist Ayn Rand, Nation of Islam leader Louis Farrakhan and Ku Klux Klan grand wizard David Duke.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdf75981-5e30-11ef-bda8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A presidential candidate’s onetime summer job is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27e41e70-5e2f-11ef-a52e-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic convention. Harris-Trump poll. Gaza talks. Connecticut floods. Ukraine. Alain Delon. Carmel-by-the-Sea. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f3d93a0-5e1a-11ef-8a1e-0000a1ace1c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a Russian town controlled by Ukrainian forces, stranded civilians wonder what’s next</title>
      <description>For the Ukrainian forces on the ground in Sudzha, the offensive is seen less as a conquest for long-term annexation and more as a negotiating tactic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48735ba0-5db8-11ef-933b-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 23:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI arrests D.C. council member Trayon White Sr.</title>
      <description>The circumstances of the arrest and the allegations against White, who represents Ward 8 in Southeast D.C., were not immediately clear. The FBI’s Washington Field Office declined to comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f292b20-5dad-11ef-a71c-0000a1ace86b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 22:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right influencers turn against Trump campaign, urging the former president’s team to take harder-right positions</title>
      <description>As Donald Trump’s campaign grapples with slumping performance in the polls, some activists are threatening a digital “war” against the Republican candidate’s aides and allies unless it adopts harder-right positions on race and immigration. The insider attacks, which come as other backers are calling for Trump to take a more disciplined, policy-oriented approach to his campaign, highlight a new vulnerability in one of the loudest corners of Trump’s nationwide base, presenting a challenge for campaign officials who have worked to publicly disavow or disregard extreme voices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df50f1c0-5d9c-11ef-8d7f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 20:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches in effect until 10 p.m. for the D.C. area</title>
      <description>Storms through late this evening could produce damaging wind gusts and flooding rains. The storms are most probable between 6 and 10 p.m.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23125c40-5d99-11ef-933b-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 19:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He found a Project 2025 duffel bag with documents inside. Then police showed up at his house.</title>
      <description>Journalist and author Malcolm Harris says he found the bag, with branding for the conservative Heritage Foundation think tank, left on a ledge in Capitol Hill. But it turned out to be more trouble than it was worth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0b37810-5d87-11ef-90da-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 17:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54f0ea10-5d7b-11ef-9f0f-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 16:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6aa6fa30-5d66-11ef-8269-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 13:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris holds slight national lead over Trump, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris holds a narrow lead over former president Donald Trump in the presidential election, a notable improvement for Democrats in a contest that a little more than a month ago showed President Joe Biden and Trump in a dead heat, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ada1cf70-5d59-11ef-93d6-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 12:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alain Delon dies at 88. The angel-faced French actor achieved global fame playing dark characters in films such as ‘Purple Noon.’</title>
      <description>Delon, who vaulted to stardom with his performance as the murderous opportunist Tom Ripley in “Purple Noon” (1960), was sometimes called “the male Brigitte Bardot” for his smoldering good looks. He became one of the most photographed men in the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31c796c0-5d52-11ef-9181-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Aug 2024 11:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chrystul Kizer, a child sex trafficking victim who killed her abuser, is finally about to learn her fate</title>
      <description>Kizer was 17 when she shot Randall Volar III, who’d been filming his abuse of her and other girls in Kenosha, Wisc. On Monday, a judge will decide whether Kizer — whose case was the subject of a 2019 Washington Post investigation — deserves a prison cell or a counseling program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9798b100-5ce4-11ef-bf18-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 22:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-congressman George Santos expected to plead guilty to multiple counts, a person familiar with the matter says</title>
      <description>The former Republican lawmaker was ousted from the House late last year after being caught in a web of lies about his background and alleged money grifting. He is expected to plead guilty in federal court on Long Island on Monday afternoon, a person familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">423c3eb0-5cc2-11ef-8750-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jared Kushner is planning a luxury resort on the Albanian coast. His use of foreign funds again raises questions of conflicts.</title>
      <description>Environmentalists fear the resort development could destroy a delicate ecosystem. Kushner said it is an “incredible canvas” for his dreams of developing luxury projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa9afa50-5ca4-11ef-b0f3-0000a1ace955</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 14:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09a14700-5c9d-11ef-88f2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine’s Kursk offensive derailed secret efforts for a partial cease-fire with Russia, officials say</title>
      <description>Moscow and Kyiv were set to send delegations to Doha this month to negotiate a landmark agreement to halt strikes by both sides on energy and power infrastructure, diplomats and officials familiar with the discussions said. But the indirect talks, with the Qataris as mediators and meeting separately with the Ukrainian and Russian delegations, were derailed by Ukraine’s surprise incursion into Russia’s Kursk region last week, according to the officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d52f0e71-5c98-11ef-8b27-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 13:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former D.C. Parks and Recreation worker convicted of manslaughter in fatal shooting of unarmed 13-year-old</title>
      <description>The worker had asserted he shot the youngster, whom he saw outside his Brookland home in the early morning hours, because he feared for his life. He was found not guilty of a more serious charge, second-degree murder. The shooting had sparked outrage in D.C. and drew comparisons to other killings of unarmed Black youths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80984010-5c08-11ef-bf04-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 19:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. proposes new Gaza cease-fire plan as talks adjourn in Qatar, seeking agreement by next week</title>
      <description>The United States, Egypt and Qatar have provided Israel and Hamas with a new cease-fire proposal they said narrows the gaps between the two parties and could lead to an agreement by the end of next week, according to a joint statement. The release did not include specific details from the proposal, however, and drew immediate criticism from Hamas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cbf47e1-5be3-11ef-b43f-0000a1aced44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 15:24:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f213b6a0-5bd3-11ef-b6d3-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 13:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans have positive first impressions of Walz and negative ones of Vance, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz has made a positive first impression after Vice President Kamala Harris announced him as her running mate. But Sen. JD Vance (R-Ohio), former president Donald Trump’s choice for vice president, is not winning the popularity contest. A Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll finds 32 percent of Americans have a favorable impression of Vance and 42 percent find him unfavorable, a net favorability rating of -10 points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">166405f0-5bca-11ef-ad3e-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 12:21:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris unveils her most detailed economic agenda since becoming the Democratic nominee, including a $6,000 tax credit for newborns</title>
      <description>Ahead of Vice President Kamala Harris’s speech in North Carolina, her campaign announced support for more than a dozen economic policies aimed at “lowering costs for American families.” Other proposals call for eliminating medical debt for millions of Americans, banning price gouging for groceries, capping prescription drug costs and providing $25,000 subsidies for first-time home buyers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fb70010-5bc1-11ef-8e6d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris momentum. Trump attacks. Ukraine. Mpox. Matthew Perry. Social Security numbers. Yoga benefits. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b07fe3e0-5bbe-11ef-8e6d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Majority Leader Chuck Schumer writes: To protect rule of law, Congress must check Supreme Court overreach</title>
      <description>To protect rule of law, Congress must check Supreme Court overreach</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92575740-5b55-11ef-a61e-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 22:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris has opened up a second path to victory over Trump, The Post’s polling model shows</title>
      <description>Relative to the day that Joe Biden dropped out of the contest, Kamala Harris has gained two percentage points nationally and, as of Sunday, leads against Donald Trump in our national polling average.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5431411-5b51-11ef-9842-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 21:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service approves new plan for Trump to continue outdoor rallies, including use of bulletproof glass</title>
      <description>In a first for Donald Trump’s 2024 campaign, the Secret Service will use technical security assets that have not normally been provided for presidential candidates, the agency said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">804fccd0-5b41-11ef-8b94-0000a1ace465</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 20:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Travel icon Rick Steves is answering your questions about how to plan a once-in-a-lifetime Europe trip and more</title>
      <description>Happening now: Travel icon Rick Steves is answering your questions about how to plan a once-in-a-lifetime Europe trip and more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d50a6c90-5b31-11ef-b142-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 18:11:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five people were charged in connection with actor Matthew Perry’s 2023 overdose death, Justice Department confirms</title>
      <description>The Los Angeles Police Department said in May that it was working with the Drug Enforcement Administration and the U.S. Postal Service to investigate the source of the ketamine that killed the “Friends” star last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2ef8ac0-5b29-11ef-95c6-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 17:13:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents are tired of the eggshell-walk around son’s moody fiancée</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents are tired of the eggshell-walk around son’s moody fiancée</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36d48dd0-5b22-11ef-b8f4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 16:19:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI detection tools can fail to catch election deepfakes</title>
      <description>Deepfake detectors have been marketed as a silver bullet for identifying AI fakes, or “deepfakes.” But the science of detecting manipulated content is in its early stages, while the videos are proliferating. See how this technology works — and where it falls short.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a0f3191-5b1d-11ef-9d03-0000a1ace9f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 15:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance and Tim Walz have both agreed to an Oct. 1 vice-presidential debate hosted by CBS</title>
      <description>Vance, the Republican vice-presidential nominee, confirmed his plans to attend, saying on X that “the American people deserve as many debates as possible.” He also proposed an earlier debate in September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd1ae8a0-5b0f-11ef-a111-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 14:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One stone’s long journey in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ed20070-5b0e-11ef-b25c-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. request. Cease-fire talks. Ukraine attack. Mpox. Aging molecules. Imane Khelif. Stonehenge. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e184fa1-5af5-11ef-8b94-0000a1ace465</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza’s Health Ministry says 40,000 Palestinians have been killed in Israel’s war against Hamas. A full count is elusive.</title>
      <description>The Gaza Health Ministry does not distinguish between civilians and combatants but says the majority of the dead are women and children. Aid workers say the 40,000 figure is likely to be an undercount that excludes thousands of bodies believed to be buried under rubble. About 1,200 people in Israel were killed in Hamas’s Oct. 7 attack, and more than 300 Israeli soldiers have died in combat since late October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">071e6210-5aef-11ef-bfc6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 10:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gena Rowlands dies at 94. The actress starred in ‘A Woman Under the Influence’ and ‘The Notebook.’</title>
      <description>Over seven decades, Rowlands worked sparingly in mainstream fare but managed to attract a cascade of superlatives and an honorary Academy Award for career achievement in 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d8c1590-5aa3-11ef-91f9-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 01:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia President Minouche Shafik resigns after drawing ire over response to pro-Palestinian protests</title>
      <description>The resignation ends a short and turbulent tenure marred by controversy and backlash over how she handled an outbreak of protests on campus last spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43bdf51-5a9e-11ef-92f2-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 00:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. tried to meet with Kamala Harris to discuss endorsing her in exchange for a Cabinet job</title>
      <description>Harris has rebuffed the outreach, while Kennedy has had conversations with Republican nominee Donald Trump about a role in his administration as well. Kennedy is exploring multiple options for the future of his presidential effort, which has seen a decline in national polling since President Joe Biden dropped out of the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d899a6b2-5a95-11ef-9843-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 23:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Stonehenge mystery has (maybe) been solved, but the revelation raises tantalizing new questions</title>
      <description>Researchers on Wednesday revealed that the long-mysterious “Altar Stone” at the heart of Stonehenge came from faraway Scotland, leading scientists to question how — and why — a six-ton slab of sandstone made its way from north to south 5,000 years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cc53ed0-5a84-11ef-9d32-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 21:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harris magnifies America’s generational and cultural divides</title>
      <description>“Make America Great Again” versus “We are not going back.” Lee Greenwood’s music versus Beyoncé’s. The two candidates, their rallies and their movements are showcasing two sides of the country split by demographics and cultural touchstones — not just party and policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6f59a31-5a74-11ef-9cc0-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WHO declares a global health emergency as a new form of mpox spreads rapidly in Africa</title>
      <description>Cases in Africa have already surpassed 15,000 this year, exceeding the toll for all of 2023. Two years ago, mpox emerged as a threat in the United States as cases surged mainly among gay men.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c3130a0-5a67-11ef-9f26-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 18:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to ditch sister’s ‘insufferable’ guy without hurting feelings</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to ditch sister’s ‘insufferable’ guy without hurting feelings</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bb7f540-5a56-11ef-b381-0000a1acec34</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Our food critic is telling the story of the time he judged Tim Walz’s hot dish</title>
      <description>Happening now: Our food critic is telling the story of the time he judged Tim Walz’s hot dish</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">340d8701-5a50-11ef-8925-0000a1ace047</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 15:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress declined to create a national monument to recognize the 1908 Springfield race riot. Now Biden will do it on his own.</title>
      <description>The president will make the designation during a Friday event with civil rights leaders and Illinois lawmakers, the White House confirmed to The Washington Post on Wednesday. More than a century after the 1908 race riot sparked the founding of the NAACP, Springfield is reeling from the fatal shooting of Sonya Massey, an unarmed Black woman, by an Illinois sheriff’s deputy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">575b9370-5a44-11ef-bff6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
