<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 06:03:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Damascus residents report hearing gunfire as Syrian rebels claim to enter the capital</title>
      <description>Rebels entered the Syrian capital in a crucial stage of a lightning advance launched by the armed Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham less than two weeks ago. They say they are looking for President Bashar al-Assad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7fd3c00-b512-11ef-a3ef-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 03:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian rebels enter strategic city of Homs, threaten Damascus, as army withdraws. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The Syrian army was “repositioning itself to the outskirts” of Homs, pro-government Sham FM said Saturday, as the Islamist group Hayat Tahrir al-Sham announced its entry into the country’s third-largest city, 90 miles north of the capital. The rapid advance of HTS from the north, joined Saturday by rebels from the south, has posed the greatest threat yet to the 24-year rule of President Bashar al-Assad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae5eb770-b4e8-11ef-8203-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 22:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>45 definitive hotel rules that every traveler should follow</title>
      <description>Hotels are here to serve you, but best not to push it. If you want to be an upstanding guest and expert traveler, you still need to follow the main tenets of a hotel stay. These are the rules for tipping, parking, cleaning and much more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">849aa5e0-b4e6-11ef-b809-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 21:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin claimed Jordanians ‘crashed’ Quantico. Feds say it was an Amazon delivery.</title>
      <description>The Republican governor has used the arrest of two undocumented men, who misunderstood directions to stop at a check-in station, to inflame fears over illegal immigration. Federal prosecutors — who initially charged the pair with misdemeanor trespassing, but later dropped those charges — say that, while the Jordanians were in the country illegally and are in the process of being deported, they did not crash the gate or intend to do any harm at Quantico.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ccd9640-b4cc-11ef-bb57-0000a1ace659</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 18:52:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrects link: All-cash buyers are still snapping up homes. See where they’re buying.</title>
      <description>The share of home buyers paying all cash reached 33 percent through August this year — one of the highest rates since the years after the Great Recession. Search by Zip code to see where all-cash purchases are happening near you. A previous alert directed readers to the wrong story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2d60c00-b4b8-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 16:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-cash buyers are still snapping up homes. See where they’re buying.</title>
      <description>The share of home buyers paying all cash reached 33 percent through August this year — one of the highest rates since the years after the Great Recession. Search by Zip code to see where all-cash purchases are happening near you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6514a720-b4b4-11ef-87a8-0000a1acec23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 16:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7399cf0-b4a7-11ef-8441-0000a1ace707</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea President Yoon Suk Yeol impeachment vote fails after martial law decision</title>
      <description>The South Korean National Assembly voted on President Yoon Suk Yeol’s impeachment Saturday but failed to meet the minimum ballot threshold after a boycott by members of Yoon’s ruling People Power Party. The failed vote, watched by thousands of protesters outside, is likely to trigger further political disarray and growing demands for resignation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d414c600-b496-11ef-bf68-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 12:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has tried to move federal jobs out of D.C. before. It didn’t go as planned.</title>
      <description>As he returns to the White House, President-elect Donald Trump has said he will relocate federal workers. Here’s what happened the last time he tried to do that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4485ddd0-b428-11ef-b861-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 23:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDA mandates testing of nation’s milk supply for bird flu, expanding previous efforts to fight H5N1 outbreak infecting U.S. cows</title>
      <description>The order requires dairy farmers and processors to share raw milk samples before pasteurization. The broader testing, which public health experts have been clamoring for, is slated to begin the week of Dec. 16, after nearly 60 people, mostly farmworkers, have been sickened with bird flu in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f088c280-b407-11ef-a153-0000a1ace028</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 19:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My wife is fed up with my ‘clingy’ friend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My wife is fed up with my 'clingy' friend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59070bb1-b3f8-11ef-92f7-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dangerous women, a divorce party and wedding bell blues: Seven writers describe their overactive group chats</title>
      <description>Everyone has at least one overactive group chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51d1b7c0-b3f6-11ef-96f2-000a1ace7cc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 17:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Naval Academy may consider race in admissions, judge rules, saying a diverse officer corps is important to national security</title>
      <description>Last year, the Supreme Court rejected race-conscious affirmative action in college admissions, but the case included a footnote carving out the potential use of race in admissions within the nation’s military academies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">435cd6b0-b3f2-11ef-a153-0000a1ace028</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are those delivery texts a scam? Michelle Singletary is answering your questions on financial fraud now.</title>
      <description>In her new seven-part series titled “Scammed,” personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary deconstructs how one woman lost her life savings to a government impersonation scam. But how do you spot potential fraudsters? Ask Michelle your questions now during our live chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24ec1f10-b3ed-11ef-a4e0-0000a1ace9c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 16:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court upholds nationwide TikTok ban that is set to take effect in January</title>
      <description>The D.C. Court of Appeals has turned away a challenge to a fast-approaching nationwide ban of short-video app TikTok unless it divests from Chinese ownership by Jan. 19. The court said the law is constitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfd1cdf1-b3e7-11ef-8373-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 15:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0482ec70-b3e0-11ef-965f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 227,000 jobs in November, a solid gain reflecting improvement in the labor market</title>
      <description>The November jobs report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics adds more evidence that the labor market is healthy enough to allow the Federal Reserve to keep a more gradual path to lowering interest rates later this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0b66dc1-b3d6-11ef-9cdc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 13:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential Trump targets. New York manhunt. Syrian rebels. Bird flu. Global warming. College football. Notre Dame. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a26485f1-b3c9-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk revealed as backer of mysterious group defending Trump’s abortion stance</title>
      <description>Filings showed the billionaire put $20.5 million into a group called RBG PAC that told voters Donald Trump would protect abortion access and was criticized by the family of late Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">219e4880-b37d-11ef-8203-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 02:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting of UnitedHealthcare CEO in New York City, home to vast network of surveillance cameras, has fueled a crowdsourced manhunt</title>
      <description>The shooter seemingly vanished after being caught on video in one of the world’s most surveilled cities, offering an online community of wannabe detectives a tantalizing case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8d2b8c0-b35c-11ef-adbd-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spies are secretly at war with Russian drones. But Moscow is fighting back — with lots of lousy weapons.</title>
      <description>Faltering Russian drones point to modest successes in Western sanctions to block Moscow’s access to technology. Yet, aided by covert operatives, Russia’s weapons production is soaring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d3b6b00-b352-11ef-84c1-000a1ace76b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 21:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major 7.0-magnitude earthquake strikes off the Northern Californian coast, prompting tsunami warnings</title>
      <description>Shaking was felt across the northern part of the state, but the greater concern was the possibility of a tsunami. Tsunami warnings are in effect from near Santa Cruz, California, northward to the central coast of Oregon southwest of Eugene. Residents in these areas are urged to immediately evacuate inland and upward from the coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06a4ece0-b342-11ef-b62d-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A single mutation of the H5N1 bird flu among U.S. cows could make the virus adept at attaching to human cells, a new study reports</title>
      <description>There have been no documented cases of one human passing avian influenza to another, and researchers stress that other barriers remain before a mutated virus could be transmitted in that way. But public health officials worry about the possibility of a more dangerous strain of avian influenza getting loose in the general population that can more easily infect humans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64b703a1-b33c-11ef-a737-0000a1ace7d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 19:09:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police release new, unmasked photos of person sought for questioning in UnitedHealthcare CEO’s fatal shooting</title>
      <description>The images released Thursday show the person sought by the New York Police Department as it investigates the shooting of UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson. The pictures were distributed hours after reports emerged that investigators found a possible message on bullet casings found at the scene possibly suggesting a potential motive for Wednesday’s killing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0fd1151-b32d-11ef-b861-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She feels ‘monstrously vain’ about her upcoming facelift</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She feels ‘monstrously vain’ about her upcoming facelift</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012803e0-b32b-11ef-8126-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 17:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sudden retirement at this struggling tech company in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">437bbd51-b316-11ef-84c1-000a1ace76b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 14:36:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian rebels enter the city of Hama as army withdraws in latest setback for Assad’s regime</title>
      <description>In a televised announcement, the Syrian army said it had withdrawn from Hama after rebels entered the city from several directions. Islamist insurgents launched a surprise offensive last week, first capturing Aleppo and then heading farther south.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81cf371-b305-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 12:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Thompson. Pete Hegseth. Transgender care. French crisis. Memphis police. Bitcoin. Ancient canines. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73b61760-b300-11ef-a153-0000a1ace028</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Memphis police engage in excessive force, discriminate against Black and disabled people, Justice Dept. says</title>
      <description>In a scathing 73-page report, federal authorities said they had identified a pattern of unlawful conduct, including serious problems in the way officers handle traffic stops and deal with children, as well as deficiencies in training, policies and accountability for officers accused of misconduct.
The report comes nearly two years after Memphis police officers on a specialized street crime unit brutally beat Tyre Nichols, a 29-year-old Black man, after a traffic stop, injuries that resulted in his death three days later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb061d30-b2a3-11ef-8368-000a1acedb6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to have charges dismissed in Georgia 2020 election interference case, citing his presidential win</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s attorneys argued in a court filing Wednesday that the charges against him are unconstitutional now that he will be returning to the White House next month. Trump and his allies are being prosecuted as part of a sprawling election interference case that accuses them of criminally conspiring to try to overturn the 2020 election in Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b8540-b280-11ef-b861-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-confidence vote topples French government as Le Pen’s far-right party exercises unprecedented power, stoking economic anxiety</title>
      <description>The backing of Marine Le Pen’s far-right National Rally lawmakers was key to the success of the motion, which makes this the shortest-serving administration in the modern French republic, stalls efforts to plug a gaping hole in public finances and plunges France into political chaos. Prolonged uncertainty in the euro zone’s second-largest economy could have ripple effects across the continent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08a152d0-b276-11ef-910f-0000a1aceb1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks former SEC commissioner Paul Atkins to lead agency again, signaling a shift on regulation of finance and cryptocurrency</title>
      <description>Atkins currently advises financial services and crypto firms. He served on the Securities and Exchange Commission from 2002 to 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">063d1650-b271-11ef-9583-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court’s conservatives seem wary of blocking Tennessee’s ban on certain medical treatments for trans minors</title>
      <description>The justices appeared deeply divided along ideological lines in a historic case involving gender-transition care for trans minors, with key conservatives expressing concern about courts intervening in an evolving nationwide debate over such treatment. The case is the first in which the Supreme Court has considered gender-transition care for minors, which has been banned in about two dozen states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69363620-b26b-11ef-a216-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash App founder’s killing drew speculation of a random act. It instead offers a look into the underbelly of San Francisco’s elite.</title>
      <description>A San Francisco jury will now decide the fate of Nima Momeni, the tech consultant accused of killing Bob Lee in April 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60b6c410-b26b-11ef-a010-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO’s shooter waited for him to arrive at hotel and remains at large, officials say. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The suspected shooter, who was last seen in Central Park, waited several minutes before Brian Thompson’s arrival at a hotel in midtown Manhattan, New York Police Commissioner Jessica Tisch said. The motive behind the fatal attack is still unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">523c2ff0-b262-11ef-b27d-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Navarro, who was imprisoned for contempt of Congress in Jan. 6 case, to join second Trump administration as trade adviser</title>
      <description>Navarro, a former adviser to Donald Trump who served prison time for refusing to cooperate with the congressional investigation into the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, will have a senior role in Trump’s second administration, the president-elect announced Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f6d3ca1-b25c-11ef-a774-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO fatally shot outside midtown Manhattan hotel, person familiar with investigation says</title>
      <description>Brian Thompson was chief executive of one of the largest insurers in the United States. Police have not officially released the victim’s name as of Wednesday morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b89a521-b255-11ef-a216-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Word (or Phrase) of the year in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7173fc60-b24c-11ef-a2ad-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considering replacing Pete Hegseth as defense pick with Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, people familiar say</title>
      <description>The planned nomination of Hegseth, the former Fox News host, is in jeopardy in the Senate amid skepticism about his qualifications for the job and allegations of sexual misconduct and excessive drinking. Trump is looking at DeSantis, a former rival for the GOP presidential nomination, as an alternative, according to two people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private conversations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04f96c32-b244-11ef-8a57-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea. Trump administration. Hush money case. Transgender care. Snow. Online shopping. Harry Potter’s sword. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fbb38f0-b237-11ef-a68f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pick to lead the Drug Enforcement Administration announces his withdrawal from consideration</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump had tapped Chad Chronister to lead the agency grappling with a drug crisis fueled by the flow of illicit fentanyl. On Tuesday, Chronister said on social media that “as the gravity of this very important responsibility set in, I’ve concluded that I must respectfully withdraw from consideration.”

Rep. Thomas Massie (R-Kentucky) was among a group of conservative voices who pushed back against Chronister's selection, criticizing his enforcement of public health orders during the pandemic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d489acb0-b1c9-11ef-9eb6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s lawyers point to Hunter Biden pardon in seeking dismissal of N.Y. hush money case</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s felony conviction for falsifying business documents is tainted by the same corruption in the justice system that President Joe Biden decried when he announced his son’s pardon, Trump’s attorneys wrote in a document released Tuesday. The attorneys pointed to comments by Biden in defending his pardon of his son. Biden signed a pardon Sunday for Hunter Biden, who was found guilty of gun-related charges in Delaware and pleaded guilty to tax evasion in California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69e3ea40-b1c6-11ef-8a59-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of Israeli soldiers’ videos highlights the willful destruction of Gaza</title>
      <description>The Post verified more than 120 photos and videos of the war in Gaza, most of which were recorded by soldiers or posted on their social media accounts. The visuals show soldiers blowing up or setting fire to buildings — and often celebrating the destruction — occupying destroyed buildings, mocking Palestinians and calling for the Israeli resettlement of Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5cdd800-b1c0-11ef-85f0-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland proposes an RFK Stadium deal: A D.C. Air National Guard squadron in exchange for senators’ help moving the plan forward</title>
      <description>The negotiations come after a bill to give D.C. control of the RFK stadium site became part of the National Defense Authorization Act talks in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d924fd30-b1bd-11ef-b947-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean president says he will lift martial law after parliamentary vote and protests</title>
      <description>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol said early Wednesday local time that he would lift the martial law he had imposed just hours earlier and that he had ordered the withdrawal of troops from the streets of Seoul. The reversal came after lawmakers convened urgently to vote to overturn the president’s decree and crowds of protesters gathered outside the National Assembly to demonstrate against the extraordinary move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9961eea2-b1af-11ef-ad19-0000a1ace1f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels left out of mother-in-law’s dying wishes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels left out of mother-in-law’s dying wishes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe787560-b197-11ef-abc7-0000a1ace4bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean military says martial law will remain in place despite parliament’s vote to reject it. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>A majority of the parliament voted to end President Yoon Suk Yeol’s state of emergency hours after it began; under the constitution, the president must comply and end the decree. But no time frame is specified for compliance, and the army said martial law will remain in place until the president lifts it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164c13b0-b196-11ef-9382-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A social media ban in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9df0ac0-b183-11ef-b357-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol declares martial law, accusing opposition of paralyzing the government and backing North Korea</title>
      <description>In a televised briefing, Yoon said he was protecting the constitutional democratic order and vowed to eradicate pro-North Korean elements. The South Korean president’s approval ratings have dropped in recent months, and he has struggled with the opposition-dominated parliament.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fe65f50-b181-11ef-8945-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden. Trump’s warning. California resistance. Hannah Kobayashi. Cucumber recall. China coffee. Strava art. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ba6f80-b16e-11ef-9805-0000a1aced75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
