<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Zappa’s kids are still grappling with his legacy — and each other</title>
      <description>Dweezil no longer speaks to his siblings. Moon has spent decades reassessing the family dynamic — emotional labor that lies thick on the pages of her new memoir.

Ahmet and Diva, meanwhile, seem dazed still by the force of their siblings’ anger — siblings with whom they share not just a fraught business partnership but also a one-of-a-kind childhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8834b451-56a6-11ef-9400-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 highlights from Paris Olympics: American Rai Benjamin rules the track; U.S. women’s basketball will play for gold</title>
      <description>Benjamin breezed to a gold medal in the men's 400-meter hurdles and helped erase the foibles of the U.S. men's 4x100 relay team, which finished seventh and was eventually disqualified because of a bad first baton exchange. Elsewhere, the U.S. women smothered Australia on the basketball court, ensuring a trip to their eighth straight gold medal game, where they will meet France on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bca4e0-56a0-11ef-b28e-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA rejects first psychedelic to treat PTSD, marking a setback and calling for more study of ecstasy-based drug</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration declined to approve MDMA to treat post-traumatic stress disorder, instead calling for another large study that could take years to complete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e97cc591-569c-11ef-845e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imane Khelif, female boxer who was a target of online attacks over ‘gender eligibility’ test, wins Olympic gold</title>
      <description>The Algerian fighter faced online hate after a Russia-linked boxing organization disqualified her from last year's world championships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3843df31-5696-11ef-9e61-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at Nixon’s resignation 50 years later</title>
      <description>On Aug. 9, 1974, Richard M. Nixon became the only U.S. president to have ever resigned. Learn more about the Watergate scandal and what led to his downfall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e3b63b0-5691-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who pleaded guilty to assaulting police during Capitol attack gets 20 years, the second longest sentence of Jan. 6 defendants</title>
      <description>David N. Dempsey deployed chemical spray on police and attacked them with poles in one of the most violent confrontations between law enforcement and the mob on Jan. 6, 2021. He pleaded guilty earlier this year to two counts of assaulting police with dangerous or deadly weapons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7352acf0-5682-11ef-a218-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A domestic flight with 62 people on board crashed in Brazil. It's unclear whether anyone survived.</title>
      <description>The plane crashed in a residential area in Vinhedo, a city in the state of São Paulo, leaving a fiery wreck as firefighters and military police responded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81e1ef1-5680-11ef-afe3-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchored by Sha'Carri Richardson, American women win gold in 4x100-meter relay, the 10th gold for U.S. track tea</title>
      <description>The American women have won the event in three of the past four Olympics and 12 times in Olympic history, more than any other country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15361410-5676-11ef-9d0d-000a1ace5b92</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam accelerates island building to challenge rising Chinese assertiveness in the South China Sea</title>
      <description>As tensions mount, Vietnam is dredging and filling in land, fortifying barriers and erecting structures to establish new military outposts. Satellite imagery reveals that Vietnam has ramped up its effort since January and is on track to create more than 1,000 acres of island territory this year, more than in any year prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a19bb90-566c-11ef-901b-0000a1acec0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: This couple want a life partnership, but worry the institution of marriage will ruin their relationship.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: This couple want a life partnership, but worry the institution of marriage will ruin their relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31ff9411-566a-11ef-ba6b-0000a1ace5d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash flood warnings in effect for D.C. area, tornadoes possible throughout region</title>
      <description>Torrential rain has prompted flash flood warnings for large parts of the metro region through late Friday morning. A tornado watch is also in effect until 2 p.m. and multiple warnings have already been issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">919afe31-5649-11ef-b6fc-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harris. Rally shooting. Ukraine attack. Debby. Mpox outbreak. Cash App payout. Noah Lyles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eb4bd70-563e-11ef-9b82-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Lyles was a reminder of the pandemic on the night he could've become an Olympic legend, columnist Jerry Brewer writes</title>
      <description>The U.S. sprinter finished third in the 200-meter race he was widely expected to win, then revealed he had tested positive for the coronavirus and indicated his Paris Games were over. Although we thought covid was behind us, Brewer writes, Thursday felt like the pandemic-affected 2021 Tokyo Olympics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adf79af1-55e2-11ef-bb84-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Harris and Walz in, some Democrats still consider withholding their vote in response to the Israel-Gaza war</title>
      <description>During the primaries, pro-Palestinian activists urged voters to withhold their support for President Joe Biden over his handling of the war. Roughly 700,000 Democrats nationwide checked a no-candidate option, left their presidential ballot blank or wrote in someone (or something) else. While that represents a tiny sliver of the electorate — and analysts lack data on each voter’s motivation — some strategists said the apparent protest turnout revealed weak spots for Kamala Harris’s campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a77b1710-55dd-11ef-bb6b-0000a1ace954</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 highlights from Paris Olympics: Holloway, Davis-Woodhall win big in track and field; U.S. men's basketball survives scare</title>
      <description>Grant Holloway cruised to victory in the men's 110-meter hurdles while Tara Davis-Woodhall captured her first Olympic gold, but they were perhaps overshadowed by Noah Lyles's bronze in the 200 meters and subsequent revelation that he ran with covid-19. In other events, the U.S. men's basketball team trailed for more than 35 of 40 minutes versus Nikola Jokic and Serbia but narrowly avoided what would have been its first Olympic loss since the 2004 Athens Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eef0f380-55d8-11ef-9b9a-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Harris confirm they will attend ABC’s Sept. 10 presidential debate as scheduled, network says</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump said in a Thursday news conference that he wants to debate his opponent three times, including the Sept. 10 date that was previously agreed to by both parties’ campaigns before President Joe Biden withdrew from the 2024 race. That date will serve as the first time Trump and Kamala Harris will share a stage since she was tapped to replace Biden weeks ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2825d90-55be-11ef-89a2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Sydney McLaughlin-Levrone breaks her own world record and wins gold in women’s 400-meter hurdles</title>
      <description>McLaughlin-Levrone ran the event in 50.37 seconds to break the world record she set at Olympic trials in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13afe850-55bd-11ef-bff7-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American sprinter Noah Lyles says he tested positive for the coronavirus before winning Olympic bronze in 200 meters</title>
      <description>After struggling in his signature event, he left the track breathing heavily while riding in a wheelchair. Lyles tested positive for the coronavirus two days ago, he told NBC, adding that he was leaning toward skipping the 4x100-meter relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a8a6090-55bc-11ef-aa1c-0000a1aced64</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Lyles, U.S. sprint star who was trying for second Paris gold, takes bronze in 200 meters. Teammate Kenny Bednarek won silver.</title>
      <description>Lyles previously won the 100-meter dash and will race for at least one more gold in Paris. He was trying to become the first man since Jamaican Usain Bolt to win the 100 and 200 in the same Games, and the first American man since Carl Lewis in 1984.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45832980-55b5-11ef-bc56-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you become an athlete at 70? Ask us how to feel like an Olympian at any age in our Well+Being chat.</title>
      <description>Can you become an athlete at 70? Ask us how to feel like an Olympian at any age in our Well+Being chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0efeac60-55a9-11ef-8a00-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debby will bring a threat of heavy rain, flooding and tornadoes. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>The remnants of the tropical storm will sweep across the Mid-Atlantic from Thursday night into Friday. In the D.C. area, it could produce 1.5 to 3 inches of rain and a few tornadoes. Mountains to the west will see more rain and a serious threat of flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f2168c0-55a5-11ef-b253-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Ukrainian attack in western Russia stuns Moscow and raises questions about Kyiv’s use of U.S.-donated weapons</title>
      <description>A cross-border assault by Ukrainian forces into the Kursk region that began Tuesday raised questions about whether Kyiv’s forces violated Western restrictions on the use of fighting vehicles and weapons donated by the United States and other countries. The operation, which Ukrainian officials have declined to comment on, is the largest Ukrainian incursion on Russian territory since 2022. It could mark a new chapter in the war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5e2d070-55a0-11ef-ac72-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to get over the hurt of a mom who never wants to get in touch?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to get over the hurt of a mom who never wants to get in touch?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74257e71-559f-11ef-94bb-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has been complaining about his campaign to friends and advisers as Harris’s poll numbers surge</title>
      <description>The GOP nominee has grown increasingly upset about Kamala Harris’s crowd sizes and media coverage since she replaced Joe Biden on the Democratic ticket. The situation has left people close to the campaign wondering why Donald Trump and his team seemed ill-prepared for Harris’s entry into the race after Biden’s disastrous June debate performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e17b401-5597-11ef-bcd0-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A boxer’s home country is your answer to today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88a46e21-558a-11ef-a9be-0000a1ace24f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump complaints. Harris protest. Taylor Swift. Covid surge. Toxic water. Stuck astronauts. Team USA. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">552cd1f0-5575-11ef-bab1-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz’s Army record faces scrutiny as GOP critics, fellow veterans question claims about his service</title>
      <description>The Harris-Walz campaign has cited the vice-presidential candidate's 24 years of military experience as an asset. But Republicans and some who served with the Minnesota governor have decried his decision to retire before their National Guard unit went to war and his characterization of aspects of his time in uniform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3f46b0-5520-11ef-bb09-000a1ace847c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Pelosi says she joined the effort to urge Biden to end reelection bid because his campaign had ‘no path to victory’</title>
      <description>In her most extensive remarks yet about the the political earthquake of the past few weeks, the former House speaker said she was concerned President Joe Biden staying in the race would inevitably lead to the reelection of Donald Trump. Pelosi, who carries tremendous clout on Capitol Hill and in the Democratic Party, also said that while she did not make any phone calls seeking Biden’s ouster, “hundreds” of people who wanted to see that outcome called her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7356eca1-5517-11ef-b860-0000a1ace404</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 highlights from Paris Olympics: Noah Lyles advances to 200-meter final; U.S. women's basketball cruises to win</title>
      <description>Lyles, the world's fastest human, qualified for the final of the men's 200 meters set for Thursday. American Quincy Hall came from behind to capture gold in the stirring men's 400-meter final. In other events, the U.S. women's basketball team easily handled Nigeria in a quarterfinal. And the United States ended a 20-year medal drought with silver in artistic swimming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80bb6260-550b-11ef-b8b1-0000a1ace979</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 22:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump took a private flight with Project 2025’s leader in 2022. He recently claimed he had ‘no idea who is in charge of it.’</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump shared a 45-minute chartered flight with Heritage Foundation president Kevin Roberts in April 2022, according to people familiar with the trip, plane-tracking data and a photograph from the plane. Trump was traveling to speak at a Heritage Foundation conference, where he said, “They’re going to lay the groundwork and detail plans for exactly what our movement will do.”

The flight and Trump’s comments from the time undercut the former president’s recent efforts to distance himself from Project 2025 once Democrats turned some of its most controversial proposals into a frequent campaign attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fbda1c0-5508-11ef-b8b1-0000a1ace979</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 21:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift cancels three shows in Vienna after authorities arrest two people suspected of plotting terror attack</title>
      <description>Authorities identified one suspect as a 19-year-old who allegedly pledged allegiance to the Islamic State. Swift’s concerts were expected to draw more than 150,000 people across three nights.

The arrests come amid a string of similar terror threats targeting major events in Europe this summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b147f2c1-5503-11ef-ab66-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it weird to choose Tim Walz? 3 columnists discuss whether he's really a unity candidate.</title>
      <description>Is it weird to choose Tim Walz?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7d63940-54fb-11ef-a2fa-0000a1ace6b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 20:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Quincy Hall wins Olympic gold in men’s 400 meters as U.S. track dominance continues</title>
      <description>It’s the sixth gold medal for the U.S. track and field team. Hall is expected to race for another medal Saturday in the 4x400 relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">329c1290-54f3-11ef-9c45-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 19:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris asked ‘probing questions’ about the Afghanistan exit. But military officials say she didn’t push Biden for a different plan.</title>
      <description>As vice president, Kamala Harris was the “last person in the room” as President Joe Biden decided to pull all U.S. troops from Afghanistan, ending a 20-year war. But military officials involved in those discussions say she didn’t significantly affect Biden’s determination to leave — or alter plans that led to a chaotic and deadly evacuation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f886a350-54e2-11ef-af9f-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 17:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Can a Midwestern hot dish be healthy? Our food writer answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Can a Midwestern hot dish be healthy? Our food writer answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11178d40-54d8-11ef-8d11-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:14:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Partner of six years comes with bothersome prior-life baggage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Partner of six years comes with bothersome prior-life baggage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35afe870-54d6-11ef-a1f6-000a1ace5438</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 16:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance’s private texts with a far-right figure show the VP nominee entertaining conspiracy theories and scorning a GOP megadonor</title>
      <description>Over 20 months, Sen. JD Vance (R-Ohio) texted regularly with Charles Johnson, a blogger and entrepreneur who has zealously promoted right-wing conspiracy theories. The messages, shared by Johnson with The Washington Post, offer a glimpse of the Republican vice-presidential nominee’s off-the-cuff musings on subjects including UFOs, Ukraine and the death of convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2f04600-54cb-11ef-8dc3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team gold was Simone Biles’s goal for the Olympics. ‘Anything else was a cherry on top,’ she tells The Post in an interview.</title>
      <description>Biles has dominated gymnastics for more than a decade, racking up one all-around title after another, often by wide margins. Watch her interview with The Washington Post as she reflects on her career, growth and influence on the sport.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">568964b1-54c5-11ef-8ec2-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A social studies pop quiz in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca7a2ac0-54c1-11ef-8d11-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 13:34:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz. JD Vance’s texts. Cori Bush. Hotel killing. Hamas leader. Team USA. Helpful sea lions. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3842e170-54ac-11ef-a1f6-000a1ace5438</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cori Bush, part of the ‘Squad’ of liberal House lawmakers, loses her Missouri primary, the AP projects</title>
      <description>Bush lost to St. Louis County prosecutor Wesley Bell (D), the Associated Press reported, in Missouri’s 1st Congressional District. Bush was the first member of Congress to call for a cease-fire between Israel and Hamas, while Bell, who was backed by a powerful pro-Israel lobbying group, says he would fully stand by Israel. Bush is the second member of the “Squad” to lose a House Democratic primary this cycle, after Rep. Jamaal Bowman (D-N.Y.) was also targeted for his stance on Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a86efd01-5469-11ef-b609-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 03:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Harris’s whirlwind, high-pressure VP vetting process: Who rose to the top and what ultimately sold her on Walz</title>
      <description>Kamala Harris interviewed three final candidates on Sunday. Her team had reservations about one of them, then another expressed doubts about leaving his current job. That paved the way for Tuesday’s announcement of Tim Walz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce119e40-5451-11ef-b9b9-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 11 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. men's basketball rolls and a Cuban wrestler makes history</title>
      <description>Devin Booker led the U.S. men's basketball team to a blowout of Brazil, setting up a semifinal against Nikola Jokic and Serbia. Elsewhere, Gabby Thomas and Cole Hocker won track gold, the U.S. women's soccer team topped Germany in a tense semifinal, and Cuban wrestler Mijaín López made history with a gold medal in his fifth straight Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">652a4b20-5442-11ef-91d1-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris makes first appearance with running mate Gov. Tim Walz at Pa. rally before multistate tour. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Walz is expected to share his and Harris’s biographies of longtime public service, according to shared excerpts of his speech. And he will distinguish their ticket from Donald Trump, whom he will portray as selfish.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94b04eb0-543f-11ef-8f35-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 22:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz made ‘weird’ happen, Karen Tumulty writes. He offers the ticket much more than that.</title>
      <description>Walz has a genuine feel for the concerns of people in conservative corners of the country, Tumulty writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb63a20-543a-11ef-984a-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 21:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: With Walz, Harris aims for broad appeal over swing-state potential, and 4 other takeaways from her VP pick</title>
      <description>Minnesota Gov. Tim Walz won out with his “weird” audition and brings a folksiness to the ticket with his recent left-leaning record. Here are takeaways from his selection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b88a190-5433-11ef-aac7-000a1ace8d94</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 20:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American runner Gabby Thomas cruises to Olympic gold in women’s 200 meters</title>
      <description>Three years after taking bronze at the Tokyo Games, Thomas left no doubt that gold was on her mind in Paris. She thumped the field in the women's 200 meters, posting a time of 21.83 seconds, a full 0.25 seconds ahead of silver medalist Julien Alfred. Fellow American Brittany Brown won bronze with a time of 22.20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83f5cbc0-542d-11ef-8e01-0000a1aceb3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:53:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. runner Cole Hocker wins gold in thrilling men’s 1,500-meter race</title>
      <description>One of the most anticipated races of the Olympic track and field meet yielded one of the most stunning champions. Hocker, a long-haired Indiana native by way of the University of Oregon, broke an Olympic record in the men's 1,500 meters, spoiled the heated rivalry between Jakob Ingebrigtsen and Josh Kerr and ran into American track history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03072680-5428-11ef-9766-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 19:13:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Bangladeshi officials meet student demand to name Nobel laureate Muhammad Yunus as transitional leader</title>
      <description>The announcement came after a six-hour meeting between the president, security chiefs and leaders of a student movement that forced Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina from office earlier this week. The appointment of Yunus, who was a pioneer of microfinance and a critic of the former government, would be an initial step to restoring order after mass protests, which left 400 people dead in the past month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edc744b1-5424-11ef-bd22-0000a1ace06d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s soccer team beats Germany, 1-0, in extra time, setting up gold medal matchup with Brazil-Spain winner</title>
      <description>With a new coach and revamped roster, the U.S. women remain undefeated in the Olympic tournament after an extra-time goal by Sophia Smith delivered the narrow win. The United States will face the winner of Tuesday’s Brazil-Spain matchup in the gold medal game on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6e66b30-5422-11ef-8ee0-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 18:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
