<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:29:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A CIA informant and elite Army commandos with blowtorches: Audacious Maduro raid relied on months of preparation</title>
      <description>Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were taken by helicopter to the USS Iwo Jima, an amphibious assault ship positioned off Venezuela and from there were flown to New York, where they will face criminal charges of drug-trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dc63501-e909-11f0-a7d2-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump goes monster-hunting, untainted by a whiff of legality, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>"That Nicolás Maduro is a monster is patent, as was the illegitimacy of his government, which disdained respect for the consent of the governed. But the urgent argument begins, not ends, with those two facts."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c2e06a0-e8fa-11f0-9e38-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife arrive in New York hours after U.S. capture in Venezuela</title>
      <description>Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, arrived in New York on Saturday afternoon following a U.S. raid that captured the couple earlier in the day. A U.S. government plane flew the couple into Stewart International Airport north of New York City, where they face federal charges of illegally enriching themselves as they conspired to flood the United States with cocaine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8b4d7f0-e8f2-11f0-989d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says U.S. will ‘run’ Venezuela during transition after U.S. raid captured Maduro</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Saturday at his Mar-a-Lago club that the United States will control Venezuela for an unspecified period after a U.S. operation captured Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro and his wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">089020b0-e8c5-11f0-bfb7-0000a1acebbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to speak following U.S. operation that captured Venezuela’s Maduro. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The United States launched a “large scale strike” on Venezuela, captured President Nicolás Maduro and his wife and flew them out of the country, President Donald Trump said in a social media post early Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfaeae80-e8bd-11f0-98cf-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s bold capture of Maduro was a victory for American interests, the Editorial Board writes. What’s next?</title>
      <description>The next challenge is setting the country up for long-term success.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0755da0-e8bb-11f0-beef-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Maduro being taken to New York by ship after his capture following Venezuela strikes</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said that the Maduros were placed on a ship, the USS Iwo Jima, to be taken to New York, and that they were removed from Venezuela by helicopter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88bd7e50-e8b5-11f0-ba75-000a1ace59b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de3fd9e0-e8b0-11f0-b860-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Maduro captured in ‘large scale strike’ against Venezuela</title>
      <description>The United States carried out a large-scale strike on Venezuela, capturing its president, Nicolás Maduro, and flying him out of the country, President Trump said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6cae80-e889-11f0-9d0d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions and aircraft heard over Venezuelan capital</title>
      <description>Explosions were heard and smoke could be seen rising in multiple locations across Caracas in the early morning Saturday, as aircraft were seen flying over the Venezuelan capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73314fe0-e873-11f0-9c87-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 07:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quest for a drug that lowers an artery-clogging particle nears finish line</title>
      <description>A clinical trial will soon reveal whether lowering high levels of lipoprotein(a) can reduce the risk of heart attacks and strokes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2af948a0-e83b-11f0-a0be-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How student loans and financial aid are changing in 2026</title>
      <description>Here's a look ahead at the federal policies taking effect that will shape how students and families pay for college.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7404b3d0-e823-11f0-a3c6-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He exposed the myth of the South’s ‘Lost Cause.’ His death shook Richmond.</title>
      <description>William “Bill” Martin, 71, died Dec. 28, a day after being struck by a car near the Valentine local history museum where he had served as director more than 30 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10aba840-e7fe-11f0-b6dd-0000a1ace147</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 best things Trump did in 2025, according to Marc Thiessen</title>
      <description>The 20 best things Trump did in 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2653be0-e7fa-11f0-aa01-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss bar fire started by sparklers on champagne bottles, officials say</title>
      <description>The deadly blaze spread quickly after the sparklers came close to the ceiling of the bar in the early hours of New Year’s Day, according to Beatrice Pilloud, attorney general of the Swiss canton of Valais. Investigators have analyzed footage of the incident and spoken to the bar’s managers as well as survivors, Pilloud said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd0a2e60-e7ec-11f0-bd99-0000a1acef04</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Blurb: Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38c0be30-e7e8-11f0-9cf4-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a longevity expert eats in a day</title>
      <description>Cardiologist Eric Topol has studied “super agers” for years. This is exactly what he eats — and avoids.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeeb2400-e7e5-11f0-aea4-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire investigation. Zohran Mamdani. Trump’s jobs claim. Sinking dams. Heart risk. ‘Super agers.’ Vacation time. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87171270-e7d2-11f0-8d3e-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu cases are rising with a strain that makes older people sicker</title>
      <description>Influenza season is ramping up in the U.S., marked by a new strain that could make vaccines less effective. Covid cases remain down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf4b220-e76d-11f0-98e9-0000a1ace702</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 things to declutter right now to start the year lighter</title>
      <description>Parting with your things can be hard. Picking some easy(ish) decluttering projects is a great way to build momentum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a5d041-e751-11f0-a113-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 40 killed, 115 injured in New Year’s bar fire at Swiss ski resort</title>
      <description>The fire struck the Constellation bar in Crans-Montana, in the heart of the Swiss Alps, around 1:30 a.m., as New Year’s celebrations were underway. Officials ruled out the possibility of an attack and are investigating the cause of the blaze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98087a90-e739-11f0-930d-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you eating for a longer life? Take our science-backed quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>If you want to know if you’re on the right track, answer the following simple questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67e296e0-e723-11f0-81ce-000a1ace6325</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year! Play On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your first points of 2026.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a25aa510-e71e-11f0-99d1-0000a1ace448</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss bar fire. National Guard. Child care. Trump’s ballroom. Flu cases. Pollution-fighting bacteria. Food quiz. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eda1d81-e709-11f0-99d1-0000a1ace448</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several dozen people killed, at least 100 injured in fire at Swiss bar</title>
      <description>The blaze at Le Constellation in Crans-Montana, in the heart of the Swiss Alps, occurred during a New Year’s celebration, police said. Beatrice Pilloud, attorney general of the Valais canton, ruled out any kind of attack and said the area would be closed amid the investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc943161-e6f7-11f0-8870-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ends effort to bring National Guard to Chicago, Los Angeles and Portland</title>
      <description>Troops already had a limited presence in those cities because states had sued to block their deployment. The president said on social media that troops would return if “crime begins to soar again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68c99690-e696-11f0-bd74-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 22:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s in and what’s out for 2026</title>
      <description>Some items on the List may be indecipherable to readers; others, outright objectionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58a97450-e683-11f0-adc9-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 20:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I support Donald Trump. But here are the 10 worst things he did in 2025.</title>
      <description>The president had a remarkable first year back in office, but he made some serious missteps, too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5278f1c0-e677-11f0-9f37-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of D.C. golf courses uncertain as Trump administration terminates lease</title>
      <description>The move clears a path for the president to put his imprint on one of the region’s most prominent public courses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">826c5d21-e674-11f0-9a59-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. vaccination rates are plunging. Look up where your school stands.</title>
      <description>The accelerating decline reveals the lasting medical consequences of a political backlash against public health efforts during the pandemic, which radicalized many against long-standing vaccine mandates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0348f010-e671-11f0-9e03-0000a1acef42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most-watched Carolyn Hax videos of 2025</title>
      <description>Advice columnist Carolyn Hax answers some of readers’ wildest questions on video.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5c9f290-e66b-11f0-837a-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 17:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy last day of 2025! Play On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your New Year’s Eve points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89c76050-e65c-11f0-9456-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center changed board rules months before vote to add Trump’s name</title>
      <description>The new bylaws limited voting to presidentially appointed trustees. The change preceded a unanimous decision this month by board members installed by President Donald Trump to add his name to the center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6124c00-e652-11f0-ad57-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 14:12:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE ads. East Wing photos. Kennedy Center. Vaccination rates. Tatiana Schlossberg. Women’s health. In and out list. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33253fe0-e640-11f0-852b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is overrated, our tech columnist writes. Here’s what to use instead.</title>
      <description>Geoffrey A. Fowler has been running a chatbot fight club for a year. Now he shares which AI tools win out — and which to avoid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">124397a0-e5e0-11f0-8410-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tatiana Schlossberg, environmental journalist and granddaughter of President John F. Kennedy, dies of cancer at 35</title>
      <description>Schlossberg announced her terminal cancer diagnosis in a New Yorker essay that took aim at her cousin, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., whom she called “an embarrassment.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">880d0a90-e5b6-11f0-82b2-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Russia’s war grinds on, its society is fraying</title>
      <description>The Kremlin presents the country as strong, united and on an inevitable path to victory. But as peace negotiations drag on and dissent is suppressed, fatigue and resentment are festering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78f7b6b0-e5a5-11f0-b4f0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Her family says don’t marry him — because they think he’s gay</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Her family says don’t marry him — because they think he’s gay</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59d14e31-e5a1-11f0-b4f0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What huge, beautiful things does 2026 have in store? Take David Ignatius’s quiz.</title>
      <description>It’s New Year’s, and another calm, uneventful year surely awaits us all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d643a50-e592-11f0-a31c-0000a1ace772</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security ends year in turmoil as record backlogs delay services</title>
      <description>Customer service deteriorated by key measures as the agency enacted sweeping cuts in President Donald Trump’s second term, internal data and interviews show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2151c890-e58e-11f0-82b2-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much do you remember about 2025? Play today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1defead0-e58c-11f0-8dd8-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security seeks emergency demolition of historic buildings in D.C.</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security is seeking to fast-track the demolition of more than a dozen historic buildings at St. Elizabeths in Southeast Washington, asserting that the conditions of the vacant structures represent an “emergency” and pose potential security risks, according to documents obtained by The Washington Post. Preservationists contend no evidence of an emergency exists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a47d960-e583-11f0-8149-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela strike. Trump and Netanyahu. Kennedy Center. Social Security. Ice storm. Wine risks. AI fight club. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09c7bfc1-e577-11f0-80aa-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duty? Insanity? These former members of Congress want to come back.</title>
      <description>By The Washington Post’s latest tally, at least 18 former members — 11 Democrats and seven Republicans — are asking voters to send them back to D.C. next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28fb8011-e50a-11f0-b169-000a1ace89f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 23:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who benefits from the new H-1B system? Use this interactive to find out.</title>
      <description>Congress mandates that only 85,000 new skilled worker visas — known as the H-1B visa — can be issued every year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">254425c0-e4fc-11f0-9a61-0000a1ace0f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother is broke, expectant and planning the ‘tackiest’ wedding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother is broke, expectant and planning the ‘tackiest’ wedding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6789d342-e4d8-11f0-af07-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The epidemic of toxic flattery is spreading</title>
      <description>What do AI, Trump’s cabinet and the academy have in common? They aim to please.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d483150-e4d0-11f0-b2db-000a1acef642</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your On the Record year in review starts now!</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa0a4200-e4c3-11f0-96d7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vance stepped in to broker a reconciliation when Trump and Musk were bickering</title>
      <description>The months-long offensive by JD Vance and other White House officials, the details of which have not been previously reported, worked. But the peace offers a glimpse into the next phase of the singular political partnership — one that carries both risk and reward for all involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb19f20-e4be-11f0-a058-0000a1acec53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Netanyahu meeting. Trump and Musk. Pipe bomb suspect. Screen time. Cellular aging. Nudge word. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe13980-e4ad-11f0-aabf-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
