<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 01:29:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Federal prosecutor in Virginia resigns after pushback from Trump over decision not to charge political foes</title>
      <description>Erik S. Siebert, the Trump-appointed U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Virginia, had determined there was insufficient evidence to indict New York Attorney General Letitia James for alleged mortgage fraud. He also recently declined to prosecute former FBI director James Comey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff6fbf40-95b8-11f0-ba43-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump adds $100,000 fee to H-1B visas for skilled foreign workers and rolls out $1 million gold-card visas</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s visa overhaul is expected to constrain a program for highly skilled workers that is widely used in Silicon Valley while opening up immigration access to wealthy foreigners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e95d780-95ad-11f0-8db2-0000a1ace210</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.-appointed CDC panel ends broad endorsement of covid vaccines, voting to recommend medical consultations</title>
      <description>The federal vaccine advisory panel voted Friday to recommend that Americans get coronavirus vaccines only in consultation with their clinicians. The recommendation now goes to the acting Centers for Disease Control and Prevention director for final approval. It may create confusion, former health officials and public health experts warn, because of practical barriers to implementing the new guidance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b889c50-959f-11f0-9d83-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and China’s Xi bless long-awaited deal to create a U.S. version of TikTok</title>
      <description>An American version of the popular app will be partly owned by a consortium of investors allied with President Donald Trump, people familiar with the deal said, sidestepping a legally mandated ban the president has repeatedly pushed off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ca74760-9580-11f0-8a0f-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when you purge the military lawyers</title>
      <description>Why has the military been so silent as the Trump administration has pushed the bounds of law by deploying troops to aid immigration enforcement actions at home and attacking alleged Venezuelan drug-smuggling boats abroad?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5379bb0-957a-11f0-9aa7-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m still sad over our breakup, and he has a new girlfriend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m still sad over our breakup, and he has a new girlfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95d53470-9577-11f0-8500-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge strikes down Trump’s $15 billion libel lawsuit against the New York Times</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Tampa, Florida, struck down President Donald Trump’s lawsuit, saying the 85-page complaint was “decidedly improper and impermissible.” A new complaint may be filed within 28 days but must be under 40 pages in length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a80fb40-9575-11f0-8071-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel killed 31 journalists in strike on Yemen newspaper complex, press freedom group says</title>
      <description>Last week’s attack was “the deadliest strike on journalists in the Middle East” ever documented by the Committee to Protect Journalists. The Israeli military said it targeted a public relations headquarters of Yemen’s Houthi rebels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cbe21a0-956f-11f0-ae8b-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 15:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill to avert government shutdown, but it’s expected to stall in Senate</title>
      <description>Government funding will expire Sept. 30. Lawmakers aren’t scheduled to be back in Washington until the week of the deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b7f12b0-9567-11f0-9ba2-0000a1ace814</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 14:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0e5fea0-955c-11f0-8500-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans critical of Trump on crime, economy and other issues, Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Ipsos poll paints a downbeat picture of Donald Trump’s presidency eight months into his second term. Despite a slight uptick in his overall approval rating compared with April, Americans disapprove of his performance on a broad range of issues — crime, the economy, immigration, foreign wars — and all by double-digit margins. Republicans hold advantages over Democrats on trust to handle crime, the economy and immigration, though a majority of Americans still say they want Democrats to control the next Congress “as a check on Trump.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4f64c60-9559-11f0-8960-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA’s push for Mexico strikes faced resistance at White House and Pentagon after some warned Congress had not authorized such action</title>
      <description>In the opening weeks of President Donald Trump’s second term, Drug Enforcement Administration officials suggested targeting cartel leadership and conducting attacks on infrastructure in Mexico, unnerving some U.S. officials who argued that such strikes had no basis in law, said people familiar with the deliberations. The suggestion was not acted upon, though Trump has repeatedly expressed a desire to use military force to halt narcotics flowing over the southern border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">453726d1-9550-11f0-a50e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s TV threat. Vaccine delay. Democrats arrested. Israel support. Wildfire smoke. Wegovy pills. OpenAI video. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9d71ca1-9547-11f0-8a00-0000a1ace890</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas A&amp;M president resigns in wake of instructor’s firing over gender teachings</title>
      <description>President Mark A. Welsh III, a retired four-star general who later served as a member of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, is stepping down. The resignation comes a little over a week after a viral video of a student accusing an instructor of illegally teaching “gender ideology” led to the instructor’s firing, the removal of a dean and department head, as well as calls for investigations — including by the Justice Department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d6c1780-9504-11f0-bbff-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC panel votes to roll back a childhood vaccine recommendation, marking first edit to routine immunization schedule under RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>The panel recommended skipping a combined measles, mumps and rubella and chicken pox vaccine — given to about 15 percent of children — until a child is 4. The recommendation goes to the acting head of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, who will decide whether to make it the official government recommendation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09420a70-94e5-11f0-b902-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 23:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The irony of Jimmy Kimmel’s ouster</title>
      <description>The irony of Jimmy Kimmel’s ouster</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cf48200-94d4-11f0-abb2-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE is seeking hundreds of new office spaces nationwide as it prepares to hire more than 10,000 additional staffers</title>
      <description>Immigration and Customs Enforcement is looking for 300 new locations to house lawyers and officers, according to federal officials familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1f63520-94cb-11f0-8a24-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:11:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks Supreme Court to allow it to fire Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook</title>
      <description>If the court decides to hear the case, it would set up a high-stakes test of President Donald Trump’s quest for greater control of the central bank and its unparalleled role in steering the U.S. economy. The Trump administration tried unsuccessfully to remove Cook ahead of a key meeting on interest rates this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">706a0be0-94a8-11f0-b4dc-000a1acec2fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.-appointed vaccine panel announces it will revisit immunizations given in pregnancy</title>
      <description>The chair of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention committee announced the formation of work groups to scrutinize the recommended vaccines during pregnancy and childhood. The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, which Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. purged and reformulated with his own picks, has drawn intense criticism for challenging long-standing policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">033fe880-94a5-11f0-a0a0-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving the ice cream behind in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e8b69c0-9494-11f0-9f9c-0000a1acefd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Latest late-night shakeup confirms that media companies must punish Trump critics if they want deals approved, our columnist writes</title>
      <description>ABC said it was pulling “Jimmy Kimmel Live!” off the air, following a similar announcement from Nexstar, the largest owner of television stations in the United States. The move was ostensibly in response to a remark Kimmel made Monday night, which Nexstar and Sinclair, its biggest competitor, have characterized as so beyond the pale that the late-night comic’s show could not be permitted to air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22be10f0-9488-11f0-b67d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Kimmel. Police killed. Fed rate cut. Gaza City. CDC hearing. Free child care. AI cheating. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fe2dac0-947e-11f0-9b79-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 police officers killed, 2 wounded in a shooting in southern Pennsylvania</title>
      <description>Police responding to a domestic investigation in York County shot and killed the suspect, whom authorities did not identify. Authorities did not give a motive for the shooting, which Gov. Josh Shapiro described as “absolutely tragic” at a news conference Wednesday evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39a435e1-9421-11f0-b176-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ABC takes Jimmy Kimmel off the air after backlash over remarks on Charlie Kirk’s death</title>
      <description>A network spokesperson did not comment beyond saying that the show will be preempted “indefinitely.” The biggest owner of ABC affiliated stations, Nexstar, said earlier Wednesday that Kimmel’s program would be replaced starting tonight, linking the move to statements the late-night show host made about last week’s killing of  Kirk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91831480-941b-11f0-9618-0000a1aced94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 23:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department to partner with conservative groups to create patriotic civics programs for America's 250th anniversary</title>
      <description>Dozens of conservative groups, including Turning Point USA, founded by Charlie Kirk, will work with the Trump administration to create civics programming that will promote patriotism ahead of America's 250th anniversary. It is unusual for a civics initiative to not include liberals, experts said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cbc2fe1-9416-11f0-b176-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$3.7 billion deal to build new Washington Commanders stadium and redevelop old RFK site gets final approval from D.C. Council</title>
      <description>The project, a decade in the works, will transform a largely vacant and blighted 180-acre swath of the city into a full neighborhood with not only a sports venue but also entertainment, retail, housing and riverside park space, and return the now-Maryland-based NFL team to the site where it had played until 1996.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c97f0680-9413-11f0-b01f-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 22:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five key takeaways from the fired CDC director’s testimony, including talk of changes to the childhood vaccine schedule</title>
      <description>Susan Monarez told senators Wednesday that Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. pressured her to support changes to the schedule, subverting the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s scientific expertise and endangering public health. Here are other major moments from the hearing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e87fb600-9400-11f0-9ff6-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 20:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed trims interest rates by a quarter percentage point in first cut this year and signals more cuts to come as economy cools</title>
      <description>The Federal Reserve’s rate cut is far short of the cuts that President Donald Trump has pushed for. Policymakers at the central bank are under scrutiny for signs of White House influence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93c794d1-93f0-11f0-8583-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband with past TBIs says his recent erratic behavior is ‘fine’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband with past TBIs says his recent erratic behavior is ‘fine’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85852150-93df-11f0-8d50-0000a1aced97</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email from top RFK Jr. aide reveals political pressure on CDC director before her firing. Follow coverage of her Senate testimony.</title>
      <description>In an Aug. 19 email to Susan Monarez, who has since been fired from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, a top aide to Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. wrote: “I wanted to elevate the absolute need for political review of major policy decisions at CDC.” Monarez is set to make her first public appearance since her ouster; follow our live updates on the Senate health committee hearing, scheduled for 10 a.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da57ab50-93ce-11f0-aff3-0000a1ace27f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting on the kettle in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a06de980-93ca-11f0-9f8d-0000a1acef69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel. Genocide finding. Shutdown fight. Luigi Mangione. Organ transplants. Robert Redford. Moon mining. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697e64a0-93b5-11f0-9a8e-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA failed to act on warnings that too many planes were being squeezed into DCA before deadly crash</title>
      <description>The crescendo of arriving and departing planes at Reagan National Airport near D.C. during the busiest periods reduced the margin of error for air traffic controllers and pilots to dangerous levels before the Jan. 29 collision, according to a review of investigative records, Federal Aviation Administration documents and testimony gathered by the National Transportation Safety Board.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">326ccc40-93b5-11f0-979b-0000a1ace711</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting suspect allegedly said Charlie Kirk was propagating hate, and other takeaways from the charging documents</title>
      <description>Tyler Robinson’s parents thought images of the suspect resembled their son, and Robinson texted his roommate shortly after the attack admitting that he did it, court documents allege.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd87d8e0-935b-11f0-bec4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:18:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House releases more documents from Epstein’s estate and an interview with former attorney general Barr about the investigation</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee released an address book and unredacted birthday greeting it received from Jeffrey Epstein’s estate, responses to its subpoenas, and a transcript of the committee’s interview with William P. Barr about the federal investigation into Epstein’s crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a699d210-932f-11f0-af3c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah prosecutor will seek death penalty for suspect in Charlie Kirk shooting. Follow our coverage as officials take questions.</title>
      <description>Tyler Robinson, 22, will make his first virtual court appearance later Tuesday. He faces seven charges in connection with the conservative activist’s fatal shooting last week, including aggravated murder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c330b0-932a-11f0-ada8-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 18:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These editor’s notes are poison. David Ignatius learned from every drop.</title>
      <description>Working with Starling Lawrence, who died last month, was a bracing course in a vanishing art.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35029c20-9322-11f0-b3ac-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Daughter-in-law ‘barely tolerates’ her. Can she ever win her over?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Daughter-in-law ‘barely tolerates’ her. Can she ever win her over?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54d98330-9316-11f0-a064-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE’s own inspectors say its giant Texas facility at Ft. Bliss has violated dozens of immigrant detention standards</title>
      <description>Locked up in the unfinished facility, migrants were subjected to conditions that violated at least 60 federal standards, the oversight unit of U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement found earlier this month in a contractually required inspection. The report raises significant concerns about the safety of workers and detainees at one of the Trump administration’s marquee immigration projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02860f80-9312-11f0-92b8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge dismisses terrorism charges against Luigi Mangione in UnitedHealthcare CEO’s killing</title>
      <description>New York Supreme Court Justice Gregory Carro said the evidence presented to the grand jury does not support charges of murder in the first and second degrees under the state’s terrorism statute. Mangione will still face a trial on murder in the second degree and other related counts. Mangione also faces federal charges related to Brian Thompson’s Dec. 4 killing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adaf8220-9307-11f0-ace5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test your Emmys knowledge in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7374f320-9301-11f0-98a6-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Redford dies at 89. One of the biggest movie stars of all time, he became the patron saint of independent American film.</title>
      <description>Robert Redford’s good looks and subtle magnetism in films such as “Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid” and “All the President’s Men” won him a massive following. Yet he forged an even more profound legacy as president and founder of the Sundance Institute, providing a vital platform for outside-the-system filmmakers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3fb13f0-92f7-11f0-859c-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk suspect. Gaza City. Trump lawsuit. Paper checks. National parks. Daylight saving time. Lego record. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c571d00-92ec-11f0-bbab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military begins ground offensive of Gaza City, official says</title>
      <description>The Israeli military launched the early stages of the offensive to seize Gaza City overnight, an Israeli military official said. Palestinians in the beleaguered enclave said they faced hours of relentless heavy bombardment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7627d50-92db-11f0-b3ac-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 09:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court allows Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook to keep her job</title>
      <description>Ahead of the central bank’s key meeting setting interest rates, a divided three-judge panel of the U.S. District Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit declined to overturn a preliminary injunction by a federal judge who ruled President Donald Trump could not fire Cook. The ruling is expected to be quickly appealed to the Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8147b221-9294-11f0-8827-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms White House economic adviser Stephen Miran to the Federal Reserve ahead of interest rate meeting</title>
      <description>Miran said he would take a leave but not resign from his post as chair of the White House Council of Economic Advisers, becoming the first White House official to simultaneously serve on the board of the central bank in 90 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1deafd41-9294-11f0-8e04-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eleanor Holmes Norton should not run for reelection, Donna Brazile writes</title>
      <description>She has been like a second mother to me. But she is 88. D.C. needs a new champion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c9644c0-927d-11f0-b900-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:46:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials order removal of exhibits related to slavery at multiple national parks, including photo of enslaved man’s scars</title>
      <description>The President’s House Site at Independence Hall in Philadelphia and Harpers Ferry National Historic Park in West Virginia are among the locations that could be impacted. The removal orders come in response to President Donald Trump’s March executive order directing the Interior Department to eliminate information that reflects a “corrosive ideology” that disparages historic Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c275bf00-9279-11f0-b522-000a1acec37d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 21:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. forces kill three alleged drug smugglers from Venezuela in latest military strike, Trump says</title>
      <description>The operation, which President Donald Trump said occurred in international waters, marks the second time this month that the U.S. military has unleashed deadly force in the region. The president claimed those targeted on Monday were carrying illegal drugs bound for the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25a8be11-9275-11f0-8c4f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance, hosting ‘The Charlie Kirk Show,’ says prominent liberal foundations contribute to political violence</title>
      <description>The vice president accused the Ford Foundation and George Soros’s Open Society Foundations of providing grants to the Nation magazine, which published an article that, he said, sought to justify Kirk’s killing. A White House official said the administration has been considering trying to strip groups of their tax-exempt status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5cfd920-9270-11f0-967e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
