<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 11:02:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘acoustic terror’ of Russia’s blasts makes people wonder if they are dead. Hear it for yourself.</title>
      <description>This summer, there were no quiet nights for Ukraine. Russian attacks have increased more than fivefold since January, deafening people with sirens, drones and ballistic missiles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0908bb20-8d07-11f0-9552-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch family resolves dispute over ownership of media empire in billion-dollar deal</title>
      <description>Lachlan Murdoch, whose politics are in line with those of his 94-year-old father, will remain in control after Rupert Murdoch’s death, with three other siblings splitting a $3.3 billion settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72682aa0-8cf9-11f0-855e-0000a1ace46b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House launches stepped up immigration enforcement operation in Chicago as Trump vows a broader crackdown on violent crime</title>
      <description>Authorities said “Operation Midway Blitz” is part of Trump’s efforts to target “sanctuary cities” that limit cooperation with the federal government. Democrats denounced the action as immigrant advocates said several people in heavily Hispanic communities had already been detained Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b9d34d0-8cf7-11f0-8688-0000a1acef13</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress receives documents it subpoenaed from Jeffrey Epstein’s estate, including book allegedly made for his 50th birthday</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee on Monday received documents from the estate of the sex offender as part of its broader probe into the federal sex-trafficking investigation of Epstein. Epstein’s jailed associate, Ghislaine Maxwell, allegedly gifted the book to him when he turned 50.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3e54840-8ce6-11f0-b43a-0000a1ace0d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth makes unannounced trip to Puerto Rico as Pentagon eyes island to assist drug cartel crackdown</title>
      <description>The Pentagon is weighing plans to make Puerto Rico a part of its operations in Latin America, possibly conducting military flights out of the island territory, said two U.S. officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The effort includes the possible deployment of fighter jets to the island, one of the officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f60abd60-8cdf-11f0-b7e4-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French Parliament votes to oust prime minister, deepening Macron’s woes as government collapses for second time in under a year</title>
      <description>The French National Assembly voted “no confidence” in Prime Minister François Bayrou, which will force his resignation. The decision exacerbates the political problems of President Emmanuel Macron, who lost his parliamentary majority after calling snap elections in June 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ca7a660-8cd7-11f0-b681-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After her scary hospital detox, planning the next step with Mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After her scary hospital detox, planning the next step with Mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93c7a1c0-8cd2-11f0-9552-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says Trump can resume immigration raids in L.A. area for now, overturning a ruling that found race-based targeting</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court overturned a lower-court ruling that curtailed Los Angeles-area detentions after finding federal agents were indiscriminately targeting people based on race and other factors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad92f8c0-8ccd-11f0-82f1-0000a1ace121</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can fire a Democratic FTC commissioner while lawsuit proceeds, Supreme Court chief justice rules</title>
      <description>Supreme Court Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr.’s ruling comes after an appeals court found last week that Commissioner Rebecca Slaughter could be reinstated to her job because President Donald Trump had fired her “without cause.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2a81a80-8cca-11f0-8846-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump loses his effort to appeal $83 million judgment in writer E. Jean Carroll’s defamation case against him</title>
      <description>A federal appeals court Monday upheld a jury’s $83.3 million judgment against President Donald Trump in a lawsuit brought by Carroll. She had accused Trump in 2019 of sexually assaulting her two decades earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee72e3a0-8cc8-11f0-a167-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta suppressed research on child safety, employees say. The company denies the allegations.</title>
      <description>Members of Congress have received a trove of internal company documents from four current and former employees who allege that Meta lawyers intervened to shape research that might have illuminated potential safety risks to children and teens on the company’s virtual reality devices and apps. A Senate Judiciary subcommittee is set to discuss the allegations, which Meta denies, at a hearing Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f7afee0-8cbc-11f0-8275-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 14:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s back! Get ready for this impending competition in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a94d970-8cb8-11f0-b766-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks Supreme Court to allow it to freeze billions in foreign aid</title>
      <description>The emergency request could set up a major test of the president’s assertion that he has the unilateral authority to block spending budgeted by Congress. The filing comes after a federal appeals court upheld a preliminary injunction requiring Trump officials to spend the money for food, medicine and development assistance before it begins to expire on Sept. 30, the end of the fiscal year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c397d3e0-8cb2-11f0-82f1-0000a1ace121</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. State spending cuts. RFK Jr. Russia-Ukraine war. Meta allegation. Carlos Alcaraz. Millennial saint. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f531af30-8ca2-11f0-b187-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shooting attack on a bus in Jerusalem kills at least five people</title>
      <description>Other people were injured after two attackers opened fire at a bus stop in north Jerusalem, according to Israel’s emergency services. The attackers were also killed at the scene, the Israeli police said. The Israeli military said troops had been deployed to “thwart terrorism and strengthen the defense effort.” Hamas praised the shooting and said it was “a natural response to the occupation’s crimes.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57519f50-8c98-11f0-ab8a-0000a1ace63d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 09:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Alcaraz of Spain wins U.S. Open, defeating Italy’s Jannik Sinner in third Grand Slam final between the rivals this year</title>
      <description>Alcaraz and Sinner became the first duo to face each other three times in a Grand Slam title match in a single season in the Open era. Alcaraz, who now has two U.S. Open championships and six total Grand Slams to his name, won this year’s French Open, while Sinner earned the Wimbledon title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f27ce450-8c32-11f0-9c95-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 21:38:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to get a complainer to stop, according to a therapist</title>
      <description>Complaining can foster camaraderie and establish common ground, but when it becomes excessive, it can annoy listeners and wreck relationships. Here are five ways to cope.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e487130-8c2c-11f0-af78-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 20:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riots and abuse troubled these former prisons. ICE plans to reopen them.</title>
      <description>The same private companies that closed facilities plan to reopen them to hold immigrants. Advocates say that puts detainees at risk of violence and mistreatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">828eba91-8c11-11f0-a4b1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 17:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd7e78c0-8c03-11f0-bf1e-0000a1acef8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 16:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California Gov. Gavin Newsom won’t stop mocking Trump online, seeking to position himself as de facto head of Democrats' resistance</title>
      <description>Influencers on both the left and the right have discussed Newsom online more than any other potential 2028 presidential contender since President Donald Trump’s inauguration, according to a Washington Post analysis. The attention has been driven by his response to immigration raids in Los Angeles, his efforts to counter a Republican redistricting push and, most recently, his mocking impersonations of Trump’s social media style.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06bf3570-8bf8-11f0-9187-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 14:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95403c0-8bee-11f0-b723-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea says it reached deal with U.S. to repatriate workers detained in Hyundai factory immigration raid</title>
      <description>The foreign workers were detained in Georgia on Thursday as part of the largest worksite enforcement operation to take place so far in President Donald Trump’s second term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">013d9080-8bec-11f0-8b46-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 13:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Prime Minister Shigeru Ishiba announces resignation after two crushing parliamentary defeats</title>
      <description>Ishiba’s move exacerbates an unusual period of political uncertainty in Japan, a major U.S. security ally in Asia, as the ruling party has lost its coalition majority in both legislative chambers after governing almost continuously since 1955.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8de16920-8bca-11f0-8d53-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 09:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aryna Sabalenka of Belarus wins second straight U.S. Open championship, defeating American Amanda Anisimova</title>
      <description>It is the fourth Grand Slam title for Sabalenka, the top-ranked player in the world. Anisimova, who also finished as the runner-up at Wimbledon this year, had been seeking her first Grand Slam championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b889f40-8b6d-11f0-8f5e-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point alumni group cancels award ceremony for Tom Hanks as Trump-era political controversies grip military academy</title>
      <description>Hanks, who starred in “Saving Private Ryan” and other films depicting U.S. service members and who has for decades advocated for veterans, was to receive a prestigious award from the West Point alumni association at an event this month. The decision to cancel the ceremony follows political moves that have rattled the military institution since President Donald Trump’s return to power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af0aa290-8b36-11f0-be68-0000a1acec58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davey Johnson dies at 82. The former Washington Nationals manager guided the New York Mets to the World Series title in 1986.</title>
      <description>Johnson led the Nationals from 2011 to 2013, including their breakthrough 2012 season, when they reached the postseason for the first time. He also starred as a player with the Baltimore Orioles, winning the World Series in 1966 and 1970.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7569ff11-8b2f-11f0-be41-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After life-altering brain surgery, a songwriter’s creativity flourished</title>
      <description>Removing a piece of his brain, Mike Frazier and his doctors thought, was his best option for combating a condition that affects about 1 percent of adults in the United States and tens of millions of people worldwide — but that is still often misunderstood and misdiagnosed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0880a351-8b2e-11f0-99d8-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60689490-8b26-11f0-b340-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 13:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 must-see films to watch this fall</title>
      <description>It’s the time of year when filmdom starts showing off a fresher, more original palette. These are our top picks, including a Bruce Springsteen biopic and Daniel Day-Lewis’s return to acting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3840fef0-8ab6-11f0-a1c2-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 00:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland leaders announce police surge in Baltimore amid Trump’s threats to deploy National Guard to city</title>
      <description>The state and city will deploy more resources to violence interruption groups and state prosecutors through a partnership that Gov. Wes Moore and Mayor Brandon Scott say has driven Baltimore’s homicide count to a 50-year low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a60b260-8aaf-11f0-9b2e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s rebranding of the Defense Department as the War Department is a worthy blow against euphemism, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>Perhaps the new name can be followed by clearer thinking about the military’s role at home and abroad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">972aa770-8aa4-11f0-a795-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts Trump officials from ending special status for Venezuelans and Haitians</title>
      <description>The decision from a federal judge in California could shield hundreds of thousands of people from possible deportation. DHS Secretary Kristi L. Noem had argued that conditions had improved enough in both countries for people to return, a finding that contradicted the State Department’s own travel warnings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cc266d1-8aa0-11f0-84d2-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI firm Anthropic agrees to pay landmark $1.5 billion settlement to book authors and publishers</title>
      <description>The company behind the chatbot Claude agreed to pay about $3,000 per book to avoid trial over claims it improperly downloaded millions of titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbe56410-8a8f-11f0-b2fd-0000a1ace475</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The uncomfortable truth about watching football</title>
      <description>The uncomfortable truth about watching football</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f444a90-8a8a-11f0-8634-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 500 workers, mostly South Koreans, arrested in immigration raid at Georgia Hyundai factory — largest of Trump’s new term</title>
      <description>Immigration officials alleged “serious federal crimes.” The Hyundai electric vehicle and battery production complex in Georgia has been hailed as “the largest project in state history.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74323910-8a84-11f0-b133-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two teens arrested in fatal D.C. shooting of college student who interned for GOP lawmaker, U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro says</title>
      <description>Two 17-year-olds have been charged as adults in D.C. Superior Court with first-degree murder while armed, Pirro said at a news conference Friday. A third suspect remains at large. Officials have said Eric Tarpinian-Jachym, who interned for Rep. Ron Estes (R-Kansas), was shot by a group of people who exited a car and opened fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17c991c0-8a78-11f0-9fb3-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Pushing partner to make amends for being an absent dad</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Pushing partner to make amends for being an absent dad</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">158de153-8a72-11f0-97e6-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our dining critic gave this popular D.C. restaurant zero stars in 2016. Has it improved?</title>
      <description>Tom Sietsema returns to Founding Farmers, one of Washington’s most popular restaurants, for a pulse check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca962ef0-8a67-11f0-972f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e8de8d0-8a5c-11f0-9487-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. economy picked up 22,000 jobs in August but in June revisions lost jobs for first time since pandemic</title>
      <description>The Bureau of Labor Statistics reported fewer jobs in downward revisions to June job creation, in a warning sign about President Donald Trump’s tougher tariffs and immigration enforcement. In August, the unemployment rate ticked up to 4.3 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2795b020-8a55-11f0-aa54-0000a1ace7c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. hearing. ‘War Department.’ Stephen Miller. Labor market. Gun rules. Jobs for robots. Leaf-peeping. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e881e0-8a47-11f0-8098-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlin Clark will miss remainder of the WNBA season with injury</title>
      <description>The Indiana Fever star's second season ends with her having appeared in just 13 games. Clark, who helped supercharge interest in the WNBA, has not played since July 15 as she has dealt with groin and ankle injuries. The Fever remains in playoff position but has been decimated by injuries and is not expected to contend for a title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82fad750-89f7-11f0-ac96-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress not planning a vote to extend Trump’s 30-day D.C. police takeover</title>
      <description>In allowing the Trump administration’s grip on D.C. police to come to an end, Congress closes one chapter in the tussle between local and federal officials vying for control of public safety in the capital. But for now, it appears unlikely that fewer federal agents or camouflage-clad troops will patrol city streets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e92f9d50-89f5-11f0-9a4f-0000a1aced0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The health risks from plastics almost nobody knows about</title>
      <description>Plastic chemicals, known as phthalates, are everywhere. The Washington Post reviewed more than 50 studies and interviewed more than two dozen scientists, former regulators and industry officials to document how the chemicals are eroding health in unexpected ways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cc50510-89e7-11f0-8674-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to change name of Defense Department to Department of War, a title the White House says more accurately reflects its mission</title>
      <description>The president is expected to sign an executive order Friday to make the change that "will sharpen the focus of this Department on our national interest and signal to adversaries America’s readiness to wage war to secure its interests," according to a document describing the forthcoming order obtained by The Washington Post. It's unclear if he can permanently change the name without legislation from Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3ab2f70-89e0-11f0-9673-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 22:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department issues subpoenas targeting Fed governor Lisa Cook in criminal probe, intensifying Trump’s efforts to oust her</title>
      <description>The White House has accused Cook of falsifying mortgage records to lenders as the Trump administration builds a legal and political case to remove her from the central bank’s board. A federal judge is considering Cook’s request to temporarily block President Donald Trump’s move and keep her on the board, which meets mid-September to consider interest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73429940-89d1-11f0-a812-0000a1ace45f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. clashed with a GOP senator over the availability of coronavirus vaccines, and other takeaways from his fiery hearing</title>
      <description>Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on Thursday defended his tenure in a roughly three-hour Senate hearing, following upheaval at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and frustration with his approach to vaccines. Here are the biggest takeaways from his testimony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">508d4500-89ca-11f0-9f26-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to end European security aid programs meant to thwart Russia, alarming allies and upsetting lawmakers</title>
      <description>The decision would impact hundreds of millions of dollars worth of military aid relied upon by some of NATO’s most vulnerable members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0225a7f0-89ba-11f0-b896-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon approves use of Chicago-area Navy base for ICE and possible military operations</title>
      <description>The Pentagon has approved the use of Naval Station Great Lakes, on the outskirts of Chicago, as a staging ground from which the Trump administration can launch operations against undocumented immigrants, said two defense officials familiar with the issue. If deployed, National Guard or active-duty service members could also be housed at the facility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">961c9080-89ac-11f0-9e29-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Drugged by a friend and spinning — in both senses</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Drugged by a friend and spinning — in both senses</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc75f20-89a8-11f0-9d52-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
