<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How one patient’s personal and political worlds collided at the doctor’s office</title>
      <description>My health and my politics walk into a doctor’s office …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">373bbe10-6260-11f0-8bd3-000a1acec913</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50fde5f0-625e-11f0-bea0-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘delicate subject’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8214f220-624d-11f0-b1ea-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. hits states with requests for voter rolls and election data, sparking concerns of interference ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>Election clerks in both parties, already facing harassment and lawsuits over President Donald Trump’s false 2020 election claims, worry about efforts to examine voting machines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4ef490-6245-11f0-ad01-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Voter data. Extreme rainfall. Confession letter. Obesity study. Emmy nominations. Sycamore Gap tree. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f954e70-6234-11f0-9e35-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelita Grijalva wins Democratic nomination for U.S. House in Arizona special election</title>
      <description>Grijalva won a contested primary in a safely Democratic district, defeating Gen Z content creator Deja Foxx and others. The contest underlined intraparty tensions over age, experience and dynastic politics. Grijalva will be a heavy favorite in the special election to succeed her father, liberal stalwart Raúl Grijalva, who represented the district until his death in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a2bcda0-61f4-11f0-bf2b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expelled D.C. Council member Trayon White Sr. (D) projected to win special election for his former Ward 8 seat</title>
      <description>White, who was expelled in February after his arrest and indictment on a federal bribery charge, will return to the council for a term that ends in January 2029. He has pleaded not guilty to the charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02736f50-61e5-11f0-b547-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 01:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth lashed out at a top DOGE official in tense Pentagon confrontation</title>
      <description>The episode in April, which has not been reported previously, was sparked by claims that a team leader with Elon Musk’s cost-cutting organization had summoned law enforcement to remove a subordinate from the Pentagon installation, people familiar with the matter said. Hegseth, these people said, deemed it an unacceptable overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcc2f90-61d7-11f0-bfba-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to automate the work of federal employees. Here are 6 agencies to watch.</title>
      <description>The Pentagon, IRS and other federal agencies are rapidly adopting AI tools to improve efficiency, an idea championed by Elon Musk that could replace some government workers with technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e7cf30-61d3-11f0-aa71-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William H. McRaven writes in an op-ed: Cuts to the State Department and USAID will put every American at risk</title>
      <description>Soft power for a tough world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012a44f0-61ce-11f0-a925-000a1ace3781</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Mike Johnson and other Republicans break with Trump administration on Epstein files as Democrats call for documents' release</title>
      <description>Johnson (R-Louisiana) called for the Justice Department to release any files related to convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein just days after the Trump administration effectively declared the matter closed. Johnson's interview was released moments after House GOP leaders barely defeated a Democratic effort to force a House vote to release the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86db6c60-61b4-11f0-ab7a-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3222240-6197-11f0-949b-000a1ace7963</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 16:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Severance,’ ‘The Penguin,’ ‘The White Lotus’ and ‘The Studio’ lead the Emmy nominations. See the list here.</title>
      <description>The annual awards show honoring the best in TV is set to take place Sept. 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90b43a71-6194-11f0-8f80-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 244 people Trump proposed for his $40 million hero garden, including a few surprises</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump first proposed the “National Garden of American Heroes” during the racial justice protests of 2020, when many Confederate monuments were being toppled. Now it has the funds to become a reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35291eb0-6184-11f0-bc47-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An interactive performance in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">118f0860-6180-11f0-ab82-0000a1aceb40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation heated up in June, as Trump’s tariffs began to pressure more sectors in the economy</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed that inflation picked up momentum in June, after months of progress bringing prices under control, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbdcb20-6177-11f0-8aa0-0000a1ace936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Putin. ICE’s bond order. Education cuts. Camp Mystic. Wildfire smoke. Elmo hacked. Solar eruptions. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db6e4530-616a-11f0-8d84-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE declares millions of undocumented immigrants no longer eligible for bond hearings</title>
      <description>A memo sent by ICE’s acting director and obtained by The Washington Post instructs officers to hold immigrants who entered the country illegally “for the duration of their removal proceedings,” which can take months or years. Lawyers say the policy will apply to millions of immigrants who crossed the U.S.-Mexico border over the past few decades, including under former president Joe Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27679210-6112-11f0-b2ca-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:25:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump administration to proceed with deep cuts at Education Department, for now</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a temporary lower-court ruling that prevented Trump officials from slashing more than a third of the department’s more than 4,100 workers and shifting some of its functions to the states and other departments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaf15170-60eb-11f0-9fb7-0000a1acef70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 19:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Distance from critical mom comes with guilt for not trying harder</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Distance from critical mom comes with guilt for not trying harder</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5b89000-60cb-11f0-8eae-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 16:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens new tariffs and sanctions on Russia and announces European countries will buy U.S. weapons to send to Ukraine</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte made the announcement Monday during a meeting at the White House. The move to increase support for Kyiv follows Trump’s frustration with Russian President Vladimir Putin’s continued bombardment of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc594b1-60c7-11f0-9d54-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 15:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quite the discovery in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1a792e0-60b6-11f0-81f7-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 13:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camp Mystic waited over an hour to evacuate after receiving ‘life threatening’ flood alert</title>
      <description>Interviews with nearly two dozen counselors, emergency officials, parents and experts reveal that as Camp Mystic Executive Director Dick Eastland conferred with family members and other employees about how to respond to the alert, the camp descended into chaos as the river rose to record levels.

Water was at least four feet high around many of the cabins, a Washington Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0675270-60af-11f0-b920-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 12:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA warning. ICE deportations. Israeli strike. Texas floods. Air quality. Jannik Sinner. Dinosaur bones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d43c20-60a1-11f0-a729-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Trump assassination attempt supercharged beliefs in a divine right of MAGA</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and many of his followers have described the rally shooting on July 13, 2024, as a mass spiritual awakening, promoting the belief that Trump enacts God’s will.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46cd0c00-603d-11f0-b582-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 23:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After franchise upheaval, Washington Nationals select infielder Eli Willits with the No. 1 pick in the MLB draft</title>
      <description>The selection of Willits, a 17-year-old high school shortstop from Oklahoma, came just one week after Washington fired its longtime general manager, Mike Rizzo. Mike DeBartolo has taken the helm as interim GM of the Nationals, who also fired manager Dave Martinez. The Nationals previously used No. 1 picks on Bryce Harper and Stephen Strasburg, setting a high bar for their choice this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1e829e0-6037-11f0-8c3f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 22:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A clinic blames its closing on Trump’s Medicaid cuts. Some patients don’t buy it.</title>
      <description>A clinic in rural Nebraska has become a political flash point after tying its pending closure to Trump’s law cutting Medicaid. Residents of Curtis — a one-stoplight town in deep-red farm country — are sorry to lose the clinic but skeptical of the rationale.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95a8b40-602f-11f0-8c59-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 21:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jannik Sinner wins first Wimbledon championship and fourth Grand Slam title, denying Carlos Alcaraz a third straight victory there</title>
      <description>It was the first appearance in the Wimbledon final for Sinner, the 23-year-old Italian who avenged his loss to Alcaraz at last month's French Open. He and Alcaraz, a 22-year-old from Spain, have combined to win the last seven men’s Grand Slam titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40694340-6017-11f0-9b1d-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 18:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service tells its gift shops to remove anything that ‘disparages Americans’</title>
      <description>Park staff were ordered to report any retail items containing content that “inappropriately disparages Americans past or living” or that includes “matters unrelated to the beauty, abundance or grandeur” of a natural feature in its description. The move is part of the administration’s wider campaign to scrub federal institutions of “corrosive ideology” recognizing historical racism and sexism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5658db0-600b-11f0-aa7e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 17:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae4899c0-6002-11f0-ac06-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 16:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six less-expensive beach vacations in the U.S., from Georgia to California</title>
      <description>Even if we’re not exploring the Mediterranean or living it up at an all-inclusive resort in Mexico, we still crave the beach — especially one relatively close to home that won’t eat up our vacation funds. We asked professional travel planners for help identifying these top budget picks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">588c0410-5ff6-11f0-aa9d-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 14:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95887a90-5fee-11f0-9140-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 13:37:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE memo outlines plan to deport migrants to countries where they are not citizens</title>
      <description>Federal immigration officers may deport immigrants with as little as six hours’ notice to countries other than their own even if officials have not provided any assurances that the new arrivals will be safe from persecution or torture, a top official said in a memo this week. The dramatic shift in policy could result in thousands of people being sent to places where they lack family ties or even a common language.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ab604d0-5f87-11f0-ad55-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He knows he was adopted from South Korea. When he started digging into his past, red flags emerged.</title>
      <description>For years, Aaron Grzegorczyk thought his birth mother had left him at a South Korean clinic in 1988. A recent report found the country had allowed a “profit-driven” adoption “industry” to flourish for decades, leaving Grzegorczyk wondering whether he’s yet another victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b873291-5f6f-11f0-9ed1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaire Marc Andreesen says colleges will ‘pay the price’ for DEI, according to private group chat with Trump officials</title>
      <description>Andreessen co-founded one of Silicon Valley’s most prominent venture capital firms, Andreessen Horowitz, which embraced Donald Trump’s candidacy last year. While Elon Musk was the most visible tech mogul in Trump’s orbit until he split with the president, Andreessen has quietly helped shape the administration’s hiring and policy decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72f11fc0-5f51-11f0-a399-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 18:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iga Swiatek defeats Amanda Anisimova to win first Wimbledon championship and sixth Grand Slam title</title>
      <description>The 24-year old Swiatek, a former world No. 1 from Poland, has never lost a Grand Slam championship match. It was the first appearance in a Grand Slam final for the American Anisimova, who upset top-seeded Aryna Sabalenka in the semifinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05726e60-5f3b-11f0-acaa-0000a1ace985</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I dread my bigoted mother-in-law’s weekly lunches</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I dread my bigoted mother-in-law’s weekly lunches</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7e2a0a0-5f38-11f0-b4cb-0000a1acec12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the dark, a teen counselor at Camp Mystic led 16 girls to safety: ‘Get ready to climb’</title>
      <description>Ainslie Bashara, 19, had arrived a week earlier for a month-long stay. She’d met campers from the Giggle Box cabin just five days earlier but had already grown devoted to them. Together they braved the relentless Texas floodwaters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d27220e0-5f2c-11f0-a89e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he’s ready to slap 30% tariffs on imports from Mexico and European Union starting Aug. 1</title>
      <description>The latest move is likely to disrupt relationships following weeks of negotiations with two of the United States’ largest trading partners. Over the past week, President Donald Trump has sent letters to various world leaders about new levies he is readying to impose on imports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11408650-5f27-11f0-940f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8fb2ca0-5f24-11f0-aead-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders halt to Trump administration’s indiscriminate immigration stops and arrests in California</title>
      <description>A federal judge ordered the Trump administration to stop patrolling and rounding up individuals without reasonable justification, including basing arrests on racial profiling, and to stop denying access to lawyers, saying the tactics are unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94e93cc0-5ecf-11f0-bb1e-0000a1ace396</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas county didn't use its most powerful and far-reaching alert system as floods grew deadly on July 4</title>
      <description>A Washington Post examination found Kerr County officials eventually sent text-message alerts on the morning of July 4 to some residents. But even as conditions deteriorated, they did not activate a more forceful tool that would have sounded an alarm on cellphones throughout the river valley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90692920-5e9e-11f0-8c51-0000a1ace218</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Gergen dies at 83. The consummate political insider held communications jobs under Nixon, Ford, Reagan and Clinton.</title>
      <description>Gergen, a conservative-leaning centrist, helped craft and protect the image of four presidents as a senior White House communications adviser and held high-profile jobs in TV punditry and academia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1f49d40-5e9a-11f0-8bd0-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected fuel cutoff preceded Air India plane crash, preliminary report says</title>
      <description>Indian investigators’ initial findings suggest that both engines stopped receiving fuel shortly after takeoff, but a final determination by the government’s Aircraft Accident Investigation Bureau into the cause of the crash is likely more than a year away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d867cf80-5e97-11f0-9596-0000a1aceb3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Trump staffers behind the push to overhaul higher education</title>
      <description>Shaped by experiences as ideological minorities on liberal campuses, these officials are targeting their alma maters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53a79460-5e88-11f0-8150-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Father-in-law destroyed the garden I inherited from my dying mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Father-in-law destroyed the garden I inherited from my dying mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13cc4710-5e73-11f0-a31d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Army combat veteran may have stopped Trump’s would-be assassin. Now he’s telling his story.</title>
      <description>Butler County SWAT team operator Aaron Zaliponi fired the “ninth shot” at Donald Trump’s Pennsylvania rally last July. He believes it hit the shooter’s rifle, but one year later, the significance of his quick action is still unresolved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61489ff0-5e66-11f0-b27a-0000a1acec85</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department is firing more than 1,300 employees by email in downsizing plan</title>
      <description>The move has come under criticism from current and former diplomats who say the cuts will degrade America’s standing in the world and curb U.S. soft power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37cd1b00-5e62-11f0-a99a-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872f6331-5e5b-11f0-94ad-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump shooting anniversary. Texas visit. Federal layoffs. Birthright citizenship. Wimbledon. AI videos. Jan. 6 show. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e491af0-5e46-11f0-b39a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
