<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 ‘Deciders’: Who are they and what makes them tick?</title>
      <description>In a nation where many voters have made up their minds in the upcoming presidential election, 6 in 10 voters in key battleground states turn out sporadically or are not firmly committed to President Biden or Donald Trump.
These Deciders skew young and non-White and are even more sour on major candidates than the broader electorate. The Washington Post and the Schar School of Policy and Government at George Mason University surveyed 3,513 registered voters in six key states to find out what they think.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cc30e60-2e8b-11ef-bdbc-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 22:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rare gene mutation helps people resist Alzheimer’s disease, study finds — a hopeful clue for new therapies</title>
      <description>In a study published Wednesday in the New England Journal of Medicine, researchers reported 27 members of an extended Colombian family carry extreme genetic risk for Alzheimer’s, along with a copy of a protective gene called Christchurch. Cognitive decline in this singular group was delayed by about five years, suggesting that a drug that emulates the gene could have similar effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">396465e0-2e7f-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran signals a major boost to nuclear program at key site</title>
      <description>The expansion in Iran’s most heavily protected nuclear facility could triple the site’s production of enriched uranium and give Tehran new options for quickly assembling a nuclear arsenal if it chooses to, according to confidential documents and analysis by weapons experts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9903320-2e65-11ef-809a-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom dumped stepdad and wants to coo about her new love to her kid</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom dumped stepdad and wants to coo about her new love to her kid</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9d0d70-2e55-11ef-82de-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A nail-biter in the 5th District, and four other takeaways from Virginia’s primary election results</title>
      <description>Virginia, home to several competitive districts and virtually a permanent bellwether for national politics, never lacks for drama in its congressional races. Here are our takeaways from Tuesday’s primary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebbd7c60-2e50-11ef-b647-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China backed the ringleaders of a global scam network — then turned on them</title>
      <description>Crime syndicates in Kokang, Myanmar, near the border with China, operated more than 300 compounds running online fraud schemes, often with trafficked workers. That made Kokang a key hub in what Interpol estimates is a $3 trillion global online scam industry, a Washington Post investigation found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5a1af50-2e48-11ef-8516-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Juneteenth! Play today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16388a40-2e45-11ef-ab3c-0000a1ace62b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat wave. Nvidia surge. Presidential debate. Willie Mays. Justin Timberlake. Childhood obesity. Black hole. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">090d6940-2e2b-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea’s Kim Jong Un declares ‘full support’ for Russian war in Ukraine during Vladimir Putin’s visit to Pyongyang</title>
      <description>The Russian president, looking for diplomatic and military support, signed a “comprehensive” agreement with Kim during a rare visit to North Korea. They gave no details, but the United States and its allies are concerned North Korea will ship more munitions to Russia to help it sustain its war against Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cf58eb0-2e25-11ef-aafb-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Army Green Beret Derrick Anderson wins GOP Va. primary for Rep. Abigail Spanberger’s (D) 7th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The GOP hopes to flip the seat, which Spanberger is vacating to run for governor. Democrats have generally fared better in recent elections in this district, which stretches from rapidly growing, diverse exurbs outside D.C. to rural foothills in the Piedmont.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2b5e770-2ddb-11ef-8c9c-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Va. state Sen. Suhas Subramanyam wins Democratic primary for Jennifer Wexton’s (D) 10th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The seat is open after Wexton announced she is not seeking reelection because of health reasons. Wexton had flipped the seat in 2018, and Democrats hope to hang onto it in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">550ef9e1-2dda-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Mays dies at 93. The legendary baseball player of peerless power and grace was the ‘Say Hey Kid’ who could do it all.</title>
      <description>With sublime athletic grace, Mays excelled in every facet of the game as a center fielder with the New York and San Francisco Giants in the 1950s and ’60s, hitting 660 home runs and becoming arguably the best all-around player in baseball history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cd7f800-2dd8-11ef-aeee-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eugene Vindman, a Trump whistleblower, is projected to win Democratic nomination in Va.’s 7th Congressional District</title>
      <description>Vindman, a former Army colonel who helped file a report prompting the first impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump, had used his celebrity on the national stage to catapult to the front of the crowded Democratic primary. He hopes to succeed Rep. Abigail Spanberger (D), who is running for governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6fe2791-2dd1-11ef-b378-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech company executive Mike Clancy wins GOP primary for Rep. Jennifer Wexton’s (D) 10th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The seat is open after Rep. Jennifer Wexton announced she is not seeking reelection because of health reasons. Wexton had flipped the seat in 2018, and Republicans hope to flip it back in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee4f540-2dce-11ef-9971-0000a1ace569</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls have closed in the Virginia primaries. Follow The Post’s coverage to see results in crucial House races and more.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post is bringing you live coverage of election results, analysis and more as votes are tallied in several contested House primaries across the state, as well as local races.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10442d20-2dc7-11ef-8ce5-0000a1ace053</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says it is nearing the end of its Rafah offensive, potentially shifting to a new, less-intense phase of the conflict</title>
      <description>Israeli forces are making progress against Hamas in Rafah, a senior military official said, destroying the group’s infrastructure and cutting the supply of weapons coming through tunnels from Egypt. A shift to more targeted operations across Gaza could bring respite to civilians who have spent months in the line of fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4e6240-2dbe-11ef-a0e2-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. won’t meet CNN debate requirement for ballot access</title>
      <description>The independent presidential candidate has said he has qualified for enough state ballots, but state election officials have said that’s not true.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92543800-2db8-11ef-8cc3-0000a1aced16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia becomes the world’s most valuable public company, pushing past Apple and Microsoft</title>
      <description>The company’s computer chips and software are crucial to training the artificial-intelligence algorithms behind image generators and chatbots like OpenAI’s ChatGPT. As the tech and business worlds throw themselves into the AI boom, demand for Nvidia's chips has skyrocketed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33d4de50-2daf-11ef-a0e2-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The national debt will grow to more than $50 trillion by 2034, CBO projects, as defense costs and safety net spending rise</title>
      <description>This year’s federal deficit will grow to $1.9 trillion, according to the Congressional Budget Office. A large debt balance could keep federal interest rates high and present risks in bond markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6a32cf0-2d9c-11ef-ae40-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does age make a person less gracious — or better at boundaries?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does age make a person less gracious — or better at boundaries?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ed001f0-2d8c-11ef-b0d0-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A major awards show is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc98581-2d76-11ef-9730-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration rule. Heat wave. Putin visit. Mark Robinson. Social media warning. Ian McKellen. NBA Finals. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">def80ad0-2d61-11ef-b168-0000a1ace076</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Celtics beat Dallas Mavericks in NBA Finals, securing the franchise’s record 18th championship</title>
      <description>The Celtics won Game 5 on their home floor Monday night to claim their first NBA title since 2008 and cap a dominant postseason in which they went 16-3. Boston moves ahead of the rival Los Angeles Lakers, who pulled even with their 17th championship in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67bb8281-2d20-11ef-ac39-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 03:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden to announce program allowing undocumented immigrants married to U.S. citizens to apply for legal residency</title>
      <description>Biden will unveil the policy Tuesday in one of the most expansive immigration programs of his presidency, according to two federal sources with knowledge of the plans. About 500,000 people are expected to be eligible to apply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20e069d0-2d01-11ef-a840-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 23:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS to enact rules that would prevent businesses and wealthy individuals from manipulating the value of assets to lower their taxes</title>
      <description>The agency wants to crack down on those who repeatedly depreciate the value of their assets. New audits could bring in an extra $5 billion a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f4fdf90-2cd1-11ef-88bb-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: I'm married to a ‘secret bigot.’ How do I reconcile the vile things he says?</title>
      <description>I'm married to a ‘secret bigot.’ How do I reconcile the vile things he says?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d89c0de1-2cc5-11ef-8a42-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 16:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $50 billion pay package in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7234100-2cad-11ef-ad96-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin traveling to North Korea on Tuesday amid concerns about growing military cooperation between the countries</title>
      <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin and Kim Jong Un are expected to pledge public support for each other and rebuff U.S.-led efforts to isolate Russia over its invasion of Ukraine. Moscow is in desperate need of the munitions that North Korea can provide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb1009a0-2c9b-11ef-bca2-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza fighting. Brutal heat. Biden ad. Marijuana pardons. Baby genomes. Screen time. Princess Kate. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b35c5a81-2c98-11ef-9bbb-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Stereophonic’ and ‘The Outsiders’ win big at the 2024 Tony Awards</title>
      <description>Daniel Radcliffe and Jeremy Strong also took home prizes at the ceremony honoring Broadway’s best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f45167c1-2c56-11ef-b360-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incoming Post editor tied to self-described ‘thief’ who claimed role in his reporting</title>
      <description>Unpublished book drafts and other documents raise questions about Robert Winnett’s journalistic record just months before he is to assume a top newsroom role at The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28250aa0-2c40-11ef-91af-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Md. governor to pardon more than 175,000 marijuana convictions, one of the nation’s most sweeping clemency acts involving the drug</title>
      <description>The pardons will forgive decades of low-level marijuana possession charges for an estimated 100,000 people in what Gov. Wes Moore (D) said is a step to heal decades of social and economic injustice that disproportionately harm Black and Brown people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4ca3ca0-2c3b-11ef-8ba3-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 23:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bryson DeChambeau wins the U.S. Open for the second time</title>
      <description>DeChambeau, 30, entered Sunday's final round at Pinehurst No. 2 with a three-shot lead. DeChambeau, who joined LIV Golf in 2022, also won the 2020 U.S. Open at Winged Foot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f13c5f60-2c31-11ef-a841-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 22:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new program allows members of Congress to receive reimbursements without receipts. See how much your representative expensed.</title>
      <description>More than two dozen members of Congress were paid at least $30,000 in addition to their salary last year as part of the program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cf9cc90-2c0b-11ef-a41c-0000a1acef9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 18:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bef84f10-2bf9-11ef-bf2d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 16:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every time you breathe, you could be inhaling microplastics. See how the tiny particles infiltrate organs, threatening our health.</title>
      <description>Scientists are increasingly concerned that microplastics may be linked to growing rates of cancer, heart disease and other chronic illnesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26bae530-2bf1-11ef-a49f-000a1ace957c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9e7ca00-2be9-11ef-af0d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 14:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An officer met a teen at Chick-fil-A, then abused her in his police car. Now a judge must decide his punishment.</title>
      <description>The high school student, who’d wanted to be a cop, was assured that the Indiana officer would be held accountable for sexually abusing her. But a Washington Post investigation found hundreds of officers evaded serious consequences for preying on children, even after they admitted to wrongdoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5ac4c30-2b5f-11ef-b939-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 21:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pledged to pardon Jan. 6 rioters. He faces pressure to name names.</title>
      <description>The presumptive Republican nominee’s vow to exercise the clemency powers of the presidency if he returns to office has raised alarms about his support for political violence and touched off private conversations among supporters about how to deliver on his pledge. There is only one known individual rioter Trump has specifically promised to pardon, according to interviews with about a dozen other prominent family members and advocates of those charged for their roles in the attack. His campaign has said he will decide on a “case-by-case” basis without specifying what criteria he would use.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ae581b0-2b3e-11ef-b939-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My friend’s new girlfriend is jealous and sent me abusive messages</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My friend’s new girlfriend is jealous and sent me abusive messages</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c83a6a60-2b34-11ef-b88d-000a1acebcb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon-owned One Medical shifted some care to a call center, leading to patient safety issues, leaked documents reveal</title>
      <description>Since Amazon acquired the primary-care service One Medical, elderly patients have been routed to a call center — staffed partly by contractors with limited training — that failed on more than a dozen occasions to seek immediate attention for callers with urgent symptoms, according to internal documents seen by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1620e80-2b2e-11ef-8514-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 15:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They’re the nation’s first Black, Muslim, nonbinary state lawmaker. The hard part came after taking office.</title>
      <description>Four years ago, Mauree Turner’s election in one of the most conservative states made history. What they’ve achieved — or failed to achieve — since taking office has come at a high personal cost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dd4d180-2b20-11ef-bd9c-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 14:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a378d090-2b1b-11ef-b030-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 13:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Jones ordered to sell personal assets to pay $1.5 billion to Sandy Hook families but judge dismisses case to shut Infowars</title>
      <description>The ruling, ending a bankruptcy case involving Infowars’s parent company, means Jones’s far-right website will continue to operate at least a little longer, as parents seek the massive damages he owes for falsely claiming that the 2012 school shooting was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da0dd140-2a9f-11ef-a32f-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:45:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stanford’s top disinformation research group collapses under political and legal attacks</title>
      <description>The Stanford Internet Observatory, which published some of the most influential analyses on the spread of false information on social media during elections, has shed most of its staff and may shut down.

Just three staffers remain, who will either leave or find roles at Stanford’s Cyber Policy Center, according to eight people familiar with the developments, some of whom spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss internal matters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25c3e180-2a71-11ef-aeeb-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:11:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is chatting with readers: My husband changed his mind about kids, months after our wedding. Did he trick me?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is chatting with readers: My husband changed his mind about kids, months after our wedding. Did he trick me?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3f363d1-2a6f-11ef-bf2d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 17:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New rules aimed at protecting transgender students are blocked in four states by a federal court</title>
      <description>The regulations, issued by the Education Department in April, represent its interpretation of Title IX, a half-century-old law that bars discrimination in schools based on sex. The preliminary injunction against the rules applies in Louisiana, Mississippi, Montana and Idaho, though similar challenges are pending in other states. The rules are set to take effect on Aug. 1 and affect every K-12 school, college and university in the country that accepts any type of federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">213cbea0-2a64-11ef-bc70-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $895 billion defense policy bill that targets abortion access and diversity protections, advances other GOP priorities</title>
      <description>The bill, initially hailed by lawmakers who drafted it as a feat of bipartisanship, is certain to set up a clash — and prolonged negotiation — with the Democratic-controlled Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c715080-2a62-11ef-82ec-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down Trump-era federal ban on bump stock devices that allow rifles to fire hundreds of bullets per minute</title>
      <description>The case turned on whether bump stocks meet the definition of a machine gun. Federal appeals courts were sharply divided over that question in earlier decisions on the ban’s legality, before the Supreme Court took up the lawsuit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a814bc0-2a59-11ef-8ee4-0000a1ace894</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Catholic bishops apologize for church’s role at Indian boarding schools, citing ‘trauma’ for generations of children</title>
      <description>The extraordinary vote represents the most direct expression of regret to date by senior officials in the Catholic Church for its participation in a U.S. government program to systematically strip Native American children of their identities and forcibly assimilate them into White society. It comes weeks after a Washington Post investigation documenting pervasive sexual abuse by Catholic priests at the schools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73651030-2a53-11ef-a3c2-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
