<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 22:03:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen, preparing to take the stand against his ex-boss, says he’s reformed. Will America buy it?</title>
      <description>After years as Donald Trump’s bruising personal attorney, Cohen is a man on a quest for redemption. But as he prepares to serve as a linchpin in the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal case against the former president, America’s most famous ex-fixer remains a divisive figure — even among partisans on the Trump-loathing left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db0f1450-0281-11ef-a142-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-controlled Arizona House votes to repeal Civil War-era abortion ban. The measure now heads to the state Senate.</title>
      <description>Soon after Roe v. Wade was overturned, the 1864 law briefly took effect in the state, only to be blocked by the courts. Earlier this month, the Arizona Supreme Court revived it, inciting a national uproar and political panic among Republicans as 2024 elections loom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d38b20-0270-11ef-8445-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court conservatives seem skeptical that federal law can require hospitals to perform emergency abortions in states with bans</title>
      <description>The Biden administration has invoked the Emergency Medical Treatment and Labor Act to argue that the federal government can penalize hospitals that fail to provide emergency abortions in states with strict abortion bans. But conservative justices appeared skeptical the 40-year-old federal law — which requires hospitals that receive federal funds to stabilize or transfer all emergency patients regardless of their ability to pay — could be used to require abortions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd683fa1-0258-11ef-a199-0000a1acefff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd2a21c0-0257-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc16e20-0253-11ef-8cd8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We have a radical democracy. Robert Kagan asks: Will Trump voters destroy it?</title>
      <description>We have a radical democracy. Will Trump voters destroy it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90ccc480-0251-11ef-8e5f-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. announces $1 billion Ukraine weapons package after Senate approves massive foreign aid bill</title>
      <description>The weapons package of artillery, ammunition and air-defense missiles restarts an expansive U.S. effort to sustain Ukraine’s embattled military as the war with Russia bleeds into its third year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9e35510-024c-11ef-b3dc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:11:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reggie Bush gets his Heisman Trophy back, more than a decade after the former USC running back was stripped of it</title>
      <description>Bush won the trophy in 2005 but forfeited it in 2010 after an NCAA investigation found he and his family had received gifts from a sports agent, and most of his college statistics were vacated. “We considered the enormous changes in college athletics over the last several years in deciding that now is the right time to reinstate the trophy for Reggie,” the Heisman Trust announced Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">688c4280-024b-11ef-98d8-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 15:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court is hearing arguments on whether hospitals must provide emergency abortions in states with bans. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>At issue is a nearly 40-year-old federal law that requires hospitals that receive federal funds to stabilize or transfer all emergency patients, regardless of their ability to pay. The Biden administration invoked the Emergency Medical Treatment and Labor Act to argue that the federal government has the power to penalize hospitals that fail to provide emergency abortions even in states with strict bans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6030fe70-0244-11ef-a00b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 14:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘next-level’ find in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to even your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5f7cef1-023e-11ef-9f64-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 13:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid. Trump witness. Abortion case. Campus protests. Larry Nassar. Air pollution. Bionic eyes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce069fb0-0229-11ef-8521-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress passes bill that forces a sale or a ban of TikTok, the most significant threat yet to the app’s U.S. operations</title>
      <description>The legislation delivers a historic rebuke of the video-sharing platform’s Chinese ownership, culminating years of failed attempts to tackle the app’s alleged national security risks.

The Senate approved the measure as part of a sprawling funding package sending $95 billion in aid to Ukraine, some of which is structured as a loan, as well as help for Israel, Taiwan and humanitarian assistance.

President Biden is expected to sign the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff8d2340-01db-11ef-9ff1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 01:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA finds evidence of bird flu virus in grocery store milk but expresses confidence in safety of dairy supply</title>
      <description>The findings by the Food and Drug Administration do not necessarily suggest a threat to human health but indicate the avian flu virus is more widespread among dairy herds than previously thought. The agency is conducting further testing to definitively confirm that milk remains safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">577f4521-01bd-11ef-aaf2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 22:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump has become angrier and more isolated on Truth Social</title>
      <description>On his company’s social network, Donald Trump is offering followers an intimate view of what his second term could look like: isolated, vitriolic and vengeful. His following is diminished, but his posting has accelerated. He has traded combative tweets for even more belligerent screeds. And above all, he persists in spreading lies about his 2020 election loss.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c85c470-01ba-11ef-9a04-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 21:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla earnings sharply declined in first quarter, casting doubt on its recovery after weak sales, layoffs and recalls</title>
      <description>Tesla has fallen far from its days as a darling of Wall Street and is now battling a complex array of challenges that threaten its business outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce8d4730-01ad-11ef-9ff1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee passes bill to let teachers carry guns on campuses, a year after Nashville school shooting left six people dead</title>
      <description>The bill, approved by the state's GOP supermajority over protests by students and parents, is one of the most expansive pro-gun steps taken by the state since the Covenant School shooting in March 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95977af1-01ac-11ef-9d9f-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 20:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC bans noncompete agreements that restrict workers from switching employers within their industry</title>
      <description>The Federal Trade Commission approved a rule that will bar employers from enforcing the clauses, which have been signed by millions of Americans. The rule is supposed to take effect after 180 days, though business groups have promised to challenge it in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6bab090-01a5-11ef-8df6-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 19:14:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. reaches $138.7M settlement with victims of former USA Gymnastics doctor Larry Nassar over FBI misconduct claims</title>
      <description>The agreement settles 139 claims brought over the department’s failure to investigate allegations that could have brought Nassar to justice sooner and prevented dozens of assaults. The settlement brings to a close the last major legal case over Nassar’s prolific abuses. Nassar, 60, is serving an effective life sentence for federal convictions relating to possession of child pornography, as well as state convictions for sexual assaults of patients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fb07790-0192-11ef-9cd1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent worries ‘beautiful’ 4-year-old hears too much about looks</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent worries ‘beautiful’ 4-year-old hears too much about looks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">976c3360-018a-11ef-b385-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 16:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 130 Israel-Gaza war protesters were arrested at NYU, police say. Columbia is offering hybrid classes amid demonstrations.</title>
      <description>Anti-war protests on college campuses are growing and continue to be met by police across the nation. More than 100 demonstrators were arrested at Columbia last week, and about 50 were arrested at Yale on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b7f2410-0185-11ef-a677-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 15:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s that buzzing in today’s On the Record?</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb5d080-0175-11ef-9b9c-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 13:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student protests. Trump trial. Supreme Court. Baltimore bridge. Hot summer. Nestlé baby food. George Washington. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0c72a70-0160-11ef-93b4-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rooftop solar panels are flooding California’s grid. That’s a problem.</title>
      <description>California, which leads the nation in solar power, and its grid operator are grappling with a strange reality: so much solar that some of it has to be thrown away. The glut is raising electricity prices and could undercut future renewable energy investment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86740971-00ef-11ef-8aaa-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test your ‘dream economy’ against reality and see which one is better</title>
      <description>We’ll tell you how your vision tracks with the real world — and what other readers thought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbfbe441-00df-11ef-8fcc-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court justices hearing case on homeless ban appear divided between protecting rights and controlling a worsening problem</title>
      <description>In arguments on a Grants Pass, Ore., statute outlawing sleeping in public places, attorneys for unhoused people argued that criminalizing homelessness when there were no other living options was cruel and unusual punishment — and thus unconstitutional. The city insisted it needed flexibility to protect public health and public spaces. The court’s decision, likely to be announced in late June, could be the most significant ruling on the rights of the unhoused in decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d23b5f2-00cd-11ef-a43a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel has not provided evidence that large numbers of U.N. Palestinian refugee agency workers have militant ties, report finds</title>
      <description>The Colonna report found that the U.N. Relief and Works Agency is in need of reforms to ensure it remains neutral, but said Israel has yet to offer evidence supporting its claims that significant numbers of UNRWA employees are members of Hamas or Palestinian Islamic Jihad. The Israeli allegations in January spurred the United States and other donor countries to suspend funding for UNRWA amid a humanitarian crisis in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d437aab0-00c5-11ef-b6b1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to revive a friendship killed by a hostile text?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to revive a friendship killed by a hostile text?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3863ff0-00c2-11ef-a021-0000a1acef1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening statements are set to begin in Trump’s hush money trial in New York. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Prosecutors and defense lawyers are expected to start laying out their cases in Donald Trump’s trial for allegedly falsifying business records to hide a hush money payment during the 2016 presidential election campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6b67dd0-00ad-11ef-b321-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A double album in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0901a91-00ac-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid. Trump trial. Supreme Court. Israeli general. Solar power. Meta AI. Cicadas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">780a7e30-0097-11ef-8ca0-0000a1ace070</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military intelligence chief resigns over Oct. 7 Hamas attack</title>
      <description>Maj. Gen. Aharon Haliva is the first general of the Israel Defense Forces staff to offer to leave his position due to the failures that led to the attack and the war in Gaza. He serves as commander of the IDF’s Operations Directorate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">067d2590-0085-11ef-9364-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nelly Korda wins the Chevron Championship for her fifth consecutive LPGA Tour victory and second career major title</title>
      <description>Korda, 25, matched the LPGA Tour record for consecutive victories held by Nancy Lopez and Annika Sorenstam. The world’s No. 1 player claimed her other major title at the 2021 Women’s PGA Championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a89306a0-0031-11ef-9379-000a1ace39dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 22:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump’s N.Y. trial, the jury pool spoke, and he had to listen</title>
      <description>The jury selection process for Donald Trump’s hush money trial created something akin to a national focus group — albeit with a New York accent — giving ordinary Americans a chance to offer their opinions and reflections on the former president’s nearly five decades in the public spotlight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a8b2e80-0022-11ef-bf6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 21:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My boyfriend’s parents treat me like an outsider</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My boyfriend’s parents treat me like an outsider</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b82e840-0011-11ef-b71f-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c3714b0-fff8-11ee-9379-000a1ace39dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her love of backcountry skiing drew her to boarding school in the Swiss Alps. Then the mountain crumbled underneath her.</title>
      <description>Emily Franciose adored backcountry treks so much that she left her Colorado home to attend Ecole d’Humanité, a small boarding school in Hasliberg, Switzerland. But an accident caused the Wellhorn mountain to fall apart beneath her skis — and left her parents wanting answers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">200f34a1-fff2-11ee-b8a7-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 15:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Oregon city outlawed homeless people from sleeping in public. The Supreme Court will decide whether the ban is cruel and unusual.</title>
      <description>Grants Pass, Ore., banned sleeping in public spaces, even though the city has no homeless shelters. The court decision, expected in late June, could be the most consequential ruling on the rights of the unhoused in decades, and could either uphold or derail increasingly punitive efforts across the country that seek to deal with homelessness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fec8cf20-ffe9-11ee-82b9-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 14:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c714ae1-ffe6-11ee-a4b7-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A real Prince of Denmark tries to live a normal life in Washington</title>
      <description>Prince Joachim and his family arrived last summer for his diplomatic post, leaving behind royal drama to raise a family in D.C. with hardly anyone noticing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d758420-ff61-11ee-b96f-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $95 billion foreign aid package, with funds for Ukraine and Israel, with bipartisan support</title>
      <description>Republicans joined with Democrats to push the measures, which also include money for Taiwan and to regulate TikTok, in a package assembled by House Speaker Mike Johnson (R-La.). Johnson defied far-right members to put Ukraine aid on the floor and may face a motion to oust him from the speakerhip because of it. The Senate is expected to take up the foreign aid package early next week and President Biden has signaled he will sign it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e878e151-ff40-11ee-9bde-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl LPs now outsell CDs. See how records get made in 2024.</title>
      <description>Artists like Taylor Swift and Beyoncé are releasing vinyl albums with exclusive tracks, cover art and more. On this Record Store Day, see how they are made— from lacquer to label.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">246d96b0-ff37-11ee-b599-0000a1ace9c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the 10 financial documents you need to keep forever, our personal finance columnist says. Scan and shred the rest.</title>
      <description>These are the 10 financial documents you need to keep forever, our personal finance columnist says. Scan and shred the rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c71d7c0-ff30-11ee-9fca-000a1ace1f21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riding the baddest bulls made him a legend — and plenty of money. Until one broke his neck.</title>
      <description>J.B. Mauney is arguably the greatest rodeo bull rider ever. But since suffering a career-ending injury last September, he has been forced to grapple with the aftermath of a career built on the edge of primal danger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">742644a0-ff22-11ee-9729-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37a35e31-ff1a-11ee-b304-0000a1aceb16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress extends controversial warrantless surveillance law for two years</title>
      <description>Laboring into the early hours of Saturday morning, Congress squeaked through the renewal of a surveillance program that U.S. spy agencies regard as one of their most valuable tools, and that critics on the left and the right say intrudes on Americans’ privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c047500-fed1-11ee-b144-0000a1acec5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen workers in Tennessee pass historic vote to unionize in a victory for the UAW</title>
      <description>In Chattanooga, Tenn., autoworkers became the first at a Southern auto factory to approve a union with an election since the 1940s. They join a handful of unionized auto factories in the South, where local laws make it harder for unions to organize. The UAW has endorsed President Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1c210d0-febd-11ee-8441-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to withdraw troops from Niger after Washington and junta fail to agree on continued military presence, U.S. officials say</title>
      <description>Kurt Campbell, the State Department’s No. 2 official, met with Niger’s prime minister Friday and accepted his demand that American forces leave the West African country, a move the Biden administration had resisted and one that is certain to transform the United States’ counterterrorism posture in that part of the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a7e3ed0-feb2-11ee-b4e6-0000a1aceb66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 01:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northern Virginia serves as the world’s internet hub. Its neighbors are paying a price.</title>
      <description>Football-field-size buildings that hold computers processing nearly 70 percent of the world’s internet traffic are gobbling up electricity at a rate that’s unsustainable. Coal will be the key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9e46e90-fe98-11ee-9a8c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration issues new Title IX rules protecting transgender students, sexual assault victims</title>
      <description>The Title IX regulations bar schools from discriminating against transgender students, feeding a culture clash with conservative states and school boards that have limited transgender rights in schools. The new rules also mandate changes for how schools handle claims of sexual assault and harassment on campus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b1b7490-fe83-11ee-841c-000a1ace4d53</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full jury seated for Trump’s N.Y. trial; opening statements expected next week</title>
      <description>A full 12-member jury and six alternates have been chosen for Donald Trump’s trial in New York on criminal charges, which began Monday, setting the stage for opening statements next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93b6db80-fe74-11ee-b6a7-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
