<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:03:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33321850-ed6b-11f0-a4fc-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 50,000 jobs in December, a solid gain capping off weak 2025</title>
      <description>The unemployment rate ticked down to 4.4 percent at the end of the worst year for the labor market since the pandemic-era recession.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29c31720-ed60-11f0-8677-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday briefing: Minneapolis ICE shooting; White House ballroom; Grok images; health tips for 2026; and more</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3437890-ed52-11f0-8134-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE officer who fatally shot a Minneapolis woman in her SUV had been dragged by a driver months earlier</title>
      <description>Federal authorities did not publicly name the officer who killed Renee Nicole Good. But court records reviewed by The Washington Post of the prior incident in Bloomington, a suburb of Minneapolis, identify the officer as Jonathan Ross, who works for an Immigration and Customs Enforcement division that detains immigrants for civil violations and attempts to deport them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66cd7fb0-ecfd-11f0-85bc-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 01:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agents shoot two people in Portland, Oregon, mayor says</title>
      <description>The victims’ conditions were not made public. Mayor Keith Wilson (D) did not identify the agency to which the federal agents who fired the shots belonged but called for Immigration and Customs Enforcement to end all operations in the city and referenced the fatal shooting of a woman by an ICE officer in Minneapolis on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed56f601-ecf4-11f0-8957-0000a1ace94b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill extending health care subsidies for 3 years, bucking GOP leaders. Its fate in the Senate remains unclear.</title>
      <description>More than a dozen House Republicans joined every Democrat to pass a bill to extend enhanced Affordable Care Act subsidies — the sharpest rejection by GOP members of the party’s leadership yet. The pandemic-era subsidies expired at the end of last year, driving up costs for millions of Americans who buy health insurance on the ACA marketplace and qualified for the assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89cc1c50-ece0-11f0-a498-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 22:22:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is planning to make his addition as tall as the mansion itself, breaking with architectural norms</title>
      <description>The president’s architect disclosed the change as federal review panels begin a fast-track review of the $400 million project. The significant change of plans defies long-standing norms requiring additions to be shorter than the main building.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94481821-ecd4-11f0-b985-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate advances bill to block further military action in Venezuela. The measure still awaits final passage.</title>
      <description>The headline of a previous alert incorrectly stated the Senate had passed the bill. The Senate voted to advance the measure toward final passage, though the timing for a vote was not immediately clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9f12cc0-ecbb-11f0-80ef-000a1ace8d41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota officials say the FBI is freezing the state out of the probe into the deadly ICE shooting</title>
      <description>The Minnesota Bureau of Criminal Apprehension said the FBI’s decision to take over the investigation into the shooting in Minneapolis will keep state officials from accessing evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">505c28c0-ecb8-11f0-8c26-0000a1ace588</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes bill to block further military action in Venezuela</title>
      <description>Though largely symbolic, the vote was a rare assertion of Congress’ role in using lethal force after the stunning raid to capture Nicolás Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4ade8d0-ecb4-11f0-acf4-0000a1ace02b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My ex ‘brainwashed’ our girls to back his lawsuit against me</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My ex ‘brainwashed’ our girls to back his lawsuit against me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0594da0-ecb3-11f0-8567-0000a1ace74c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 17:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Foundation paper calls for ‘marriage bootcamp,’ discourages online dating, among other ideas</title>
      <description>The conservative think tank aims to boost U.S. marriage and birth rates through recommendations to restrict pornography, create tax credits for bigger families while capping alimony payments and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc0934f0-ecae-11f0-8864-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The tragedy in Minnesota underscores a moral and political failure, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>Rioting in response to fatal shooting plays into Trump’s hands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4206860-ecac-11f0-a425-0000a1ace122</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 16:13:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pass this dessert item in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2afcd51-ec9e-11f0-b634-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Footage shows ICE agent in Minneapolis fired at driver as vehicle veered past him</title>
      <description>A deadly encounter in Minneapolis between federal Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents and a 37-year-old woman escalated in a matter of seconds. A frame-by-frame analysis of video footage raises questions about officials’ accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f6bd4e0-ec96-11f0-9a43-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE shooting. Greenland threats. Dietary advice. United Nations. Heritage report. AI job threat. Daydreaming. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaedef00-ec89-11f0-9efd-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 12:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wizards to acquire four-time all-star Trae Young from Hawks for CJ McCollum, Corey Kispert</title>
      <description>The trade for the point guard adds a key piece to the rebuilding Wizards, who have the youngest roster in the NBA and the second-most players age 22 or younger. Young is averaging 25.2 points per game over his eight-year career, and his 9.8 assists per game are the most among active players.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bfc1182-ec3f-11f0-896f-0000a1ace490</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 03:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Steny Hoyer to retire, ending storied career representing Maryland in Congress</title>
      <description>The 86-year-old Hoyer, the third-longest-serving member of the House, said he decided not to seek a new term over the holidays with his family, feeling content with a career that never brought the brass ring of the House speaker’s gavel but put him at the center of this century’s biggest debates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bffd080-ec3d-11f0-88fb-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 02:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experts say these 5 exercises are key to staying healthy and aging better</title>
      <description>These simple moves can help you stay strong and build muscles as you age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b4b8100-ec2a-11f0-84da-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s swaggering campaign to buy — or seize — Greenland could damage American security for decades, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>Trump’s Greenland fixation curdles into a crisis</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98883b70-ec27-11f0-b446-0000a1ace2d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, one of the oldest American newspapers, says it will close down, citing losses and labor rules</title>
      <description>After losing a battle with unionized employees, the owners of 240-year-old paper have decided to shut it down. The newspaper will print its final edition on May 3, according to a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">435625c0-ec0b-11f0-8f35-000a1ace3c99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 20:55:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE officer fatally shoots woman during Minneapolis operation</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security confirmed the incident, which took place amid the Trump administration’s massive enforcement operation in the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaecd571-ebf8-11f0-896f-0000a1ace490</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BFF is moving to fulfill her expat dreams. I’m so sad. Hax readers give advice.</title>
      <description>BFF is moving to fulfill her expat dreams. I’m so sad. Hax readers give advice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4cb78e0-ebea-11f0-b9b8-0000a1aceb1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 17:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New dietary guidance under RFK Jr. pushes whole milk, discourages processed food</title>
      <description>The Dietary Guidelines for Americans are updated every five years to recommend what people should eat and is considered a cornerstone of federal nutrition policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08b0ad80-ebe5-11f0-88f7-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do empty restaurants seat us at bad tables? Ask your dining questions.</title>
      <description>Why do empty restaurants seat us at bad tables? Ask your dining questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30b09db0-ebe3-11f0-90ff-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe draws red line on Greenland as Trump seems to bristle at suggestions he is endangering NATO</title>
      <description>European efforts to manage President Donald Trump rather than confront him have been jolted by the U.S. president’s hawkish comments about “getting” Greenland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14079bd0-ebe0-11f0-8a4f-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not running for reelection in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b17a761-ebd6-11f0-84da-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. seizes Russian-flagged tanker that fled Venezuela blockade</title>
      <description>The tanker Marinera has been pursued by the U.S. Coast Guard for weeks. Marinera “has been secured,” a U.S. official told The Washington Post. “U.S. federal law enforcement personnel are currently on board it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cd08610-ebd1-11f0-b969-0000a1ace5f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:59:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela raid. Tulsi Gabbard. Jan. 6 website. CDC turmoil. ICE agents. Warm weather. Essential exercises. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d407940-ebc0-11f0-b373-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 75 people were killed in Venezuela during military raid to capture Maduro, U.S. officials assess</title>
      <description>The sizable death toll adds meaning to President Donald Trump’s public remarks that the operation he approved was “effective” but “very violent.” Details of the operation indicate that there were zero U.S. fatalities, but seven service members were injured, the Pentagon said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38ac5381-eb64-11f0-adad-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House floats military option for seizing Greenland, rattling Denmark and NATO</title>
      <description>The rhetoric follows a dramatic U.S. raid in Venezuela and revives Trump’s long-standing focus on the Danish territory, transforming diplomatic discussions into fears of coercion. But U.S. military posture there remains unchanged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1446fa0-eb62-11f0-adad-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aldrich Ames, the most damaging CIA traitor in agency history, dies in prison at 84</title>
      <description>Ames turned over the names of recruited Soviet and Warsaw Pact agents and information about hundreds of intelligence operations to Moscow in return for money. His actions reportedly caused the deaths of at least 10 recruited CIA or allied intelligence agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">547abfc1-eb5a-11f0-a1c1-000a1ace544b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown University suspect admitted to planning shooting for a long time, prosecutors say</title>
      <description>Federal officials released a transcript of short videos they said Claudio Manuel Neves Valente recorded in Portuguese. Police found Valente dead of a self-inflicted gunshot wound Dec. 18 at a New Hampshire storage facility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47bd79c2-eb56-11f0-8f14-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Ravens part ways with coach John Harbaugh after 18 seasons</title>
      <description>Under Harbaugh, the Ravens reached the playoffs 12 times and won a Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7a54580-eb50-11f0-9bc0-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear grips Caracas as a new wave of repression is unleashed</title>
      <description>Venezuela’s government has moved quickly to suppress any public expression of support for Nicolás Maduro’s ouster, launching a nationwide crackdown that has included the detention of journalists, the arrest of civilians and the deployment of armed gangs across the capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd7f0170-eb4e-11f0-a221-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming Supreme Court strikes down first-of-its-kind ban on abortion pills</title>
      <description>The court also rolled back a broader prohibition on abortions, citing a state constitution provision that guarantees residents the right to make health care decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5bdd481-eb3b-11f0-b020-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: They’ve become this mom’s free day care, and she has notes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: They’ve become this mom’s free day care, and she has notes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ed77ef1-eb21-11f0-81d1-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump might have his hubris checked in Venezuela, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>The president has launched a violent process of change that he can’t fully control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">791de040-eb1f-11f0-8ac7-0000a1ace9f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McMansions may be making homeowners miserable. Our columnist explains why.</title>
      <description>As the size of the average American home has nearly doubled, the people living in them aren’t any happier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65444fc0-eb1d-11f0-acde-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Doug LaMalfa (R-California) has died at 65. His passing challenges the GOP’s House majority.</title>
      <description>The seven-term congressman represented a district that encompassed much of Northern California’s interior. His district was redrawn last year, taking it from a safely GOP seat to a Democratic-leaning one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b54f2640-eb11-11f0-ba54-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A memorable character in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5809380-eb0b-11f0-afec-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro in court. Childhood vaccines. Pete Hegseth. FEMA cuts. Grok images. ADHD drugs. Fiber advice. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31969820-eaf7-11f0-8a19-0000a1acebdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents outline potential cuts affecting thousands of FEMA disaster responders</title>
      <description>Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem has said she wants to reduce FEMA’s staff by half. Drafted plans show how it can happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c486c610-ea9c-11f0-b8be-0000a1ace517</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This fun hobby may reduce your dementia risk by 76 percent</title>
      <description>There are several science-based ways to boost your brain health, Dr. Trisha Pasricha writes, but this one might surprise you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a252000-ea96-11f0-b77b-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. overhauls childhood vaccine schedule, recommending fewer shots</title>
      <description>The new strategy would no longer broadly recommend vaccines for RSV, flu, hepatitis A and B, rotavirus and meningitis. The Trump administration says this aligns the U.S. with peer countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47473f90-ea6a-11f0-b8be-0000a1ace517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband does travel — just not with spouse to visit family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband does travel — just not with spouse to visit family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">665ec080-ea59-11f0-98bd-0000a1ace5d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela’s Nicolás Maduro is set to appear in court for his arraignment in Manhattan. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The deposed Venezuelan leader has been transferred by helicopter to Manhattan, where he and his wife, Cilia Flores, are set to be arraigned at noon at the U.S. District Court on charges that they enriched themselves through drug trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41a67e10-ea57-11f0-a3ca-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s some turbulence in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af4ae70-ea55-11f0-b1bd-0000a1ace8f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth announces censure and potential demotion of Sen. Mark Kelly</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has targeted the Arizona Democrat, a retired Navy officer, over a video reminding U.S. troops they can disobey illegal orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf11031-ea4e-11f0-a339-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is college worth it? This quiz shows the reality.</title>
      <description>Views on the importance of higher education have fallen sharply in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3caa5cd0-ea4b-11f0-a339-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
