<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 06:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Reformist Masoud Pezeshkian will be Iran’s next president</title>
      <description>A heart surgeon and relative unknown, Pezeshkian campaigned on engaging with the West to help free the country’s economy from crippling sanctions. He prevailed in the second round of snap elections Friday organized after the death of President Ebrahim Raisi in a May helicopter crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f67a240-3b54-11ef-a889-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 04:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This natural gas exporter is building a fortress on sinking land. Can its 26-foot-high wall protect it from sea level rise?</title>
      <description>In a part of Louisiana threatened by hurricanes and storm surge, a company has built a massive sea wall around its gas export plant.
That raises a question: How far will the fossil fuel industry go to protect itself from climate impacts it helped cause?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a783b5b0-3b1a-11ef-9c74-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 22:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mark Warner (D-Va.) is seeking to assemble a group of senators to ask Biden to exit the presidential race</title>
      <description>Warner is telling Democratic senators that Biden can no longer stay in the election in the wake of his faltering debate performance, according to two people familiar with private conversations who spoke on the condition of anonymity to talk freely.
As the chair of the Senate Intelligence Committee, the Virginia Democrat is viewed as a serious voice privately advocating for the president to step aside. He represents a state that Democrats must win in November to maintain their hold on the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed43c9a1-3b06-11ef-b109-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 19:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden has displayed signs of accelerated aging with lapses appearing more common, those who have interacted with him say</title>
      <description>Aides, foreign leaders, donors and members of Congress say Biden has seemed slower and more often loses his train of thought in recent months, though close aides insist he remains mentally sharp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12807af0-3ae0-11ef-9f63-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Supreme Court clears way for ballot drop boxes, reversing an earlier decision by a conservative-controlled court</title>
      <description>Liberals on the Wisconsin Supreme Court on Friday overturned a decision that banned absentee ballot drop boxes made by conservatives when they controlled the court two years ago. The 4-3 ruling came a year after liberals took a majority on the top court in a crucial swing state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2199b020-3ad5-11ef-8c52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager. It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager. It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4472cf20-3ad3-11ef-9a2d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican excommunicates Carlo Maria Viganò, former ambassador to the U.S., for refusing to recognize the pope</title>
      <description>In a rare trial, the Vatican took action against one of Pope Francis’s most vociferous internal critics. Viganò, who was loyal to the previous pope, Benedict XVI, had called on the pope to resign, be arrested, and excoriated him in harsh terms, including calling him “a servant of Satan.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3546a171-3ace-11ef-8c52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy adds 206,000 jobs in June, as the resilient labor market continues to grow despite some headwinds</title>
      <description>The labor market notched another month of growth in June, according to data released Friday from the Bureau of Labor Statistics. Even as interest rates remain high, weighing on some parts of the economy, the labor market continues to buoy workers, wages and consumer spending, preventing a broader downturn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5bddf50-3aca-11ef-a88f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 12:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keir Starmer becomes Britain’s next prime minister, ushering in a new era after 14 years of Conservative rule</title>
      <description>King Charles III invited the Labour Party leader to form a government, after Conservative Prime Minister Rishi Sunak tendered his resignation at Buckingham Palace. It marks a huge reversal for Britain’s top parties, with a new government dominated by the center left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78b626f0-3ac0-11ef-9471-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 11:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election. Biden interview. Hurricane Beryl. Jobs market. Threads. Wimbledon. Hot dogs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b93e42f0-3abd-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election exit poll projects big win for Labour, ending 14 years of Conservative Party rule</title>
      <description>In an election that was more about mood than policy, voters appear to have conveyed their frustration with the incumbent Conservative Party and a willingness to give a chance to a renewed Labour Party, purged of its hard-left elements and socialist rhetoric.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff1112a1-3a48-11ef-a4de-0000a1ace5dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 21:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new men’s hot-dog eating champion is crowned: Patrick Bertoletti ate 58. Miki Sudo downed a record 51 to win the women’s contest.</title>
      <description>Bertoletti won for the first time, while 10-time champion Sudo defended her title at this year's Nathan's Famous International Hot Dog Eating Contest, held at Coney Island in New York City. It was the first time since 2004 that Joey Chestnut, the 16-time champion who had won the previous eight contests, was missing from the competition. He was banned last month after signing a sponsorship agreement with Nathan's rival Impossible Foods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbbfe0a0-3a27-11ef-ae5c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 17:06:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Guy who berated spouse over butter would like his second chance now</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Guy who berated spouse over butter would like his second chance now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2de9221-3a1e-11ef-94ab-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We spoke to dozens of Biden’s delegates. Some are having doubts.</title>
      <description>In interviews with more than three dozen delegates to next month’s Chicago convention, most expressed support. But some were candid about their preference for another option, perhaps Vice President Harris. All said they will vote for President Biden — unless he bows out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e81bc730-3a1a-11ef-b633-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 15:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands will celebrate Independence Day by becoming U.S. citizens — after taking a civics test. Try our quiz to see if you’d pass.</title>
      <description>Before taking part in naturalization ceremonies, all aspiring U.S. citizens must prove their knowledge of civics in an oral exam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a456ff20-3a0f-11ef-9c18-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 14:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Fourth! Celebrate with today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Enjoy the holiday!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43b5a40-3a09-11ef-9ea3-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 13:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boil-water advisory lifted for D.C. and Arlington; utility says it confirmed that water quality ‘never deviated' from EPA standards</title>
      <description>The warnings were issued because of clarity issues, which can interfere with disinfection or indicate the presence of bacteria, viruses and parasites, according to D.C. Water.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc0303c1-3a04-11ef-aced-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 12:56:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign crisis. Hurricane Beryl. U.K. election. Wildfire. Banned additive. Longer workweek. Ant surgery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8502ee60-39f4-11ef-9051-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. and Arlington issue boil-water advisories</title>
      <description>The District and Arlington County advised residents to boil their water because of clarity issues in local water sources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26bd5511-39b9-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2024 03:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and aides concede he needs to quickly demonstrate his fitness for office or face pressure to step aside</title>
      <description>Growing concern from Capitol Hill, top donors and senior party strategists, including some of his own advisers, prompted Biden to start contacting allies in recent days to admit that he is in a tough moment and that he has to prove to voters he is up for the job.
His critics have been shaken by his relative inaction over the previous six days to directly address the panic ignited by his halting debate performance last Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bab15b0-3989-11ef-914d-0000a1ace264</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 22:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat advisory issued for D.C. area on the Fourth of July with strong storms also possible</title>
      <description>Factoring in humidity, it could feel as hot as 100 to 105 Thursday afternoon, prompting a heat advisory from the National Weather Service for areas near the Interstate 95 corridor. The heat and humidity could also fuel some strong late-day thunderstorms with dangerous lightning, strong winds and heavy rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a34ade30-397e-11ef-ac86-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:55:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If not Biden, who? Five columnists rate the potential field of replacements for the Democratic presidential nominee.</title>
      <description>If President Biden were to decide not to run for reelection, who should replace him? That would be a question for the 4,000-plus delegates in August at the Democratic National Convention in Chicago, but before then, it’s a question for five Post Opinions columnists, who kicked the tires on the options over email this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f68b7fc0-397c-11ef-904b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents of teen dad wonder if they’re the ones making mistakes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents of teen dad wonder if they’re the ones making mistakes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b084e40-3955-11ef-a9fb-0000a1aced20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 16:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why are some restaurants switching to fixed-price menus? Our food critic is answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why are some restaurants switching to fixed-price menus? Our food critic is answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe04030-394f-11ef-9a8d-0000a1ace241</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who are America’s best leaders? How can we make more of them? Garrett Graff explores what makes a good leader in his first column.</title>
      <description>Great leaders are scarce. How do we increase the supply?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e29d21d0-3945-11ef-a7bc-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 14:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A duo that ‘could be magical’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67b54d89-3940-11ef-9b24-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sentencing delay. Biden crisis. Alzheimer’s drug. India stampede. Wildfires. Covid cases. Frog saunas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62770940-392b-11ef-a2ee-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. would pursue Donald Trump's criminal cases past Election Day, even if he wins</title>
      <description>Prosecutors believe a Justice Dept. ban on charging or prosecuting sitting presidents applies to Inauguration Day, not Election Day, according to people familiar with internal deliberations. That means Trump could face court hearings or even trials until Jan. 20, 2025, if he is elected in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b750f171-38c6-11ef-9301-0000a1ace642</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They left Maryland for Mecca, but they didn’t all come home. Texts, recordings and witness accounts reveal ‘nightmare’ Hajj tour.</title>
      <description>A mosque in Prince George's County is mourning three members who died during the Hajj amid extreme heat in Saudi Arabia. Family members and fellow travelers say tour operators failed to provide proper visas, sufficient transportation and adequate support during the sacred pilgrimage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d701431-38bf-11ef-9962-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 22:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s N.Y. hush money sentencing is postponed until September, showing initial impact of Supreme Court immunity ruling</title>
      <description>The judge in Donald Trump's trial for falsifying records related to a hush money payment has pushed his sentencing back to September, just weeks before the November election, to give his lawyers time to argue that Monday's Supreme Court ruling on presidential immunity means Trump's 34 felony convictions should be tossed out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53fb47a0-38a9-11ef-a047-000a1ace0715</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 19:28:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves Alzheimer’s drug donanemab, only the second drug shown to modestly slow the disease, after months of delay</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration had initially delayed green-lighting Eli Lilly’s donanemab so that it could further study the drug’s safety and efficacy, including unique features of the clinical trial. But the agency ultimately determined that the potential of slowing the devastating disease in patients with mild cognitive impairment outweighs the risks of brain bleeds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dc7ed10-389d-11ef-bfd1-0000a1aceb70</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Joe Manchin III threatened to break with Biden after the president’s debate performance before senior Democrats intervened</title>
      <description>The West Virginia senator intended to break with Biden on a Sunday news show, a high-profile defection that would have underscored Biden’s weakness had senior Democrats not helped dissuade Manchin from doing so. Manchin is an independent who caucuses with the Democrats and would have been the first elected official allied with Democrats to break with Biden. On Tuesday, however, Rep. Lloyd Doggett (D-Tex.) became the first sitting House member to urge Biden to step aside, saying in a statement that “too much is at stake to risk a Trump victory.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c6ae030-3899-11ef-8ed1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 17:35:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rudy Giuliani disbarred in New York for efforts to overturn 2020 election</title>
      <description>A state appeals court found that Giuliani, as a personal attorney to former president Donald Trump, “flagrantly misused his prominent position.” The panel said that Giuliani, a former prosecutor and former mayor of New York, repeatedly made false statements to courts and lawmakers about the election and that he “baselessly attacked and undermined the integrity of this country’s electoral process.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d433540-388d-11ef-87e2-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does ambivalence about parenthood mean you shouldn’t have kids?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does ambivalence about parenthood mean you shouldn’t have kids?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8987f3e0-388c-11ef-a2e1-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 16:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s July 11 sentencing in N.Y. hush money case may be postponed in light of Supreme Court immunity ruling</title>
      <description>The former president asked a judge to postpone the sentencing for his 34 felony convictions, arguing that Monday’s Supreme Court ruling on presidential immunity could invalidate some of the evidence used in the Manhattan trial this spring. On Tuesday, the Manhattan district attorney told the judge he would not oppose a delay in sentencing, increasing the likelihood the July 11 sentencing date will be pushed back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6bcf30-3888-11ef-8554-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 15:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 70 people were killed in northern India during a stampede at a religious event, local officials say</title>
      <description>While the cause of the stampede was not immediately clear to authorities, a district official told local television reporters that “stuffiness” triggered it. Weather conditions hit 90 degrees and 77 percent humidity in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39914f30-3878-11ef-88fc-0000a1ace02c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This person tries to bounce back in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bb98d90-3877-11ef-afe8-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Beryl is the earliest on record to reach Category 5 in the Atlantic. Here’s where it is expected to hit next.</title>
      <description>Beryl is expected to gradually weaken in the days ahead, but the National Hurricane Center still expects “life-threatening winds and storm surge” in Jamaica on Wednesday, as well as probable impacts in Mexico’s Yucatán Peninsula by Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a966a60-3876-11ef-b95e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 13:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump immunity. Hurricane Beryl. Khan Younis. Karen Read. Turbulence. Forecast accuracy. Prosthesis breakthrough. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b2585c0-3862-11ef-af32-0000a1ace6f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden blasts the Supreme Court for decision on presidential immunity</title>
      <description>Biden, speaking from the White House, issued a blistering attack on the high court for its decision earlier in the day declaring that Donald Trump was immune from prosecution for official acts he took during his presidency. Biden said that the high court was setting a dangerous new precedent that could fundamentally change the world’s most powerful office.
“For all practical purposes, today’s decision almost certainly means that there are virtually no limits on what the president can do,” Biden said, adding that he pledges “to respect the limits of the presidential powers.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a28b20-3810-11ef-8bde-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2024 01:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal court blocks Biden’s pause on approving new gas export projects</title>
      <description>The decision by a federal judge in Louisiana represents the latest legal setback to the president’s climate agenda. Republican attorneys general from 16 states had sued over the administration's action, calling it federal overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb16e150-3802-11ef-b9f0-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 23:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A victory for once and future presidents, and other takeaways from Trump immunity ruling by Supreme Court</title>
      <description>Capping a string of bad days for Democrats, Monday’s decision by the high court makes further Trump trials unlikely before the 2024 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94a84c0-37e6-11ef-a910-0000a1ace9c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 20:16:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistrial declared in Karen Read trial on charges of murdering her Boston police officer boyfriend</title>
      <description>A jury was deadlocked after nearly five days of deliberations in the case of Read, who was accused of fatally striking John O’Keefe with her car amid a volatile romance. It’s unclear whether prosecutors will seek to retry Read, who has maintained she was being framed by police officers to protect another potential suspect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccd2cce0-37da-11ef-9c63-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 18:50:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Snowflake’ asks in-laws not to fight in front of their grandkid</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Snowflake’ asks in-laws not to fight in front of their grandkid</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61841ae0-37c4-11ef-ae16-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 16:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FTC opens investigation into Teva over ‘junk patent listings,’ a significant escalation of Democrats’ fight with pharma industry</title>
      <description>The agency is demanding internal communications, analysis and financial data related to Teva’s contested patents for asthma and COPD inhalers. Top Democrats have accused Teva and other companies of gaming the patent system and inflating patient costs by blocking generic competition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38258941-37bf-11ef-b154-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court tells lower courts to take another look at Texas, Florida social media laws barring platforms from deleting content</title>
      <description>The justices said lower courts had not conducted a proper analysis of the free speech issues in the laws governing social media content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03604eb0-37bb-11ef-a345-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 15:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says presidents have ‘absolute’ immunity for clearly official acts, but no immunity for unofficial acts</title>
      <description>Former president and presumptive Republican nominee Donald Trump faces four federal felony counts in D.C. for allegedly trying to undo Joe Biden’s 2020 election victory. The high court’s 6-3 ruling sends the case back to the lower court to determine when and whether Trump will go to trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e61f480-37b7-11ef-ac01-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 14:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to rule on presidential immunity, impacting Trump’s D.C. election-interference trial. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>On the final day of a momentous term, the Supreme Court will rule on whether Donald Trump may be shielded from prosecution for any of the acts alleged in his federal election-interference case. The ruling will determine whether and how soon he stands trial in D.C., and it could impact his other criminal cases. The justices also will rule on whether states can bar social media companies from removing certain political posts or accounts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2085dbf0-37b0-11ef-8432-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A toothless dog is crowned champion in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to kick off July with points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">320ec280-37ae-11ef-8470-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden campaign. Trump immunity. French elections. Hurricane Beryl. Gaza hospitals. Math scores. Simone Biles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d5f330-3799-11ef-afd5-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
