<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:02:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Robots are learning to make human babies. Twenty have already been born.</title>
      <description>According to the World Health Organization, one in six adults experiences infertility. Can groundbreaking automation help answer their prayers?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">542ce290-9f16-11f0-887d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House fires much of the National Council on the Humanities</title>
      <description>Fired council members described the terminations as abrupt. An agency website listed only four Trump appointees remaining on the board, which advises the National Endowment for the Humanities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3cb8ad0-9efe-11f0-a5a2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jane Goodall dies at 91. Her long-term study of wild chimpanzees led her to see them as individuals.</title>
      <description>Jane Goodall’s startling observations about chimpanzee behaviors — from making tools to making war — revolutionized not only scientific understanding of the capabilities and inner lives of our simian cousins, but also long-held notions about what it means to be human.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7da31780-9ef2-11f0-a687-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Bonding over estranged daughters now feels like a competition</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Bonding over estranged daughters now feels like a competition</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10a88d70-9ee0-11f0-91b2-000a1ace93d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plans widespread random polygraph testing and nondisclosure agreements to stanch leaks</title>
      <description>The Pentagon is planning to require thousands of uniformed officials and civilian personnel to sign nondisclosure agreements and submit to random polygraph testing, according to two officials and documents obtained by The Washington Post. The moves come as Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth ramps up restrictions on media and a war on leakers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa5fa010-9edc-11f0-bc23-000a1ace5fc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How our critic decides where to eat</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How our critic decides where to eat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f484520-9edc-11f0-a446-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Lisa Cook to stay on Fed Board for now</title>
      <description>The justices denied President Donald Trump’s request to allow him to remove Cook immediately. The court will hear arguments in the case later this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df2a3d50-9ed7-11f0-b2e6-0000a1ace120</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 100,000-mile check-up in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7c7d530-9eca-11f0-9388-0000a1aced81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 13:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government shutdown. Pete Hegseth. Drug prices. Abortion pills. Comedy controversy. Delivery bots. Fat Bear Week. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccb616c0-9eb5-11f0-aa8f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They scaled the equivalent of Mt. Everest in 36 hours, carrying with them scars, belief, bricks and the memory of a 3-year-old boy</title>
      <description>For most, the pull was less about prizes than about something deeper. For them, the mountain is a metaphor — a physical challenge, but also a mental and spiritual trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8aa729c1-9e62-11f0-a0f1-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 01:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House withdraws the nomination of E.J. Antoni to run the Bureau of Labor Statistics</title>
      <description>Trump nominated Antoni after firing the previous BLS chief, after he accused her of manipulating jobs report data, which came in weaker than expected. Antoni’s nomination appeared uncertain in the Senate, which had yet to schedule a confirmation hearing. A White House official said that the administration looked forward to nominating a new candidate soon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a63ea10-9e60-11f0-959e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The government will shut down at 12:01 a.m., after Senate Democrats blocked a Republican bill to extend the funding deadline</title>
      <description>It’s the first shutdown since 2018-2019. Democrats say they won’t vote to fund the government unless Republicans agree to extend expiring health care subsidies. The GOP says Democrats are holding the government hostage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14e70010-9e54-11f0-911f-0000a1ace485</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORRECTION: The Trump administration illegally arrested and sought to deport international students for their pro-Palestinian activism, judge rules. A previous alert incorrectly stated that the students in the case were deported.</title>
      <description>A previous alert headline incorrectly stated the Trump administration had illegally deported international students for their pro-Palestinian activism. No students in the case have yet been deported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7b9cbb0-9e2b-11f0-abf4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration illegally arrested and deported international students for their pro-Palestinian activism, judge rules</title>
      <description>In a blistering rebuke of the administration, U.S. District Judge William Young said that the push to deport noncitizens for their activism against Israel's war in Gaza was a “truly scandalous and unconstitutional suppression of free speech.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e6e65e0-9e25-11f0-bfea-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump delivers highly partisan presentation at unprecedented gathering to U.S. military leaders who remained mostly silent</title>
      <description>The hastily organized event became a forum for President Donald Trump to tout his political agenda while Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth lectured the brass on standards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee1785f0-9e1b-11f0-bf84-0000a1ace8b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is insomnia putting you at a higher risk of dementia? Ask our brain health expert.</title>
      <description>Richard Sima is chatting with readers about how to reduce your risk of dementia. Send in your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cb2bc30-9e10-11f0-bf97-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropping out in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d15d1660-9e01-11f0-a5bf-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth begins his address to senior military leaders; Trump expected to follow. See our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The extraordinary meeting with hundreds of senior U.S. military officers at Marine Corps Base Quantico in Virginia was ordered by Hegseth last week, requiring some top generals and admirals to fly thousands of miles on short notice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dd7da00-9df7-11f0-b9f3-0000a1ace6b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. Military meeting. Gaza plan. Stranded aid. YouTube settlement. Dangerous heat. Landlines. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6089b70-9dec-11f0-89d0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will mining destroy America’s most-visited wilderness?</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is moving quickly to approve a mine next to the Boundary Waters that many fear will pollute the pristine wilderness area in Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e301fc0-9d94-11f0-9f6e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lally Weymouth dies at 82. The Post journalist, a member of the storied Graham family, interviewed presidents and prime ministers.</title>
      <description>As the granddaughter, daughter, sister and mother of five different Washington Post publishers, Weymouth moved in social circles that helped shape American media and government.
While her younger brother Donald E. Graham was tapped to succeed their mother, Katharine Graham, as publisher of The Post in the 1970s, Weymouth initially pursued a career outside the paper. She joined The Post in 1986, eventually rising to become a senior associate editor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83d191d0-9d8b-11f0-9f6e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Military leaders have raised concerns over Hegseth’s new Pentagon strategy, exposing divide among officials ahead of defense summit</title>
      <description>The critiques from multiple top officers, including Gen. Dan Caine, chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, come as Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth reorders U.S. military priorities — focusing the Pentagon on perceived threats to the homeland, narrowing competition with China, and downplaying America’s role in Europe and Africa, according to people familiar with the classified planning document.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">249a7220-9d88-11f0-938d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTube will pay $24.5 million to settle Trump lawsuit over company’s decision in 2021 to remove his account after Jan. 6 attack</title>
      <description>The agreement says that President Donald Trump has directed YouTube to contribute $22 million of the settlement to help construct the new White House ballroom. The rest of the money will go to a handful of other plaintiffs who accused YouTube of censoring them. The settlement follows similar deals earlier this year with social platforms Meta and X, which also suspended or blocked Trump’s accounts after the Jan. 6, 2021, attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b74cbe00-9d80-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu agrees to Trump peace deal. If Hamas refuses, Trump offers Israel full support to keep fighting.</title>
      <description>The plan, which is subject to approval by Hamas, would require an immediate ceasefire as well as the release of all remaining Israeli hostages within 72 hours of both sides agreeing to the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82d0ab0-9d66-11f0-a9a2-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding for federal agencies expires tomorrow night. Here's how this potential shutdown may differ from previous ones.</title>
      <description>Broad swaths of the federal government — from national parks to small business loans to taxpayer services — could go offline this week unless lawmakers and President Donald Trump strike a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c70b8830-9d58-11f0-9a38-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent feels awkward posting baby but not stepchild on social feed</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26144d41-9d4e-11f0-973c-0000a1ace5f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader John Thune writes: Democrats, let’s avoid this shutdown</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7d13c70-9d48-11f0-af6a-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing work from this platform in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4352b60-9d38-11f0-a4a3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Church shooting. Government shutdown. Military meeting. Portland troops. Gaza plan. Tropical Storm. Bad Bunny. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71504eb0-9d23-11f0-a9d5-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe retains the Ryder Cup, holding off the United States at Bethpage Black</title>
      <description>The European team secured the trophy Sunday on Long Island, claiming the Ryder Cup on U.S. soil for the first time since 2012. The Americans fell into a massive hole Friday and Saturday and could not recover despite a strong Sunday surge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7f1f530-9cb0-11f0-a752-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Mayor Eric Adams says he is ending his reelection bid</title>
      <description>The incumbent has faced pressure — particularly from the Trump administration — to quit his bid and coalesce more support around former New York governor Andrew M. Cuomo. Cuomo is running as an independent candidate against the Republican nominee Curtis Sliwa and the Democratic nominee and front-runner Zohran Mamdani.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cc9fe72-9c95-11f0-9a95-0000a1ace037</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 person killed, several injured in shooting at Mormon church in Michigan, police say. The suspect is also dead.</title>
      <description>A local police chief said a man rammed a vehicle through the front doors of a Mormon church in Grand Blanc, Michigan, before opening fire. Officials did not identify the suspect by name or describe a motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c594620-9c92-11f0-8d94-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59aef620-9c84-11f0-9563-0000a1aceff4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to attend gathering of top generals, upending last-minute plans</title>
      <description>Hundreds of top military officers and staff have been summoned to Virginia on short notice for a speech by Pete Hegseth. President Donald Trump decided this weekend to attend the meeting, adding new security concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f047600-9c78-11f0-a2ec-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4a7b5a0-9c6f-11f0-9f1d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House considers funding advantage for colleges that align with Trump policies</title>
      <description>The proposal could transform the government’s vast research funding operation, which has long awarded university grants based on scientific merit. Officials hope to launch it within a few months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f762110-9c6c-11f0-a86a-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:10:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Administration's 21-point proposal leaves door open for a Palestinian state</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's 21-point plan, which was obtained by The Washington Post, outlines an agreement for Hamas disarmament, an international security force and a “Trump development plan” to rebuild the shattered enclave. But Israel might balk at some proposals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fe95050-9c06-11f0-a056-0000a1ace1f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump deploys troops to Portland, authorizing ‘full force’ if necessary</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump announced Saturday that he was sending troops to Portland, Oregon, and to immigration detention facilities around the country, escalating a campaign to use the U.S. military against Americans that has little modern precedent. It was not immediately clear whether Trump was ordering solely a National Guard deployment or a broader military operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f817c80-9bb3-11f0-9063-0000a1aced1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 15:07:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Weather Service at ‘breaking point’ as storm approaches</title>
      <description>Staffing cuts under the Trump administration mean forecasters are struggling to maintain normal operations just as wildfires ramp up in the West and the Atlantic hurricane season peaks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd261980-9baf-11f0-8bee-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 14:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18331fa0-9ba8-11f0-916b-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 13:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“I went nose-to-nose with a mountain lion. It was scary — and magical,” Post columnist writes.</title>
      <description>Mountain lions used to range across the entire continental U.S., but now they are limited to the west coast. Returning these carnivores east of the Mississippi could help maintain entire ecosystems by keeping animals lower down the food chain in check, limiting invasive species, reducing fire danger, boosting biodiversity and even potentially combating climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3054c1e0-9b2d-11f0-b3ee-000a1ace5879</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 23:04:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexstar stations will join Sinclair in broadcasting Jimmy Kimmel again, bringing him back to his former full audience</title>
      <description>Kimmel's show was pulled off the air by ABC following comments the late-night host made on the killing of Charlie Kirk, but was restored on Tuesday, while Nexstar and Sinclair stations continued to boycott the program until today. The reinstating of Kimmel's show to Nexstar and Sinclair stations brings him back to his former audience following the controversy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29fa65a0-9b20-11f0-9fb7-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 21:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for Trump administration to freeze billions in foreign aid for now</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a preliminary injunction from a federal judge who found the president had usurped Congress’s power of the purse by refusing to spend roughly $4 billion it had budgeted for food, medicine and development around the world. The ruling is a victory for the president’s push to exert greater control over federal spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad18eec1-9b1b-11f0-a3c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sinclair will bring Jimmy Kimmel back to its ABC affiliate stations, ending boycott that began after his Charlie Kirk comments</title>
      <description>Sinclair Broadcast Group will end its boycott of the late-night talk show this evening in roughly 30 markets, including D.C. This move comes more than a week after Kimmel’s comments about the shooting of Kirk angered supporters of the conservative activist and following ABC reinstating the program Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed9a78e0-9b09-11f0-9d7f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:52:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details emerge about Pete Hegseth’s unusual order to gather top generals and admirals for ‘warrior ethos’ speech</title>
      <description>The defense secretary has summoned hundreds of top military brass to fly in from around the world for what is planned as a short address on the “warrior ethos,” according to multiple people familiar with the order to gather in-person at the Quantico Marine Corps base in Virginia on Tuesday. The Pentagon has refused to comment on the nature of the meeting, alarming and confusing top military officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbb3a660-9b02-11f0-b748-000a1acef2b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: We visited my in-laws. Their ‘lousy hosting’ was insulting.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: We visited my in-laws. Their ‘lousy hosting’ was insulting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e2feab0-9afa-11f0-aca1-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Barnett dies at 79. The Washington lawyer was a consummate political insider, with clients on both sides of the aisle.</title>
      <description>Barnett, a partner at Williams &amp; Connolly, represented corporations as well as public officials, many of whom he helped transition into the private sector.

He served as Hillary Clinton’s personal attorney beginning in 1992 and represented clients including Washington Post journalist Bob Woodward, former vice president Dan Quayle and Democratic strategist James Carville.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56b8fa0-9aee-11f0-9fb7-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager. It’s your weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73189221-9adf-11f0-b3c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:48:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After U.S. strikes, Iran is increasing work at a mysterious underground site, according to a Post review of satellite imagery</title>
      <description>The work is at a site known as Pickaxe Mountain, where since 2020, Iranian engineers have been tunneling deep into the Zagros mountain range — about a mile south of the nuclear complex at Natanz, which was a target of U.S. bombing strikes in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5ad39e0-9ad0-11f0-b955-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Comey. New tariffs. Pete Hegseth. Iran nuclear site. Amazon refund. Tropical Storm Humberto. Ancient human. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e80bca1-9ac8-11f0-be6e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 11:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
