<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 02:28:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan measure to block Trump’s lethal strikes against alleged Venezuelan drug smugglers fails in Senate</title>
      <description>Democrats called the administration’s strikes unconstitutional but were unable to persuade enough Republicans to vote for a restraining measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbe9b440-a4a9-11f0-bb6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hamas agree to peace deal to begin ending war in Gaza, Trump says</title>
      <description>The president’s announcement says the agreement includes the release of hostages by Hamas and the withdrawal of Israeli troops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87895330-a49d-11f0-8d85-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best restaurants in and around D.C.</title>
      <description>Washington Post food critic Tom Sietsema celebrates, one last time, some of the many places that make D.C. one of the best food cities in the country — starting with a Top 5 list. His restaurant of the year: Albi, the Levantine jewel that just keeps getting better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a610ff0-a492-11f0-9099-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 22:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s sprawling hunt for Charlie Kirk critics spans nearly 300 investigations</title>
      <description>The inquiry, resulting in a smattering of disciplinary action so far, follows an extraordinary Pentagon directive aimed at silencing criticism of the slain activist and Trump supporter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4f02f0-a47d-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quarter of FBI agents have been assigned to immigration enforcement, internal data shows</title>
      <description>The intense focus on immigration has raised alarm among current and former FBI agents who say morale is low across the bureau as agents have less time to dedicate to national security, white-collar crime and complex cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">409d6b40-a476-11f0-8e3e-0000a1ace64f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for allegedly starting L.A.-area Palisades Fire that killed 12 people in January, officials say</title>
      <description>Jonathan Rinderknecht, a 29-year-old from Florida, was charged with destruction of property by means of fire, authorities said at a news conference. The fire burned more than 23,000 acres in the area before being contained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f71bac0-a462-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ffb8a0-a460-11f0-b1d0-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</title>
      <description>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">774763d2-a458-11f0-b9fa-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James Comey makes first court appearance and pleads not guilty in case roiling Justice Department</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has opened several criminal investigations into President Donald Trump’s perceived foes in what legal experts and retired judges have described as an unprecedented attack on the rule of law. Comey is the first former senior government official to be charged as part of Trump’s efforts, but the case against him has been fraught for years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd71e9e1-a452-11f0-81ef-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pynchonian elements in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22c31c80-a44b-11f0-875f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They say they can’t walk or see. Meet the veterans defrauding the government.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found that the Department of Veterans Affairs’s $193 billion disability program has turned into a rich target for fraudsters. Some of them fake blindness or paralysis to get as much as $1 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e4f88b0-a43e-11f0-a0f2-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight delays. Supreme Court. Troop deployments. Gaza rescue. Storm tracker. AI pessimism. Bob Ross. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ee0cc0-a435-11f0-995f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel in chemistry awarded to trio researching metal-organic frameworks, a kind of molecular scaffolding with wide implications</title>
      <description>The Nobel Prize winners were Susumu Kitagawa of Kyoto University in Japan, Richard Robson of the University of Melbourne in Australia and Omar Yaghi of the University of California at Berkeley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a01bb040-a430-11f0-98d8-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TikTok keeps its users scrolling for hours a day</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters analyzed data from more than 800 TikTok users to learn how the app turns people into power users, some of whom spend hours per day scrolling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cccc9c0-a3d7-11f0-a65b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six surgeons general write in an op-ed: It’s our duty to warn the nation about RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>We took an oath to declare dangers when we found them. We’re doing that again today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a8e3321-a3aa-11f0-a949-000a1ace22b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears deeply skeptical of Colorado law that bans conversion therapy for gay and transgender minors</title>
      <description>A majority of justices appeared sympathetic to an evangelical therapist whose attorney argued that the state ban infringes on the therapist’s free-speech rights to counsel religious teens dealing with their sexual orientation and gender dysphoria in ways she said are consistent with biblical teachings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c44cbf0-a39f-11f0-bd46-000a1ace63c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal workers are not entitled to back pay after shutdown, White House budget office argues in memo</title>
      <description>The top lawyer at the Office of Management and Budget argued in a draft memo obtained by The Washington Post that a law Congress passed and President Donald Trump signed in 2019 does not guarantee back pay to furloughed workers, ratcheting up tensions in Washington over the week-long shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7512af1-a399-11f0-84ea-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Twin teens don’t want to meet their widowed parent’s new love</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Twin teens don’t want to meet their widowed parent’s new love</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05d8cd0-a396-11f0-8ca3-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE has kept most offices open during the government shutdown — but not the one inspecting conditions at detention centers</title>
      <description>Immigration and Customs Enforcement’s entire Office of Detention Oversight has been placed on furlough, despite surging numbers of detainees. The contrast between the office’s temporary closure and the ongoing immigration crackdown highlights how the Trump administration’s priorities have steered ICE’s operations during the funding impasse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9294dc20-a391-11f0-95db-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70441a0-a386-11f0-b403-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 14:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sietsema says goodbye after 25 years. And we finally reveal what our food critic looks like.</title>
      <description>He’s written hundreds of restaurant reviews and thousands of reader Q&amp;As and somehow never had his face appear online before now. Far from retiring, Tom plans to cook more and stay connected with fellow food enthusiasts -- and has some suggestions for getting more out of your restaurant experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9cc6af1-a375-11f0-afec-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Oct. 7 anniversary. Pam Bondi. Covid shots. Everest rescue. TikTok addiction. Food critic reveal. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bef247f0-a36c-11f0-847c-000a1ace3410</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel in physics awarded to scientists showing quantum mechanics on a macro scale</title>
      <description>John Clarke, Michel Devoret and John Martinis shared the prize for demonstrating quantum mechanics on a new scale, used in today’s phones, computer, cameras and fiber optic cables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7422e470-a36a-11f0-973d-0000a1ace551</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slashed university funding. Here are six key drugs that relied on it.</title>
      <description>The Post examined six major drugs tied to federally funded research, which is now under threat at universities nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b040c10-a2f7-11f0-9a11-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 21:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These photos show what it looks like in the world’s data center capital</title>
      <description>These photos show what it looks like in the world’s data center capital</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6de5740-a2cf-11f0-b0bf-0000a1ace16b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s arguments can end only when boyfriend decides he’s done</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s arguments can end only when boyfriend decides he’s done</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d321abc0-a2cd-11f0-b6e9-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court won’t hear Ghislaine Maxwell’s appeal</title>
      <description>Maxwell, an associate of deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein, was convicted of sex trafficking in 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a23b560-a2bc-11f0-a250-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing is real on this new app in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9708bda0-a2b8-11f0-a250-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA spends billions on dubious, even fraudulent disabilities benefits</title>
      <description>Military veterans are swamping the U.S. government with dubious disability claims — including cases of brazen fraud totaling tens of millions of dollars — that are exploiting the country’s sacred commitment to compensate those harmed in the line of duty, according to a Washington Post investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98d70b71-a2ac-11f0-944b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Gaza talks. Unusual shutdown. Supreme Court. Disability benefits. Ozempic at Costco. SNL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6ff4e0-a2a3-11f0-a0f6-0000a1ace1d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize for medicine awarded for discoveries about the immune system</title>
      <description>Mary E. Brunkow, Fred Ramsdell and Shimon Sakaguchi shared the Nobel Prize for fundamental discoveries in how the immune system keeps itself in check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec596ec0-a29b-11f0-8c32-0000a1ace806</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks California National Guard members from deploying to Oregon</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Karin J. Immergut said the government appeared to be directly defying her previous order by instead sending members of California’s Guard. She broadened the terms of her restraining order to prohibit the administration from sending any state’s National Guard troops to Oregon. Immergut, a Trump appointee confirmed to the bench in 2019, issued a new, broader order Sunday to prohibit the administration from sending any state’s National Guard troops under federal control to Oregon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">530b06b0-a26a-11f0-86c3-0000a1acec44</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 04:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions spike in Chicago, Portland as Trump faces legal challenges over troop use</title>
      <description>California will sue the Trump administration, Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) said, over plans to send 300 state National Guard troops to Oregon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25a66e10-a221-11f0-9cf6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They grew up unvaccinated. After age 18, they faced a choice.</title>
      <description>Some who received little to no vaccination in childhood sought out the shots themselves in adulthood — and risked family relationships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">868af3d0-a21d-11f0-9f12-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">990d25f0-a204-11f0-b2d7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 16:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b156d940-a1ef-11f0-87b3-0000a1ace9b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 13:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plan would limit Social Security disability benefits for older Americans</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is preparing a plan that will make it harder for older Americans to qualify for Social Security disability payments, part of an overhaul of the federal safety net for poor, older and disabled people that could result in hundreds of thousands of people losing benefits, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98ef1cd0-a1e7-11f0-9285-0000a1acec20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 12:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks Trump from deploying troops in Portland</title>
      <description>Oregon officials had challenged President Donald Trump’s move to send troops to the state’s largest city, calling it “patently unlawful.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53cfae0-a17e-11f0-9c5e-0000a1ace7fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medical Mysteries: A high-schooler with hip pain, then a life-threatening diagnosis</title>
      <description>One doctor told her the hip pain was a twisted pelvis. Another said the pain was just in her head.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71ac9630-a15a-11f0-b74d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 19:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This billionaire Trump ally and his son are building an unprecedented media empire</title>
      <description>Larry and David Ellison’s holdings span movies, TV networks, CBS and soon a stake in TikTok, in a paradigm shifting portfolio with huge influence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04e49a61-a133-11f0-bb4e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a62287d1-a128-11f0-a020-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many American Jews sharply critical of Israel on Gaza, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>Most said Israel is committing war crimes — and 39 percent said genocide — while often distinguishing between the country and its leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebd6c1a0-a124-11f0-bef3-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 13:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanae Takaichi is set to become Japan’s first female prime minister</title>
      <description>The new leader will take the helm of the world’s fourth-largest economy at a time of unusual political instability, rising prices and increasing regional tensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40353110-a0e8-11f0-994d-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 06:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Kavanaugh assassination plotter sentenced to eight years in prison</title>
      <description>Nicholas Roske, 29, had flown across the country, with a gun packed in a suitcase, intending to break into the justice’s Maryland home to kill him. The punishment was 22 years less than the minimum of 30 years sought by prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cdd3d40-a0a4-11f0-8440-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 22:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs sentenced to 50 months in prison</title>
      <description>The judge will also fine Combs $500,000, and impose five years of supervised release once he completes his sentence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">973bd060-a09b-11f0-9f17-0000a1aceb72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas accepts Trump’s plan to end Israel’s war in Gaza but with conditions</title>
      <description>The plan aims to secure the release of Israeli hostages held in the Gaza Strip and end a two-year conflict that has reduced much of the enclave to rubble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97d3d960-a095-11f0-88f2-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 20:14:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. kills four more alleged drug smugglers near Venezuela, Hegseth says</title>
      <description>Questions remain as to the legal justification underpinning the administration’s ongoing attacks targeting Latin American drug cartels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6253ed40-a084-11f0-84f2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrat Abigail Spanberger holds wide lead in Virginia governor’s race, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Spanberger leads Republican Winsome Earle-Sears by double digits in the contest for governor, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll of Virginia voters, picking up strong support from independent voters as well as those who are worried about the state’s job market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13984a80-a079-11f0-a614-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I handle my mother-in-law correcting my kids?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I handle my mother-in-law correcting my kids?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">deb128b0-a077-11f0-b58e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean “Diddy” Combs to be sentenced and is expected to speak in court for first time since his arrest. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Prosecutors want the music producer to be imprisoned for more than 11 years following his conviction in the prostitution case, arguing at trial earlier this year that he used beatings, blackmail and drugs to abuse two girlfriends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb83c9d0-a066-11f0-8330-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 14:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
