<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 11:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ICE memo outlines plan to deport migrants to countries where they are not citizens</title>
      <description>Federal immigration officers may deport immigrants with as little as six hours’ notice to countries other than their own even if officials have not provided any assurances that the new arrivals will be safe from persecution or torture, a top official said in a memo this week. The dramatic shift in policy could result in thousands of people being sent to places where they lack family ties or even a common language.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ab604d0-5f87-11f0-ad55-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 01:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He knows he was adopted from South Korea. When he started digging into his past, red flags emerged.</title>
      <description>For years, Aaron Grzegorczyk thought his birth mother had left him at a South Korean clinic in 1988. A recent report found the country had allowed a “profit-driven” adoption “industry” to flourish for decades, leaving Grzegorczyk wondering whether he’s yet another victim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b873291-5f6f-11f0-9ed1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 22:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech billionaire Marc Andreesen says colleges will ‘pay the price’ for DEI, according to private group chat with Trump officials</title>
      <description>Andreessen co-founded one of Silicon Valley’s most prominent venture capital firms, Andreessen Horowitz, which embraced Donald Trump’s candidacy last year. While Elon Musk was the most visible tech mogul in Trump’s orbit until he split with the president, Andreessen has quietly helped shape the administration’s hiring and policy decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72f11fc0-5f51-11f0-a399-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 18:53:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iga Swiatek defeats Amanda Anisimova to win first Wimbledon championship and sixth Grand Slam title</title>
      <description>The 24-year old Swiatek, a former world No. 1 from Poland, has never lost a Grand Slam championship match. It was the first appearance in a Grand Slam final for the American Anisimova, who upset top-seeded Aryna Sabalenka in the semifinals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05726e60-5f3b-11f0-acaa-0000a1ace985</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 16:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I dread my bigoted mother-in-law’s weekly lunches</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I dread my bigoted mother-in-law’s weekly lunches</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7e2a0a0-5f38-11f0-b4cb-0000a1acec12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 15:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the dark, a teen counselor at Camp Mystic led 16 girls to safety: ‘Get ready to climb’</title>
      <description>Ainslie Bashara, 19, had arrived a week earlier for a month-long stay. She’d met campers from the Giggle Box cabin just five days earlier but had already grown devoted to them. Together they braved the relentless Texas floodwaters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d27220e0-5f2c-11f0-a89e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he’s ready to slap 30% tariffs on imports from Mexico and European Union starting Aug. 1</title>
      <description>The latest move is likely to disrupt relationships following weeks of negotiations with two of the United States’ largest trading partners. Over the past week, President Donald Trump has sent letters to various world leaders about new levies he is readying to impose on imports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11408650-5f27-11f0-940f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:49:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8fb2ca0-5f24-11f0-aead-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 13:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders halt to Trump administration’s indiscriminate immigration stops and arrests in California</title>
      <description>A federal judge ordered the Trump administration to stop patrolling and rounding up individuals without reasonable justification, including basing arrests on racial profiling, and to stop denying access to lawyers, saying the tactics are unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94e93cc0-5ecf-11f0-bb1e-0000a1ace396</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 03:23:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas county didn't use its most powerful and far-reaching alert system as floods grew deadly on July 4</title>
      <description>A Washington Post examination found Kerr County officials eventually sent text-message alerts on the morning of July 4 to some residents. But even as conditions deteriorated, they did not activate a more forceful tool that would have sounded an alarm on cellphones throughout the river valley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90692920-5e9e-11f0-8c51-0000a1ace218</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Gergen dies at 83. The consummate political insider held communications jobs under Nixon, Ford, Reagan and Clinton.</title>
      <description>Gergen, a conservative-leaning centrist, helped craft and protect the image of four presidents as a senior White House communications adviser and held high-profile jobs in TV punditry and academia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1f49d40-5e9a-11f0-8bd0-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 21:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unexpected fuel cutoff preceded Air India plane crash, preliminary report says</title>
      <description>Indian investigators’ initial findings suggest that both engines stopped receiving fuel shortly after takeoff, but a final determination by the government’s Aircraft Accident Investigation Bureau into the cause of the crash is likely more than a year away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d867cf80-5e97-11f0-9596-0000a1aceb3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 20:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Trump staffers behind the push to overhaul higher education</title>
      <description>Shaped by experiences as ideological minorities on liberal campuses, these officials are targeting their alma maters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53a79460-5e88-11f0-8150-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Father-in-law destroyed the garden I inherited from my dying mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Father-in-law destroyed the garden I inherited from my dying mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13cc4710-5e73-11f0-a31d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Army combat veteran may have stopped Trump’s would-be assassin. Now he’s telling his story.</title>
      <description>Butler County SWAT team operator Aaron Zaliponi fired the “ninth shot” at Donald Trump’s Pennsylvania rally last July. He believes it hit the shooter’s rifle, but one year later, the significance of his quick action is still unresolved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61489ff0-5e66-11f0-b27a-0000a1acec85</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department is firing more than 1,300 employees by email in downsizing plan</title>
      <description>The move has come under criticism from current and former diplomats who say the cuts will degrade America’s standing in the world and curb U.S. soft power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37cd1b00-5e62-11f0-a99a-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 14:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872f6331-5e5b-11f0-94ad-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump shooting anniversary. Texas visit. Federal layoffs. Birthright citizenship. Wimbledon. AI videos. Jan. 6 show. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e491af0-5e46-11f0-b39a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 35% tariffs on Canada, injecting fresh turmoil into a strained bilateral relationship</title>
      <description>The levy sets back Prime Minister Mark Carney’s efforts to negotiate a new economic partnership with the U.S. In a letter, President Donald Trump said the announcement was because of Canada's tariffs on the U.S. and in response to the incoming flow of fentanyl, though there is little evidence the drug is being smuggled across the northern border in significant quantities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57068f90-5e14-11f0-b727-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 05:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Firings without explanation across Justice Dept., FBI have created climate of fear, people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is firing and pushing out employees in multiple departments, creating rampant speculation and worry over who might be terminated next, according to multiple people with knowledge of the removals, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to avoid retribution. The terminations appear more individually targeted than the high-profile ousters of senior Justice Department and FBI officials in the early months of President Donald Trump’s second term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03bc6b00-5dbc-11f0-93ed-000a1acecc10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 18:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A band of innovators reimagines the spy game for a world with no cover</title>
      <description>For spies, there is literally no place to hide. Millions of cameras around the world record every movement and catalogue it forever. Every action leaves digital tracks that can be studied and linked with others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7056420-5dab-11f0-9460-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Daughter-in-law needs help processing child’s new gender identity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Daughter-in-law needs help processing child’s new gender identity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11fe3780-5da7-11f0-b5d7-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge places new block on Trump’s birthright citizenship ban nationwide, in line with Supreme Court ruling</title>
      <description>A federal judge in New Hampshire issued the temporary injunction after agreeing to certify a class-action lawsuit against President Donald Trump’s administration on behalf of U.S.-born children or future children whose automatic citizenship could be jeopardized by the president’s executive order, lawyers for the plaintiffs said. The Supreme Court ruled last month that such nationwide orders apply only in limited circumstances, including class-action lawsuits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6d96500-5d9f-11f0-a6fd-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 15:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tennis fans deserve better than John McEnroe in the broadcast booth, our columnist writes</title>
      <description>McEnroe maintains his grip on tennis microphones, despite a refusal to work at his craft or study the modern game, columnist Sally Jenkins writes. Tennis is a gorgeous game deserving of more eloquence than this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4601b870-5d9a-11f0-9e32-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 14:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actually, you don’t need to remove these in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your daily points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40544bc0-5d92-11f0-b758-0000a1aceb04</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 13:31:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Brazil. Federal firings. Ukraine-Russia shift. Tunnel collapse. Texas search. X CEO. French national hero. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0808b950-5d7d-11f0-9fa4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos and videos show how the Texas flooding surged in a matter of hours and how rescues unfolded</title>
      <description>See how water from the swollen Guadalupe River surged into Camp Mystic and other parts of Kerr County, and how people have searched for and recovered victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b94cfbb1-5d12-11f0-bae7-0000a1acec23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 22:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 50% tariffs on Brazil starting Aug. 1, citing its treatment of former president Jair Bolsonaro</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump scrambled his trade agenda and delivered a broadside against the government of Brazilian President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva over its treatment of Bolsonaro, the former leader who is on trial for trying to overthrow the government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73cedc20-5d0d-11f0-b157-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 21:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flooding and severe thunderstorm watches issued, with worst weather expected toward evening</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service is cautioning that storms could produce locally significant flooding, damaging wind gusts and isolated large hail. Storms are expected to be heavier and more widespread than Tuesday’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5541810-5cf0-11f0-9c42-0000a1ace777</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 18:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think surprise medical bills are in the past? Surprise!</title>
      <description>The surprise medical bills just keep coming</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">542c4f80-5ced-11f0-b335-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 17:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Gay man avoids homophobic brother-in-law. But at what cost?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Gay man avoids homophobic brother-in-law. But at what cost?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee858160-5cdd-11f0-88d4-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 16:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda Yaccarino steps down as CEO of Elon Musk’s X. The resignation comes a day after the Grok chatbot’s antisemitic outbursts.</title>
      <description>Yaccarino announced her departure from the social media site in a post on X, one day after Grok made posts referencing Hitler that were later deleted. She did not provide a reason for her decision. She was hired by Musk to run the social network formerly known as Twitter in 2023, after he acquired the company for $44 billion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe9c7ab0-5cd6-11f0-a7aa-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Can I tip less now that Trump's bill has mostly done away with taxes on gratuity?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Can I tip less now that Trump's bill has mostly done away with taxes on gratuity?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40a0e40-5cd6-11f0-bea5-0000a1ace5cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 15:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s moves on immigration, Ukraine and the Epstein case are roiling the MAGA base</title>
      <description>Some of his most loyal supporters fear President Donald Trump is going back on promises crucial to his political movement. White House officials disputed the idea that the unrest seriously threatens Trump’s support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7a9c780-5ccd-11f0-b822-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 14:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Red spots in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fce84360-5cc8-11f0-a148-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 13:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass firings. Trump vs. Putin. Texas floods. Spy agency logs. Chatbot rant. Airport shoes rule. AI music. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e118ddd0-5cb3-11f0-80d2-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>161 people known to be missing from flooding in Kerr County area, Texas governor says</title>
      <description>Gov. Greg Abbott said the confirmed death toll in the state was 109. The incident is among the deadliest flood events in the past 50 years, shaking the region in a scene that Abbott has described as “nothing short of horrific.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79b45bc0-5c44-11f0-8589-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 21:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to launch mass layoff and restructuring plans at federal agencies, including CDC, Social Security Administration</title>
      <description>The justices lifted a lower-court order that temporarily blocked the plans to fire thousands of workers at 19 agencies and departments while litigation continues. Their order said they were not ruling on the legality of specific firing plans but simply allowing the administration to launch such efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d33b3420-5c35-11f0-b732-000a1ace520d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches in effect into this evening, fueled by sweltering heat and humidity</title>
      <description>Dangerous thunderstorms are possible between about 3 and 8 p.m. In addition to lightning, some storms could contain damaging winds and flooding rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac88cd30-5c24-11f0-adc9-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 17:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In 1956, her father was planning to run for president. She attended Camp Mystic.</title>
      <description>Lynda Bird Johnson Robb recalls how the Texas camp shaped her childhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98290470-5c1c-11f0-9e5b-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to fix dull life with incurious spouse — but not blow it all up</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to fix dull life with incurious spouse — but not blow it all up</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b465f80-5c1a-11f0-87df-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA tests security lines allowing passengers to keep their shoes on at some airports, a change that may be rolled out more widely</title>
      <description>The change in security protocol began at certain airports over the weekend, according to a union official and passenger accounts. TSA officials would not confirm reports Monday that the agency was ending the requirement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c9d8ee0-5c17-11f0-b98d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: What’s next for the Nationals now that they’ve fired their manager and GM? Our reporters are answering your questions.</title>
      <description>How will the last-place Nationals move forward after firing longtime manager Dave Martinez and GM Mike Rizzo? And what went into the decision to make a change now? Post staffers Barry Svrluga, Chelsea Janes and Spencer Nusbaum are answering reader questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5669f11-5c14-11f0-87df-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 16:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team created by Tulsi Gabbard shows interest in spy agencies’ emails, chat logs amid hunt for efforts to undermine Trump’s agenda</title>
      <description>The Director’s Initiative Group has expressed an interest in gaining access to emails and chat logs of the largest U.S. intelligence agencies to root out “weaponization,” according to multiple people familiar with the effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bdd01f0-5c13-11f0-94eb-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to ban Chinese purchases of U.S. farmland, citing national and food security threats</title>
      <description>In a joint news conference with Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth and Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem, Agriculture Department Secretary Brooke Rollins said the administration would work with state partners and pursue executive actions to halt farmland purchases by foreign adversaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26c33100-5c0a-11f0-989b-0000a1ace0cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trending downward in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b46f0c51-5bff-11f0-89a4-0000a1aced75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Marco Rubio impostor using AI has contacted three foreign ministers, a U.S. governor and a member of Congress</title>
      <description>An impostor pretending to be the secretary of state contacted high-level officials by sending them voice and text messages that mimic Rubio’s voice and writing style using artificial intelligence-powered software, according to a senior U.S. official and a State Department cable obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4b01950-5bec-11f0-8dcf-0000a1ace7df</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas floods. Trump’s tariffs. Netanyahu’s gift. Elon Musk. Epstein files. Credit scores. Fateful kisses. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b52ac7c0-5bea-11f0-ac58-0000a1ace38c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Affairs reverses course on large-scale job reductions after promising to cut 83,000 roles</title>
      <description>The agency says it will have reduced the number of staff by the end of fiscal 2025 by approximately 30,000 through hiring freezes, retirements and attrition.

Further cuts to the agency would have brought deep political risks for President Donald Trump, who remains popular with military veterans and has promised to not do anything that would affect their benefits or care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b99c72d0-5b73-11f0-93d7-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 20:48:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals name Miguel Cairo interim manager amid franchise shake-up</title>
      <description>The Nationals announced Cairo would take over as interim manager Monday, one day after ousting Dave Martinez and longtime general manager Mike Rizzo. Cairo, who previously served as Martinez's bench coach, will now guide a Nationals team that includes outfielder James Wood and lefty MacKenzie Gore, two young talents who were named all-stars Sunday. The changes in Washington come amid a long rebuild for the franchise, which has shed its stars in the years since its 2019 World Series triumph.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8993e5b2-5b5e-11f0-b98b-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
