<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 12:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>In shift, Trump says House should vote to release Epstein files</title>
      <description>The president’s reversal came after key lawmakers said Sunday that support is growing in the House for the measure ahead of a closely watched vote this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036f9450-c366-11f0-84d7-000a1ace3079</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA is lifting all flight restrictions imposed during shutdown, restoring full operations at airports</title>
      <description>The restrictions will be lifted Monday, transportation authorities said, after mandating cuts during the shutdown that caused thousands of cancellations and delays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6ae4580-c35b-11f0-a0cb-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 02:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 definitive rules for the airport bar</title>
      <description>If you don’t see a jigger, don’t order a martini — plus more unspoken guidelines from travel pros.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c84fcce0-c348-11f0-b7e3-0000a1ace328</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One man’s obsessive quest to uncover Brazil’s buried Nazi past</title>
      <description>The story of Ibirubá’s fugitive Nazis is clouded by uncertainty and conspiracy theories. But one local journalist is convinced he is closing in on the truth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc729dc0-c330-11f0-a691-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04c76420-c30e-11f0-812c-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP’s plans to replace Obamacare have failed. Here’s what lawmakers propose now.</title>
      <description>Lawmakers are racing toward a mid-December deadline, with Republicans hoping to present side-by-side legislation with Democrats’ plan to extend Affordable Care Act subsidies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ef3740-c30b-11f0-b286-000a1acef338</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 16:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">664f9a60-c2fe-11f0-b220-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How snowy could it be where you live? Look up your area to see whether you’ll have a winter wonderland – or a snow shortage.</title>
      <description>Swaths of central and eastern states have received much less snow than average over the past five winters – a trend that may continue this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e15710-c2f2-11f0-a17e-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 13:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice Wong, disability rights advocate and wordsmith, dies at 51</title>
      <description>Wong was a leader for disabled culture and author of the acclaimed 2022 memoir, “Year of the Tiger: An Activist’s Life.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82ee991-c280-11f0-bbb3-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The Secret Lives of Mormon Wives’ is essential viewing. Seriously.</title>
      <description>The soapy reality show is a perfect mirror of America’s strange cultural moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b937610-c273-11f0-b59e-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 22:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They bought cheap health insurance promoted by the Trump administration. Then they needed surgery.</title>
      <description>Some states have banned “short-term” insurance plans with limited coverage, and consumer advocates have warned of the drawbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57f48b80-c24d-11f0-886e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d82043d1-c22f-11f0-b175-0000a1ace787</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How America’s political unease found its way to a small town in Wisconsin</title>
      <description>In Palmyra, population 1,719, the texture of everyday life is beginning to fray as it grapples with how to deal with ICE — and a threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0e1632-c22b-11f0-99d4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump repeals tariffs he set on some foods as Americans face high grocery prices</title>
      <description>The announcement — which includes agricultural products such as beef, coffee and tomatoes — represents the most significant shift in the “reciprocal tariffs” the president announced in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3253300-c1b9-11f0-8d7d-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein texted lawmaker during Michael Cohen's 2019 congressional hearing, documents show, possibly influencing questions</title>
      <description>Time-stamps on the text messages match with video from the hearing, indicating that Epstein was texting with Del. Stacey Plaskett, a Democrat who represents the U.S. Virgin Islands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e50f3d0-c1a7-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump weighs Venezuela strikes as U.S. forces prepare for attack order</title>
      <description>High-level discussions over whether to attack Venezuela — and how — have been underway for days, according to people familiar with the matter. It remains unclear if President Donald Trump has decided to pursue such an escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c285632-c1a1-11f0-8fb5-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Beam, coach featured in ‘Last Chance U’ series, dies after campus shooting</title>
      <description>Beam, a decorated football coach who was prominent in the Netflix series, died Friday after he was shot Thursday at Laney College in Northern California, the Oakland Police Department said. Authorities have arrested a suspect in the shooting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03f97900-c19e-11f0-8327-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bondi says Justice Dept. will investigate relationships to Epstein as requested by Trump</title>
      <description>Attorney General Pam Bondi indicated that she had appointed a prosecutor to examine the links between deceased sex offender Jeffrey Epstein and prominent Democrats — including Bill Clinton and former treasury chief Larry Summers — who had been identified by the president in a social media post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ac91a0-c19a-11f0-b149-0000a1ace530</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The path to peace in Gaza is coming to a crossroads at the U.N., Ambassador Mike Waltz writes</title>
      <description>The path to peace in Gaza comes to a crossroads at the U.N.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">871001f0-c190-11f0-b306-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Widow never wants to date. Her friends keep trying to set her up.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Widow never wants to date. Her friends keep trying to set her up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">546f9cd0-c184-11f0-9898-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 18:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f25a8950-c166-11f0-8eec-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a frog apocalypse has endangered thousands of people</title>
      <description>An emerging area of research is uncovering hidden connections between biodiversity and illnesses like malaria.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c9ffcc0-c164-11f0-bfba-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA rift. Redistricting battle. Black troops. Family size. Frog apocalypse. Music and dementia. Stumbling robot. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b426331-c151-11f0-943b-000a1ace7d0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani, Aaron Judge are baseball’s historic most valuable players</title>
      <description>Shohei Ohtani of the Los Angeles Dodgers and Aaron Judge of the New York Yankees captured MLB's Most Valuable Player awards, with Judge edging Seattle catcher Cal Raleigh in a very tight vote. Ohtani was a unanimous choice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7505e0e0-c0f7-11f0-a74c-0000a1ace2f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 01:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These Thanksgiving recipes have stood the test of time. We made them even better.</title>
      <description>We combed through The Washington Post’s recipe archives and updated cooking instructions to include more useful details and reflect what we now know thanks to food science and safety, ensuring all but guaranteed success in the kitchen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6be4b40-c0e8-11f0-94ed-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 23:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This rising House Democrat is a voice for the angry middle, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>Why David Ignatius is keeping an eye on the political trajectory of Jason Crow, a veteran of Iraq and Afghanistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebabc130-c0b9-11f0-bb0e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is she ‘terrible’ for not wanting to be close to mother-in-law?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is she ‘terrible’ for not wanting to be close to mother-in-law?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">517b4470-c0b2-11f0-8f19-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIFA will use Kennedy Center free of charge for World Cup draw, contract says, even as ticket revenue declines</title>
      <description>The Kennedy Center’s arrangement with soccer’s international governing body will disrupt its performance schedule, forcing the relocation or postponement of several concerts at an institution that has seen a sharp decline in ticket sales since it was taken over by President Donald Trump earlier this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee5ced90-c0b0-11f0-b0e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrity memoirs in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96af1361-c09d-11f0-9ef0-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settle in for a chilly winter around D.C., but snowfall looks modest</title>
      <description>Our forecast calls for 8 to 14 inches of snow in the D.C. area, and up to a foot and a half in colder spots north and west of the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1e28580-c09c-11f0-a9bf-0000a1aced6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:27:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How and when flights, SNAP benefits, museums will return to normal</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump signed a bill into law Wednesday night to reopen the government after a 43-day stalemate. Here’s what we know so far about what will happen now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9eccd710-c095-11f0-a6d4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown end. Epstein files. Visa rejections. Kennedy Center. Emissions record. AI writing. Last pennies. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">403d2681-c088-11f0-8a41-0000a1ace743</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill to reopen government after longest-ever shutdown</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is expected to sign it into law later Wednesday night. Many federal employees are expected back to work Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dd07b70-c02f-11f0-9713-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 01:23:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the world’s worst hot spots for dangerous rainfall is in the U.S.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation shows why much of Appalachia is increasingly vulnerable to extreme rain and floods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70d49120-c024-11f0-99d0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Adelita Grijalva (D-Arizona) sworn in after 7-week standoff, setting up vote on release of Epstein files</title>
      <description>House Speaker Mike Johnson swore Grijalva into office 50 days after she won the seat her late father held. Her addition to the House is expected to give Democrats the numbers they need to advance a measure demanding that the Justice Department release its files on deceased sex offender Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e8be2d0-c00d-11f0-b3f8-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 21:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The CIA secretly dropped modified poppy seeds in a decades-long mission to sabotage Afghanistan’s billion-dollar opium crop</title>
      <description>The Central Intelligence Agency blanketed Afghan farmers’ fields with seeds that germinated plants containing almost none of the chemicals that are refined into heroin, The Washington Post has learned — a previously unreported chapter in the 2001-2021 U.S. war in Afghanistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13e4e9e0-bff4-11f0-81b8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I lost my big holiday traditions. What now?’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘I lost my big holiday traditions. What now?’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a7a98f0-bfe9-11f0-9765-000a1ace135b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 17:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. troops are not liable in deadly strikes on alleged drug-trafficking boats, classified Justice Department memo says</title>
      <description>The Justice Department’s Office of Legal Counsel stated in a classified opinion drawn up in the summer that personnel taking part in military strikes in Latin America would not be exposed to future prosecution, according to four people familiar with the matter. The decision to pursue an opinion reflects heightened concerns within the government that such strikes would be illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">160732d0-bfe2-11f0-97fb-0000a1ace64f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 16:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Democrats release Epstein email that claimed Trump ‘spent hours’ with victim</title>
      <description>Democrats on the House Oversight Committee released an email from Jeffrey Epstein on Wednesday that claimed President Donald Trump had “spent hours” at Epstein’s house with one of his sex trafficking victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12beb501-bfd6-11f0-a0a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Political tensions in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bb12d40-bfd4-11f0-9921-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown endgame. Venezuela. Extreme rain. Bridge collapse. ChatGPT conversations. Cancer symptoms. Devil bee. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15a72660-bfbf-11f0-b51a-000a1aceb455</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela placed on high alert with massive mobilization of soldiers and militia, defense minister says</title>
      <description>The move comes as the USS Gerald R. Ford aircraft carrier enters waters near Latin America amid speculation that the Trump administration intends to escalate its deadly counternarcotics campaign there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac936020-bf6f-11f0-981a-000a1ace7b51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 02:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How this major city became one of America’s most affordable for home buyers</title>
      <description>While there are many yardsticks for calculating housing affordability, Pittsburgh stands out as uniquely livable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d75400-bf5e-11f0-80d6-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court extends pause on order requiring Trump administration to pay full SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>The ruling comes in a high-stakes battle over funding that helps about 1 in 8 Americans afford groceries — and amid signs the issue could soon be resolved on Capitol Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8948d920-bf5a-11f0-b894-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Still forced to parent a ‘man-child’ ex so he shows up for the kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Still forced to parent a ‘man-child’ ex so he shows up for the kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c6296e0-bf20-11f0-83cc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. aircraft carrier nears Latin America as naval buildup fuels speculation that Trump intends to escalate antidrug campaign</title>
      <description>The USS Gerald R. Ford and its three accompanying warships arrived in the region Tuesday, the Navy said. Since early September, the Trump administration has directed the killing of at least 75 people in its counternarcotics campaign. President Donald Trump has been particularly fixated on Venezuela and its leader, Nicolás Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c51be870-bf1e-11f0-b53f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Supreme Court cases in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15028ec1-bf0b-11f0-a8c7-0000a1ace30b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ByHeart recalls all baby formula amid botulism outbreak</title>
      <description>This marks a significant expansion of the organic baby formula company’s weekend recall of two batches after federal health officials said they were investigating 13 botulism hospitalizations potentially linked to its formula.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70a7a050-bf09-11f0-a532-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How women feel about Trump’s presidency: Heartbreak, fatigue, gratitude</title>
      <description>We asked women how they felt about Donald Trump right after he won the election. One year later, we caught up with them to see what they think now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fadbea0-bf04-11f0-991f-0000a1ace13c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown bill. Supreme Court. Tariff rebates. ICE incident. Oil drilling. Hormone therapy. AI-designed viruses. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb5e5be1-bef5-11f0-8349-0000a1acedcb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
