<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:01:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin Gov. Tony Evers (D) announces he won’t seek a third term in his swing state</title>
      <description>The decision is expected to set off a scramble as other Democrats weigh running to replace Evers. He defeated Gov. Scott Walker (R) in 2018, ending Republicans’ eight-year run of complete control of state government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64766960-68b0-11f0-9617-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:05:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hulk Hogan dies at 71. The pro wrestling star’s tabloid-centric private life became a legal battleground over the First Amendment.</title>
      <description>Florida wrestler Terry Bollea, who shot to stardom as Hulk Hogan, reigned supreme for a generation of professional wrestling fans. Decades after his heyday in the ring, Bollea became a fixture in the courtroom after suing the owners of a popular gossip website that showed portions of a sex tape featuring Bollea and the wife of a friend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52071ea0-68ab-11f0-88be-0000a1ace5fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband is losing his ability to manage small frustrations</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband is losing his ability to manage small frustrations</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5efc3720-68a7-11f0-8e9a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 16:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE moves to shackle some 180,000 immigrants with GPS ankle monitors, a sharp increase in round-the-clock monitoring</title>
      <description>In an internal ICE document reviewed by The Washington Post, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement ordered staff to place ankle monitors on all people enrolled in the agency’s Alternatives to Detention program “whenever possible.” Currently, just 24,000 of these individuals wear ankle monitors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71a95030-6896-11f0-88be-0000a1ace5fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sweaty crop in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b6ba2e0-6892-11f0-9c58-0000a1ace764</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Ankle monitors. Gaza starvation. Bryan Kohberger. Candace Owens. Corn sweat. Penis worm. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e2b6bb0-687d-11f0-9617-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia University and Trump administration strike a deal over federal funding</title>
      <description>White House officials have cast Columbia University as the epicenter of antisemitism. This deal would resolve a dispute over federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa6d2590-681e-11f0-aa9b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With GOP support, House Oversight subcommittee takes step to subpoena Justice Department for Epstein files</title>
      <description>Three Republicans joined with Democrats to advance language to force the full release of the Epstein files after an amendment was introduced by Rep. Summer Lee (D-Pennsylvania). Republican lawmakers have been feeling the same pressure as President Donald Trump to respond to anger from his base about the Justice Department's recent decision not to release the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a513d30-6819-11f0-a6af-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 23:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He got away with murder for 23 years. Video shows his response as police confront him.</title>
      <description>Eugene Gligor struggled to collect himself after learning his DNA was at the scene of a 2001 murder in Chevy Chase, Maryland. What came next wasn’t a confession. But it wasn’t exactly a denial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9524d5b0-6810-11f0-b135-0000a1acec6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 22:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to remove Democrats from agency that regulates safety of everyday consumer products</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had asked the justices to allow the president to remove three of the five members of the Consumer Product Safety Commission, which evaluates products such as strollers and bicycles and coordinates recalls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21fd8280-6806-11f0-977e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 20:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disclosures by Hegseth’s Signal account derived from email classified ‘SECRET,’ IG is told, contradicting Trump officials' claims</title>
      <description>The Pentagon’s independent watchdog has received evidence that messages from the defense secretary's Signal account previewing a U.S. bombing campaign in Yemen derived from a classified email labeled “SECRET/NOFORN,” people familiar with the matter said, contradicting repeated claims by the Trump administration that no classified information was divulged in unclassified group chats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2801cb21-67f5-11f0-bd4b-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department's request to release Epstein transcripts is denied by Florida judge</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Florida has denied the Justice Department’s request to unseal grand jury transcripts from the investigation of deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein in that state.
The department — facing increasing pressure from President Donald Trump’s political base — petitioned the court last week to release those typically closely held records of witness testimony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce473dc0-67f1-11f0-9d81-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who killed four University of Idaho students in 2022 gets four consecutive life sentences</title>
      <description>Bryan Kohberger pleaded guilty earlier this month as part of a plea deal that eliminated the possibility of the death penalty. The high-profile case disrupted a quiet Idaho town, inspired several books and became a subject of speculation by true-crime fans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69c730d0-67ec-11f0-86c9-000a1ace7c27</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 17:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Embarrassing, off-script officiant steals couple’s thoughtful show</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Embarrassing, off-script officiant steals couple’s thoughtful show</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">658e7180-67de-11f0-996f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N.’s highest court rules that countries have a duty to limit greenhouse gases, potentially bolstering climate lawsuits worldwide</title>
      <description>The International Court of Justice ruling said countries are obliged to cut planet-warming pollution and any breach represents an “internationally wrongful act.” While non-binding, the decision could boost cases across the globe and ultimately lead to reparations for vulnerable countries damaged by global warming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46210d90-67dd-11f0-a13f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Help! I’m routinely seated at bad tables.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Help! I’m routinely seated at bad tables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cd94310-67d6-11f0-aff8-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen kept a dark secret in the Amazon. Then a priest made a call.</title>
      <description>Poor laborers were lured to the automaker’s cattle ranch in the Amazon and promised a better life. Brazilian prosecutors say many were enslaved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96698621-67cd-11f0-ad98-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 14:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary drama in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98838950-67c9-11f0-9edb-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 13:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama vs. Trump. Tariff impacts. Ozzy Osbourne. Arrest video. Trans athletes. Avoiding AI. Peacock heist. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f9d2f50-67b4-11f0-acc8-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judges vote to oust former Trump lawyer Alina Habba as New Jersey’s interim U.S. attorney</title>
      <description>New Jersey’s federal judges declined Tuesday to appoint Habba, President Donald Trump’s pick for the state’s top federal prosecutor, to continue serving in that role, delivering a resounding rebuke to one of his most polarizing Justice Department appointees. The state’s U.S. district court judges made the announcement in a brief order that did not offer any explanation for their decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50f40dd0-6733-11f0-afbb-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 19:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozzy Osbourne dies at 76. The Black Sabbath frontman helped pioneer heavy metal’s thunderous, earsplitting sound.</title>
      <description>Playful and flamboyant, with an exuberant personality that belied the foreboding music he recorded with Black Sabbath in the 1970s, Osbourne was a dominant figure in heavy metal for more than four decades, known as much for his manic performance style as his distinctive nasal yawp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ffcb9c0-672b-11f0-99d6-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 18:42:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Can you really walk your way to better health in 30 minutes a day? Our fitness columnist is chatting with readers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Can you really walk your way to better health in 30 minutes a day? Our fitness columnist is chatting with readers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1dc0da1-6716-11f0-a27f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 16:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPR editor in chief says she's stepping down days after Congress cut all federal funding for public broadcasting</title>
      <description>News veteran Edith Chapin says she is leaving her post at National Public Radio. NPR CEO Katherine Maher said in an email that Chapin’s decision came two weeks ago ahead of the Senate’s vote to pass President Donald Trump’s rescission bill, which stripped the Corporation for Public Broadcasting of $1.1 billion for NPR, PBS and member stations over the next two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece84551-6713-11f0-996e-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:52:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House grinds to a halt before its planned recess to avoid voting on release of Jeffrey Epstein files</title>
      <description>Republican leaders are struggling to assuage an irate group of lawmakers who are demanding that the Justice Department release files related to deceased sex offender Epstein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46a2ec00-6712-11f0-a397-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 15:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social workers knew of a mother’s troubled history. Then her toddler died of hunger and thirst in her custody.</title>
      <description>For months, relatives feared Ebony Washington’s daughter Kemy was in peril. Why didn’t anybody save her?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f11dd9b0-6708-11f0-b402-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 14:34:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coke says cane sugar soda is coming to the U.S., a move hailed by Trump. There’s little evidence it’s healthier, studies show.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said last week that he had spoken to Coca-Cola about making its product in the United States with cane sugar, as it does in Mexico. The company announced Tuesday it would roll out a U.S. version as an option this fall. But studies do not show it has substantial benefits over Coke with high-fructose corn syrup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d68dbf00-6700-11f0-916d-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Good trouble’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68205b50-66ff-11f0-8be4-0000a1ace593</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 13:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein distractions. MLK Jr. files. Breonna Taylor. Israeli attacks. Organ donation. Malcolm-Jamal Warner. Colbert. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00a6e250-66eb-11f0-bff4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jul 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Louisville police officer sentenced to 33 months in relation to Breonna Taylor’s killing</title>
      <description>Former officer Brett Hankison faced up to life in prison. His case has been closely watched by civil rights activists who have pressed for police accountability in Taylor’s death, which helped spark mass social justice protests in 2020. In an unusual court filing last week, the Justice Department suggested Hankison shouldn't have faced federal charges and recommended that he be sentenced to a day in jail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318903d0-6682-11f0-92ba-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:29:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our travel writer had 21 hours of flight delays. Here’s what she did wrong.</title>
      <description>During a nightmare travel day, it took our reporter nearly 22 hours to get from D.C. to Martha’s Vineyard. Lesson learned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24088e80-6676-11f0-82be-000a1ace5cb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 21:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Cosby Show’ actor Malcolm-Jamal Warner dies at 54 in accidental drowning, AP reports. He starred as the witty teen Theo Huxtable.</title>
      <description>Warner died while on a family vacation in Costa Rica, according to the Associated Press. Representatives for the actor declined to provide a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87c7de20-6668-11f0-bfcf-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 19:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divorce and adultery allegations against Ken Paxton jolt a key Senate race in Texas</title>
      <description>In one of the biggest Republican primaries of the midterms, Sen. John Cornyn and his allies are attacking Paxton, the state attorney general, over his personal life — and some backers are rethinking their support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ada308a0-665d-11f0-b79d-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: As parents jockey for the last word, their 10-year-old tunes out</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: As parents jockey for the last word, their 10-year-old tunes out</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de8fd080-664c-11f0-bfcf-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 16:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the population really collapsing? Test your assumptions in this quiz.</title>
      <description>Is the population really collapsing? Test your assumptions in this quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2671d910-6644-11f0-b682-0000a1ace2dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 15:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials are accused of defying 1 in 3 judges who ruled against the administration in lawsuits</title>
      <description>Plaintiffs say Justice Department lawyers and the agencies they represent are snubbing rulings, providing false information, failing to turn over evidence and inventing pretexts to carry out actions that have been blocked. Judges appointed by presidents of both parties have often sided with the plaintiffs in these cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5418a410-663b-11f0-86ce-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 14:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This is all just going away’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edf61540-6636-11f0-abd4-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 13:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza deaths. Trump support. Harvard lawsuit. Microsoft hack. Texas search. B-52 incident. Carbon dump. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d705f091-6621-11f0-94ed-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S.’s only native caffeinated plant may soon get a huge boost from tariffs on coffee and tea</title>
      <description>Yaupon, a holly, may be little known outside Indigenous groups, but a tight-knit group of farmers, producers and wild harvesters are ready and waiting for a potential resurgence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">907b37e0-65ac-11f0-9fbc-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottie Scheffler wins the British Open, capturing his second major championship of the year and the fourth of his career</title>
      <description>The No. 1 player in the world expertly navigated Royal Portrush in Northern Ireland, running away from the rest of the field over the final two rounds. Scheffler, 29, also won the PGA Championship in May after winning the Masters in 2022 and 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837d1a0-6591-11f0-a953-0000a1ace0dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 17:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb75930-6582-11f0-b8d5-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Mexican Coke really better than the U.S. version? We put it to the test.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Coca-Cola will switch to “real cane sugar” instead of high-fructose corn syrup in the United States. Could we taste the difference?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2607d840-6576-11f0-8c4e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">019bc8c0-656e-11f0-b90a-0000a1acec83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another senior aide to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth is leaving the Pentagon, officials say</title>
      <description>Justin Fulcher was at the center of two strange controversies, including one first reported by The Washington Post on Tuesday in which he stormed out of a meeting with another Pentagon official. He and Hegseth's team both said Saturday that his departure was “amicable.” It's at least the fifth departure of a top adviser in Hegseth’s first six months in office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb761e70-64f4-11f0-b16f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 23:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In an attempt to help lower-income residents, Kansas City poured millions into a grocery store. It’s on the verge of closure.</title>
      <description>Cities and states across the country are experimenting with publicly supported supermarkets. But the problems encountered in Kansas City show these efforts often don’t account for social issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4a34160-64c1-11f0-87fa-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I keep my boundary-stomping parents from ruining my home?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I keep my boundary-stomping parents from ruining my home?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d163c773-64b9-11f0-a7b9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A family found safety and their dream home in America. Then both began to crack.</title>
      <description>For a Haitian family in Springfield, Ohio, the house on Chestnut Avenue represented their future in this country. With their legal status here now threatened, they’re wondering what can be salvaged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c457f80-64ab-11f0-bd8f-0000a1ace992</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccade281-64a3-11f0-a3c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 13:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA eliminates its scientific research arm, cementing plans to cut nearly a quarter of its entire staff</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency said it would dismantle the Office of Research and Development, which conducts independent research on environmental hazards. Agency officials said the EPA has now cut 23 percent of its overall staff through layoffs, separations and retirements, saving taxpayers more than $748 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95cb030-6437-11f0-9af5-0000a1ace334</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department asks a federal court to release Epstein grand jury testimony</title>
      <description>Trump administration officials have asked a federal court to unseal more grand jury testimony in the sex-trafficking case against former financier Jeffrey Epstein. The request comes as political outcry intensifies over the administration’s unfulfilled promise to release more details on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea338d60-6425-11f0-93a3-000a1ace6899</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What causes obesity? A major new study is upending common wisdom.</title>
      <description>The study found that people living in developed countries expend about the same number of calories most days as hunter-gatherers and anyone living in less-industrialized nations, suggesting that inactivity is not the main cause of obesity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">959ee3a0-641e-11f0-b0d5-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 21:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
