<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 01:29:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bankruptcies soar as companies grapple with inflation and tariffs</title>
      <description>Businesses in vulnerable sectors find themselves caught between rising costs and beleaguered consumers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df729480-e381-11f0-9e77-0000a1ace39b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two baby giraffes are missing. Alicia Silverstone and others want answers.</title>
      <description>The giraffes would be around eight months old, which would make them about 9-feet tall and 700 pounds. Silverstone, of “Clueless” fame, has joined PETA in offering a $50,000 reward for information leading to their whereabouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b10e6bc0-e370-11f0-9f38-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 22:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74 suicide warnings and 243 mentions of hanging: What ChatGPT said to a suicidal teen</title>
      <description>Analysis of high-schooler Adam Raine’s ChatGPT account by attorneys for his parents shows how the chatbot became a confidant as he planned to end his life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">548ac790-e352-11f0-9680-0000a1ace615</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04a9a7b0-e333-11f0-9d4f-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. sank the alleged narco-terrorists’ boat — and let them go</title>
      <description>In blowing up the vessel, destroying evidence and repatriating the survivors, the U.S. cut short a process that has helped bring down traffickers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eee553a0-e32f-11f0-906d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology just can’t kill this popular Midwestern bar game</title>
      <description>Pull tabs, legal in Minnesota and a few other states, have been a cherished tradition for nearly 50 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c552a00-e2a7-11f0-9f0c-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of residents signed up for FEMA buyouts after Hurricane Helene. Not one has been approved.</title>
      <description>Some of the homeowners seeking help are still paying mortgages on homes that are no longer livable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc07c8e0-e289-11f0-9050-0000a1ace903</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I perform at a piano bar. The most requested song might surprise you.</title>
      <description>So long “Piano Man.” Chappell Roan’s ode to a gay bar now draws the most requests, Jesse Rifkin writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf941260-e287-11f0-8ae1-0000a1ace30d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus! It’s the holiday edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday weekend points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0e704c0-e272-11f0-825e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 good things that happened in 2025</title>
      <description>25 good things that happened in 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">819cc0f0-e26a-11f0-9576-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New science points to 4 distinct types of autism</title>
      <description>Scientists are redefining autism as a complex condition with multiple forms, challenging traditional notions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62532390-e267-11f0-9ca0-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. strikes Islamic State in Nigeria after Trump's warnings against Christian killings</title>
      <description>U.S. forces struck Islamic State targets in northwestern Nigeria on Christmas evening, following up on threats to the country over killings of Christians, President Donald Trump announced in a Truth Social post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba58b5c0-e1ed-11f0-babc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 charts that show where the economy is heading</title>
      <description>The U.S. economy experienced steady growth in 2025, despite concerns over inflation and the job market, with artificial intelligence playing a significant role in driving growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e350eca0-e1bf-11f0-aaec-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 things about living a healthy life we learned from super agers this year</title>
      <description>People in their 80s, 90s and 100s (and the scientists who study them) taught us plenty about aging well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6418a160-e1a3-11f0-8c87-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b02dbf1-e1a0-11f0-b7d1-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a nearly 70-year-old debut novelist published 2025’s breakout hit</title>
      <description>With virtually no marketing or social media presence, Allen Levi’s book became a blockbuster, with a late-breaking plot turn so brutal, anguished readers grill him about it at all public appearances. The author’s own path has taken a few twists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7ffba90-e116-11f0-8f40-0000a1aced24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Laissez-faire mom-in-law leaves the stress to me’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘Laissez-faire mom-in-law leaves the stress to me’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a4a91e1-e0ea-11f0-bc6c-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The old-world antisemitism in a Christmas pageant near you</title>
      <description>"I’m certainly not the first immigrant to discover Old World darkness lurking in the U.S."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cc1a270-e0e2-11f0-8c78-0000a1aceb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE documents reveal plan to hold 80,000 immigrants in warehouses</title>
      <description>Rather than shuttling detainees around the country to wherever detention space is available, as happens now, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement aims to speed up deportations by establishing a deliberate feeder system, an internal document says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43c03381-e0d9-11f0-8ce0-000a1ace1088</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A holiday diss track in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Christmas Eve points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5702a660-e0d6-11f0-94b9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court. Epstein files. ICE warehouses. News subscriptions. Nursing home. Coffee vs. tea. Deer cam. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c318540-e0c0-11f0-bc00-0000a1aced78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We read thousands of internal ICE messages. They show how officials make raids go viral.</title>
      <description>Internal discussions reveal how the agency has coordinated with the White House to satisfy Trump administration demands for arrest videos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d8b67b0-e057-11f0-a2e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court will not allow National Guard deployment in Chicago area for now, handing Trump a major defeat</title>
      <description>“At this preliminary stage, the Government has failed to identify a source of authority that would allow the military to execute the laws in Illinois,” the court wrote in an unsigned ruling. The decision is a significant setback for President Donald Trump’s campaign to push troops into cities across the country over the objections of local and state leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a35e5d30-e03e-11f0-85d4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her daughter was unraveling, and she didn’t know why — until she found the AI chat logs</title>
      <description>Generative AI has attracted a rising number of users under the age of 18. For children in the midst of critical stages of emotional, mental and social development, the appeal of an artificial companion — designed to create the illusion of intimacy — can be powerful, one expert said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ebc0e60-e029-11f0-a971-000a1aced838</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dad’s new wife assumes grandma role by stepping on toes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dad’s new wife assumes grandma role by stepping on toes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">468db500-e021-11f0-a2e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former GOP senator Ben Sasse announces he has terminal cancer</title>
      <description>“Last week I was diagnosed with metastasized, stage-four pancreatic cancer, and am gonna die,” Sasse, 53, wrote in a social media post. He was first elected to the Senate in 2014, representing Nebraska, and was one of a handful of Republican senators who regularly spoke out against President Donald Trump. Sasse resigned from his seat partway through his second term to become president of the University of Florida.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41def3a0-e019-11f0-94ae-0000a1acef7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A polarizing modern holiday classic (?) in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to keep up with your festive points!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23a5e770-e00c-11f0-88ce-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. economy grew at its fastest pace in two years this summer</title>
      <description>New data from the Commerce Department on Tuesday — delayed by two months because of the government shutdown — showed that gross domestic product grew at an annualized rate of 4.3 percent between July and September driven mainly by consumer spending and a rise in net exports, as U.S. companies sold more industrial supplies, pharmaceuticals and gold abroad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4046de90-e005-11f0-88ce-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:42:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second big batch of Epstein files includes many mentions of Trump</title>
      <description>In a statement Tuesday morning, the Justice Department said: “Some of these documents contain untrue and sensationalist claims made against President Trump” that it characterized as “unfounded and false.”

The department did not immediately respond to questions about why the documents had been posted Monday and then apparently removed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0688a420-e002-11f0-9b97-000a1acef9b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:19:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Trump battleships. ICE messages. Turning Point. Home ownership. AI chatbots. Banksy mural. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df3162f0-dff6-11f0-9bfb-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here are 10 science-backed tips to help you get healthier</title>
      <description>New routines don’t stick overnight, our Ask a Doctor columnist Dr. Trisha Pasricha writes. So pick one habit at a time and make it as easy as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7caa8830-df94-11f0-9f01-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:15:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department sues D.C. over ban of AR-15s and other semiautomatic guns</title>
      <description>Government attorneys chastised the city for its code that bans most semiautomatic rifles and certain firearms from being registered with the police department, ultimately making any possession of those weapons illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c05f3ff0-df79-11f0-9dfc-0000a1ace060</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘60 Minutes’ executive producer told staff she stands by segment but ‘had to comply’ when CBS News chief Bari Weiss shelved it</title>
      <description>The postponed segment was set to cover the Trump administration’s deportations of Venezuelan migrants to El Salvador’s CECOT prison. Weiss this weekend said the story could not run after the administration refused to grant an interview, according to an internal email. “We pushed back, we defended our story, but she wanted changes, and I ultimately had to comply,” EP Tanya Simon said to staff, according to a partial transcript of the meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0c9aca0-df75-11f0-8ed3-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 20:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Second-guessing choices after putting down a beloved dog</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Second-guessing choices after putting down a beloved dog</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ac8c50-df58-11f0-9c0b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best state of the year? Here is the winner of the Editorial Board’s new year-end tradition.</title>
      <description>Which of the 50 improved the most in 2025?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">230a43c0-df48-11f0-a9c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your holiday-themed week of On the Record starts today</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your festive Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec00db01-df42-11f0-aafb-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They survived a Cybertruck crash. Then a fire killed them.</title>
      <description>In several instances, Tesla passengers have struggled to access or exit the vehicles during life-threatening emergencies, including fires. Lawsuits allege the company’s futuristic features have caused injuries and deaths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da95cef0-df3f-11f0-aee6-000a1ace340d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 14:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz. Epstein files. Federal worker stories. Venezuela. Remote work. Holiday travel forecast. Video games. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5e03ee0-df2d-11f0-a648-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A middle-class family’s only option: A $43,000 health insurance premium</title>
      <description>Consumers are left with few options and crushing prices as insurers offering Affordable Care Act plans pull out of some regions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47c55de0-deb1-11f0-ade0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 21:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23 Christmas traditions, ranked from worst to best</title>
      <description>We love them, we hate them, we complain and then do them anyway. Based on an entirely unscientific and highly emotional survey of Washington Post staffers, we explain which experiences makes us crazy and the ones we can’t live without.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b31ec91-de97-11f0-89b3-0000a1acef27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 18:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">444f6970-de8f-11f0-a83c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 17:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The year Trump broke the federal government</title>
      <description>Millions of federal employees were caught up in a once-unthinkable overhaul of the nation’s sprawling bureaucracy, carried out in less than a year by one of the most polarizing presidents in American history. And more changes are coming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1584cbd2-de80-11f0-9f89-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 15:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50422060-de7b-11f0-88a9-0000a1ace0fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 14:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘TrumpKennedyCenter.org’ website is taken. This comedian owns it.</title>
      <description>The creator of satirical websites bought the domain this summer and is plotting its content, even if some things are “hard to parody.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df3b8260-de04-11f0-b04a-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 17-year lawsuit between a Trump official and his interior designers</title>
      <description>Pete Marocco helped dismantle USAID in weeks. But for nearly two decades, he has been embroiled in a legal “boondoggle” in Tallahassee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05096ba0-dde8-11f0-910e-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 21:08:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Saving pedestrian lives is not that hard. Here’s what one city is doing.</title>
      <description>As the rate of pedestrian deaths soars, The Washington Post priced out practical solutions and examined what Albuquerque has pursued to show what is possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38b10c91-ddbd-11f0-993c-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54d76ec0-ddb1-11f0-98b7-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:36:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tucker Carlson inflames a raging battle for MAGA’s future</title>
      <description>The provocative podcaster has an audience – online, among influencers and inside the White House. That worries some on the right.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b7bf890-ddac-11f0-bea9-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump renaming calls the Kennedy Center’s legacy into question</title>
      <description>Can he do that? Is it legal? Most of us haven’t experienced this level of dissonant brand synergy since our first visit to a combination KFC/Taco Bell, writes Michael Andor Brodeur.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f19e8ea0-dd39-11f0-b729-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 00:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. strikes dozens of sites in Syria in retaliation for killing of two American soldiers and an interpreter</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth acknowledged the strikes, saying U.S. forces had begun Operation Hawkeye Strike “in direct response to the attack” on American personnel last weekend in Palmyra. “This is not the beginning of the war — it is a declaration of vengeance,” Hegseth said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94b8d2a1-dd2e-11f0-a356-0000a1ace385</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 23:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
