<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 03:12:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Salt Typhoon breach is ‘worst telecom hack in our nation’s history — by far,’ says Senate Intelligence Committee chair</title>
      <description>The Chinese government's espionage campaign has penetrated more than a dozen U.S. telecommunications companies and collected information on federal wiretaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb96f210-a870-11ef-b72b-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani of the Los Angeles Dodgers and Aaron Judge of the New York Yankees named MLB’s most valuable players</title>
      <description>Ohtani, who played his first season in the National League after signing a record contract with the Dodgers last offseason, is an MVP for the third time after the designated hitter became the first player with at least 50 home runs and 50 stolen bases in a season. Judge earned his second American League MVP award after the outfielder hit a major league-leading 58 home runs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b10c4e1-a866-11ef-973b-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Pam Bondi to be attorney general, replacing Matt Gaetz hours after he withdrew bid</title>
      <description>Bondi, a former Florida attorney general, served in the Trump White House in 2019 during his first impeachment. She is the second selection the president-elect has made to lead the Justice Department. Gaetz, who's been accused of sexual misconduct, announced earlier Thursday he would no longer pursue the Cabinet role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e2e9520-a864-11ef-a739-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 23:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Ovechkin expected to miss four to six weeks with fractured fibula, an injury that comes as he chases Wayne Gretzky’s record</title>
      <description>The Washington Capitals on Thursday announced the timeline for Ovechkin, whose season has paused amid his chase of Gretzky’s NHL goals record. The Capitals’ captain has 15 goals in 18 games this season and 868 in his NHL career. Ovechkin, 39, needs just 27 goals to break Gretzky’s record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a59c62e0-a859-11ef-b919-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 22:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming of snow this winter? Look up the forecast in your area.</title>
      <description>Most of the United States is expected to see less snow this year, continuing a long-term trend of snowfall decline as global temperatures rise. Look up your area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98fea940-a849-11ef-b762-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 20:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John J. DeGioia, Georgetown University’s longest-serving president, will step down to focus on recovery after a stroke</title>
      <description>DeGioia, a Georgetown alumnus who became president in 2001, suffered a stroke in June. He will remain a faculty member.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4223ae70-a841-11ef-a908-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 19:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz withdraws bid to be attorney general in Trump administration, saying ‘confirmation was unfairly becoming a distraction’</title>
      <description>In a statement on X, the former Florida congressman, who met with Republican senators on Wednesday, said that there was “no time to waste on a needlessly protracted Washington scuffle.” Gaetz, who was tapped by President-elect Donald Trump, has faced allegations of sexual misconduct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3a52a90-a82f-11ef-a75b-000a1ace12d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 17:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend gives gifts that he would like for himself</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend gives gifts that he would like for himself</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4df50210-a82a-11ef-b270-0000a1ace796</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 17:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Illinois Supreme Court overturns actor Jussie Smollett’s conviction for falsely reporting hate crime, citing due process violation</title>
      <description>The court found that a special prosecutor’s move to retry the former “Empire” actor after charges had been dropped was a violation of his due process rights. Smollett had been convicted of falsely claiming men attacked him while shouting racist and homophobic slurs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09c27550-a825-11ef-82a6-000a1ace1018</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 16:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dessert company is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5acdefc0-a815-11ef-810a-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 14:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Nancy Pelosi. Kerry Washington. Lara Trump. Innovative entrepreneurs. WNBA All-Stars. Watch our Global Women’s Summit.</title>
      <description>From key political leaders challenging the status quo to entrepreneurs shaking up the distilled spirits world to dynamic visionaries owning new spaces in entertainment, women are redefining the game. Watch The Washington Post’s Global Women’s Summit, spotlighting women who are architects of change and dynamos of innovation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3713dc0-a812-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 14:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICC issues arrest warrants for Netanyahu and Gallant, accusing them of war crimes in Gaza, and a Hamas commander for Oct. 7 attacks</title>
      <description>The International Criminal Court said it found reasonable grounds to believe that Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and former defense minister Yoav Gallant were responsible for war crimes and crimes against humanity in Gaza, including using starvation as a method of warfare and directing attacks against civilians. Both men have vehemently denied the allegations. The court also issued a warrant for Hamas commander Mohammed Deif for crimes against humanity committed on Oct. 7. Israel said it killed Deif in a July airstrike but the ICC said it had not confirmed his death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">486c88b1-a805-11ef-98d7-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 12:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Matt Gaetz. Google Chrome. Israeli weapons. Egg shortage. AI power demands. EagleCam. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">240f65f0-a800-11ef-b2d1-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. seeks to force Google to sell its Chrome browser, along with other big changes, in monopoly case</title>
      <description>The filing from federal prosecutors is one of the last expressions of President Joe Biden’s aggressive antitrust stance before President-elect Donald Trump takes the reins.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">906baa40-a7bc-11ef-bd02-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 03:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut women's basketball coach Geno Auriemma sets record for most wins in college basketball history</title>
      <description>Auriemma achieved the milestone Wednesday night, passing former Stanford women's coach Tara VanDerveer with his 1,217th victory. Auriemma, who has spent his entire 40-year career as a head coach at Connecticut, has won 11 national championships and made 22 Final Four appearances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">962d3a00-a7aa-11ef-b4fb-0000a1acec2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 01:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a brutally repressive African country freely raises money in the U.S.</title>
      <description>Three years ago, the United States imposed sanctions against the ruling party of Eritrea, a small country in the Horn of Africa. And yet, Eritrea’s embassy in Washington has helped raise millions of dollars on behalf of the cash-strapped country since then, while Eritrean officials acknowledge that the government and the ruling party are one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d43cbe40-a78e-11ef-92e6-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 22:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pleads guilty to killing three University of Virginia classmates on a bus in 2022</title>
      <description>Christopher Darnell Jones Jr. was arrested in November 2022 after authorities say he opened fire on a bus carrying U-Va. students as they returned to the Charlottesville campus from a field trip in D.C. D’Sean Perry, Lavel Davis Jr. and Devin Chandler were killed, and two other students were injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12119ef0-a77d-11ef-bf1f-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 20:21:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel saw records suggesting Gaetz paid two women $10,000, in part for sex, according to a person familiar with investigation</title>
      <description>The records that were exhibited during closed-door testimony displayed 27 different PayPal and Venmo payments totaling over $10,000 paid to the two witnesses, the person said. The House Ethics Committee investigated whether former congressman Matt Gaetz, President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run the Justice Department, paid for sex with a 17-year-old and now faces calls to release its findings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8732c0f0-a774-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He’s a great boyfriend, the one night a week he’s free</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He’s a great boyfriend, the one night a week he’s free</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25ec0e11-a764-11ef-a8df-000a1ace2244</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 17:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Does Michelin Guide recognition still matter? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Does Michelin Guide recognition still matter? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a548011-a75d-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 16:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan national found guilty of murdering nursing student Laken Riley in case that inflamed immigration debate</title>
      <description>Jose Ibarra, an undocumented immigrant, was accused of murdering the University of Georgia student while she was on a run. Republicans made Riley’s death a national flash point ahead of the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">038b1b61-a75d-11ef-8509-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 16:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. wants fluoride out of drinking water. Oregon shows what’s coming.</title>
      <description>Fluoride is added to water to strengthen teeth and reduce cavities. Now more Americans are starting to question a practice experts have lauded as one of the greatest public health achievements of the 20th century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">093367b1-a754-11ef-9a4e-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 15:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Cosmic justice’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17b3d7f0-a74c-11ef-b65d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 14:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. moves to protect giraffes under the Endangered Species Act by restricting imports of their body parts</title>
      <description>The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service announced a proposal Wednesday to protect a wide swath of giraffes for the first time, as the long-necked animals decline because of poaching, development and drought fueled by climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ce9dda0-a747-11ef-ac46-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 13:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linda McMahon. Trump’s hush money case. Ukraine mines. Starship splashdown. Snow. Climate risk. Nadal’s farewell. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd4c66d0-a736-11ef-92e6-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump selects transition co-chair Linda McMahon to be education secretary</title>
      <description>McMahon led the Small Business Administration from 2017 to 2019 and is the co-founder and former chief executive of World Wrestling Entertainment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e401910-a6ea-11ef-ac46-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 02:49:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden approves antipersonnel land mines for Ukraine, reversing his 2022 policy and drawing criticism from arms control groups</title>
      <description>The decision comes after the White House recently authorized Ukraine to use a long-range missile system to strike inside Russia — part of a sweep of urgent actions the outgoing Biden administration is taking to boost Kyiv’s faltering war effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4558360-a6d8-11ef-af3c-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:45:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Social investors hoped to get ‘very rich’ after Trump’s win. Instead, they ‘are in trouble.’</title>
      <description>Trump Media &amp; Technology Group’s revenue and share price have sagged as its losses have piled up. The president-elect’s return to the White House could complicate things even more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9694d51-a6ce-11ef-837a-0000a1ace815</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 23:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Trump in attendance, Elon Musk’s SpaceX aborts a second attempt to re-capture Starship booster at launch pad</title>
      <description>A SpaceX Starship rocket splashed down in the Gulf of Mexico on Tuesday after the company aborted its second attempt to “catch” the returning booster at the launch pad — a disappointing outcome to a test mission observed by President-elect Donald Trump, who traveled to Texas to watch</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80b9e7d0-a6c5-11ef-828d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 22:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks celebrity doctor Mehmet Oz to serve as administrator of the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump announced his plans to nominate the onetime U.S. Senate candidate in Pennsylvania to lead the agency that administers the Medicare and Medicaid programs. “I have known Dr. Oz for many years, and I am confident he will fight to ensure everyone in America receives the best possible Healthcare, so our Country can be Great and Healthy Again!” Trump said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62b8f0b0-a6ba-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 21:08:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas education officials back optional Bible lessons in public elementary schools</title>
      <description>The Texas State Board of Education voted 8-7 to move forward with approval for the optional curriculum, which opponents say promotes Christian beliefs in public school. The final vote is scheduled for Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19720950-a6b5-11ef-b9ef-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 20:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Do they apologize for mocking in-law’s ‘weird’ Thanksgiving meal?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Do they apologize for mocking in-law’s ‘weird’ Thanksgiving meal?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da6fb6e0-a69f-11ef-99bf-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 17:58:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents with damaging testimony against Matt Gaetz were accessed in an apparent breach</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run the Department of Justice was investigated on allegations of sexual misconduct with a 17-year-old girl; he was never charged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d1383f0-a697-11ef-886a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is expected to name Wall Street banker Howard Lutnick as commerce secretary, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Lutnick, who serves as co-chair of President-elect Donald Trump’s transition team, had been under consideration for treasury secretary. He is the CEO and chairman of Cantor Fitzgerald, an investment firm, and has donated to both Democrats and Republicans in the past. He also once appeared on Trump’s NBC reality TV show, “The Apprentice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81f13781-a692-11ef-8612-0000a1acef27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 16:22:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unlikely find in Australia is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ed62b21-a687-11ef-b529-0000a1ace284</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 15:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine used U.S.-made ATACMS missiles inside Russia for the first time, according to Russian and Ukrainian officials</title>
      <description>A Ukrainian official confirmed the ATACMS missiles were used inside Russia overnight. Russia said it shot down five of the six missiles fired at a facility in the Bryansk region. The attack comes soon after the Biden administration lifted restrictions on the use of the powerful, long-range, guided missiles inside Russia, long a Ukrainian request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d73fdb0-a674-11ef-a28f-0000a1ace0f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 12:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz. Trump’s plans. Gaza gangs. Hong Kong. Atmospheric river. Doctors and AI. Wave power. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5a389d0-a66d-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong sentences 45 pro-democracy leaders to jail terms of up to 10 years, including the city’s most prominent activists</title>
      <description>Benny Tai, a 60-year-old legal scholar who spearheaded the Occupy Central movement, received the harshest sentence. Former student activist Joshua Wong, one of the most recognizable of the group, was sentenced to four years and eight months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd6a72a0-a624-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 03:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks former congressman and Fox Business host Sean Duffy as transportation secretary</title>
      <description>Duffy, a former reality TV star who was elected to the House in 2010, will head a department that oversees the funding of roads, bridges and rail lines, as well as the running of the aviation system — and that plays a major role in overseeing companies run by billionaire Elon Musk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0c99b90-a603-11ef-855a-0000a1ace880</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 23:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two women told House Ethics Committee that Matt Gaetz paid them for sex, lawyer says</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s pick for attorney general has been met with shock and pushback, including from Senate Republicans. Some have raised doubts that Gaetz would have the 50 votes needed to be confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9380200-a5fb-11ef-ad0c-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 22:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gangs looting aid convoys in Gaza operate in areas under Israeli military control, humanitarian officials say</title>
      <description>Criminal looting near Israel’s Kerem Shalom crossing has become the greatest impediment to distributing aid in the southern half of Gaza, aid groups say, amid a deepening hunger crisis. The gangs “may be benefiting from a passive if not active benevolence” or “protection” from the Israeli military, according to an October U.N. memo obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">066b7c20-a5f6-11ef-8559-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 21:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Smithsonian quietly removed the American Art Museum director this summer after years of staff complaints about her management style</title>
      <description>The Smithsonian Institution placed Stephanie Stebich in a role as a senior adviser after Smithsonian American Art Museum staff complained of feeling frustrated and confused, according to interviews with current and former museum employees and an internal email confirming her job change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdf22cf0-a5e7-11ef-b113-0000a1ace520</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 20:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Attorney General Jason Miyares (R) announces he’s running for reelection, not governor, in 2025</title>
      <description>By running for reelection, Miyares avoids a potentially expensive and bruising gubernatorial primary with fellow Republican Lt. Gov. Winsome Earle-Sears, who has already announced her campaign to succeed the term-limited Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1580bee0-a5d9-11ef-832b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Late mother’s best friend was like a second mom — till she vanished</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Late mother’s best friend was like a second mom — till she vanished</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6ba1840-a5d0-11ef-b04d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 17:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans are exploring significant changes to Medicaid and food stamps to help offset the cost of extending Trump’s tax cuts</title>
      <description>Continuing the 2017 tax law would cost trillions. Seeking some budget savings, GOP lawmakers say safety net spending has ballooned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c6f3561-a5cc-11ef-a3b1-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 16:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress must stop offensive weapons sales to Israel, Sen. Bernie Sanders writes</title>
      <description>Continuing to provide Israel with the offensive weapons it uses on civilians is morally wrong.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f691cd01-a5c7-11ef-97de-0000a1ace478</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 16:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A taped message has solved the mystery of a World War I doughboy’s death</title>
      <description>Foster Stevens was killed nine days before the Nov. 11, 1918, armistice that ended the Great War. Now his family knows about the man who was with him when he died.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">700d2bf1-a5c0-11ef-9a8b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 15:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A masterpiece restored in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f41a2b0-a5ba-11ef-8c84-000a1ace9234</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s team. Ukraine weapons. Pope Francis. Carrot recall. Spirit Airlines. Ancient kitten. Gladiator Airbnb. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2628580-a5a4-11ef-bfa1-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit Airlines files for bankruptcy, says it will continue to operate as it seeks to restructure its debt</title>
      <description>“Spirit expects to continue operating its business in the normal course throughout this prearranged, streamlined chapter 11 process,” it said in a release. “Guests can continue to book and fly without interruption and can use all tickets, credits and loyalty points as normal.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b5a4041-a59c-11ef-a646-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 10:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
