<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:09:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Zelensky. Mail-in voting. Epstein files. Teacher test. Measles risk. Hurricane Erin. MSNBC rebrand. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a810fdd0-7ceb-11f0-b7ba-000a1ace3d91</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Air Force general forced out in Hegseth’s latest shake-up of Pentagon</title>
      <description>Gen. David Allvin will retire halfway through his four-year term, becoming the most recent senior military official to be pushed out by the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1bca20-7c91-11f0-85ff-000a1ace17b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department will begin sharing Epstein files with Congress on Friday, Oversight Committee chairman says</title>
      <description>House Oversight Committee chairman James Comer (R-Kentucky) said in a statement the Justice Department “will begin to provide Epstein-related records” on Friday in response to the panel’s subpoena. The department, which was facing a Tuesday deadline to comply with the subpoena, did not immediately comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c1cf120-7c6c-11f0-9c38-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky arrives at the White House for a high-stakes Ukraine meeting with Trump and European leaders. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s arrival marks the start of a meeting that could determine whether a peace deal can be worked out to end more than two years of war between Ukraine and Russia. A parade of Zelensky’s European allies arrived earlier in the afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bd30710-7c57-11f0-babf-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columnist Jules Witcover dies at 98. Over six decades, he covered presidents, assassinations, civil rights and the Cold War.</title>
      <description>Witcover was known as one of the best-sourced political reporters of his generation and wrote a long-running syndicated column with his Baltimore Sun colleague Jack Germond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a39df30-7c52-11f0-a572-0000a1ace0b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After wife’s hysterectomy, husband regrets not having kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After wife’s hysterectomy, husband regrets not having kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b5b4aa0-7c4c-11f0-8e48-0000a1ace032</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The judge who refuses to bend to Trump’s will: ‘We’ll do what’s right’</title>
      <description>In an interview with The Washington Post, Brazilian Federal Supreme Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes said he’s preserving democracy in his country. The Trump administration, backing former Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro, says Moraes is destroying it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2987af21-7c3e-11f0-94b0-0000a1ace1b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A historic stadium show in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b66eff0-7c37-11f0-a9b8-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Violent arrest. Israel protests. Coronavirus wave. Nighttime humidity. ‘AI slop.’ Pearl Harbor find. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75ab0580-7c22-11f0-9d00-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a37f72a0-7b89-11f0-b9e5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We stayed out all night in D.C. this weekend after Trump’s National Guard deployment. Here’s what we saw.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spent 12 hours on U Street as federal police roamed, bartenders worried and clubgoers tried to enjoy themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc3df8e0-7b7c-11f0-8380-0000a1ace2d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3906c790-7b6e-11f0-9e39-0000a1ace25f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top European and NATO leaders will join the Trump-Zelensky meeting Monday, presenting a united front</title>
      <description>NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, French President Emmanuel Macron, German Chancellor Friedrich Merz and and Finnish President Alexander Stubb confirmed Sunday that they will join Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky when he meets with President Donald Trump in D.C. on Monday. Ukraine’s future amid Russia’s war could hinge on the high-stakes and potentially emotional meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79729f70-7b5f-11f0-9808-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 11:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican-led states to send hundreds more National Guard troops to D.C.</title>
      <description>Three Republican-led states, responding to a Trump administration request, said Saturday they would send up to 750 National Guard troops to join the 800 already deployed in the District of Columbia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">395350a0-7b10-11f0-9625-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE documents reveal plan to double immigrant detention space this year</title>
      <description>Billions will be spent to reach more than 107,000 beds, including in mega-facilities, tents and at least two new family detention centers, according to an internal agency roadmap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f5ec570-7ad5-11f0-a531-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 19:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin rapidly intensifies into powerful Category 5 storm, a day after becoming year’s first Atlantic hurricane</title>
      <description>By midday Saturday, the storm had exploded from a low-end Category 1 to a monster Category 5 storm, with maximum sustained winds of 160 mph. It is expected to pass north of the Caribbean islands but could bring heavy rain and blustery winds to Puerto Rico on Saturday afternoon and evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">396c5680-7ac6-11f0-94ae-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Divorced desi woman worries about talking about her dating life</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Divorced desi woman worries about talking about her dating life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1edea9a1-7aba-11f0-82bd-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-in solar promises an easy, cheap way to power your home. Our columnist tried it.</title>
      <description>Millions of people in the United States can’t install rooftop solar, because they are renters or live in buildings with roof limitations. But for a few hundred dollars, portable panels that hang on any sunny surface can pump free solar electricity into your home via a wall socket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcd8850-7ab3-11f0-bf86-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a871c530-7aab-11f0-bd83-0000a1ace6d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 14:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin gets a small public-relations victory, the Editorial Board writes. What happens next will be more consequential.</title>
      <description>Putin’s short-term, public-relations win is less important than the meetings that follow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08c18500-7aa8-11f0-b0fa-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:50:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump drops Ukraine war ceasefire demand, in a reversal that aligns him with Russia’s Putin, splits with European allies</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, with the backing of European leaders, has previously insisted that a ceasefire must be in place before any negotiations to end the war. Russian President Vladimir Putin has long pushed for negotiations toward a final agreement that would allow fighting to continue in the meantime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0c97150-7a8d-11f0-95f8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 10:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky says he will meet with Trump in Washington on Monday to discuss Alaska summit</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky made the announcement after a “long and substantive” telephone conversation with President Donald Trump. He said the meeting on Monday would be used to “discuss all of the details regarding ending the killing and the war.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b4223c0-7a7f-11f0-92a5-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 08:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Air Canada cancels hundreds of flights as a strike involving some 10,000 flight attendants takes effect</title>
      <description>The strike means most Air Canada flights will be grounded, including international flights, a union spokesperson said. More than 600 flights have been canceled, with more expected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0a065b0-7a64-11f0-bb84-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 05:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Gavin Newsom and other Democrats roll out a new map to counteract a GOP plan to redraw districts in Texas and other states</title>
      <description>The new California map would add up to five more Democratic House seats, likely wiping out the gains Republicans hope to make in Texas and intensifying a brutal national redistricting fight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b59f80b0-7a35-11f0-85a2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 00:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Putin signal no concrete agreement on Ukraine, take no questions after breaking off summit early</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin emerged sober-faced from their closed-door talks, exchanging niceties but acknowledging that no final deal had been reached to achieve peace in Ukraine. Trump said he would soon be speaking to Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, along with European leaders, to continue the push for agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ddba520-7a30-11f0-8cf9-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 23:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After more than three hours of private talks in Alaska, Trump and Putin prepare to take reporters' questions. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and Russian President Vladimir Putin's high-stakes talks Friday held the potential to end the Kremlin’s war in Ukraine and shape the course of security in Europe for a generation. Trump said on his way to Anchorage that he is optimistic that "something’s going to come of it."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13f0700-7a26-11f0-b01c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 22:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge: D.C. police chief remains in command, but Trump can demand help on immigration</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Ana C. Reyes did not issue a ruling but got attorneys for D.C. and the Justice Department to hash out an agreement that preserves local control of the police department. The judge also said Friday that President Donald Trump likely had the legal authority to get help from local police on immigration enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf59e591-7a21-11f0-b5ba-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 21:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Witkoff and Rubio land in Anchorage for talks with Russian President Vladimir Putin, with Ukraine peace on the line</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump, who is joined by special envoy Steve Witkoff and Secretary of State Marco Rubio, has said he will know quickly whether the meeting will be productive and will end it early if warranted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3d22280-7a07-11f0-9795-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michigan football receives array of fines and suspensions for sign-stealing operation uncovered during national championship season</title>
      <description>The NCAA’s announcement Friday marks the conclusion of a nearly two-year process that began when news broke early in the 2023 season that Connor Stalions, then a low-level member of then-coach Jim Harbaugh’s staff, allegedly coordinated an improper in-person scouting and sign-stealing operation against future Michigan opponents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd8ea700-79f0-11f0-b979-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first hurricane of the season has formed in the Atlantic. Erin could intensify into a major Category 4 storm by Monday.</title>
      <description>Erin will track close enough to the Caribbean islands to bring heavy rain, possible flooding and dangerous waves this weekend, even as the storm is expected to avoid landfall. The East Coast isn’t out of the woods for next week, with rip currents and rough surf expected. Bermuda may also see bad weather next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d29263d0-79eb-11f0-8792-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem is living for free in Coast Guard commandant's home in highly unusual arrangement</title>
      <description>Noem recently moved into Quarters 1, a spacious waterfront residence on a military base where the Coast Guard commandant typically resides and is not paying rent. Her spokesperson says the arrangement is because of concerns over the secretary's safety.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8807270-79e6-11f0-be40-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3083b7b1-79dc-11f0-9bef-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. attorney general sues Trump administration as federal government seeks to exert more control over city's police department</title>
      <description>The announcement came hours after U.S. Attorney General Pam Bondi ordered sweeping changes to law enforcement policies in the city and said a Trump official should assume all duties and responsibilities of the police chief.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d064300-79d7-11f0-b127-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 12:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Putin. ICE expansion. D.C. police. Kids’ vaccines. Looming hurricane. Alcohol poll. Hairy toothpaste. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f737f350-79c6-11f0-92ac-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bowser, D.C. attorney general reject Bondi move to name emergency police commissioner in first major pushback to federal takeover</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser and D.C. Attorney General Brian Schwalb said the order by Attorney General Pam Bondi — which also ordered sweeping changes to D.C. police polices — was unlawful and suggested they would not comply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">676e9fc0-7990-11f0-b508-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Pam Bondi orders D.C. mayor to recognize DEA chief as ‘emergency police commissioner’</title>
      <description>In a signed order, Attorney General Pam Bondi said Terrance Cole, head of the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration, should assume all powers and duties of the chief of police and that the department’s top officers “must receive approval” from him before issuing any directives. Bondi said Cole's appointment would last through President Donald Trump’s emergency declaration in the District.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4596a240-7980-11f0-bf0d-0000a1ace568</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police chief expands cooperation with ICE as federal agents ramp up immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>D.C. Police Chief Pamela A. Smith issued an order Thursday that officers may now assist federal immigration enforcement efforts by sharing information about people not in custody, including those encountered at traffic stops. They may also assist by transporting federal immigration agency employees and their detained suspects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb78d3f0-795b-11f0-8d5d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS is reviving a childhood vaccine safety task force, fulfilling a demand from anti-vaccine activists</title>
      <description>The committee is tasked with issuing recommendations to develop and refine childhood vaccines with “fewer and less serious adverse reactions.” An anti-vaccine group founded by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. funded a lawsuit against the health agency to force the revival of the task force, raising concerns from vaccine experts about the motivations of a new committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd15d2f0-793f-11f0-b09f-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP is betting Latino Trump voters will keep them in power. That’s no sure thing.</title>
      <description>The congressional maps that Texas Republicans are drawing to boost their chances of keeping control of Congress depend, to varying degrees, on preserving their gains with Hispanic voters. But that doesn’t mean they’ve locked these voters down, according to conversations with more than two dozen Latino voters, elected officials and strategists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95ae8f60-7938-11f0-b946-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who threw sandwich at law enforcement was Justice Department employee and has been fired, AG Bondi says</title>
      <description>Police allege that Sean Charles Dunn began yelling obscenities at officers in D.C., including Metro Transit Police and U.S. Customs and Border Protection officials. Dunn allegedly told one of his arresting officers: “I did it. I threw a sandwich.” Attorney General Pam Bondi said Thursday that he had been fired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6d09ee0-792a-11f0-8c3c-0000a1ace725</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b74772-7928-11f0-a609-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The two reasons Americans aren’t having babies, according to data</title>
      <description>An analysis of where Americans keep having babies reveals what works.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bcd1e80-7920-11f0-ad2c-0000a1ace1bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill in the blank in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8ad3e91-7912-11f0-8296-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift’s new album is inspired by the Eras Tour, and 4 other takeaways from her interview on Travis Kelce’s podcast</title>
      <description>During a conversation that was unprecedented in both length and tone, she talked about everything, casually, as if she were just hanging out with her family or friends — while millions of people watched. Here are five highlights from the episode of “New Heights,” the sports podcast co-hosted by her boyfriend, Kansas City Chiefs star Travis Kelce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50deaaa0-7906-11f0-bb84-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. protests. Foreign aid. Kennedy Center. Tropical storm. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Ancient teeth. Rabbit ‘tentacles.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc217890-78fd-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance becomes the latest affluent American to fall for England’s storybook vacation spot</title>
      <description>The vice president’s family is vacationing in the Cotswolds. Ellen DeGeneres has made it a home. Kourtney Kardashian recently called it a “dreamy storybook fairy tale.” For the region’s tourism industry and real estate brokers, the American market is a goldmine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34c35fb0-7888-11f0-ac65-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer changes you, but I never saw my new hair coming</title>
      <description>It’s not clear why chemotherapy gave me curls, Rachel Manteuffel writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb481381-7884-11f0-8010-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c32deb60-7862-11f0-9bac-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will host this year’s Kennedy Center Honors. The class includes Sylvester Stallone, Gloria Gaynor and Kiss.</title>
      <description>The annual production may see significant changes under President Donald Trump, who revealed the honorees during a visit to the arts complex on Wednesday. The list also includes George Strait and Michael Crawford.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f002080-785f-11f0-8b2d-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b536cf0-7857-11f0-9ac6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
