<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 20:02:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Crashes involving Tesla’s Full Self-Driving prompt new federal probe of system’s use in low-visibility conditions</title>
      <description>Car safety regulators opened an investigation into four crashes, including one that killed a pedestrian. The new probe appears to be taking a more direct look at the technology underpinning the Full Self-Driving system, which relies on cameras to guide Tesla vehicles without the aid of other kinds of sensors. The system is available in more than 2 million vehicles, though not all Tesla owners pay for the FSD package.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">448108f0-8d72-11ef-a295-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 16:58:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hotel sometimes charged Secret Service 300 percent or more above government rates during his presidency, House Democrats find</title>
      <description>Trump’s D.C. hotel sometimes charged the protective agency more than it did other patrons, including a foreign royal family, House Democrats found. Republicans dismissed the report as misleading and outdated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6414a240-8d62-11ef-a98e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:05:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21613511-8d55-11ef-bebf-0000a1acec6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 13:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas leader. Harris vs. Trump. Secret Service. Postponed execution. Winter weather. Subscriptions. Mount Vernon. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f68a5f0-8d40-11ef-9a98-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How just saying ‘vote’ can cause Instagram to suppress your posts</title>
      <description>Washington Post tech columnist Geoffrey Fowler shows how Meta’s Instagram, Facebook and Threads are reducing content related to the election in people’s feeds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f73d1380-8ce1-11ef-8c6b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 23:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs threw parties like a ‘modern-day Gatsby.’ New accusations cast the star-studded events in a dark light.</title>
      <description>Until recently, most of the abuse accusations against Combs had focused on the alleged sex parties he called “freak-offs.” Now his troubles have prompted a closer examination of his White Parties, which one accuser says had a sinister side from the very beginning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13643d30-8ccf-11ef-bfc6-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 21:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia men’s basketball coach Tony Bennett to retire, effective immediately</title>
      <description>Bennett, 55, will announce his retirement during a news conference Friday morning, the basketball program announced on Thursday. The unexpected news comes just weeks before Bennett was set to begin his 16th season with the Cavaliers. He is one of the most decorated active coaches in the country, guiding Virginia to two ACC tournament titles and the 2019 national championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff9eff60-8cc9-11ef-a7ec-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 20:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mitzi Gaynor dies at 93. The song-and-dance queen starred in 1950s Hollywood musicals such as ‘South Pacific.’</title>
      <description>The vivacious Hollywood musical star later gained a wide following with TV variety-show specials and her long-running cabaret act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8c16690-8cb4-11ef-baf3-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 18:23:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury formally indicts alleged Georgia school shooter, 14, and his father on dozens of additional charges</title>
      <description>Colt Gray, the accused shooter, was arrested and charged last month with four counts of felony murder for allegedly shooting and killing two students and two teachers on Sept. 4 at Apalachee High School in Winder, Ga. A Barrow County grand jury indicted him on 55 counts tied to the shooting, which wounded nine other students. Colin Gray, the alleged shooter’s father who was arrested and charged last month on second-degree murder and manslaughter charges, was indicted by the same grand jury on 29 total charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7886e30-8cb0-11ef-b983-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar, architect of the Oct. 7 attacks, killed in Gaza, Israeli official confirms</title>
      <description>Sinwar planned last year’s deadly assault on southern Israel, setting off a devastating war in Gaza that has rippled across the Middle East. He was killed by the Israeli military in Gaza after eluding their forces for more than a year, and his body was identified after DNA testing in Israel, an Israeli official said. Hamas did not immediately confirm his death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a154ecb0-8ca3-11ef-b73a-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Ukrainian President Zelensky ‘should never have let that war start’ with Russia</title>
      <description>Russia invaded Ukraine in February 2022. Former president Donald Trump made his comment in a podcast published Thursday. Trump has reportedly maintained a relationship with Russian President Vladimir Putin since leaving the White House and said this week that “Russia has never had a president that they respect so much.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2839ec50-8ca2-11ef-b14a-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Do good husbands leave the ‘half-dressed’ damsels on the stoop?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Do good husbands leave the ‘half-dressed’ damsels on the stoop?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cdf38a0-8ca1-11ef-a038-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 16:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five key moments from Kamala Harris’s heated Fox News interview</title>
      <description>Harris sparred with Fox chief political anchor Bret Baier as they discussed issues including immigration, gender-affirming surgery and her differences with President Joe Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0102ce90-8c9d-11ef-bdc9-0000a1ace5b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel is investigating whether Hamas leader Yahya Sinwar was killed. A body has been taken for DNA testing, Israeli official says.</title>
      <description>The Israeli military says Sinwar, the architect of the Oct. 7 attacks, may have been killed in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">720050d0-8c8f-11ef-9eea-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:55:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A multifaceted history lesson in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08c3bb50-8c8c-11ef-bfc6-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 13:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service needs a major shake-up and new leadership team after Trump rally shooting, independent review says</title>
      <description>The independent panel called for outsiders to lead the Secret Service, saying the protective agency needs a major overhaul to prevent security failures such as the July 13 shooting at a Donald Trump campaign rally in Butler, Pa. President Joe Biden called for the panel after a gunman fired shots that killed one and injured Trump and others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aabaf891-8c7f-11ef-a520-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 12:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris on Fox News. JD Vance. Liam Payne. Gaza plan. Surrogacy law. CEO pay. Penguin nests. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f346d5b0-8c76-11ef-a6c1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge blocks array of new rules approved by pro-Trump election board</title>
      <description>The ruling prevents implementation of a series of decisions that critics had said threatened to cause chaos in the battleground state this election season. The judge admonished the board, a majority of whom are aligned with former president Donald Trump, calling the rules “ILLEGAL, UNCONSTITUTIONAL AND VOID.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dc96cb0-8c13-11ef-a412-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 23:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liam Payne dies at 31. The former One Direction singer died after a fall in Argentina.</title>
      <description>The English-born singer died after falling from the third floor of his room at the CasaSur Palermo hotel in Buenos Aires, according to the city’s emergency medical services director, Alberto Crescenti. The official said the circumstances of the fall are still unclear and under investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bc8a581-8c12-11ef-9eea-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 22:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears the way for Biden crackdown on planet-warming pollution from power plants</title>
      <description>Wednesday’s denial of an emergency appeal by more than two dozen Republican-led states, utilities and others allows one of President Joe Biden’s most sweeping climate policies to remain in effect while lower-court battles continue. The rule, finalized in April, requires all coal-fired power plants that operate beyond 2039 and new natural gas-fired power plants to reduce their carbon emissions by 90 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">439cfec0-8bf7-11ef-9ee7-0000a1acecbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 19:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia school shooting suspect kept a ‘shrine’ to previous school shootings in his bedroom, investigators say in court</title>
      <description>Investigators say Colt Gray — the suspect in the deadly Sept. 4 shooting at Apalachee High School in Winder, Ga. — maintained a “shrine” inside his bedroom to previous school shootings, which they said included a photo of Parkland, Fla., gunman Nikolas Cruz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba7a64d0-8bf0-11ef-a9a0-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: What are some healthy meals that take 5 minutes or less to make? Ask our food writers.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: What are some healthy meals that take 5 minutes or less to make? Ask our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b27c4b1-8bdd-11ef-866c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italy passes West's strictest international anti-surrogacy law, effectively barring gay couples from becoming parents</title>
      <description>The law threatens would-be parents who use birth mothers abroad with jail time and severe fines in a move that critics say will chiefly target same-sex couples. Adoption, IVF and domestic surrogacy are already banned for gay couples in Italy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d3d6580-8bdb-11ef-b54e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:28:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Perks of dating a prominent man stir up old sibling rivalry</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Perks of dating a prominent man stir up old sibling rivalry</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ff44140-8bd9-11ef-b3b3-000a1ace9981</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 16:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 2025 ex-director condemns ‘violent rhetoric’ from president of the conservative Heritage Foundation</title>
      <description>Paul Dans, who led the right-wing policy and personnel blueprint Project 2025 until July, also called on Republican vice presidential nominee JD Vance to withdraw his foreword for Heritage President Kevin Roberts’s book.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d63ea8a1-8bca-11ef-84e1-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 14:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A welcome return in the nation’s capital in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9c8a1a0-8bc2-11ef-92f9-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign. Harris on Fox. Middle East. Hurricane relief. Tyron McAlpin. ‘Don’t Ask Don’t Tell.’ Hidden tomb. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8c8f171-8bad-11ef-a446-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge blocks requirement that counties hand-count ballots</title>
      <description>Critics said the new requirement, instituted by a pro-Trump majority on the state election board, would have almost certainly led to errors and could have disrupted the process of certifying the vote in a crucial battleground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">316e5e60-8b61-11ef-ba55-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 01:51:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change may be coming for your house. Look up your level of risk.</title>
      <description>The growing threat of extreme weather is starting to drag down home prices in the most exposed neighborhoods. Here are the tools you need to assess your risk and protect yourself.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a9f9e40-8b41-11ef-bc83-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 22:03:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBA fund for disaster victims is out of money, Biden says, after two hurricanes recently struck the Southeast</title>
      <description>The Small Business Administration’s disaster loan program is a critical lifeline to small businesses, homeowners and renters affected by disasters. Hurricanes Helene and Milton have strained the government’s ability to respond, though FEMA still has money available for grants and assistance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e2367b0-8b36-11ef-927c-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse is aware of husband’s affair and ‘not really bothered by it’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse is aware of husband’s affair and ‘not really bothered by it’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b87df440-8b0e-11ef-80d8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. may halt arms transfers to Israel unless humanitarian situation in Gaza improves, Biden administration warns</title>
      <description>The Biden administration intensified pressure on Israel this week to improve dire humanitarian conditions in the Gaza Strip, warning that the United States would be forced to undertake new actions — including a potential suspension of military assistance — if food and other aid to Palestinians is not increased within a month. Since the spring, the amount of aid delivered to Gaza “has dropped by more than 50 percent,” the United States says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46ff2420-8b08-11ef-9efe-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 15:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘climate of chaos’ went unchecked at this maximum-security psychiatric hospital, culminating in a brawl, rape and death</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found that officials didn’t act on staff complaints about violence at Clifton T. Perkins Hospital Center in Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d55178a1-8afd-11ef-9b04-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 14:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An icy moon of this planet is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4037cab0-8afa-11ef-b185-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 13:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris vs. Trump. Israel’s plan. Helene misinformation. Jupiter mission. Covid impacts. Home values. Giant pandas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f87d2f0-8ae4-11ef-8513-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s a vast divide between Republicans and Democrats over fast food, our Department of Data found</title>
      <description>Campaign finance reports revealed strikingly partisan preferences for various restaurants, with few more polarizing than McDonald’s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff708770-8a7b-11ef-8cb6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is waging a campaign against real-time fact checks</title>
      <description>The Trump campaign is pushing TV networks, journalism organizations and others to abandon the practice if they hope to interact with the Republican nominee. The moves are the latest example of his long-held resistance to being called to account for his falsehoods, which have formed the bedrock of his political message for years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ab885e0-8a6f-11ef-86d7-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 21:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two giant pandas are departing China for D.C. Visitors will have to wait at least several weeks to see them at the National Zoo.</title>
      <description>Qing Bao, a 3-year-old female, and Bao Li, a 3-year-old male, are being transported to D.C., officials in China said. Veterinarians and zookeepers are escorting the bears, whose arrival will resume a beloved animal conservation program in Washington that goes back more than a half-century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95edf1a1-8a5f-11ef-972d-0000a1ace132</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 19:07:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six new lawsuits accuse Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs of sexual assault, including at his famous White Parties</title>
      <description>A 16-year-old male who attended one of the parties is among the accusers who filed civil lawsuits against Combs on Monday. Combs has remained in federal custody since his arrest last month on sex trafficking and racketeering charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f4edc10-8a5d-11ef-bdd9-000a1ace161c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 18:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NASA’s Europa Clipper launched from the Kennedy Space Center on a mission to see if a moon of Jupiter can sustain life</title>
      <description>The $5 billion mission, decades in the making, seeks to investigate ice-encrusted Europa, which appears to have a subsurface ocean and has long been identified by scientists as potentially habitable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e7da7d0-8a47-11ef-8463-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom pesters adult son about his budding online romance</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom pesters adult son about his budding online romance</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a633a30-8a45-11ef-8a4b-0000a1ace85d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane recovery officials in N.C. relocated amid report of ‘armed militia,’ email shows, underscoring threat of misinformation</title>
      <description>The setback is one of the latest examples of growing concerns about safety and security among federal responders to Helene in North Carolina. On Monday, authorities said they arrested an individual for making alleged threats against FEMA workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06cf1aa0-8a44-11ef-b002-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada expels 6 Indian diplomats, alleging wider campaign by Modi government against Sikhs</title>
      <description>India’s top diplomat in Ottawa, Sanjay Kumar Verma, was among those ordered to leave the country, Canadian officials said.

A statement by India’s Ministry of External Affairs said the government “strongly rejects these preposterous imputations.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e07fc70-8a3d-11ef-b256-0000a1ace514</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 15:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This person is sending a message in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc9db100-8a30-11ef-9a0d-0000a1ace2d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 13:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election polls. Middle East. Hurricane recovery. China threats. ER shortages. Marathon record. SpaceX. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72430680-8a1b-11ef-b256-0000a1ace514</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in economics awarded to Daron Acemoglu, Simon Johnson and James A. Robinson</title>
      <description>The prize was awarded Monday to the three, who work at U.S. universities, “for studies of how institutions are formed and affect prosperity.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c8fd490-8a13-11ef-84e8-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘It’s devastating’: Asheville braces for peak tourism season without visitors after Helene changed everything</title>
      <description>Tourism brought nearly $3 billion to North Carolina’s Buncombe County last year. Now, Asheville’s businesses are entering what would normally be a prosperous October with the prospect of earning little to no revenue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7526951-89ab-11ef-9c7a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 21:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal flood maps vastly underestimated the threat in places hit hardest by Hurricane Helene, Post analysis shows</title>
      <description>Federal Emergency Management Agency flood maps identified just 2 percent of properties in the mountainous areas of western North Carolina as within the “Special Flood Hazard Area” that is at risk of a 1-in-100-year flood. A Washington Post analysis of data from First Street, a climate modeling group, found that the number of properties at risk could be seven times higher than what FEMA flood maps indicate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0439bd40-8995-11ef-ad19-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 18:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. will send an antimissile system and personnel to Israel to counter potential attacks from Iran, Pentagon says</title>
      <description>The Terminal High Altitude Area Defense missile system, or THAAD, will strengthen Israel’s defenses against an attack from Iran or its proxies, Pentagon spokesman Pat Ryder said in a statement. Israeli officials have said they will retaliate against Iran for the barrage of ballistic missiles it fired at Israel this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07f58000-8985-11ef-916d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">282f23b0-897d-11ef-9e58-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 16:06:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
