<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 02:29:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Aryna Sabalenka of Belarus wins second straight U.S. Open championship, defeating American Amanda Anisimova</title>
      <description>It is the fourth Grand Slam title for Sabalenka, the top-ranked player in the world. Anisimova, who also finished as the runner-up at Wimbledon this year, had been seeking her first Grand Slam championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b889f40-8b6d-11f0-8f5e-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 22:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>West Point alumni group cancels award ceremony for Tom Hanks as Trump-era political controversies grip military academy</title>
      <description>Hanks, who starred in “Saving Private Ryan” and other films depicting U.S. service members and who has for decades advocated for veterans, was to receive a prestigious award from the West Point alumni association at an event this month. The decision to cancel the ceremony follows political moves that have rattled the military institution since President Donald Trump’s return to power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af0aa290-8b36-11f0-be68-0000a1acec58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davey Johnson dies at 82. The former Washington Nationals manager guided the New York Mets to the World Series title in 1986.</title>
      <description>Johnson led the Nationals from 2011 to 2013, including their breakthrough 2012 season, when they reached the postseason for the first time. He also starred as a player with the Baltimore Orioles, winning the World Series in 1966 and 1970.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7569ff11-8b2f-11f0-be41-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After life-altering brain surgery, a songwriter’s creativity flourished</title>
      <description>Removing a piece of his brain, Mike Frazier and his doctors thought, was his best option for combating a condition that affects about 1 percent of adults in the United States and tens of millions of people worldwide — but that is still often misunderstood and misdiagnosed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0880a351-8b2e-11f0-99d8-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 14:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60689490-8b26-11f0-b340-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 13:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 must-see films to watch this fall</title>
      <description>It’s the time of year when filmdom starts showing off a fresher, more original palette. These are our top picks, including a Bruce Springsteen biopic and Daniel Day-Lewis’s return to acting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3840fef0-8ab6-11f0-a1c2-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 00:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland leaders announce police surge in Baltimore amid Trump’s threats to deploy National Guard to city</title>
      <description>The state and city will deploy more resources to violence interruption groups and state prosecutors through a partnership that Gov. Wes Moore and Mayor Brandon Scott say has driven Baltimore’s homicide count to a 50-year low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a60b260-8aaf-11f0-9b2e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s rebranding of the Defense Department as the War Department is a worthy blow against euphemism, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>Perhaps the new name can be followed by clearer thinking about the military’s role at home and abroad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">972aa770-8aa4-11f0-a795-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 22:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts Trump officials from ending special status for Venezuelans and Haitians</title>
      <description>The decision from a federal judge in California could shield hundreds of thousands of people from possible deportation. DHS Secretary Kristi L. Noem had argued that conditions had improved enough in both countries for people to return, a finding that contradicted the State Department’s own travel warnings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cc266d1-8aa0-11f0-84d2-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 21:36:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI firm Anthropic agrees to pay landmark $1.5 billion settlement to book authors and publishers</title>
      <description>The company behind the chatbot Claude agreed to pay about $3,000 per book to avoid trial over claims it improperly downloaded millions of titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbe56410-8a8f-11f0-b2fd-0000a1ace475</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 19:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The uncomfortable truth about watching football</title>
      <description>The uncomfortable truth about watching football</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f444a90-8a8a-11f0-8634-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 500 workers, mostly South Koreans, arrested in immigration raid at Georgia Hyundai factory — largest of Trump’s new term</title>
      <description>Immigration officials alleged “serious federal crimes.” The Hyundai electric vehicle and battery production complex in Georgia has been hailed as “the largest project in state history.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74323910-8a84-11f0-b133-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two teens arrested in fatal D.C. shooting of college student who interned for GOP lawmaker, U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro says</title>
      <description>Two 17-year-olds have been charged as adults in D.C. Superior Court with first-degree murder while armed, Pirro said at a news conference Friday. A third suspect remains at large. Officials have said Eric Tarpinian-Jachym, who interned for Rep. Ron Estes (R-Kansas), was shot by a group of people who exited a car and opened fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17c991c0-8a78-11f0-9fb3-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Pushing partner to make amends for being an absent dad</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Pushing partner to make amends for being an absent dad</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">158de153-8a72-11f0-97e6-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 16:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our dining critic gave this popular D.C. restaurant zero stars in 2016. Has it improved?</title>
      <description>Tom Sietsema returns to Founding Farmers, one of Washington’s most popular restaurants, for a pulse check.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca962ef0-8a67-11f0-972f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e8de8d0-8a5c-11f0-9487-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. economy picked up 22,000 jobs in August but in June revisions lost jobs for first time since pandemic</title>
      <description>The Bureau of Labor Statistics reported fewer jobs in downward revisions to June job creation, in a warning sign about President Donald Trump’s tougher tariffs and immigration enforcement. In August, the unemployment rate ticked up to 4.3 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2795b020-8a55-11f0-aa54-0000a1ace7c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. hearing. ‘War Department.’ Stephen Miller. Labor market. Gun rules. Jobs for robots. Leaf-peeping. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78e881e0-8a47-11f0-8098-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlin Clark will miss remainder of the WNBA season with injury</title>
      <description>The Indiana Fever star's second season ends with her having appeared in just 13 games. Clark, who helped supercharge interest in the WNBA, has not played since July 15 as she has dealt with groin and ankle injuries. The Fever remains in playoff position but has been decimated by injuries and is not expected to contend for a title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82fad750-89f7-11f0-ac96-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress not planning a vote to extend Trump’s 30-day D.C. police takeover</title>
      <description>In allowing the Trump administration’s grip on D.C. police to come to an end, Congress closes one chapter in the tussle between local and federal officials vying for control of public safety in the capital. But for now, it appears unlikely that fewer federal agents or camouflage-clad troops will patrol city streets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e92f9d50-89f5-11f0-9a4f-0000a1aced0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 01:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The health risks from plastics almost nobody knows about</title>
      <description>Plastic chemicals, known as phthalates, are everywhere. The Washington Post reviewed more than 50 studies and interviewed more than two dozen scientists, former regulators and industry officials to document how the chemicals are eroding health in unexpected ways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cc50510-89e7-11f0-8674-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 23:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to change name of Defense Department to Department of War, a title the White House says more accurately reflects its mission</title>
      <description>The president is expected to sign an executive order Friday to make the change that "will sharpen the focus of this Department on our national interest and signal to adversaries America’s readiness to wage war to secure its interests," according to a document describing the forthcoming order obtained by The Washington Post. It's unclear if he can permanently change the name without legislation from Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3ab2f70-89e0-11f0-9673-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 22:43:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department issues subpoenas targeting Fed governor Lisa Cook in criminal probe, intensifying Trump’s efforts to oust her</title>
      <description>The White House has accused Cook of falsifying mortgage records to lenders as the Trump administration builds a legal and political case to remove her from the central bank’s board. A federal judge is considering Cook’s request to temporarily block President Donald Trump’s move and keep her on the board, which meets mid-September to consider interest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73429940-89d1-11f0-a812-0000a1ace45f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. clashed with a GOP senator over the availability of coronavirus vaccines, and other takeaways from his fiery hearing</title>
      <description>Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on Thursday defended his tenure in a roughly three-hour Senate hearing, following upheaval at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and frustration with his approach to vaccines. Here are the biggest takeaways from his testimony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">508d4500-89ca-11f0-9f26-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to end European security aid programs meant to thwart Russia, alarming allies and upsetting lawmakers</title>
      <description>The decision would impact hundreds of millions of dollars worth of military aid relied upon by some of NATO’s most vulnerable members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0225a7f0-89ba-11f0-b896-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon approves use of Chicago-area Navy base for ICE and possible military operations</title>
      <description>The Pentagon has approved the use of Naval Station Great Lakes, on the outskirts of Chicago, as a staging ground from which the Trump administration can launch operations against undocumented immigrants, said two defense officials familiar with the issue. If deployed, National Guard or active-duty service members could also be housed at the facility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">961c9080-89ac-11f0-9e29-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Drugged by a friend and spinning — in both senses</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Drugged by a friend and spinning — in both senses</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc75f20-89a8-11f0-9d52-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Federal Reserve pick plans to keep his White House job while serving on central bank, in unusual threat to Fed independence</title>
      <description>White House economic adviser Stephen Miran, if confirmed to the Federal Reserve, would not resign but would take a leave of absence from the White House, making him the first modern-day Federal Reserve Board member to maintain ties to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ce9e30-89a5-11f0-ac1c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. attorney general sues Trump over National Guard deployment, calling it an illegal ‘military occupation’</title>
      <description>The lawsuit seeks to force President Donald Trump to withdraw the nearly 2,300 National Guard members stationed in the nation’s capital. D.C. Attorney General Brian Schwalb said the involuntary deployment has infringed on the District’s limited autonomy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d3ac5e0-89a1-11f0-933d-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:12:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Democrats call for RFK Jr.’s resignation before he faces a grilling on vaccine policy. Follow live coverage of the hearing.</title>
      <description>Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is appearing before senators for the first time after turmoil at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The White House fired CDC director Susan Monarez after she resisted pressure from Kennedy to change vaccine policy, and three top CDC leaders resigned in protest. Calls for Kennedy's resignation have mounted from Democratic lawmakers, public health advocacy organizations and current and former HHS employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cf3cf00-8999-11f0-b36e-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This ‘beautiful locale’ is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82ba8681-8995-11f0-8ebf-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:46:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giorgio Armani dies at 91. The designer’s streamlined fashions ruled the red carpet for years.</title>
      <description>Giorgio Armani’s suits and couture gowns were a staple at awards shows. He debuted his first collection at age 40 in 1975, bringing elegance and refinement to the art of the power suit and revolutionizing the way modern men and women dress. “Elegance doesn’t mean being noticed,” he said. “It means being remembered.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c44772e0-8993-11f0-8c94-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccine mandates. Trump vs. Harvard. Epstein victims. Abortion pills. Putin hot mic. NFL kickoff. Toilet scrolling. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c0f96a1-897e-11f0-be8d-0000a1ace646</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration appeals lower-court ruling that invalidated his tariffs, potentially setting up blockbuster Supreme Court case</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court will now decide whether to hear the administration’s appeal to overturn a ruling that voided most of President Donald Trump’s tariffs on goods from dozens of nations. It could set up a case with huge implications for consumers, businesses, the U.S. economy and global trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02982e90-8967-11f0-91d1-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 08:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans will seek to permanently overhaul criminal justice in D.C. and further restrict home rule</title>
      <description>One of the draft bills would remove the locally elected D.C. attorney general and replace that official with a presidential appointee. The effort would represent a large step backward in the city's quest to expand its autonomy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2be050a0-892d-11f0-83b6-0000a1acec12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 01:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas moves to allow anyone to sue abortion pill prescribers, distributors in effort to stop flow of shipments from blue states</title>
      <description>Gov. Greg Abbott (R) is expected to sign a bill that would allow residents to sue doctors, pill-makers and distributors that supply the drugs to Texans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">851728b0-8928-11f0-8fdf-0000a1ace04d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:45:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $1.4 billion Powerball win sounds life-changing. Here’s the catch.</title>
      <description>Sudden wealth might seem like a dream come true, but it can’t shield you from poor choices, says our personal finance columnist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a055840-8916-11f0-a72f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. could have stopped boat allegedly trafficking drugs from Venezuela but Trump chose to blow it up, Rubio says</title>
      <description>The strike Tuesday on the vessel in the Caribbean, which U.S. officials said killed 11 people, was intended to send a message, Secretary of State Marco Rubio told reporters. “Instead of interdicting it, on the president’s orders, we blew it up,” he said. “And it’ll happen again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cc51510-8910-11f0-b575-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:50:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard wins court battle against Trump; administration cannot withhold federal funding, judge rules</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Boston ruled that the Trump administration illegally withheld billions from the Ivy League school for alleged violations of rules against antisemitism. The administration is expected to appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f989e440-8909-11f0-b575-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:07:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House Republicans vote to establish new subcommittee to reinvestigate Jan. 6</title>
      <description>Lawmakers slipped a resolution into a rule on the House floor that would establish a subcommittee to revisit the events of Jan. 6, 2021, in which pro-Trump protesters stormed the Capitol aiming to prevent Joe Biden's certification as president. Republicans have complained that the previous probe was biased against President Donald Trump, who has repeatedly denied he lost the 2020 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d5c4b1-8900-11f0-8242-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 20:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I resigned from the CDC. Here are three questions for RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>I resigned from the CDC. Here are three questions for RFK Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68025630-88e4-11f0-a7cd-0000a1ace239</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wedding opens new front in cold war with late wife’s sister</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wedding opens new front in cold war with late wife’s sister</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9eb35f60-88e1-11f0-89de-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida moves to end vaccine mandates to attend school, the first state to do so</title>
      <description>Florida Surgeon General Joseph A. Ladapo’s stances on vaccines and other measures have drawn criticism from public health experts and advocates, who have warned that the overhaul of vaccine policies could cause a resurgence of preventable diseases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18150d10-88e0-11f0-aea6-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A high-profile split in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">450a7551-88ca-11f0-8d52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportation ruling. Space Command. Epstein files. China parade. ChatGPT controls. Wildfires. SNL cast. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">241528f0-88b5-11f0-8956-0000a1acecc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appellate panel rejects Trump’s deportations under Alien Enemies Act</title>
      <description>The appellate panel ruled Tuesday that President Donald Trump unlawfully invoked the centuries-old wartime law to deport Venezuelan migrants, finding no invasion or “predatory incursion” had occurred to justify using the statute to fast-track migrant removals. The decision is widely expected to be appealed to the Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa0095f0-887c-11f0-a9d7-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At an ICE career expo, a Marine veteran and a former MMA fighter are among thousands vying to carry out Trump’s deportation agenda</title>
      <description>The administration is aiming to hire 10,000 new immigration officers next year, drumming up interest through militaristic branding and a signing bonus of up to $50,000 for top recruits. Applicants said they were not deterred by waning public support for the president's hardline approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88388041-8854-11f0-9464-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First batch of Epstein files released by Congress</title>
      <description>The House Oversight and Government Reform Committee released 33,295 pages of documents related to convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein. The committee said it was the first in a series of expected releases as a bipartisan group of lawmakers seeks more transparency from the Trump administration on the subject.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9285c392-884b-11f0-b797-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. conducts ‘lethal strike’ on alleged drug vessel in Caribbean, a dramatic escalation as Trump intensifies focus on cartels</title>
      <description>Administration officials said the operation targeted a boat that departed Venezuela and was operated by a “designated narco-terrorist organization.” It appeared to mark the first known time the Trump administration used deadly force to target illicit drug shipments originating in Latin America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d5da8f0-8842-11f0-802c-0000a1acefb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge bars Google from exclusive deals for its search engine but says it can keep Chrome in high-profile monopoly case</title>
      <description>Judge Amit P. Mehta rejected prosecutors’ call to break up the Silicon Valley giant as he laid out remedies for his finding last year that it has an illegal monopoly in search.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22eea361-883e-11f0-aca6-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
