<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 20:03:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>IT consultant found guilty in fatal stabbing of Cash App founder Bob Lee, a case that shocked the tech world</title>
      <description>A San Francisco jury convicted Nima Momeni of second-degree murder, rejecting arguments that he was acting in self-defense during the April 2023 altercation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb27360-bca2-11ef-b9d6-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 18:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Are you a jerk for dialing back a one-sided friendship?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Are you a jerk for dialing back a one-sided friendship?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc892b90-bc99-11ef-a1f5-0000a1aceb67</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 17:10:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. wants fluoride out of drinking water — but about a dozen states require it</title>
      <description>Robert F. Kennedy Jr., President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run the nation’s health agency, wants to remove fluoride from drinking water. Fluoridation efforts have not followed traditional political lines. Here’s how common fluoridation is in each state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">740199c0-bc8c-11ef-bae0-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 15:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new biopic in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b33ecdf0-bc83-11ef-88df-000a1ace40c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 14:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School shooting. Moscow explosion. Trump ruling. Elon Musk. Health insurers. CNN report. ‘Dirty Dancing.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a1a8ec2-bc6e-11ef-b242-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of Russia’s nuclear defense forces killed in bombing, officials say</title>
      <description>An explosive device on a parked scooter near the entrance of a residential building killed Lt. Gen. Igor Kirillov and his assistant in Moscow on Tuesday morning, Russia’s Investigative Committee said in a statement shared on Telegram.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f97295a0-bc4b-11ef-b792-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 07:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police identify Wisconsin school shooter as a 15-year-old female student</title>
      <description>Authorities in Wisconsin said Natalie Rupnow was the Madison school shooter on Monday who killed a teenager and a teacher. Six others were wounded. Rupnow apparently died of a self-inflicted wound, police said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44c29440-bc21-11ef-bd30-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 02:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resident doctors call off strike at George Washington University Hospital as union, university reach labor agreement</title>
      <description>A union representing hundreds of resident doctors at GWU Hospital had threatened to go on strike if it did not secure a labor deal that included better pay and increased mental health benefits, among other provisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6012b020-bc14-11ef-9c5d-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 01:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two men with ties to Iran arrested in drone attack that killed three U.S. troops, wounded dozens in Jordan earlier this year</title>
      <description>The men are accused of violating export laws by leaking sensitive information on American technology to Iran that allegedly enabled the attack in January on a facility known as Tower 22, the Justice Department said Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29eff350-bc0e-11ef-9c5d-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.Y. judge rejects Trump’s effort to toss hush money conviction over presidential immunity</title>
      <description>The judge, Juan Merchan, denied President-elect Donald Trump’s motion to dismiss his 34-count hush money conviction, saying that last summer’s Supreme Court ruling on presidential immunity did not require him to overturn the jury’s verdict. Merchan must decide separately whether to sentence Trump before he takes office next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">633630e0-bc0c-11ef-9c5d-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:18:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana decertifies an ex-police officer who sexually abused a teen in his patrol car. It took 2 years and a Post investigation.</title>
      <description>The state took action against former South Bend officer Timothy Barber after a Washington Post story about his abuse of a 16-year-old girl. He had kept his law enforcement certification for more than two years, despite pleading guilty in 2022 to child seduction and official misconduct and registering as a sex offender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aa262c1-bc01-11ef-bd13-0000a1ace65f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 22:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South America’s most dangerous gang is invading the Amazon forest and threatening its most isolated peoples</title>
      <description>The Brazilian criminal organization PCC is expanding into environmental crime, including illegal gold mining and timber extraction. That has deepened the Amazon’s peril, introducing an unpredictable new level of criminality to the biome.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">178b9850-bbf9-11ef-847c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 21:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A teacher and a student were killed in Wisconsin shooting, police say, revising death toll. The shooter was a teen student.</title>
      <description>The shooter, who is also dead, was a student at Abundant Life Christian School, Madison Police Chief Shon Barnes said at a news conference Monday. Officials are not releasing the student’s age or gender, and they had not identified a motive as of Monday afternoon, Barnes said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fcdc5b0-bbf1-11ef-847c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 21:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student kills four people at a Christian school in Madison, Wisconsin, police chief says</title>
      <description>A juvenile killed four people and injured five at Abundant Life Christian School, the Madison police chief said Monday. The shooter is also dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa823040-bbdd-11ef-9c5d-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not even Andrew Jackson would use this long-dormant constitutional weapon to dismiss Congress. Could Trump?</title>
      <description>How a long-ago fight over a dormant constitutional weapon echoes today</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfb2be80-bbdb-11ef-94d3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 18:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How do grandkids learn life skills if the parents outsource chores?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How do grandkids learn life skills if the parents outsource chores?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6937be60-bbcf-11ef-9efd-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 17:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council committee votes to recommend expelling indicted Ward 8 Democrat Trayon White Sr.</title>
      <description>The unanimous vote of the ad hoc committee, which is made up of all members of the council except White, comes after a report found “substantial evidence” of rules violations following his indictment on a federal bribery charge. White has pleaded not guilty to the federal charge and can mount a defense against his proposed expulsion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3880e025-bbcb-11ef-a85f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deny and delay: The practices fueling anger at U.S. health insurers</title>
      <description>Doctors say treatment increasingly is being delayed by demands for pre-authorization — or denied outright. Many consumers don’t know they can appeal. Some states are trying to help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">525a3980-bbc9-11ef-942b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 16:18:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>German Chancellor Olaf Scholz loses confidence vote, triggering early elections for Europe’s largest economy</title>
      <description>The parliamentary elections will take place Feb. 23, seven months earlier than the standard schedule. The latest opinion polls suggest a rightward shift in the results and a next chancellor who would cut welfare benefits, take a harder line on migration policy and lift restrictions on weapons use by Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22ced861-bbc4-11ef-85ce-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 15:40:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A spicy question in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">765c0cf0-bbba-11ef-8e16-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 14:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris. Trump lawsuit. UnitedHealthcare CEO. Cyclone. Murder exoneration. Cruise protests. Fugitive dog. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45724790-bba5-11ef-acd7-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so many in western North Carolina are hesitant to seek FEMA help after Hurricane Helene</title>
      <description>Many local residents battered by the hurricane don’t trust the federal response, threatening the region’s recovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9f25100-bb34-11ef-b792-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 22:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turkey exploits post-9/11 counterterrorism model to target critics in exile, a Post investigation shows</title>
      <description>Turkey has used renditions, secret detentions, terrorism watch lists, asset seizures and torture against exiles, according to U.N. documents and human rights groups. Turkish officials said they are targeting people they have charged as terrorists and that Ankara abides by legal processes that the United States often bypassed in its own operations against terrorist groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164748a0-bb21-11ef-817c-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">338e81f1-bb06-11ef-83f4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 17:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whataburger is going national — and disappointing some loyal fans along the way</title>
      <description>As the brand continues to grow after Chicago-based BDT Capital Partners bought it in 2019, it faces the same existential question as any beloved regional business attempting to scale: Can it maintain the Texan values that made people fall in love with it? Or will it become indistinguishable from every other burger joint on the highway?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c1dc890-bafe-11ef-83f4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Need a holiday cookie idea? Use our generator to find recipes for every taste, craving and occasion.</title>
      <description>Need a holiday cookie idea? Use our generator to find recipes for every taste, craving and occasion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ad9e930-baf8-11ef-a87c-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 15:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33267de0-baf1-11ef-927e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 14:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado's Travis Hunter wins Heisman Trophy. He is first two-way player since 1997 to earn NCAA football's top individual honor.</title>
      <description>Hunter, a junior wide receiver and cornerback, beat out fellow finalists Ashton Jeanty of Boise State, Dillon Gabriel of Oregon and Cam Ward of Miami to become the first Heisman winner to play regular snaps on both offense and defense since Michigan's Charles Woodson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba526cd1-ba87-11ef-b05b-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 01:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado's Travis Hunter offers a lesson on Heisman Trophy weekend: He is one of one</title>
      <description>https://washpost.slack.com/archives/C0DTU30BS/p1734211920786649</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">daae47e0-ba66-11ef-a233-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 22:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President-elect Trump wants his daughter-in-law in the Senate. DeSantis has a big choice to make.</title>
      <description>Lara Trump’s interest in replacing Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Florida), Donald Trump’s pick for secretary of state, complicates an already fraught relationship between Trump and the state’s Republican governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec4264f0-ba57-11ef-ab15-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 20:13:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho offers little help for families needing child care. As many scrimp to afford it, one family-run center is buckling.</title>
      <description>TLC for Tots has seen an entire generation of little ones since Krystal McFarlane’s parents founded it in 2006. But economics are bearing down hard these days — one reason for a child-care crisis that is nationwide — and the red state’s leaders maintain that government isn’t the solution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143cfef0-ba4b-11ef-bc10-0000a1ace67d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I maintain a distant relationship with my in-laws?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I maintain a distant relationship with my in-laws?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32a49e90-ba3f-11ef-8160-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 10 new holiday cookie recipes are a gift worth giving</title>
      <description>These 10 new holiday cookie recipes are a gift worth giving</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1650dae1-ba37-11ef-b03d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 16:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In this million-dollar go-kart scene, some kids arrive in helicopters. Some have bodyguards.</title>
      <description>Go-karting has become a magnet for the money and power flowing through motorsports. It is now the wildly expensive first step to the exclusive world of Formula One racing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">644fe663-ba2c-11ef-b0de-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 15:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2fd6b81-ba27-11ef-9be8-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol impeached after decision to declare martial law</title>
      <description>Yoon must immediately hand over power to the prime minister, who will act as caretaker while the courts review the impeachment vote. The process could take months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26a47130-b9f2-11ef-ad81-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plans to allow California to ban sales of new gas-powered cars by 2035. Trump could try to reverse the move.</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to grant the state the right to set stronger climate rules for cars, SUVs and pickup trucks as soon as next week, according to two people briefed on the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the decision is not yet public. President-elect Donald Trump will probably try to reverse the move, although those efforts could run into legal obstacles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d85231-b9a4-11ef-ab42-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 22:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian rebels hand over American Travis Timmerman to U.S. troops near the country’s border with Jordan, photos show</title>
      <description>Timmerman, a Missouri native who has said he was taken prisoner after crossing into Syria months ago, was discovered in the days since Bashar al-Assad’s ouster as the country’s long-ruling dictator. On Friday, Timmerman was escorted by the rebels to a U.S. military garrison in southeastern Syria and later flown by helicopter to Jordan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99bd0f10-b993-11ef-998a-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 20:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia is packing up military equipment in Syria after the fall of ally Bashar al-Assad, satellite imagery shows</title>
      <description>Images released by Maxar show cargo planes at a Russian airfield in Syria with their nose cones opened to receive heavy equipment. Russian S-400 air defense systems have also been moved. Assad fled Syria for Moscow this week as rebels took control of the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d66c74d0-b97c-11ef-a430-0000a1ace05f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax live chat: My stepson’s mom hits on my husband and is cold to me</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax live chat: My stepson’s mom hits on my husband and is cold to me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62451290-b979-11ef-adc9-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Uyghur man escaped from China, then was deported back. He has not been heard from since.</title>
      <description>The secret repatriation from Cambodia of 23-year-old Abdureqip Rahman is a chilling example of how China exerts its will extrajudicially outside its borders, not only over Southeast Asian countries but also international bodies — including the United Nations, whose systems were designed to protect the world’s most vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac699870-b96d-11ef-9737-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cb8c400-b960-11ef-adc9-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 report. Trump’s victory lap. Freed American. Electric vehicles. Bird die-off. Neanderthal babies. Meteors. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c73141e1-b949-11ef-aafd-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>François Bayrou named as prime minister of France as President Emmanuel Macron seeks stability after government collapse</title>
      <description>The new prime minister must now try to cobble together a government and get a handle on France’s spiraling deficit and debt burden — in a way that satisfies enough of the warring political factions to avoid everything crashing down again. The political and financial instability in France has unsettled broader Europe as it prepares for the Trump presidency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc0b0bb0-b948-11ef-aafd-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient DNA has helped pinpoint when humans had babies with Neanderthals</title>
      <description>Studies in the journals Science and Nature found that interbreeding unfolded for an extended period, peaking 47,000 years ago. Faint remnants of our Neanderthal ancestry remain, influencing skin pigmentation, immune response — even whether or not you’re a morning person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e6bf320-b8e1-11ef-9886-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 23:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin made saving the Assad regime his personal project. Its collapse in Syria shows the limits of Russia’s global power.</title>
      <description>Russia intervened with a massive show of airpower in 2015 to prevent Bashar al-Assad’s defeat by Syrian rebels. His fall this week has humiliated Moscow, dealing a blow to President Vladimir Putin’s goal of forging Russia into a great world power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ea5c4a0-b8dd-11ef-bfac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 23:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) takes aim at ‘sanctuary cities’ with proposal to require local law enforcement to work with ICE</title>
      <description>Youngkin said the state budget plan he will unveil next week will seek to require local law enforcement across the state to cooperate with federal immigration authorities. Fairfax and Arlington counties are among the localities that would have to start complying with requests from immigration officials. Youngkin’s proposal would still require approval by the General Assembly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779ef500-b8cc-11ef-8cc3-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 21:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. watchdog cites missteps in FBI intelligence gathering before Jan. 6, 2021, attack on U.S. Capitol</title>
      <description>The FBI properly shared the intelligence it gathered before the violent and chaotic riot with relevant law enforcement agencies but made some missteps that may have hampered preparations, including failing to canvas field offices for information that confidential human sources may have provided, according to a report released by the Justice Department’s inspector general. The FBI and Department of Homeland Security have been sharply criticized for what a Senate committee report described as a failure to believe the intelligence tips they received in the run up to the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ee0710-b8b4-11ef-8ca7-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Injured husband ignored spouse’s pleas to take care of himself</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Injured husband ignored spouse’s pleas to take care of himself</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1445eca0-b8ab-11ef-b4ea-000a1acec017</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This insect flies into today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc6b20f0-b895-11ef-9750-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
