<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 23:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Am I abandoning my family if I move overseas?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Am I abandoning my family if I move overseas?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27713ef0-f884-11f0-9312-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ice, power outage risks grow as D.C. area braces for winter snow storm</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service has placed the area under a winter storm warning from 11 p.m. Saturday through 4 a.m. Monday. The potential for heavy amounts of ice that could lead to power outages has increased, especially south and east of the Beltway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42640221-f883-11f0-b485-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 17:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘He treats us with contempt’: At Davos, Fareed Zakaria encounters a blunt reaction to Trump</title>
      <description>America’s allies may comply for now. But the damage to trust will have consequences, Zakaria writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53d81b70-f871-11f0-9a84-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19c47cc0-f868-11f0-bf23-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 12 cities will be hit hardest by the massive winter storm</title>
      <description>Around 205 million people across the country are under winter weather alerts for snow, ice or extreme cold ahead of the forming tempest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1005cd90-f860-11f0-a585-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:33:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger in Minnesota. Board of Peace. Jack Smith. Storm forecast. Slavery exhibit. Oscars. How to rebuild hope. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01e404a1-f853-11f0-9ee5-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharp drops in crime mean the U.S. may now be as safe as it was pre-pandemic</title>
      <description>The country remains in a multiyear trend of falling crime rates in cities nationwide, ushering in a period of relative safety, according to a Washington Post analysis of data from more than 100 police departments. The most striking changes are seen in homicide data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0161d9c0-f7fa-11f0-99d2-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 01:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says deal to spin off its U.S. business to non-Chinese investors has been finalized</title>
      <description>The divestiture from TikTok’s Beijing-based former parent company, ByteDance, means that the wildly popular app will continue to operate in the United States and will be owned by a consortium including tech company Oracle and private equity firm Silver Lake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0190da0-f7f4-11f0-9170-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service removes slavery exhibit at Independence Park in Philadelphia</title>
      <description>The exhibit was at the President’s House Site, where George Washington lived as president. The informational panels discussed Washington’s ownership of enslaved people, as well as the broader history of slavery, and included details about their lives. The Park Service has been removing information on historic racism, sexism, LGBTQ+ rights, slavery and climate change since last year as it carries out a Trump executive order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ad1c81-f7e8-11f0-be32-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes DHS funding bill despite Democratic opposition over ICE</title>
      <description>The House narrowly passed $1.2 trillion in government funding, overcoming intense Democratic opposition to funding Immigration and Customs Enforcement as the agency surges operations in Minneapolis and other cities. The Homeland Security funding bill would allocate $64.4 billion to the department, including $10 billion for ICE.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c74bf0-f7de-11f0-be32-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 22:05:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walmart found negligent for selling a shotgun used in a suicide</title>
      <description>A federal jury in Maryland awarded millions to the family of Jacob Mace, a store employee who bought the gun on his lunch hour. Mace’s family said managers knew Mace was suicidal and did nothing to ensure that he couldn’t buy a gun from the store.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24456360-f7d4-11f0-a44a-0000a1ace390</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 20:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI is investigating the death of Colts owner Jim Irsay. He had been receiving opioids and ketamine from a recovery doctor.</title>
      <description>A federal grand jury subpoena, reviewed by The Washington Post, shows the agency is seeking records and information relating to Irsay’s death in May, his “substance (illegal and prescription) use” and his “relationship with Dr. Harry Haroutunian,” a prominent addiction specialist based in California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4016d9b0-f7c6-11f0-ae1c-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sues JPMorgan and its CEO over cutting off his banking access, seeking at least $5 billion in damages</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump alleged that JPMorgan Chase improperly closed his accounts in 2021 and blacklisted him and his family from doing business with the firm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e89ce2f0-f7c1-11f0-9c39-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump budget office orders review of federal funding for 13 Democratic-controlled states and D.C.</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is looking to cut off resources for “sanctuary” jurisdictions that refuse to collaborate with immigration enforcement authorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70cf58e1-f7ba-11f0-a0ca-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ says it arrested activists accused of helping organize anti-ICE protest at a Minnesota church that became a flash point</title>
      <description>The protest, which interrupted church services, has drawn widespread condemnation from online right-wing influencers and vows from top Justice Department officials that demonstrators will be prosecuted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f9b130-f7b0-11f0-bde5-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This obsession has held Iran back for a half-century</title>
      <description>Time and again, idealism untethered from reality has brought ruin to Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b22c8d0-f7ad-11f0-b878-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 16:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about the high-impact winter storm expected to slam the area this weekend</title>
      <description>The main question is how much snow will fall and whether precipitation will change to an icy mix, coating snow, trees and power lines with a hazardous glaze. Substantial snowfall of at least 4 to 8 inches is likely before any change to ice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17c861e0-f7a8-11f0-92ef-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘One of the greatest stories of all time’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e4fa720-f79f-11f0-aa7a-0000a1ace763</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Sinners’ breaks record for most Oscar nominations with 16, followed by ‘One Battle After Another.’ See the full list.</title>
      <description>“Frankenstein,” “Hamnet,” “Marty Supreme” and “Sentimental Value” also earned multiple nods in a packed field for the annual awards show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0ff21b0-f79c-11f0-9306-0000a1acec17</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland talks. Detainee death. Israeli strike. Trump project. Winter storm. Jimmy Kimmel. Air travel. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d881a281-f789-11f0-9556-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Uvalde officer acquitted of felony child endangerment charges from 2022 school shooting</title>
      <description>Prosecutors had portrayed the case against Adrian Gonzales as a way to deliver justice and accountability. The defense said he had been unfairly targeted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91af4f20-f738-11f0-9407-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 02:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The recent death of an ICE detainee in Texas has been officially deemed a homicide, autopsy confirms</title>
      <description>The report comes the same day a federal judge temporarily barred the deportation of two fellow detainees who said 55-year-old Geraldo Lunas Campos was killed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8baffd0-f72c-11f0-bc93-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 daily habits to slow aging, from a Harvard brain expert</title>
      <description>Neurology professor Rudolph E. Tanzi is the architect of SHIELD, a lifestyle intervention plan for brain health that emphasizes the importance of sleep, handling stress, interaction with others, exercise, learning and diet. Here’s what it looks like in Tanzi’s daily life and some of his tips for continuing to age well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">271deaf0-f728-11f0-9138-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks government from searching data seized from Washington Post reporter for now</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Virginia issued the ruling hours after The Post demanded in a court filing that federal law enforcement officials return the electronic devices the government seized from a staff reporter’s home last week. The extraordinary search “flouts the First Amendment and ignores federal statutory safeguards for journalists,” The Post told the court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49b01c10-f709-11f0-8dfc-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he has reached ‘framework’ of a Greenland deal with NATO secretary general and will reverse tariff threat against Europe</title>
      <description>The announcement, made on President Donald Trump’s social media account, was the latest twist in his effort to seize the Arctic territory from Denmark. The deal is likely to fall far short of the full sovereign possession he was seeking, as NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte is not empowered to negotiate the transfer of territory from one NATO member to another.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d591d701-f704-11f0-9d79-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 20:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal officials launch ICE operation in Maine and begin arrests</title>
      <description>Officials are hoping to avoid a repeat of the widespread resistance that Immigration and Customs Enforcement’s heavy presence has triggered in Minneapolis, according to several officials familiar with the preparations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c256dd0-f6fa-11f0-9d79-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 18:53:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to allow Lisa Cook to remain on Fed board, a move that would limit Trump’s power over central bank</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has complained for months that the Fed is not dropping interest rates quickly enough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">155760f0-f6ef-11f0-a236-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post demands return of reporter’s materials, writing in court filing that government search flouted First Amendment</title>
      <description>Federal agents executed a search warrant on Jan. 14 at the Virginia home of reporter Hannah Natanson. The seizure “chills speech, cripples reporting, and inflicts irreparable harm,” The Post said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413b1070-f6ec-11f0-9138-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 17:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A whopper storm could soon engulf a 2,000-mile stretch of the U.S. with snow and ice this weekend. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>Significant snow and ice, as well as frigid temperatures, will affect more than 200 million people across the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac6ce740-f6e4-11f0-931d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘An icon’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6acda00-f6d5-11f0-8d17-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks for ‘immediate negotiations’ to acquire Greenland, says he does not intend to use force to gain territory</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump asserted during his remarks at the World Economic Forum in Davos, Switzerland, that Greenland is “actually part of North America” and is therefore “a core national security interest of the United States of America.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f9fce70-f6d5-11f0-9138-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump opens speech at Davos touting U.S. economy. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s remarks to the annual gathering of executives, politicians and other prominent figures from around the world comes as European leaders try to de-escalate tensions with the United States over the president’s plan to acquire Greenland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14794380-f6cf-11f0-9138-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 13:42:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Davos disputes. Trump monologue. Jan. 6 pardons. DOGE and data. ICE in Minneapolis. Winter storm. Brain aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad25e161-f6c0-11f0-9048-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Halligan out as U.S. attorney following pressure from judges</title>
      <description>One federal judge in Virginia sought applications for her replacement. Another called her use of the U.S. attorney title a “charade."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">606862c0-f66c-11f0-9f59-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:56:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An earlier alert incorrectly concluded a court filing had said a DOGE member fulfilled an agreement to share Social Security data to overturn elections</title>
      <description>The Justice Department submitted a court filing Friday in an ongoing case saying that the Social Security Administration had discovered a secret agreement between a DOGE employee and an unidentified political advocacy group. The agreement called for sharing Social Security data with the aim of overturning election results in certain states, according to the filing. An earlier alert failed to acknowledge, the agency learned of the agreement in November, according to the court filing, but had “not yet seen evidence that SSA data were shared with the advocacy group.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccf2b5f0-f66a-11f0-b20a-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 01:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DOGE Service members shared sensitive Social Security data with the aim of overturning election results, court filing shows</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has acknowledged for the first time in a court filing that members of DOGE accessed and shared the data without the awareness of agency officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3f409f0-f65e-11f0-8ec8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Beltrán elected to National Baseball Hall of Fame despite sign-stealing scandal. Andruw Jones also heads to Cooperstown.</title>
      <description>Beltrán was voted in by baseball writers despite his reputation as a ringleader of Houston’s infamous scheme in 2017.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8da3df41-f657-11f0-ad49-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:27:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Democrats target military college’s funding after anti-DEI push, a move that could jeopardize its state-funded status</title>
      <description>A resolution filed Tuesday would, if approved, establish a task force with broad authority to investigate whether Virginia Military Institute has done enough to root out racism and sexism at the school.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b3e9f41-f655-11f0-a68d-00000a1ace07</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 23:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plans to cut U.S. participation in some NATO advisory groups in latest move to scale back investment in Europe’s defense</title>
      <description>The move has been under consideration for months, according to two U.S. officials, one of whom said it is unrelated to President Donald Trump’s escalating threats to seize the Danish territory of Greenland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd04ccb0-f642-11f0-b572-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 21:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge seeks replacement of Trump loyalist Halligan as interim U.S. attorney in Virginia, escalating standoff with Justice Dept.</title>
      <description>In a pair of extraordinary moves, two federal judges issued court orders saying they intend to remove Lindsey Halligan at the helm of the key U.S. attorney’s office and threatening disciplinary sanctions for any government lawyer who continues to refer to her as U.S. attorney in legal filings. An out-of-district judge had ruled in November that the Trump administration used an unlawful maneuver to install her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b92f861-f63d-11f0-a1cd-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 20:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Stepchild’s mom has much lower income and ‘expects’ not to pay</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Stepchild’s mom has much lower income and ‘expects’ not to pay</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068bc9e2-f626-11f0-8034-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeking the ideal protein? You’re probably already eating it.</title>
      <description>Humans need (some) protein, of course. But an entire multibillion-dollar industry has sprung up to sell us a lot more of something we don’t need. Our columnist’s journey through the scientific literature and decades of research led to one conclusion: We’re overthinking this.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1de78070-f621-11f0-b620-0000a1ace831</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A proposed Homeland Security rule could empty U.S. stadium seats</title>
      <description>Asking visitors from allied countries to submit social media data could curb World Cup tourism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef42f00-f61a-11f0-aeaf-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A prize is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5315370-f60c-11f0-9790-0000a1ace54f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 14:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland. Gun regulations. ICE protest. MLK march. Drought maps. College football. ‘House burping.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">842fd5a0-f5f7-11f0-810d-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana fights off Miami, caps perfect season with College Football Playoff national championship</title>
      <description>The Hoosiers were among the least successful programs in major college football for generations. Now they are an undefeated national champion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c3597e0-f5b7-11f0-add1-0000a1ace2fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 04:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She helped him flee a rally, then learned he was a right-wing provocateur</title>
      <description>Jake Lang, a pardoned Jan. 6 rioter, jumped into a stranger’s car after he was driven from his anti-immigrant march in Minneapolis by a large counterprotest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4958df30-f5a7-11f0-8a51-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 02:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department considering rollback of gun regulations, seeking to bolster support from Second Amendment advocates</title>
      <description>The administration seeks to placate gun-rights groups that have criticized Attorney General Pam Bondi. Some of the changes are expected to ease restrictions on the private sale of guns and loosen regulations around shipping firearms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13709350-f5a1-11f0-8a51-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 01:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public health groups file lawsuit to reverse RFK Jr.’s new vaccine guidance for children</title>
      <description>Several health organizations are suing to overturn a decision from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, arguing that Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and others failed to consider how the policy would endanger families and burden the health care system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d152950-f592-11f0-bd23-0000a1ace401</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 23:57:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to dress better with the 3-3-3 rule and 6 other numerical guides</title>
      <description>Experts break down all those viral fashion recommendations — what works, what to tweak and one to avoid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd13bae0-f572-11f0-aeb4-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
