<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:01:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump demands ‘unconditional surrender’ from Iran, says U.S. knows where supreme leader is but won’t kill him, ‘at least for now’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump posted the comments to social media as he gathered top security advisers Tuesday at the White House to weigh U.S. involvement amid ongoing missile exchanges between Iran and Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a36c4370-4b9f-11f0-bf10-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend slow to move his belongings to make room for partner’s</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend slow to move his belongings to make room for partner’s</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85480ce0-4b94-11f0-a601-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See where humidity will soon surge to extreme levels</title>
      <description>Humidity levels will reach high or extreme points in around 40 states over the next two weeks, a result of surging ocean temperatures in the Gulf of Mexico and western Atlantic. The surge is expected to fuel a summer of higher-than-average humidity across the East. Our maps also show what U.S. states and cities will experience temperatures above 90 degrees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">281f10e0-4b8a-11f0-aec0-0000a1ace3df</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Canadian province stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58ebe5f0-4b7f-11f0-99bd-0000a1ace201</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican budget bill faces nearly 2-to-1 opposition with many Americans unaware of the legislation, Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Overall, 42 percent of Americans say they oppose the sweeping tax-and-spending bill that won narrow passage last month in the Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives. 

That’s compared with 23 percent of Americans who support the legislation, which aims to extend tax cuts from President Donald Trump’s first term while cutting Medicaid spending and authorizing new spending on immigration enforcement and national defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4be092e0-4b6e-11f0-a198-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-Iran conflict. ICE raids. Russian strikes. Minnesota shooting. Humidity map. Overtourism. Office snacks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d7e3db1-4b6a-11f0-8ab7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian barrage of missiles, drones on Ukraine’s capital kills 15 in the deadliest strike of the year</title>
      <description>Russia pummeled Kyiv and its suburbs with 175 drones, 14 cruise missiles and two ballistic missiles, Tymur Tkachenko, head of the Kyiv city military administration, said in a post on Telegram. At least 114 people were injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25d4d490-4b4f-11f0-9122-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump reverses position, signs G-7 statement criticizing Iran and backing Israel’s right to defend itself</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump initially declined to sign the statement, but changed course following discussions with other leaders in the group and changes to the initial draft, according to a U.S. official who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the sensitive conversations. An earlier draft of the statement called for both Iran and Israel “to show restraint,” according to a copy viewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f41b7fa0-4b38-11f0-a311-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE agents should continue conducting immigration raids on farms, hotels and restaurants in a reversal of guidance, officials say</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security on Monday told staff it was reversing guidance issued last week that agents were not to conduct immigration raids at farms, hotels and restaurants. Last Thursday's decision had been at odds with President Donald Trump’s previous calls for mass deportations of anyone without legal status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fe4e801-4b1d-11f0-a311-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 01:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves G-7 summit a day early, returns to Washington to attend to Mideast conflict, White House says</title>
      <description>The president had been scheduled to spend another day in Alberta, Canada. The announcement comes after he declined to sign onto a statement by the other leaders calling for de-escalation of the conflict between Israel and Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15b26c60-4b10-11f0-9a82-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Iranian state TV headquarters in Tehran mid-broadcast on fourth day of conflict, sending presenter running for cover</title>
      <description>In footage of the live broadcast, an explosion tears through the studio and debris falls into frame. Israel’s military, which had issued a warning order for the area earlier Monday, said the building was concealing military infrastructure. The claim could not be verified independently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da794801-4adb-11f0-80c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged in Minnesota shootings visited four politicians’ homes as he carried out attacks Saturday, officials say</title>
      <description>The suspect allegedly stopped at the homes of at least two more Minnesota lawmakers’ homes in between the shootings that killed two and injured two others, said Joseph H. Thompson, acting U.S. attorney for the District of Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d66e870-4ad0-11f0-9f3f-0000a1ace293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother has a wife and young kids and cheated with a 22-year-old</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother has a wife and young kids and cheated with a 22-year-old</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d25d300-4acb-11f0-82b3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wanted a military spectacle. Instead, he got a history lesson, our art critic writes.</title>
      <description>It was a family-friendly conclusion to a celebratory day, with events on the Mall and fireworks at the end. What had been billed as an overwhelming display of military might turned out to be a display of civics, not power, Philip Kennicott writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e17745d0-4abd-11f0-8139-0000a1aceb35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heat advisory in this state in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e82dbbe0-4ab6-11f0-ad82-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 13:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota shooting. Israel and Iran. Travel ban. Trump protests. Deadly floods. Flight turbulence. AI confessions. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a19abd1-4aa1-11f0-baa3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect captured after manhunt following shootings that killed a Democratic Minn. lawmaker and her husband, and wounded two others</title>
      <description>Authorities have detained Vance Boelter, 57, in two shootings. One killed a top Democrat in the state House, Rep. Melissa Hortman, and her husband. Another wounded Democratic state Sen. John Hoffman and his wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a440f5e0-4a5d-11f0-9840-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 02:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Spaun wins the 125th U.S. Open for the first major title of his career</title>
      <description>Spaun, 34, entered the week having never finished higher than 23rd at a major championship. The Los Angeles native was the only player to finish under par at Oakmont Country Club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4d58c30-4a46-11f0-b810-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As floods keep coming, this small city can’t afford to let people leave</title>
      <description>The federal government has long bought the homes of people who live in flood-prone areas. But officials in Barre, Vermont, which had devastating floods in 2023 and 2024, are rejecting applicants because the city can’t afford to lose their tax revenue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f237f0-4a2b-11f0-b1b7-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 21:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Was Trump’s Army parade a success? Three columnists weigh in.</title>
      <description>Was Trump’s Army parade a success? Three columnists weigh in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b033cc20-4a02-11f0-b91f-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 16:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f483b3a0-4a01-11f0-9557-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 16:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. officials are investigating a former Syrian official’s claim that American journalist Austin Tice was ordered executed in 2013</title>
      <description>Bassam al-Hassan, a member of Bashar al-Assad’s inner circle, told U.S. investigators in Beirut in April that Assad ordered him to have Tice killed in 2013, according to U.S. officials and other people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80a51a30-49fe-11f0-ac70-0000a1ace933</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 15:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The average used-car price hit $30,000. Should you just buy new? Our personal finance columnist weighs in.</title>
      <description>The new-vs.-used-car debate just got complicated thanks to the rising price of pre-owned vehicles. Michelle Singletary explains how to make the best choice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7b8110-49f3-11f0-8245-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 14:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2765ae10-49ec-11f0-82a7-0000a1ace828</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 13:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities probing private security company connections of man suspected in shooting of Minnesota lawmakers</title>
      <description>Authorities have named Vance Boelter, 57, as a suspect in the targeted shootings that killed one state legislator and her husband, and injured another state senator and his wife. Investigators said they are looking into Boelter’s apparent connection to a private security company, which could have given him familiarity with tactics used in the attack, Minnesota Bureau of Criminal Apprehension Superintendent Drew Evans said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2fccd10-4960-11f0-b6a3-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 20:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People are protesting from Philadelphia to Los Angeles ahead of Trump’s military parade in D.C. See the action across the U.S.</title>
      <description>Thousands are gathering in cities across the country for an organized day of protests dubbed “No Kings Nationwide Day of Defiance” against President Donald Trump’s policies. Saturday evening, the nation’s capital will host a parade that celebrates the 250th anniversary of the U.S. Army and falls on Trump’s 79th birthday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33668220-4951-11f0-812c-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration eyes adding dozens of countries to travel ban list, including U.S. partners in Africa, some Caribbean nations</title>
      <description>An internal memo reviewed by The Washington Post sets a 60-day deadline for the targeted governments to conform with certain requirements, or face a full or partial entry ban. Among the new list of countries that could face restrictions are significant U.S. partners such as Egypt and Djibouti, plus countries in the Caribbean, Central Asia and several Pacific Island nations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3abc96c0-494e-11f0-9550-0000a1ace767</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Minnesota Democrat killed in ‘politically motivated assassination,’ Gov. Tim Walz says. A manhunt is underway for the suspect.</title>
      <description>State Rep. Melissa Hortman, who recently served as the speaker of the Minnesota House, was shot and killed early Saturday by a gunman impersonating a police officer, authorities said. Another lawmaker was injured in a connected shooting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fb4f910-4934-11f0-bd6f-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 15:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ninety percent of U.S. adults aren’t eating enough seafood — are you? Here are the healthiest types and what to avoid.</title>
      <description>Studies suggest eating fish is good for your brain, eye and cardiovascular health. Experts recommend that adults eat at least two servings every week, equivalent to about eight ounces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00cd32a1-4929-11f0-8f9a-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 14:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbfb46f0-4922-11f0-b9bb-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 13:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘No buy’ sparks a rebellion against spending. Here’s how you can join.</title>
      <description>‘No buy’ sparks a rebellion against spending. Here’s how you can join.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">191654b0-489b-11f0-9ac7-000a1aced1fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 21:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fires ballistic missiles at Israel; explosions heard in Tel Aviv</title>
      <description>Iran said late Friday that its military retaliation against Israel had begun. State media reported that hundreds of ballistic missiles were fired at Israel after the Israeli military launched a wave of strikes against Iranian nuclear and military sites.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f48e450-4885-11f0-af93-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 18:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Portrait Gallery director Kim Sajet steps down, two weeks after Trump claimed to fire her</title>
      <description>The resignation comes days after the Smithsonian said it would review content across its museums, which the White House has slammed as being influenced by "divisive, race-centered ideology."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e61d66c0-4877-11f0-bc99-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: ‘Star student’ daughter to opt out of college because of AI</title>
      <description>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/06/13/live-chat-carolyn-hax/</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94d88010-4877-11f0-8d01-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 16:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four people escaped from a Newark migrant detention facility, DHS says</title>
      <description>The detainees escaped from Delaney Hall, a privately run detention facility. Protesters faced off with law enforcement there Thursday over conditions at the center, an immigration advocate said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a021ab60-4875-11f0-9f18-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 16:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What kids wish adults knew about growing up in D.C.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post asked middle school students to explain, in their words, what it’s like to grow up in the city, and how they feel about crime and their safety. They responded with a mix of joy and despair.

In 2023, crime surged in the District as homicides reached levels not seen in a generation. We set out to find what happened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc359ad0-4866-11f0-8d01-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 14:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6c94a0-485a-11f0-be13-0000a1ace110</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘miracle’ of the sole passenger who survived the Air India flight</title>
      <description>Viswash Kumar Ramesh, on Air India Flight 171 in seat 11A, was the only survivor after the plane crashed in Ahmedabad. An expert called his escape “extraordinary.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84f5ab60-4858-11f0-99af-0000a1ace565</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 13:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel attacks Iran. Alex Padilla. ‘No Kings’ protests. Crash survivor. Antonio Brown. Extreme rain. Wedding photo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">890e6290-4845-11f0-881e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran launches more than 100 drones in retaliation for Israel’s strikes, according to the Israeli military</title>
      <description>Israel Defense Forces spokesperson Effie Defrin said Friday morning that Iran had launched “over 100 UAVs toward Israel, and the IDF is working to intercept them.” He said Israeli fighter jets had struck over 100 targets across Iran, including the locations of top Iranian military officials, and that the strikes were ongoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7d5f4f0-4817-11f0-87f2-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 05:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court temporarily allows Trump administration to continue using National Guard in Los Angeles, staying lower court’s order</title>
      <description>The decision by the U.S. Court of Appeals for the 9th Circuit allows President Donald Trump to maintain command of the California National Guard for now and blocks a federal judge’s earlier order to return control of the troops to the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b184f60-4810-11f0-97cb-0000a1ace0f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 04:37:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes in Tehran kill the chief commander of Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, state media says</title>
      <description>Maj. Gen. Hossein Salami was killed alongside the former head of Iran's Atomic Energy Organization and at least one other senior military officer, Iran's state-run news agency reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3790df50-47fb-11f0-a006-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump administration's use of National Guard in California amid immigration protests</title>
      <description>California had sued to stop the military from being deployed "for law enforcement purposes on the streets of a civilian city." U.S. District Judge Charles R. Breyer ruled Thursday evening that President Donald Trump acted illegally in dispatching the National Guard.
Breyer stayed his decision until noon Friday, and the Justice Department immediately filed a notice of appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80165a31-47fa-11f0-bf8f-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 02:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Iran, braces for potential retaliation</title>
      <description>Israeli Defense Minister Israel Katz said Israel had launched a “preemptive strike” against Iran and declared a “special emergency situation” in Israel in anticipation of a potential retaliatory attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6101d034-47ef-11f0-ac0f-0000a1ace295</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Army parade Saturday will bring street closures, security checkpoints, tanks, troops and protests. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>The military parade — expected to be the largest in the nation’s capital since the end of the first Gulf War in 1991 — honors the Army's 250th birthday. Saturday is also President Donald Trump’s 79th birthday. We’ve answered some frequently asked questions about the event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54eca880-47d4-11f0-b75f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Alex Padilla (D-California) forcibly removed from Homeland Security Secretary Noem’s news conference after he interrupted it</title>
      <description>Padilla briefly interrupted Kristi Noem’s news conference in the Los Angeles FBI headquarters, saying he had questions for her. Security pushed him out, telling him to put his hands up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">742024a0-47bd-11f0-9ed1-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least one passenger survived Air India plane crash with more than 240 people aboard</title>
      <description>Indian Home Minister Amit Shah said he met with the survivor, Vishwash Kumar, who was slightly injured. Kumar told the Hindustan Times that he saw bodies and pieces of the plane all around him after the crash in Ahmedabad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8fb83e1-47b5-11f0-8d41-000a1ace8074</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After visits to their mom’s, stepkids unleash on their stepmom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After visits to their mom’s, stepkids unleash on their stepmom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">936f3f12-47a6-11f0-8047-0000a1acef43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein’s sexual assault retrial in New York ends in mistrial on final charge</title>
      <description>The disgraced Hollywood producer was convicted Wednesday on a separate criminal sex act charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a56745b0-47a5-11f0-b3c5-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says it’s winning in Ukraine. The data says otherwise.</title>
      <description>Russia has paid an extraordinary price in blood and equipment for marginal gains in Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cae0d70-47a2-11f0-9924-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
