<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 12:01:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s plan. Tariff impacts. Election fights. Hurricane season. Instagram Map. Weight-loss pills. Female umpire. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5619400-7446-11f0-9f99-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s security cabinet approves plan for military to occupy Gaza City</title>
      <description>The decision comes after Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said Thursday that his government intends to take military control of the entire Gaza Strip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee0d0870-7407-11f0-991c-0000a1ace280</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 03:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Senate staffer who survived a stabbing in 2023 could have been the GOP’s voice on crime. His faith intervened.</title>
      <description>Phillip Todd, an aide to Sen. Rand Paul (R-Kentucky), was nearly killed in a random attack in D.C. He took two years to figure out what he wanted to say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bef2f170-73db-11f0-b50c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:13:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders temporary halt to construction at Alligator Alcatraz immigrant detention center in Florida</title>
      <description>The ruling by U.S. District Court Judge Kathleen Williams came after a two-day hearing in a lawsuit filed by environmental groups and joined by the Miccosukee Tribe of Indians.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9872270-73ca-11f0-a610-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:12:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will nominate White House economic adviser Stephen Miran to sit on Federal Reserve board through January</title>
      <description>Miran is the chair of the White House Council of Economic Advisers and served in the Treasury Department in Trump's first term. Trump announced the move on social media Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6543930-73c9-11f0-9332-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy is cracking. This trend is most alarming.</title>
      <description>The economy is cracking. This trend is most alarming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae0c6300-73a9-11f0-a52c-0000a1ace150</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Heartbroken dad wants to approach his daughter about her weight</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Heartbroken dad wants to approach his daughter about her weight</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">256c7450-73a8-11f0-a350-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The trains are not running on time in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ac1edf0-7392-11f0-96be-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:29:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Tulsi Gabbard. Human rights. Army base shooting. Alzheimer’s clue. Nuclear power. Heathy potatoes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3d84b0-737d-11f0-a152-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs take effect, potentially upending global trade and prices</title>
      <description>The president has already announced frameworks of trade agreements with roughly a dozen of the country’s closest trading partners, including the United Kingdom, the European Union, Japan and South Korea.
But goods from nations with which the U.S. does hundreds of billions of dollars of trade, such as India, Switzerland and South Africa, will see new taxes of up to 39 percent, with India’s rate set to jump to 50 percent in three weeks. Economists say the sweeping new taxes on imports will likely get passed on to U.S. consumers and businesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">032cdf30-7347-11f0-b772-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 04:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump warns companies they will pay double for computer chips unless they ‘build in the United States’</title>
      <description>The president’s latest aggressive tariffs policy puts firms under pressure to pledge new investments in the U.S. and could make smartphones and other products more expensive. Apple won an exemption from the new levy after promising to spend an additional $100 billion on U.S. hiring and components.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece2ecf0-732e-11f0-b125-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 01:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to scale back human rights criticism of El Salvador, Israel and Russia, leaked documents show</title>
      <description>Documents reviewed by The Washington Post show the administration is planning to eliminate or downplay accounts of prisoner abuse, corruption, LGBTQ discrimination and other alleged abuses. The human rights reports were due to Congress earlier this year but have been delayed as the administration ordered extensive changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66550141-7320-11f0-abdb-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 23:52:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research on reversing Alzheimer’s reveals lithium as a potential key</title>
      <description>Scientists at Harvard Medical School have reported that they were able to reverse the disease in mice and restore brain function with small amounts of the compound lithium orotate, enough to mimic the metal’s natural level in the brain. The finding could lead to earlier detection of Alzheimer's, new treatments and a broader understanding of how the human brain ages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3f1f3f0-730c-11f0-9614-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 21:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Putin plan to meet on Ukraine as early as next week, with a possible Zelensky meeting to follow</title>
      <description>“The Russians expressed their desire to meet with President Trump, and the President is open to meeting with both President Putin and President Zelensky,” White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt said in a statement. A meeting could come as soon as next week, according to an administration official.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fe24e60-7301-11f0-9c15-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard overrode CIA officials’ concerns to release classified report on 2016 Russian election meddling</title>
      <description>CIA officials worried that the release of the House report could reveal top-secret spying techniques and sources, but Director of National Intelligence Tulsi Gabbard authorized a lightly redacted version in July, with President Donald Trump’s blessing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779f5900-72ee-11f0-ab9c-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:54:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five soldiers were shot at Fort Stewart in Georgia, Army says. A suspect is in custody.</title>
      <description>It was not immediately clear whether there were any fatalities. The five victims were taken to a hospital for treatment, officials said. The base was put on lockdown as law enforcement responded to the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77aff470-72e6-11f0-bf61-0000a1ace9c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: They were ethical vegans till husband flipped for meat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: They were ethical vegans till husband flipped for meat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4e71f0-72df-11f0-bc1d-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump raises tariffs on imports from India to 50 percent in bid to stop India from buying Russian oil</title>
      <description>Indian products already faced a 25 percent import tax due to kick in Wednesday night. The new 50 percent rate would take effect in three weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb060f0-72da-11f0-8f55-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘My teeth told me’: What it was like aboard the Enola Gay</title>
      <description>‘My teeth told me’: What it was like aboard the Enola Gay</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134269a0-72d7-11f0-8290-0000a1ace8c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaving this state in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e04a6410-72c9-11f0-a7b3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agencies stepped up arrests in D.C. at Trump’s order. Now Trump threatens takeover of city after DOGE worker was attacked.</title>
      <description>The recent arrests, including many for low-level offenses, were among the latest operations that White House officials say are part of an effort to improve the quality of life in the nation’s capital — a city President Donald Trump has derided as a “dirty, crime-ridden death trap” and pledged to turn around.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69a9c570-72bb-11f0-80a1-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas political fight. Epstein files. mRNA vaccines. Palestinian state. Jim Acosta. Titan disaster. Zoo predators. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">810b5a50-72b4-11f0-a946-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Republican governor sues to remove Democratic leader amid election map fight</title>
      <description>Gov. Greg  Abbott asked the state’s high court Tuesday to remove a top lawmaker from office, arguing he had abandoned his job by leading dozens of his colleagues out of state to block a GOP plan to redraw the state’s congressional map. Legal scholars have questioned whether courts would go along with an attempt to eject the Democrats from office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe0b1091-7255-11f0-9d9f-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 23:43:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As vouchers soar, their public school shuts its doors: ‘It’s like a death’</title>
      <description>Arizona has supported a robust charter school system, tax money for home schooling and expansive private school vouchers, which are available to all families regardless of income. This “Wild West” of schooling offers a window into the GOP vision for K-12 education.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44d32600-723f-11f0-ac96-0000a1ace2f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Cheating college ex has changed a lot in six years. Or has he?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Cheating college ex has changed a lot in six years. Or has he?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b490cb0-7215-11f0-bca8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 16:01:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two artists re-created a 200-year-old garden. This is what they learned.</title>
      <description>We re-created a 200-year-old garden. This is what we learned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a47d0a0-7213-11f0-be32-0000a1aceb26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican-led House issues subpoena for Epstein files and summons Clintons, Garland and other high-profile officials</title>
      <description>House Oversight Chairman James Comer (R-Kentucky) issued the subpoena after a subcommittee panel voted to pursue the files. It’s unclear how President Donald Trump’s Justice Department will respond to the request, which includes subpoenas for testimony from officials in both Republican and Democratic administrations, including Bill and Hillary Clinton; former attorney general Merrick Garland and former special counsel Robert S. Mueller III.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ecbcbc0-720b-11f0-bbcd-0000a1aced3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:47:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Laura Loomer’s rise in Trump’s orbit: ‘Obsessive’ research, Oval Office visits and ‘contempt’ from staff</title>
      <description>Loomer has taken credit for ousting a raft of federal workers from their jobs, leveraging a personality that friends label “obsessive” and an extreme loyalty to President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b53a2e10-7204-11f0-9d94-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘wonderful tradition’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7314b9f1-7200-11f0-ba0d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One gene reveals clues to why humans thrived and Neanderthals didn’t</title>
      <description>An international team of researchers scrutinized a version of a gene, ubiquitous in humans today, that is not present in Neanderthals or Denisovans — the hominins that lived alongside our ancestors. Their findings suggest tiny changes in brain chemistry could trigger behavioral change that sets us apart from Neanderthals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad04b6f0-71fc-11f0-98d4-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza occupation. Pete Hegseth. Texas map fight. Visa bonds. Disaster funds. Neanderthal genes. Starfish goo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c1911d0-71eb-11f0-bbb0-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top aide to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth tried to oust a senior White House liaison from the Pentagon</title>
      <description>The unusual dispute received White House intervention and appears rooted in deeper frustrations over failed attempts to fill jobs on the defense secretary’s staff, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ff56b70-717f-11f0-abd9-0000a1ace25f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 22:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg fired the fact-checkers. We tested Meta’s new replacement.</title>
      <description>Our tech columnist drafted 65 community notes, Meta’s crowdsourced replacement to fight falsehoods on Facebook, Instagram and Threads. It failed to make a dent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0db19a10-7179-11f0-a528-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 21:21:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s economic picture is getting darker amid federal cuts. These charts show how.</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s overhaul of the federal workforce is being acutely felt in the region that was already struggling to recover from the pandemic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f87b3e1-716a-11f0-a176-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Expose friend’s affair or mind your own business?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Expose friend’s affair or mind your own business?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f5c7d40-714c-11f0-82b0-0000a1acecd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli government votes to remove its attorney general, a Netanyahu critic who was chief prosecutor in his corruption case</title>
      <description>The dismissal of Attorney General Gali Baharav-Miara is one of the most significant moves in Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s years-long effort to remake the judiciary. It could also trigger a constitutional crisis, pitting the elected government against the power of the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e811ff0-7148-11f0-abb6-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask the sharks in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3da85f71-7137-11f0-a9d6-0000a1acec59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas governor says he will attempt to expel Democrats who fled if they do not return, escalating tensions over congressional map</title>
      <description>The Texas state House is set to reconvene at 3 p.m. Central time Monday. Democrats said Gov. Greg Abbott’s expulsion threat was bluster and announced they were committed to staying away for two weeks, while Abbott (R) cited a legal opinion that would allow him to call special elections to replace them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f45edf0-7132-11f0-878d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 12:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Nancy Mace, a Trump critic turned ally, announces run for South Carolina governor</title>
      <description>Mace joins a crowded race in the Republican primary to succeed term-limited Gov. Henry McMaster. The field includes state Lieutenant Governor Pamela Evette, Rep. Ralph Norman (R-South Carolina) and state Attorney General Alan Wilson, who is the son of Rep. Joe Wilson (R-South Carolina). It’s unclear whether President Donald Trump will make an endorsement in the primary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b47df60-7125-11f0-878d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump firing. Texas election map. Gaza images. Montana manhunt. Heart health. AI obituaries. Volcano. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">392099f1-7122-11f0-b26b-000a1ace94d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She owes a private school $27,000. Her daughter never attended.</title>
      <description>In a region with one of nation’s highest private school enrollment rates, there’s a side not often talked about: the lawsuits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">114ad430-70ba-11f0-b806-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 22:34:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Democrats to flee state in effort to block GOP from overhauling House map</title>
      <description>By leaving, Democratic state legislators can stall a Republican plan that would give the GOP five more seats to protect their narrow House majority. Past boycotts slowed, but did not stop, Republican legislation in Texas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7333a100-70aa-11f0-9a22-0000a1ace624</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 20:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ede4d190-7086-11f0-8ca7-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 16:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After 47 years on the political beat for The Post, it’s transition time for Dan Balz</title>
      <description>In his final Sunday Take, Balz writes on his retirement from full-time work at The Washington Post and looks back on his lifelong education in politics and government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99566960-707f-11f0-82b4-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 15:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reeling over an alleged child sex ring, an Alabama community asks: ‘Did no one know?’</title>
      <description>At prayer meetings and other gatherings, Bibb County residents have grappled with the realization that horrific crimes may have been happening in their town.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae791980-7072-11f0-8c27-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 14:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34a1fc70-706e-11f0-b4e2-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In beloved national parks, deep concern among Americans of all political persuasions</title>
      <description>To see how the parks are faring amid the turmoil of the federal government’s downsizing, Washington Post reporters visited four locations just before peak summer season. We found that changes so far were subtle, though staff members cautioned that issues might emerge in coming months. We also found profound affection for America’s “crown jewels” — as the national parks have historically been described — strong support for their protection, and vivid concern over what budget and staffing cuts will mean in the years to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5e80030-6fee-11f0-8ba1-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 22:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian says it will restore information about Trump’s two impeachments to museum exhibit in coming weeks</title>
      <description>The announcement came two days after the Smithsonian said it had removed Donald Trump’s name from the exhibits about presidential impeachments at the National Museum of American History. The Washington Post reported on Thursday that in July the museum removed a temporary placard describing Trump's impeachments and reverted the exhibit to how it looked in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">497fedc0-6fe5-11f0-82fb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 21:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My family doesn’t understand me at all. I’m so lonely.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My family doesn’t understand me at all. I’m so lonely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4f3f60-6fd5-11f0-8f62-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 19:17:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare aerial imagery of Gaza shows the displacement and destruction in the region</title>
      <description>Washington Post photojournalist Heidi Levine captured photos and video from a Jordanian Air Force aid flight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dc829b0-6fbb-11f0-98cf-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 16:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
