<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 23:03:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to have charges dismissed in Georgia 2020 election interference case, citing his presidential win</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s attorneys argued in a court filing Wednesday that the charges against him are unconstitutional now that he will be returning to the White House next month. Trump and his allies are being prosecuted as part of a sprawling election interference case that accuses them of criminally conspiring to try to overturn the 2020 election in Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b8540-b280-11ef-b861-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 20:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-confidence vote topples French government as Le Pen’s far-right party exercises unprecedented power, stoking economic anxiety</title>
      <description>The backing of Marine Le Pen’s far-right National Rally lawmakers was key to the success of the motion, which makes this the shortest-serving administration in the modern French republic, stalls efforts to plug a gaping hole in public finances and plunges France into political chaos. Prolonged uncertainty in the euro zone’s second-largest economy could have ripple effects across the continent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08a152d0-b276-11ef-910f-0000a1aceb1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 19:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks former SEC commissioner Paul Atkins to lead agency again, signaling a shift on regulation of finance and cryptocurrency</title>
      <description>Atkins currently advises financial services and crypto firms. He served on the Securities and Exchange Commission from 2002 to 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">063d1650-b271-11ef-9583-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court’s conservatives seem wary of blocking Tennessee’s ban on certain medical treatments for trans minors</title>
      <description>The justices appeared deeply divided along ideological lines in a historic case involving gender-transition care for trans minors, with key conservatives expressing concern about courts intervening in an evolving nationwide debate over such treatment. The case is the first in which the Supreme Court has considered gender-transition care for minors, which has been banned in about two dozen states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69363620-b26b-11ef-a216-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cash App founder’s killing drew speculation of a random act. It instead offers a look into the underbelly of San Francisco’s elite.</title>
      <description>A San Francisco jury will now decide the fate of Nima Momeni, the tech consultant accused of killing Bob Lee in April 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60b6c410-b26b-11ef-a010-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 18:12:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO’s shooter waited for him to arrive at hotel and remains at large, officials say. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The suspected shooter, who was last seen in Central Park, waited several minutes before Brian Thompson’s arrival at a hotel in midtown Manhattan, New York Police Commissioner Jessica Tisch said. The motive behind the fatal attack is still unknown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">523c2ff0-b262-11ef-b27d-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 17:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Navarro, who was imprisoned for contempt of Congress in Jan. 6 case, to join second Trump administration as trade adviser</title>
      <description>Navarro, a former adviser to Donald Trump who served prison time for refusing to cooperate with the congressional investigation into the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, will have a senior role in Trump’s second administration, the president-elect announced Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f6d3ca1-b25c-11ef-a774-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UnitedHealthcare CEO fatally shot outside midtown Manhattan hotel, person familiar with investigation says</title>
      <description>Brian Thompson was chief executive of one of the largest insurers in the United States. Police have not officially released the victim’s name as of Wednesday morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b89a521-b255-11ef-a216-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 15:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Word (or Phrase) of the year in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7173fc60-b24c-11ef-a2ad-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 14:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump considering replacing Pete Hegseth as defense pick with Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis, people familiar say</title>
      <description>The planned nomination of Hegseth, the former Fox News host, is in jeopardy in the Senate amid skepticism about his qualifications for the job and allegations of sexual misconduct and excessive drinking. Trump is looking at DeSantis, a former rival for the GOP presidential nomination, as an alternative, according to two people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private conversations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04f96c32-b244-11ef-8a57-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea. Trump administration. Hush money case. Transgender care. Snow. Online shopping. Harry Potter’s sword. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fbb38f0-b237-11ef-a68f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pick to lead the Drug Enforcement Administration announces his withdrawal from consideration</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump had tapped Chad Chronister to lead the agency grappling with a drug crisis fueled by the flow of illicit fentanyl. On Tuesday, Chronister said on social media that “as the gravity of this very important responsibility set in, I’ve concluded that I must respectfully withdraw from consideration.”

Rep. Thomas Massie (R-Kentucky) was among a group of conservative voices who pushed back against Chronister's selection, criticizing his enforcement of public health orders during the pandemic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d489acb0-b1c9-11ef-9eb6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:56:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s lawyers point to Hunter Biden pardon in seeking dismissal of N.Y. hush money case</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s felony conviction for falsifying business documents is tainted by the same corruption in the justice system that President Joe Biden decried when he announced his son’s pardon, Trump’s attorneys wrote in a document released Tuesday. The attorneys pointed to comments by Biden in defending his pardon of his son. Biden signed a pardon Sunday for Hunter Biden, who was found guilty of gun-related charges in Delaware and pleaded guilty to tax evasion in California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69e3ea40-b1c6-11ef-8a59-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 22:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A year of Israeli soldiers’ videos highlights the willful destruction of Gaza</title>
      <description>The Post verified more than 120 photos and videos of the war in Gaza, most of which were recorded by soldiers or posted on their social media accounts. The visuals show soldiers blowing up or setting fire to buildings — and often celebrating the destruction — occupying destroyed buildings, mocking Palestinians and calling for the Israeli resettlement of Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5cdd800-b1c0-11ef-85f0-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 21:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland proposes an RFK Stadium deal: A D.C. Air National Guard squadron in exchange for senators’ help moving the plan forward</title>
      <description>The negotiations come after a bill to give D.C. control of the RFK stadium site became part of the National Defense Authorization Act talks in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d924fd30-b1bd-11ef-b947-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean president says he will lift martial law after parliamentary vote and protests</title>
      <description>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol said early Wednesday local time that he would lift the martial law he had imposed just hours earlier and that he had ordered the withdrawal of troops from the streets of Seoul. The reversal came after lawmakers convened urgently to vote to overturn the president’s decree and crowds of protesters gathered outside the National Assembly to demonstrate against the extraordinary move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9961eea2-b1af-11ef-ad19-0000a1ace1f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 19:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels left out of mother-in-law’s dying wishes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels left out of mother-in-law’s dying wishes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe787560-b197-11ef-abc7-0000a1ace4bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean military says martial law will remain in place despite parliament’s vote to reject it. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>A majority of the parliament voted to end President Yoon Suk Yeol’s state of emergency hours after it began; under the constitution, the president must comply and end the decree. But no time frame is specified for compliance, and the army said martial law will remain in place until the president lifts it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164c13b0-b196-11ef-9382-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A social media ban in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9df0ac0-b183-11ef-b357-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol declares martial law, accusing opposition of paralyzing the government and backing North Korea</title>
      <description>In a televised briefing, Yoon said he was protecting the constitutional democratic order and vowed to eradicate pro-North Korean elements. The South Korean president’s approval ratings have dropped in recent months, and he has struggled with the opposition-dominated parliament.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fe65f50-b181-11ef-8945-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 14:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden. Trump’s warning. California resistance. Hannah Kobayashi. Cucumber recall. China coffee. Strava art. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ba6f80-b16e-11ef-9805-0000a1aced75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects Elon Musk’s record-breaking $56 billion pay package, despite Tesla shareholder vote supporting the plan</title>
      <description>A Delaware judge ruled against Tesla CEO Elon Musk’s attempt to reinstate a $56 billion pay package, saying that a shareholder vote backing the plan didn’t change her earlier decision to block the compensation scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e27fc841-b106-11ef-b9e3-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 23:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you reuse plastic water bottles and to-go containers? Scientists say that’s a bad idea.</title>
      <description>Many of us reuse single-use plastics. But the potential health impacts may outweigh the benefits, experts say, because these items contain chemicals and microplastics that can leach into our bodies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">593b41b0-b0f0-11ef-a73b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 20:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Potential conflicts of interest may haunt Dr. Oz’s confirmation to run the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services</title>
      <description>Mehmet Oz, President-elect Donald Trump’s pick to run CMS, has extolled Ozempic’s promise for weight loss. Now he could play a key role in the decision on whether to expand coverage for the costly, life-changing drug to millions of Medicare and Medicaid beneficiaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5ff6af0-b0df-11ef-a676-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Take money from husband’s rich family to join huge, luxury reunion?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Take money from husband’s rich family to join huge, luxury reunion?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bc56761-b0cf-11ef-a9eb-0000a1acebfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 17:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She believed she was an FBI ‘asset.’ It was a lie that cost her nearly $600,000.</title>
      <description>Americans are being conned every day by increasingly sophisticated scammers. Maryland resident Judith Boivin opens up to personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary about a government impersonation scam that drained her life’s savings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c45b870-b0c3-11ef-b2ec-0000a1acebf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 15:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s the holiday season in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">503ff870-b0ba-11ef-b4df-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 14:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden. Kash Patel. Syrian rebels. Plastic pollution. Snow. Cash home buyers. Country music discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7307d50-b0a4-11ef-bbbf-000a1ace7b94</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Joe Biden pardons his son Hunter</title>
      <description>The president said Sunday he had pardoned his son Hunter, who was found guilty of gun-related charges in Delaware and pleaded guilty to tax evasion in California. He said “raw politics has infected this process and it led to a miscarriage of justice.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fc24e80-b047-11ef-94b3-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mar-a-Lago becomes a magnet for foreign leaders, haunting Biden’s final acts</title>
      <description>Declarations by President-elect Donald Trump that may or may not become policy have set some foreign governments on edge, while delighting others. Traditions to ensure a smooth transfer of power have been ignored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04389950-b038-11ef-a2be-0000a1ace2dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 23:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They didn’t thank you for your gift. Our personal finance columnist suggests ways to talk it out.</title>
      <description>They didn’t thank you for your gift. Our personal finance columnist suggests ways to talk it out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">effb5610-b016-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 19:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world fails to deliver a treaty on cleaning up plastic after marathon U.N. negotiations fall flat</title>
      <description>Delegates from more than 170 countries meeting in South Korea failed to agree on how to curb plastic pollution. A broad coalition of nations pushed for manufacturing cuts, but oil-rich countries balked at the idea of limiting future plastics production. Negotiators said they hoped to continue the talks next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afa32180-b00a-11ef-97ac-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb6b99c0-b006-11ef-b964-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 17:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4d48360-aff1-11ef-b09f-0000a1ace935</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 14:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Kash Patel as his choice to lead the FBI, an agency he has repeatedly criticized</title>
      <description>FBI directors serve 10-year terms, so Donald Trump would have to fire Christopher Wray, or Wray would have to resign before his term is up in 2027. Patel has publicly mused about targeting journalists and government officials, and he published a list of “deep state” names in a book last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036f3210-af78-11ef-a273-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best books of 2024, according to The Post’s Book World staff</title>
      <description>Expertly shaped fiction, brisk and original nonfiction: We've collected the year’s standouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2738dc20-af35-11ef-830b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 16:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">072ee081-af28-11ef-a273-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 14:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>59 gifts to surprise everyone on your list</title>
      <description>From maximalist dog accessories to candles too pretty to burn, these gifts were selected for their quality, idiosyncrasy and charm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f61b2f90-ae9d-11ef-8fbc-0000a1ace0dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 22:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s inability to stand up to parents isn’t okay anymore</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s inability to stand up to parents isn’t okay anymore</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79b7570-ae73-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 recipes to give your Thanksgiving leftovers new life</title>
      <description>15 recipes to give your Thanksgiving leftovers new life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a5d9520-ae6c-11ef-b047-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 16:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you know more about civics than an eighth-grader? Take our quiz.</title>
      <description>Like millions of Americans, you probably have strong feelings about how the president should lead, what Congress should do and how the courts should rule, but do you know what gives them those powers in the first place? Test your knowledge to see if you know as much about government as a middle-schooler.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f482bc1-ae67-11ef-ac1c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 15:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. lawmakers back bill to legalize assisted dying in England and Wales, as more countries consider legalization</title>
      <description>The bill, modeled after Oregon’s law, would apply to terminally ill patients and could usher in one of the most dramatic social changes Britain has seen in years.

The bill still faces months of further scrutiny and procedural hurdles, but there’s a good chance of it becoming law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bdeb7e0-ae61-11ef-afed-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:52:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ce15e0-ae5e-11ef-9f50-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 14:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notre Dame’s post-fire restoration is unveiled with a grand tour led by France’s Macron. See the first photos.</title>
      <description>The tour is the first in-depth look inside since a 2019 fire gutted the cathedral. The tour celebrates the stonecutters, carpenters, sculptors and engineers who helped repair Notre Dame after French President Emmanuel Macron promised it would be rebuilt in five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b48d8081-ae4a-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 12:08:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s plans. Hostages in Gaza. Missing hiker found. Snow. Black Friday. Ancient footprints. Orcas vs. sharks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c0b4be2-ae49-11ef-ac1c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: X is Elon Musk’s MAGA World. Threads is a mess. Is Bluesky any better?</title>
      <description>Underneath the leadership of Musk, many people left X (formerly Twitter) with the digital equivalent of only the clothes on their back — abandoning their followings and taking only their usernames. Now the virtual town square is fragmented as people flee to bluer pastures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20f0f8f0-add4-11ef-86a1-0000a1ace902</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: New job took care of the burnout. So why doesn’t it feel better?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: New job took care of the burnout. So why doesn’t it feel better?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56b5c2a0-adab-11ef-bc83-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exercising to lose weight? Science says it rarely works.</title>
      <description>A metabolism researcher dispels myths about how we burn calories and how this changes as we age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc1f34e0-ada0-11ef-a6d2-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 15:53:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving! Play today's On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Turkey Day points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db9608b1-ad95-11ef-ba18-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to roast a turkey: Times and temperatures to count on</title>
      <description>How to roast a turkey: Times and temperatures to count on</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a33cbd0-ad90-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 13:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
