<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texas gets the Supreme Court’s green light to enforce a harsh immigration law, for now</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court on Tuesday cleared the way for Texas to begin enforcing a law that makes it a state crime for migrants to illegally cross the border and allows state officials to deport undocumented individuals.  Liberal justices dissented, saying the change would invite "chaos and crisis" at the border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a930aa-e61f-11ee-b8f4-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 18:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Teen sees new stepsiblings as ‘too Brady Bunch for me’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Teen sees new stepsiblings as ‘too Brady Bunch for me’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134e7911-e60c-11ee-b0c2-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 16:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone footage raises questions about the Israeli justification for the deadly IDF strike on Gaza journalists</title>
      <description>Footage recovered from the drone of an Al Jazeera team killed by the Israel Defense Forces in a targeted Jan. 7 missile strike raises critical questions about the Israeli justification for the attack. Hamza Dahdouh and Mustafa Thuraya are among 90 journalists and other media workers who have been killed in less than six months of fighting in Gaza, according to the Committee to Protect Journalists — the deadliest period for the profession since the group began collecting data in 1992.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bd13c60-e606-11ee-b296-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 15:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The perfect bracket to win your March Madness men’s pool</title>
      <description>Before the start of the NCAA men’s basketball tournament, The Post’s bracket expert Neil Greenberg presents his annual “perfect bracket” to help you win your office pool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d0b920-e5fa-11ee-bb25-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 14:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An enigmatic artist’s mural appears in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce0c5640-e5f4-11ee-b1d0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s finances. Supreme Court. Gaza famine. ‘Havana syndrome.’ Asbestos ban. Kate Middleton. Banksy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54d3a60-e5df-11ee-bbbc-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring: Abstraction as ruin. Artist Amy Sillman’s animated video conjures our unfurling world.</title>
      <description>Spring: Abstraction as ruin</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7462041-e56e-11ee-8339-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 21:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A high-ranking Hamas commander was killed in an Israeli strike in Gaza earlier this month, White House confirms</title>
      <description>Marwan Issa, the highest-ranking militant commander to be killed in five months of fighting, was believed by Israel to have played a central role in Hamas’s day-to-day military operations and to have helped plan its Oct. 7 attack on Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5215f760-e55b-11ee-b1cc-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 19:11:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears likely to reject an effort by GOP-led states to limit White House contacts with social media platforms</title>
      <description>A majority of justices from across the ideological spectrum expressed concern about hamstringing the federal government’s communications with social media platforms on issues such as public health, national security and elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77593001-e542-11ee-9865-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent embarrassed that college-grad son is a bartender</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent embarrassed that college-grad son is a bartender</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fd5bc01-e541-11ee-8212-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 16:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can’t secure a bond to cover his $450-million-plus business-fraud judgment, his lawyers say</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump has been unable to finance an appeal bond for at least $450 million to cover a judgment in the New York attorney general’s business fraud case, his attorneys said in a court filing, and is seeking a reprieve from an appellate court to keep the state from seizing assets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1e4f440-e53e-11ee-94fc-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. bans most common form of cancer-causing asbestos, ending new uses of a deadly mineral after more than 30 years of attempts</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency finalized the ban on chrysotile asbestos on Monday. It comes more than three decades after the EPA first tried to ban all types of the toxic mineral — which kills roughly 40,000 Americans yearly — but was blocked by a federal judge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e70c1030-e53c-11ee-bb86-000a1ace83b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 15:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joann, the decades-old crafts and fabrics retailer, files for bankruptcy as shoppers go online and demand wanes</title>
      <description>The 81-year old company is forced to seek Chapter 11 protection as consumers continue to pull back on discretionary spending. The company does not plan to shutter any of its 829 stores and expects it could complete the bankruptcy process by next month, after which it will become a private company.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a267ad0-e536-11ee-9d35-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patients with mysterious ‘Havana Syndrome’ show no sign of brain injuries, NIH studies reveal, but ‘these symptoms are real’</title>
      <description>Two studies published Monday in JAMA found few significant differences in a range of cognitive and physical tests among more than 80 patients compared to a control group. The results are the latest attempt by medical and national security experts to explain the sometimes debilitating ailments among government workers, which previously sparked a rash of inconclusive investigations, roiled the State Department and Central Intelligence Agency and heightened tensions between the United States and Cuba.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24411fb0-e531-11ee-9b4d-0000a1ace43c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:09:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Illustrated’s owner announces new publisher after planned layoffs put magazine's future in doubt</title>
      <description>Authentic Brands Group, which owns the magazine, announced the deal Monday. Minute Media, a London-based digital media company that publishes websites including the Players’ Tribune, will now chart the magazine's future, including the fate of employees who were told recently they'd be laid off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1be66920-e530-11ee-905d-000a1acec4f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 14:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A star turn for this instrument in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3298060-e52b-11ee-94fc-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian election. Trump rally. Boeing plane. Volcanic eruption. Home prices. March Madness. Supersonic travel. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac38f840-e516-11ee-94fc-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina, Iowa, Southern California and Texas earn No. 1 seeds in NCAA women’s basketball tournament. See the full bracket here.</title>
      <description>March Madness has arrived, and the women’s field of 68 was revealed Sunday night before play begins with opening-round games Wednesday.
Use our comprehensive live bracket to stay up to date all the way through the national championship game on April 7 in Cleveland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c995330-e4c0-11ee-9391-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 00:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut, Houston, Purdue and North Carolina earn No. 1 seeds in NCAA men’s basketball tournament. See the full bracket here.</title>
      <description>March Madness has arrived, and the men’s field of 68 was revealed Sunday evening before play begins with opening-round games Tuesday.
Use our comprehensive live bracket to stay up to date all the way through the national championship game on April 8 in Glendale, Ariz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47d85140-e4b0-11ee-be07-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 22:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's Selection Sunday, and the NCAA men's and women's tournament brackets are about to be revealed. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The men’s field will be revealed first, at 6 p.m. Eastern on CBS, followed by the bracket for the women's tournament, which will be announced at 8 p.m. on ESPN. Follow along for insight and analysis as March Madness gets underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">088b0ac0-e4a9-11ee-9ce3-0000a1acef7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia claims big victory for Putin to extend his rule in election condemned as rigged</title>
      <description>The Russian president, who has defied term limits repeatedly since taking power on Dec. 31, 1999, will extend his rule to 2030. The vote drew protests in Russia and allegations of war crimes in occupied Ukraine, where ballots were cast at gunpoint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7634cd20-e4a6-11ee-a618-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She wanted to take America back to ‘biblical truth.’ Then she won a school board seat.</title>
      <description>Linda Wenhold teaches Patriot Academy classes, which tap into a growing fear among some evangelical Christians that their faith is under siege. Her election to the school board forced her to make a choice about how to use her newfound power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5680c010-e4a1-11ee-ba08-000a1ace6731</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 21:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s cherry blossoms hit peak bloom at the second-earliest date on record, reflecting the impact of climate change</title>
      <description>Sunday’s peak at the Tidal Basin tied with 2000 as the second-earliest on record; only the March 15, 1990, bloom came sooner in observations since 1921. This year’s was so early that it preceded the March 20 start of the National Cherry Blossom Festival, which runs through April 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db24b60-e49a-11ee-bc2b-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 20:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s stunning recovery from the covid crisis, in 11 charts</title>
      <description>Four years ago this week, the first wave of what would grow to be 20 million job losses set in, although most Americans were more terrified of catching a new, very transmissible and sometimes fatal virus. After a pandemic-fueled roller coaster, a new normal has settled into the U.S. economy — one that nobody could have predicted four years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20ba52e0-e481-11ee-ba08-000a1ace6731</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 17:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52db0d40-e478-11ee-b169-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 16:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a sleuth defense attorney in the Trump Georgia case and a disgruntled former law partner seized on the Willis-Wade rumor</title>
      <description>When defense attorneys in the election interference case first heard the rumor that Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis (D) had hired a lover to lead the case, the reaction was muted. It was early September, just three weeks after their clients had been indicted, and they were busy preparing their cases. But one lawyer was interested — and quickly started tracking down records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09a4e860-e46b-11ee-ab37-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 14:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89ec0e91-e466-11ee-a578-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 13:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russians protest Putin’s rule in long lines outside polling stations, answering a call from late opposition leader Navalny</title>
      <description>Showing their anger over a presidential election with only one possible outcome — another victory for Vladimir Putin — thousands of Russians formed long queues outside of polling stations at noon on Sunday. Alexei Navalny had urged the midday protest action before he died suddenly in prison last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbc51361-e449-11ee-adba-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2024 10:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think spring is starting earlier? Check out how it’s changed in your town.</title>
      <description>Washington Post readers told us how the season has changed where they live. Our interactive tool shows where leaves are sprouting sooner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25b25ce0-e3c6-11ee-b9d5-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 18:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stout stew, Irish coffee, shepherd’s pie and more: Recipes for your tastiest St. Patrick’s Day yet</title>
      <description>Celebrate the patron saint of Ireland with some delicious Irish fare. Choose from classic dishes or twists on tradition — with some of our favorite recipes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47db9960-e3af-11ee-ba08-000a1ace6731</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 16:07:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A veteran was hailed as a hero for helping stop a mass shooter. But that was just part of the story.</title>
      <description>Rich Fierro’s family made it through his service in America’s wars abroad. Then a different kind of war disrupted their peace at home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e5be0b0-e3a8-11ee-a248-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 15:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee8c72a0-e398-11ee-ba08-000a1ace6731</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 13:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Maryland ends Greek life restrictions, says some chapters still under investigation</title>
      <description>The University of Maryland has lifted a two-week ban on alcoholic events and any socializing with new recruits at several dozen fraternities and sororities, saying its investigation into reports of dangerous activity was complete. But five groups and some individual members are now facing further scrutiny.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e4a730-e310-11ee-ba5f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 21:09:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's New York hush money trial delayed 30 days to consider new evidence</title>
      <description>The judge overseeing Trump’s pending trial in New York on charges related to 2016 hush money payments granted a 30-day delay on Friday while he considers arguments about evidence in the case. The criminal trial, the first for a former U.S. president, had been scheduled to start March 25.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa8866d0-e30d-11ee-86c9-000a1aceb80c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former vice president Mike Pence says he will not endorse Donald Trump in 2024, in a remarkable break from tradition</title>
      <description>Pence served under Trump but has been critical of the former president following the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol in which Pence was targeted by a mob of pro-Trump supporters. Pence rebuked his former boss in strong terms Friday, saying Trump’s agenda doesn't align with conservatives.
“Donald Trump is pursuing and articulating an agenda that is at odds with the conservative agenda that we governed on during our four years, and that is why I cannot in good conscience endorse Donald Trump in this campaign,” Pence told Fox News.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18dbebd0-e30d-11ee-8fd4-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 20:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nathan Wade resigns as lead prosecutor in Trump Georgia case after judge calls for him to do so</title>
      <description>Wade, the special prosecutor who led the Georgia election interference case against former president Donald Trump and several of his allies, faced allegations that he had an improper personal relationship with Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis (D) and paid for her travel expenses. The judge ruled Friday that Willis could continue with the prosecution only if Wade exited the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af119971-e302-11ee-9f5b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 19:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Realtor giant agrees to overhaul commission structure, fundamentally altering how much home sellers pay agents</title>
      <description>Under the deal, the National Association of Realtors would pay $418 million to resolve lawsuits over excessive fees. As part of the deal, the group will change the current rules that support 5 to 6 percent commissions for real estate agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12a9b0d0-e2db-11ee-bcc1-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland House Democrats push $1.2 billion in tax, fee and toll increases to avoid cutting prized programs</title>
      <description>Online poker, electric vehicles and corporations are among revenue-raising targets in the package, which is designed to force Senate Democrats to the negotiation table over a looming deficit projected to reach $4 billion in four years. The money would pay for imperiled transportation projects and help implement a landmark education plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc2624a0-e2d4-11ee-9997-000a1ace422c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 14:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99392c80-e2d0-11ee-b9b1-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge orders District Attorney Fani Willis to step aside or remove top prosecutor in Trump election interference case</title>
      <description>In a ruling issued Friday, Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee wrote that defendants “failed to meet their burden” in proving Willis’s relationship with lead prosecutor Nathan Wade was a “conflict of interest" enough to merit her removal from the case. But the judge also found an appearance of “impropriety” and said either Willis and her office must fully leave the case or Wade must withdraw from the proceeding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c96eed80-e2cc-11ee-8b0c-0000a1ace029</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 13:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Crumbley verdict. Chuck Schumer. Kamala Harris. Police abuse. Tornado damage. SpaceX flight. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2889df30-e2bb-11ee-acab-0000a1ace2d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father of Michigan school shooter found guilty of involuntary manslaughter, a month after teen’s mother was convicted</title>
      <description>James Crumbley's teenage son Ethan Crumbley killed four students at Oxford High School in 2021. Both James and his wife, Jennifer Crumbley, were accused of failing to secure a weapon in their home and ignoring their son's pleas for help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85523cb0-e259-11ee-9973-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 23:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Georgia case hangs on the decision of a relatively new judge, who plans to rule on Willis misconduct allegations by Friday</title>
      <description>Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee’s ruling is likely to be a career-defining moment for the 34-year-old judge. His decision, whatever it is, will almost certainly be questioned because of its implications for the 2024 presidential election and is sure to draw political attacks in an already contentious election year in which he, Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis and former president Donald Trump will each be on the ballot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee6bea2-e24e-11ee-ab1a-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan DA suggests one-month delay to Donald Trump’s hush money trial</title>
      <description>Manhattan District Attorney Alvin Bragg suggested that the pending trial of former president Donald Trump be delayed a month from its planned March 25 start because of new documents turned over by federal prosecutors — a surprising twist in what has been expected to be the first criminal trial of a former president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4162dcd2-e23b-11ee-9ac8-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 19:44:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump adviser Peter Navarro must go to prison for ignoring Jan. 6 subpoena, appeals court says</title>
      <description>Navarro was convicted for refusing to testify before Congress about his involvement in efforts to undo the results of the 2020 election. He has been ordered to report to a prison in Miami by Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2550d9e0-e22f-11ee-8fc6-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$730 hotel rooms and $75 parking for fans? Youngkin’s own report calls forecasts for proposed Capitals-Wizards arena rosy.</title>
      <description>The analysis, commissioned by the administration of Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R), found the financing plan assumes thousands of fans will pay $75 for parking, the teams’ owner will host 53 more events annually in Alexandria than it did last year at its current D.C. arena, and a new luxury hotel will book rooms at a “historically unprecedented” rate of $731 a night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95093e0-e22d-11ee-a832-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:07:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All that is true about aging is illuminated on a walk, Anne Lamott writes</title>
      <description>We work, love and help others as best we can, gawk at nature, rest. Is that it? Pretty much.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89073360-e222-11ee-9973-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: His version of respect for women results in few second dates</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: His version of respect for women results in few second dates</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1259a2d0-e21c-11ee-b91b-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Orleans police officer took a 14-year-old girl for a rape kit. Then he sexually assaulted her, too.</title>
      <description>Hundreds of police officers have been charged with sexually abusing children over the past two decades, a Washington Post investigation found. This is how one patrol officer preyed on a girl he met on the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ccdabd0-e210-11ee-8ee3-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer to call for ‘new election’ in Israel as U.S. frustrations grow over Netanyahu’s handling of Gaza</title>
      <description>Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer’s remarks are the clearest signal to Israel yet that frustrations over Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu have reached the highest echelons of the U.S. government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1516da0-e20d-11ee-b104-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 14:18:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
