<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 09:02:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bowser, D.C. attorney general reject Bondi move to name emergency police commissioner in first major pushback to federal takeover</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser and D.C. Attorney General Brian Schwalb said the order by Attorney General Pam Bondi — which also ordered sweeping changes to D.C. police polices — was unlawful and suggested they would not comply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">676e9fc0-7990-11f0-b508-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 04:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Pam Bondi orders D.C. mayor to recognize DEA chief as ‘emergency police commissioner’</title>
      <description>In a signed order, Attorney General Pam Bondi said Terrance Cole, head of the U.S. Drug Enforcement Administration, should assume all powers and duties of the chief of police and that the department’s top officers “must receive approval” from him before issuing any directives. Bondi said Cole's appointment would last through President Donald Trump’s emergency declaration in the District.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4596a240-7980-11f0-bf0d-0000a1ace568</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police chief expands cooperation with ICE as federal agents ramp up immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>D.C. Police Chief Pamela A. Smith issued an order Thursday that officers may now assist federal immigration enforcement efforts by sharing information about people not in custody, including those encountered at traffic stops. They may also assist by transporting federal immigration agency employees and their detained suspects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb78d3f0-795b-11f0-8d5d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:14:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HHS is reviving a childhood vaccine safety task force, fulfilling a demand from anti-vaccine activists</title>
      <description>The committee is tasked with issuing recommendations to develop and refine childhood vaccines with “fewer and less serious adverse reactions.” An anti-vaccine group founded by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. funded a lawsuit against the health agency to force the revival of the task force, raising concerns from vaccine experts about the motivations of a new committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd15d2f0-793f-11f0-b09f-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:51:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP is betting Latino Trump voters will keep them in power. That’s no sure thing.</title>
      <description>The congressional maps that Texas Republicans are drawing to boost their chances of keeping control of Congress depend, to varying degrees, on preserving their gains with Hispanic voters. But that doesn’t mean they’ve locked these voters down, according to conversations with more than two dozen Latino voters, elected officials and strategists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95ae8f60-7938-11f0-b946-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who threw sandwich at law enforcement was Justice Department employee and has been fired, AG Bondi says</title>
      <description>Police allege that Sean Charles Dunn began yelling obscenities at officers in D.C., including Metro Transit Police and U.S. Customs and Border Protection officials. Dunn allegedly told one of his arresting officers: “I did it. I threw a sandwich.” Attorney General Pam Bondi said Thursday that he had been fired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6d09ee0-792a-11f0-8c3c-0000a1ace725</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Discouraged partner thinks they’re ‘abjectly failing’ as parents</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b74772-7928-11f0-a609-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The two reasons Americans aren’t having babies, according to data</title>
      <description>An analysis of where Americans keep having babies reveals what works.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bcd1e80-7920-11f0-ad2c-0000a1ace1bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fill in the blank in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8ad3e91-7912-11f0-8296-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift’s new album is inspired by the Eras Tour, and 4 other takeaways from her interview on Travis Kelce’s podcast</title>
      <description>During a conversation that was unprecedented in both length and tone, she talked about everything, casually, as if she were just hanging out with her family or friends — while millions of people watched. Here are five highlights from the episode of “New Heights,” the sports podcast co-hosted by her boyfriend, Kansas City Chiefs star Travis Kelce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50deaaa0-7906-11f0-bb84-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. protests. Foreign aid. Kennedy Center. Tropical storm. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Ancient teeth. Rabbit ‘tentacles.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc217890-78fd-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance becomes the latest affluent American to fall for England’s storybook vacation spot</title>
      <description>The vice president’s family is vacationing in the Cotswolds. Ellen DeGeneres has made it a home. Kourtney Kardashian recently called it a “dreamy storybook fairy tale.” For the region’s tourism industry and real estate brokers, the American market is a goldmine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34c35fb0-7888-11f0-ac65-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer changes you, but I never saw my new hair coming</title>
      <description>It’s not clear why chemotherapy gave me curls, Rachel Manteuffel writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb481381-7884-11f0-8010-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 20:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Mr. Married’ lied about leaving his wife. Where’s his punishment?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c32deb60-7862-11f0-9bac-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will host this year’s Kennedy Center Honors. The class includes Sylvester Stallone, Gloria Gaynor and Kiss.</title>
      <description>The annual production may see significant changes under President Donald Trump, who revealed the honorees during a visit to the arts complex on Wednesday. The list also includes George Strait and Michael Crawford.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f002080-785f-11f0-8b2d-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: We watched a manager berate our server. How should we respond?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b536cf0-7857-11f0-9ac6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani’s rise could be useful for America — by exposing socialism’s many harms, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Why Mamdani’s socialism-on-the-Hudson would be useful for America</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a5f50d0-784e-11f0-97be-0000a1ace54f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:05:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $4 trillion company in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cea5ab1-784a-11f0-8490-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:34:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austin Tice vanished in Syria 13 years ago. The Post uncovered details and previously unreported efforts to find the journalist.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters interviewed more than 70 people who knew, met, negotiated over or investigated the disappearance of the American journalist, revealing new information about his imprisonment and the effort to free him from Syria’s brutal prison system.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e64ffb1-783d-11f0-a61f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 12:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Smithsonian review. Austin Tice. DOGE data. Bursting glacier. AI therapy. Jellyfish swarm. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a22f3280-7834-11f0-b746-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeanine Pirro: I'm the U.S. attorney for D.C. These three laws are detrimental to making our capital safe.</title>
      <description>Jeanine Pirro: The fight to make D.C. safe and beautiful</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56759ae0-77d6-11f0-9121-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who gets Kennedy Center Honors under Trump? George Strait, Kiss and Michael Crawford being eyed.</title>
      <description>The arts complex’s marquee awards ceremony may see significant changes as President Donald Trump continues to overhaul the institution he took over in February.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43a68010-77d5-11f0-a115-000a1ace4057</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard to deploy in D.C. tonight, White House says, a day after Trump announced federalization of city police force</title>
      <description>A White House official, speaking on the condition of anonymity under ground rules set by the administration, said the Guard is expected to “begin being on the streets starting tonight.” A small number of the about 800 National Guard members who are expected to be a part of the mission had been mobilized as of Tuesday afternoon, defense officials said, with more expected in coming days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3a66ea0-77d1-11f0-b09d-0000a1ace09f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 23:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House announces more aggressive review of Smithsonian museums</title>
      <description>In a letter, White House officials said they would focus "on Americanism" in a review of the Smithsonian’s exhibition text, curation, exhibition planning and collections, starting with eight museums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4d5cf0-77ba-11f0-b0b9-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Republicans say they will start second House session on congressional maps this week, pressuring absent Democrats to return</title>
      <description>Republicans said Tuesday they would begin another special legislative session Friday to redraw the state’s maps in favor of their party, aiming to force Democrats to quickly return or commit to remaining away for another month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e89057f0-779d-11f0-98e4-0000a1ace862</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC shooter expressed discontent with coronavirus vaccines before firing hundreds of bullets at headquarters Friday, officials say</title>
      <description>The assault on the Atlanta headquarters of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has left many employees angry at Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. for his criticism of the agency and false claims about vaccines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8eb287f1-7796-11f0-94ce-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:08:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to face people’s questions after twin pregnancy loss?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to face people’s questions after twin pregnancy loss?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b54c6300-7795-11f0-9e0e-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dial-up memories in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfdfa2e0-7780-11f0-a27e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation held steady in July, as the full effects of Trump’s tariffs have yet to take hold</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s tariffs are lifting consumer prices in some parts of the economy, according to new Labor Department data, but less than analysts predicted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9bfe530-7779-11f0-bd76-000a1ace887c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plan would require hundreds of National Guard members to be ready around the clock to quell civil unrest</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is evaluating plans that would establish a “Domestic Civil Disturbance Quick Reaction Force,” with 600 troops on standby at all times to deploy in as little as one hour, according to internal Pentagon documents reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e49bdb20-776f-11f0-a5f1-0000a1ace415</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 11:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s D.C. crackdown. Pentagon plan. Tariff delay. Slain journalists. CDC shooting. Tropical storm. Taylor Swift. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74aa01b0-776b-11f0-946d-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House delays sharper tariffs on Chinese imports for 90 days</title>
      <description>Trade negotiators say they want more time to work out a deal to avoid tariffs as high as 145 percent on Chinese products. The new pause would expire Nov. 9.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece07340-7710-11f0-9b15-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to nominate Bureau of Labor Statistics critic E.J. Antoni to run the agency after he fired its previous chief</title>
      <description>If confirmed by the Senate, Antoni, an economist at the Heritage Foundation, would replace Erika McEntarfer, whom Trump fired this month after a bleak report revised spring jobs figures downward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c98ae70-7708-11f0-9c70-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:11:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘An extraordinary escalation’: What Trump’s police takeover means for D.C.</title>
      <description>On Monday, President Donald Trump announced that he would nationalize the D.C. police and deploy the D.C. National Guard in the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">247447e0-76f9-11f0-b5f8-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. mayor calls Trump’s federal takeover of the city’s police department ‘unsettling and unprecedented’</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) said that while President Donald Trump can deploy the National Guard, D.C.’s police chief remains in control of its force. “Chief Pamela Smith is the chief of the Metropolitan Police Department, and its 3,100 members work under her direction,” she said. Trump said that 800 National Guard members have been activated, and there will be “much more if necessary, much more.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3840d350-76eb-11f0-b9ad-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One dead, two missing and dozens injured in explosion at U.S. Steel plant near Pittsburgh</title>
      <description>Officials sent 15 ambulances to the site of the explosion at U.S. Steel Clairton Coke Works, which sits along the Monongahela River.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebcf80a1-76dd-11f0-89bd-0000a1ace64d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent concerned about 30-year-old daughter’s lax housekeeping</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent concerned about 30-year-old daughter’s lax housekeeping</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcd1cfe0-76cc-11f0-9297-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to place D.C. police under federal control and deploy National Guard to city’s streets, vowing a crackdown on violent crime</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump says he’s ordering the National Guard to assist the D.C. police in combatting carjackings and other violent crimes. The move has raised concerns among city officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7df04770-76c1-11f0-acb1-0000a1ace9c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge denies Justice Department’s request to release Ghislaine Maxwell grand jury transcripts</title>
      <description>The ruling by a New York federal judge comes after a similar rejection by a federal judge in Florida for Jeffrey Epstein-related grand jury transcripts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98a23110-76c0-11f0-9340-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:36:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to the juice in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48622650-76b7-11f0-a894-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. D.C. Putin meeting. 2028 contenders. Palestinian state. Working moms. Sunscreen. ‘AI slop.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a1b5490-76a2-11f0-8141-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia, AMD agree to pay U.S. government 15% of AI chip sales to China</title>
      <description>The chipmakers have agreed to pay the cut to obtain export licenses for China, according to two people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity as they were not authorized to discuss the matter in public.
The arrangement is highly unusual, with U.S. tech export controls usually based on national security imperatives rather than whether they can raise funds for Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57422e40-7658-11f0-b72d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 02:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 scenic road trips to explore America this summer</title>
      <description>These drives deliver volcanoes, parks, lakes and striking views all over the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89089270-7635-11f0-80ea-0000a1ace429</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 22:01:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agents dispatched to fight local crime in D.C., while Trump vows to 'immediately' clear out the city’s homeless</title>
      <description>The unusual moves come as the president, who is planning a news conference for Monday on the issue, warns of a federal government takeover of the nation’s capital that he says would be as aggressive as his immigration crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c13d870-7621-11f0-b01b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 19:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e05212e0-7603-11f0-a374-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 16:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A family opened a South Dakota town’s first bookstore. A bathroom bill is driving them away.</title>
      <description>The Phelans ran the only bookstore in Vermillion. They sold it and moved after a new law would have required their daughter to use a boy’s bathroom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6952a3b0-75fb-11f0-a01e-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f663ecb0-75f0-11f0-835b-0000a1ace920</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 13:50:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birds kept dropping dead in D.C. A biologist cracked the case.</title>
      <description>A call led to a weeks-long investigation and a new discovery in the District.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e54e040-7562-11f0-aa9d-0000a1acefb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 20:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: For 30 years, I’ve been ‘nice’ to my in-laws. I’m tired.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: For 30 years, I’ve been ‘nice’ to my in-laws. I’m tired.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4769280-7543-11f0-a4ea-000a1ace6998</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 17:11:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House and IRS officials clashed over sharing immigrants’ tax data before the agency head was ousted, people familiar say</title>
      <description>The tax agency said Friday it wouldn’t tell immigration authorities whether people had claimed the earned income tax credit, citing privacy protections, the people told The Washington Post. Later that day, Billy Long — a former Republican member of Congress — was on his way out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a04d1a0-753c-11f0-ad6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 16:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
