<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:01:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for nearly $800 million in cuts to grants for the National Institutes of Health</title>
      <description>The justices sided with the Trump administration, which argued that research on diseases in minority, gay and transgender communities was unscientific and went against the president’s efforts to eliminate initiatives related to diversity, equity and inclusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">343042f0-7ed4-11f0-a048-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 21:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge rules Alina Habba, Trump’s pick for U.S. attorney in New Jersey, is not serving lawfully</title>
      <description>The decision means Habba must be disqualified from participating in ongoing cases. But the judge paused his decision to give the Justice Department a chance to appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a461f770-7ecb-11f0-8925-0000a1ace34d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California House Democrats push through redistricting plan to counteract Texas GOP ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>The California Democrats’ measure to create a new ballot question is one of three redistricting bills that are expected to pass in the state Senate and House, then reach Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) for his signature today. State voters must then decide in November on a plan that would create five new Democratic-leaning congressional districts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ac6e050-7ec5-11f0-b3f6-0000a1ace80b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 19:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will patrol D.C. streets tonight alongside law enforcement officials</title>
      <description>“I’m going to be going out tonight with the police and with the military," President Donald Trump said in an interview aired with talk show host Todd Starnes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c02ab900-7eae-11f0-9e52-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Physical 5-year-old roughhouses right through parental warnings</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Physical 5-year-old roughhouses right through parental warnings</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97b28530-7ea8-11f0-965b-0000a1acedc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court voids $500 million fine in N.Y. civil case against Trump but upholds fraud finding</title>
      <description>In February, New York Attorney General Letitia James won a history-making civil case against President Donald Trump, his company, two of his children and two former executives when a state court judge determined that they collectively committed a long-running fraud. On Thursday, the state appeals court called the nearly $500 million fine “excessive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e51c46d0-7ea3-11f0-b4b1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Justice Department employee threw a sub at a federal agent and was fired. Now ‘Sandwich Guy’ is a resistance icon.</title>
      <description>Sandwich Guy’s real name is Sean Charles Dunn, a D.C. resident who was captured on video hurling a footlong at a federal officer and now faces a felony charge. His likeness has popped up around the city in protest art and in online memes. And, yes, you can buy a shirt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c2cb8d0-7ea0-11f0-a8f0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelical leader James Dobson dies at 89. He fueled the rise of the religious right through his group Focus on the Family.</title>
      <description>Dobson, a child psychologist, built a national following with his talk radio empire and nonprofit, Focus on the Family. He attracted an estimated 7 million weekly listeners and marshaled support for President Ronald Reagan’s election in 1980.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df68f8a0-7e99-11f0-b058-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This South American country is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47d6ff10-7e93-11f0-93b9-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S and E.U. release details of trade pact that would keep tariffs high on European vehicles and lower semiconductor tariffs</title>
      <description>A joint statement confirmed that the United States will impose a 15 percent tariff on most European products. The U.S. has now agreed to lower its 25 percent tariff on imported cars to 15 percent for European vehicles once the European Union introduces legislation to eliminate its already-low tariffs on American industrial products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af920600-7e88-11f0-b773-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine-Russia. ICE in D.C. Voting maps. Transgender patients. Beef prices. Reading slump. Windowless window seats. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f943fe80-7e7d-11f0-9922-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. subpoenas sought addresses, doctors’ notes, text messages on care for transgender minors</title>
      <description>The unusual demand for detailed information about patients suggests the Trump administration wants to launch civil or criminal investigations of medical providers in states where gender transition care for minors remains legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b151cd20-7e35-11f0-a1b7-000a1ace433b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 02:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas House approves election map favored by Trump after Democrats return to state, moving it closer to final passage</title>
      <description>The Republican-controlled chamber passed the map, which would create five new congressional districts in areas President Donald Trump won by double digits in 2024 and set off a nationwide partisan fight over redistricting. The state Senate is expected to pass it as soon as this week and send it to Gov. Greg Abbott (R) for his signature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b5fc990-7e1d-11f0-a15d-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department drops long-standing guidance that directed schools to accommodate students who are not fluent in English</title>
      <description>The move is an acceleration of President Donald Trump’s executive order declaring English the country’s “official language.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46219940-7e17-11f0-9fae-0000a1ace9c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department fires top press officer for Israeli-Palestinian affairs after internal debates over Middle East policies</title>
      <description>Shahed Ghoreishi recommended expressing condolences for slain journalists in Gaza and opposing the forced displacement of Palestinians, according to documents reviewed by The Washington Post. U.S. officials said the firing sent a chilling message to State Department employees that communication straying from ardent pro-Israel messaging — even if it’s in line with long-standing U.S. policy — will not be tolerated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d5d8c0-7e12-11f0-8173-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so few Americans read for pleasure, according to a new study</title>
      <description>Only 16 percent of Americans age 15 and over read for leisure every day in 2023, according to a study published Wednesday in the journal iScience, compared with 28 percent of Americans in 2003. The new findings from researchers at the University of Florida and University College London come as Americans’ attention spans and print book sales are in decline, and artificial intelligence technology is aiming to summarize knowledge as quickly as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0624bc0-7e08-11f0-8d0a-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third federal judge rejects DOJ’s request to unseal Epstein grand jury transcripts, saying public interest doesn’t outweigh secrecy</title>
      <description>The Justice Department asked three different federal judges to release transcripts related to the investigation. And U.S. District Judge Richard Berman, who has been overseeing the legal proceedings of the Jeffrey Epstein case in New York, is the third judge to reject the request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f72a7950-7df9-11f0-a7d4-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s happening: People are starting to talk like ChatGPT</title>
      <description>It’s happening: People are starting to talk like ChatGPT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">844d7590-7def-11f0-9340-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Tell busybody sister about diagnosis that could affect her, too?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Tell busybody sister about diagnosis that could affect her, too?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4faaa90-7dde-11f0-af4b-0000a1ace596</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls for resignation of Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook in his latest effort to bend the U.S. central bank to his will</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump issued the call after Bill Pulte, director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency, accused Cook of mortgage fraud and asked the Justice Department to investigate her. In targeting Cook, Trump appears to be looking to open up more vacancies on the Fed board, accelerating the point at which Trump-aligned governors could hold a majority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b8fef11-7dd4-11f0-ab79-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These places will be hit by big waves and coastal flooding as Hurricane Erin passes</title>
      <description>A dozen eastern states are under weather alerts as the storm makes its closest approach to the United States starting today. Erin’s massive wind field brings risks of dangerous surf and possible flooding to coastal communities, even as the storm passes hundreds of miles offshore. See whether your region might be impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c699f980-7dce-11f0-abed-0000a1acec61</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new name in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93a36470-7dca-11f0-8e75-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most D.C. residents strongly oppose Trump’s takeover of city police, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Washington, D.C., residents overwhelmingly oppose President Donald Trump’s decision last week to take over the D.C. police and order federal law enforcement and the National Guard onto District streets, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll. And 65 percent don’t think his actions will make the District safer from violent crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98ea1de0-7dc3-11f0-b73c-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s unusually large personal security requirements are straining the Army agency charged with protecting him</title>
      <description>The Army Criminal Investigation Division, which fields security for top Defense Department officials, has had to pull agents off criminal investigations to staff weeks-long assignments guarding family homes in Minnesota, Tennessee and D.C., according to numerous officials familiar with the operation. The assignments have at times extended to residences belonging to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s former spouses, the officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a54a7c0-7db9-11f0-a29d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Pete Hegseth. Jeanine Pirro. Voting maps. English learners. Hurricane Erin. Good life. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d899d1b0-7db4-11f0-89c7-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C’s top prosecutor says her office will no longer pursue gun charges for people carrying rifles, shotguns</title>
      <description>U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro said the new policy was crafted by the Justice Department and its solicitor general. The shift comes as the Trump administration ramps up federal law enforcement to unprecedented levels in D.C. and complicates the White House’s boasts of seizing guns as part of the crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18ed9e41-7d65-11f0-9f85-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeanine Pirro boasted of working to help Trump and GOP while at Fox News, unredacted documents show</title>
      <description>Court filings from voting technology company Smartmatic in its $2.7 billion defamation suit against Fox News include previously unreported text messages and emails between the network’s employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d2cd2f0-7d5c-11f0-a5bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The city is dead’: As Restaurant Week arrives in D.C., owners see a decline in reservations amid takeover of city’s police force</title>
      <description>Business owners are concerned that the continued surge in law enforcement could affect their revenue during a vital period of the summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55fd19d0-7d58-11f0-8dc3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. probes whether D.C. police manipulated data to make crime rates appear lower, escalating tensions between Trump, city</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump confirmed the investigation on social media, saying the city is “under serious investigation.” D.C. government officials have questioned the unprecedented federal takeover of local police, repeatedly citing department statistics showing violent crime down 27 percent from a year ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8783870-7d1c-11f0-a07e-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Moving nearby exposes mother-in-law as ‘closeted’ nightmare</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Moving nearby exposes mother-in-law as ‘closeted’ nightmare</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7aeeb02-7d15-11f0-a3a7-0000a1ace841</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A San Francisco musical in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3fcb340-7d00-11f0-b6f0-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump offers ‘assurance’ he won’t send ground troops to Ukraine but suggests U.S. will offer support to European nations</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s comments during a television interview added some clarity to the role the United States is willing to play in providing security guarantees for Ukraine, a subject discussed at a White House summit Monday with Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and other European leaders. Trump hinted the United States could be willing to provide air support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abc64d90-7cff-11f0-af86-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Zelensky. Mail-in voting. Epstein files. Teacher test. Measles risk. Hurricane Erin. MSNBC rebrand. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a810fdd0-7ceb-11f0-b7ba-000a1ace3d91</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Air Force general forced out in Hegseth’s latest shake-up of Pentagon</title>
      <description>Gen. David Allvin will retire halfway through his four-year term, becoming the most recent senior military official to be pushed out by the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1bca20-7c91-11f0-85ff-000a1ace17b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department will begin sharing Epstein files with Congress on Friday, Oversight Committee chairman says</title>
      <description>House Oversight Committee chairman James Comer (R-Kentucky) said in a statement the Justice Department “will begin to provide Epstein-related records” on Friday in response to the panel’s subpoena. The department, which was facing a Tuesday deadline to comply with the subpoena, did not immediately comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c1cf120-7c6c-11f0-9c38-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky arrives at the White House for a high-stakes Ukraine meeting with Trump and European leaders. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s arrival marks the start of a meeting that could determine whether a peace deal can be worked out to end more than two years of war between Ukraine and Russia. A parade of Zelensky’s European allies arrived earlier in the afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bd30710-7c57-11f0-babf-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 17:17:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columnist Jules Witcover dies at 98. Over six decades, he covered presidents, assassinations, civil rights and the Cold War.</title>
      <description>Witcover was known as one of the best-sourced political reporters of his generation and wrote a long-running syndicated column with his Baltimore Sun colleague Jack Germond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a39df30-7c52-11f0-a572-0000a1ace0b8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After wife’s hysterectomy, husband regrets not having kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After wife’s hysterectomy, husband regrets not having kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b5b4aa0-7c4c-11f0-8e48-0000a1ace032</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The judge who refuses to bend to Trump’s will: ‘We’ll do what’s right’</title>
      <description>In an interview with The Washington Post, Brazilian Federal Supreme Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes said he’s preserving democracy in his country. The Trump administration, backing former Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro, says Moraes is destroying it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2987af21-7c3e-11f0-94b0-0000a1ace1b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A historic stadium show in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b66eff0-7c37-11f0-a9b8-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Violent arrest. Israel protests. Coronavirus wave. Nighttime humidity. ‘AI slop.’ Pearl Harbor find. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75ab0580-7c22-11f0-9d00-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a37f72a0-7b89-11f0-b9e5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 16:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We stayed out all night in D.C. this weekend after Trump’s National Guard deployment. Here’s what we saw.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spent 12 hours on U Street as federal police roamed, bartenders worried and clubgoers tried to enjoy themselves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc3df8e0-7b7c-11f0-8380-0000a1ace2d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 15:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3906c790-7b6e-11f0-9e39-0000a1ace25f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 13:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top European and NATO leaders will join the Trump-Zelensky meeting Monday, presenting a united front</title>
      <description>NATO Secretary General Mark Rutte, European Commission President Ursula von der Leyen, French President Emmanuel Macron, German Chancellor Friedrich Merz and and Finnish President Alexander Stubb confirmed Sunday that they will join Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky when he meets with President Donald Trump in D.C. on Monday. Ukraine’s future amid Russia’s war could hinge on the high-stakes and potentially emotional meeting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79729f70-7b5f-11f0-9808-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 11:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican-led states to send hundreds more National Guard troops to D.C.</title>
      <description>Three Republican-led states, responding to a Trump administration request, said Saturday they would send up to 750 National Guard troops to join the 800 already deployed in the District of Columbia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">395350a0-7b10-11f0-9625-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 02:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE documents reveal plan to double immigrant detention space this year</title>
      <description>Billions will be spent to reach more than 107,000 beds, including in mega-facilities, tents and at least two new family detention centers, according to an internal agency roadmap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f5ec570-7ad5-11f0-a531-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 19:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Erin rapidly intensifies into powerful Category 5 storm, a day after becoming year’s first Atlantic hurricane</title>
      <description>By midday Saturday, the storm had exploded from a low-end Category 1 to a monster Category 5 storm, with maximum sustained winds of 160 mph. It is expected to pass north of the Caribbean islands but could bring heavy rain and blustery winds to Puerto Rico on Saturday afternoon and evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">396c5680-7ac6-11f0-94ae-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 17:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Divorced desi woman worries about talking about her dating life</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Divorced desi woman worries about talking about her dating life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1edea9a1-7aba-11f0-82bd-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plug-in solar promises an easy, cheap way to power your home. Our columnist tried it.</title>
      <description>Millions of people in the United States can’t install rooftop solar, because they are renters or live in buildings with roof limitations. But for a few hundred dollars, portable panels that hang on any sunny surface can pump free solar electricity into your home via a wall socket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcd8850-7ab3-11f0-bf86-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 15:16:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
