<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Business titans privately urged New York City’s mayor to use police on Columbia protesters, WhatsApp chats show</title>
      <description>A group of billionaires and business titans working to shape U.S. public opinion of the war in Gaza privately pressed Mayor Eric Adams (D) last month to send police to disperse pro-Palestinian protests at Columbia University, according to communications obtained by The Washington Post and people familiar with the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc4cafb0-13b9-11ef-885a-0000a1ace0d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to end coal leasing in nation’s largest coal-producing region, a win for climate activists</title>
      <description>The Biden administration announced it will end coal leasing on federal lands in the Powder River Basin, which produces nearly half the coal in the United States. The decision by the Interior Department’s Bureau of Land Management affects a vast coal-producing region that stretches more than 13 million acres across Montana and Wyoming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f95e5180-13ae-11ef-9e32-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's trial revealed he likes the Oxford comma. How stunning, strange and disorienting.</title>
      <description>Also, now we know what Trump and Flaubert have in common.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e758130-13a8-11ef-8992-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 17:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé plans to have a baby with someone else</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé plans to have a baby with someone else</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e457c10-139e-11ef-9a3f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 16:05:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects broad conservative challenge to funding for CFPB, a consumer watchdog agency created by Congress 12 years ago</title>
      <description>The justices reversed a lower-court ruling that would have undermined the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau. The CFPB case is one of several the Supreme Court heard this term that challenge the power of federal agencies, long a target of conservatives concerned about regulation and government bureaucrats whom they see as unaccountable to the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e24e97e0-138e-11ef-a3c9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 14:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Something we could root for’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71487a30-1388-11ef-9b31-0000a1ace556</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 13:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden asserts executive privilege on special counsel Hur’s tapes as Congress moves to hold Garland in contempt for withholding them</title>
      <description>The Justice Department, which asked President Biden to assert privilege over the recordings, disclosed the decision in a letter Thursday, shortly before congressional Republicans planned to move forward with a contempt resolution against Attorney General Merrick Garland. They accuse Garland of defying a subpoena to turn over the audio and video recordings from the special counsel investigation, which includes an interview with Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a116f540-1381-11ef-99bf-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public concern over safety in D.C. grows despite drop in crime, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>D.C. residents are more worried about public safety now than they were a year ago despite a significant drop in violent crime in early 2024 and a raft of popular local legislation aimed at curtailing some of the city’s more progressive public safety policies, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll. Sixty-five percent of Washingtonians say crime is an “extremely” or a “very serious” problem in the District, up from 56 percent in 2023. While 70 percent of D.C. residents feel at least “somewhat” safe from crime in their neighborhoods, that is down from 77 percent last year. That includes 23 percent who feel “very safe,” down slightly from 29 percent last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0564f6b0-137c-11ef-83e3-000a1ace0666</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 12:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential debates. Michael Cohen. Slovakia shooting. Florida climate. HPV test. NFL schedule. Cheating mice. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72adbc10-1373-11ef-99bf-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL’s 2024 schedule is out. Here are the 21 can't-miss games, including a starry season opener and a Christmas doubleheader.</title>
      <description>The NFL’s regular season will start Sept. 5, when the Kansas City Chiefs will host the Baltimore Ravens in a rematch of the AFC championship game. The league will play on six days of the week — every day but Tuesday — and on three continents, showcasing veterans like Patrick Mahomes and Aaron Rodgers and a host of intriguing young quarterbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fb6f1e0-131f-11ef-bb0c-0000a1ace52b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 00:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court restores Louisiana voting map with majority-Black district. A lower court had ruled it a racial gerrymander.</title>
      <description>The move ends for now a prolonged legal fight over district lines with just months to go before an election that will determine which party controls the narrowly divided House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97208d50-1302-11ef-9cda-0000a1ace089</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 21:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis signs bill scrubbing ‘climate change’ from Florida law, eliminating it as a priority in energy policy decisions</title>
      <description>Environmentalists say the new law is the latest example of Republican Gov. Ron DeSantis’s eagerness to use climate change as a culture war issue. But it may not have much practical effect, since solar power remains popular in the state and polls show Floridians remain highly concerned about climate change and sea-level rise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29bf7c71-12f4-11ef-9a92-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the authoritarian Middle East became the capital of Silicon Valley</title>
      <description>Virtually overnight, the Middle East has emerged as the most powerful geopolitical force in the tech industry, due in part to the Biden administration’s fears about China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">562502f1-12ed-11ef-8e0f-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 19:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Dining Guide: The 26 best new restaurants in the D.C. area, according to our food critic</title>
      <description>Critic Tom Sietsema’s picks include a bevy of Mexican options, plant-based fine dining, beautiful burgers and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a734d512-12db-11ef-9d7c-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Aging mom’s increasing anxiety robs child of a valued confidante</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Aging mom’s increasing anxiety robs child of a valued confidante</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c5e70b1-12d4-11ef-8490-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 16:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Trump agree to debate on CNN on June 27</title>
      <description>The agreement came together hours after President Biden announced he would bypass the decades-old tradition of three fall debates organized by the bipartisan Commission on Presidential Debates. Biden proposed two debates, including a second in September. Former president Donald Trump publicly embraced the idea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">161ac1f0-12ce-11ef-b57b-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 100-year-old law tried to keep America White. Instead, diversity triumphed, Eduardo Porter and Youyou Zhou explain.</title>
      <description>100 years ago, the U.S. tried to limit immigration to White Europeans. Instead, diversity triumphed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85aeb630-12cd-11ef-aa5b-0000a1aceb91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 15:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slovakian Prime Minister Robert Fico has been shot. He was hospitalized, and his condition is unknown.</title>
      <description>Local media reported that a suspect had been detained by police at the scene, outside the House of Culture in the central town of Handlova. Slovakia’s president condemned the “brutal and ruthless attack.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04f64ae1-12c2-11ef-aad3-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lighting up the sky in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">690e40d1-12bf-11ef-aad3-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual inflation shows signs of improvement, but prices are still rising faster than normal</title>
      <description>The economy is still confounding Federal Reserve officials, and it’s not clear when they’ll be able to lower high interest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">652ae5c0-12b7-11ef-8754-0000a1ace616</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:33:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden proposes June and September faceoffs with Trump, ditching the bipartisan debate commission</title>
      <description>President Biden called on Donald Trump to debate him on television in June and September but said he would not participate in the three fall meetings organized by the Commission on Presidential Debates, which has convened presidential debates since the 1988 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5bbc20-12b3-11ef-9043-0000a1acec1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 12:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel weapons. Michael Cohen. Primary results. Ukraine. Coronavirus variant. Solar flare. Dog show winner. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44e76391-12aa-11ef-a326-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sage the miniature poodle wins Best in Show at the Westminster Dog Show, proving that she’s the bestest girl</title>
      <description>Also up for the top honor were sporting dog Micha, a cocker spaniel; working dog Monty, a giant schnauzer; toy dog Comet, a Shih Tzu; hound dog Louis, an Afghan hound; terrier dog Frankie, a colored bull; and herding dog Mercedes, a German shepherd.
Catch up on our live coverage of Tuesday night's competition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44ef0020-1267-11ef-87a5-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 03:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sarah K. Elfreth wins Democratic nomination for the U.S. House seat in Maryland’s 3rd District, AP projects</title>
      <description>Voters selected Elfreth, who served five sessions as the youngest woman in Maryland’s Senate, over former Capitol Police officer Harry Dunn and 20 other Democrats in a race shaped by hefty fundraising and super PAC spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c54e511-1264-11ef-94ac-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 02:37:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>April McClain Delaney wins Democratic nomination for the U.S. House seat in Maryland’s 6th District, AP projects</title>
      <description>Voters selected Delaney, a lawyer and former Biden official, over state Del. Joe Vogel and nearly a dozen others in a race marked by attacks on the candidates’ ideological purity and integrity. She will face off with the Republican nominee, Neil Parrott, in Maryland’s most politically competitive district.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae79fd60-1262-11ef-a0ef-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 02:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neil Parrott wins Republican nomination for the U.S. House seat in Maryland’s 6th District, AP projects</title>
      <description>Voters selected Parrott over former state delegate and failed gubernatorial candidate Dan Cox in a race that pitted Trumpian politics against Parrott’s more moderate platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c50b30a0-1260-11ef-ab3a-0000a1ace7c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 02:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angela Alsobrooks wins Democratic nomination for U.S. Senate in Maryland, AP projects</title>
      <description>The win sets up a general election contest between the Prince George’s County leader and popular former Republican governor Larry Hogan, in one of the few races that could determine the balance of power in the U.S. Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c164a8c0-125e-11ef-9532-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 01:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden advances $1 billion in arms for Israel despite Netanyahu's escalation in Rafah</title>
      <description>The administration on Tuesday signaled its plan to move forward on the deals amid concerns that Israel's planned offensive in Rafah will cause enormous civilian casualties. The move comes a week after the White House said it was delaying a single shipment of munitions due to concerns that 2,000 pound bombs could be used in densely populated areas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d77a6410-1254-11ef-aeff-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Jim Justice wins the GOP Senate nod in West Virginia, per AP, in a seat that is expected to go Republican in November</title>
      <description>Justice, a billionaire and former Democrat, beat Rep. Alex Mooney (R-W.Va.), the Associated Press reported, to clinch the GOP nomination for the seat of outgoing Sen. Joe Manchin (D). With Manchin no longer running, Justice is well positioned to put the Senate seat in Republican hands in November in a state that voted for Donald Trump by 39 points in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0df90e3-1250-11ef-9532-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship that struck Baltimore bridge suffered two electrical blackouts that disabled key equipment, federal investigators find</title>
      <description>The ship that knocked down Baltimore’s Francis Scott Key Bridge experienced multiple electrical failures ahead of the crash, safety investigators said in a preliminary report released Tuesday. (edited)</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fe52b11-122c-11ef-aeff-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona prosecutors haven't been able to serve Rudy Giuliani his indictment</title>
      <description>Nearly three weeks ago, the former New York mayor was charged in Arizona in connection with actions he allegedly took after the 2020 presidential election to try to reverse Donald Trump's loss in the state. Two state attorney general agents traveled to New York to hand-deliver a summons to Giuliani but weren't able to get past a doorman. Other attempts have also failed. If Giuliani doesn't appear in court on May 21, he could be held in contempt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b5072d1-1228-11ef-bcd1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:29:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A group of TikTok creators has filed a lawsuit asking court to block law that could lead to TikTok ban</title>
      <description>Eight TikTok creators filed the suit before the U.S. Court of Appeals for the District of Columbia Circuit, saying the law that requires the sale of TikTok by its Chinese parent company or risk its ban violates their First Amendment rights. The law firm that filed the suit, Davis Wright Tremaine of Seattle, has won other lawsuits seeking to block previous efforts to ban the app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c93e500-1224-11ef-af23-000a1ace1bd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 19:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel-winning author Alice Munro has died at 92. The Canadian writer was celebrated as a master of the short story.</title>
      <description>Munro was a towering woman of letters whose works of short fiction often illuminated the emotional landscape of seemingly ordinary lives. She received the Nobel Prize in 2013, months after announcing she was ending her literary career because of health problems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ba5eb90-1210-11ef-967b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:36:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it ‘charming’ to stage a surprise wedding at a family reunion?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it ‘charming’ to stage a surprise wedding at a family reunion?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ed632a0-120b-11ef-99a1-0000a1ace873</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen tells jurors in Trump’s trial about allegedly false invoices and records, and his own lies to Congress. Follow live.</title>
      <description>In his second day on the stand, the key prosecution witness looked at records that classified his reimbursement payments as a legal retainer, which Cohen said was a false description. Trump is accused of falsifying the records to cover up a hush money payment by Cohen to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels before the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57cd37c0-1208-11ef-82ee-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:40:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Biden nearly died after a misdiagnosis decades ago. His surgeon recounts saving his life.</title>
      <description>Biden woke up fully clothed on a hotel room floor in 1988 with an excruciating pain in his head — the signs of a burst brain aneurysm. Only a risky, 100-mile journey to D.C. and then hours of brain surgery saved his life. As voters now question the 81-year-old’s health, doctors say the episode carries little long-term risk, although the near miss changed his life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42c0d3f0-1203-11ef-9ce0-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An anniversary for this pop group in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79a8d730-11f6-11ef-a346-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia parliament adopts controversial foreign agent law, defying protesters and putting E.U. bid at risk</title>
      <description>Lawmakers from the governing Georgian Dream party adopted a Russian-style law against foreign agents that had drawn sustained street protests by tens of thousands who say the measure will be used to stifle political freedoms. Some European Union critics of the law are calling for Georgia’s membership bid to be suspended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e9da360-11f2-11ef-952c-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 13:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. threats led to a rupture of vital military ties in West Africa, Nigerien leader says</title>
      <description>In an exclusive interview, Nigerien Prime Minister Ali Mahaman Lamine Zeine blamed the United States for the breakdown in bilateral relations, culminating with the planned ouster of more than 1,000 American troops. Before a military coup in Niger last year, the country had been the United States’ closest ally in West Africa, and the operation of a massive U.S. drone base there had been central to efforts at containing a mounting insurgency by Islamist extremists across the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da180e41-11e4-11ef-9e7e-0000a1ace8c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen. Gaza fighting. Wildfire smoke. U.S. Senate primaries. Home prices. Google AI. Ancient coins. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4acd50-11e1-11ef-908a-000a1acec02c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden signs bill banning Russian uranium imports, key to nuclear fuel supply</title>
      <description>Until now, U.S. companies have paid a Russian firm about $1 billion a year for enriched uranium, the main fuel used by nuclear power plants. The new law further sanctions the Kremlin for its war in Ukraine and is expected to give a boost to America’s uranium industry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5175a21-117f-11ef-ab5d-0000a1ace153</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 23:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our personal finance expert cuts through the bad money advice proliferating on social media</title>
      <description>About a third of U.S. adults turn to social media for guidance on managing their money. The personal finance team, led by advice columnist Michelle Singletary, scanned the most popular hashtags on TikTok, looking for top money videos. Take our quiz to see if you can spot sensible suggestions from foolish recommendations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28ee9e60-1174-11ef-aa69-0000a1ace429</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 22:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Schumer’s long-awaited ‘road map’ for regulating AI is coming this week. It will cost billions.</title>
      <description>A bipartisan group of senators including Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer will unveil a long-awaited “road map” for regulating artificial intelligence this week, directing Congress to infuse billions of dollars into research and development of the technology, according to people who have been briefed on the plan. The plan, which is not yet finalized, reviews a host of issues — including AI’s impact on the military, health care and workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f992b5e0-1167-11ef-9dbd-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 20:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are pizza boxes recyclable or not? Here are three recycling myths you should discard.</title>
      <description>Recycling has been around for decades, and yet many questions about what can — and can’t — go into our bins persist. Here’s what to do with pizza boxes, why not all paper products are recyclable and how clean things have to be before they go in the bin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4da18440-1163-11ef-b6ec-0000a1aced20</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 19:59:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen testifies that hush money deal ‘was all about the campaign,’ says Trump ‘wasn’t thinking about Melania’</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s former lawyer and fixer is back on the witness stand after telling jurors before a lunch break that the hush money payment to Stormy Daniels was an effort to keep her quiet as Trump ran for president in 2016. Michael Cohen’s testimony is key for prosecutors, who are seeking to prove Trump falsified records as a way to keep the hush money payment from public view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e012710-1155-11ef-b241-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 18:18:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: What’s the real cost of going halfsies on a modest engagement ring?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: What’s the real cost of going halfsies on a modest engagement ring?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e03220b0-1142-11ef-b75f-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 16:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen is on the witness stand in Trump’s hush money trial in New York. Follow our coverage as the former fixer testifies.</title>
      <description>Prosecutors will ask Cohen, an outspoken critic of Donald Trump and the trial’s most anticipated witness, to show that Trump was directly involved in falsifying business records to keep secret a $130,000 hush money payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels ahead of the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8259b662-112e-11ef-846e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A state’s official gesture in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4346ab00-112d-11ef-b0b0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Mayor Bowser’s approval rating drops below majority for first time in her tenure, Washington Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Fewer than half of D.C. residents — 46 percent — say they approve of Mayor Muriel E. Bowser’s overall job performance, a decrease from 58 percent in a 2022 Post-Schar School poll and 67 percent in both 2019 and 2017. Residents continue to give her negative marks for her efforts to reduce crime while growing increasingly critical of her handling of other major issues, like addressing homelessness and improving the city’s public schools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6316110-1128-11ef-be8c-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 13:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen. Gaza fighting. Bob Menendez trial. Pig kidney. Climate record. Office mandates. Northern lights. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2166a51-1117-11ef-900a-0000a1ace012</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
