<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 05:02:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Bela Karolyi, who coached Olympic gymnastics superstars and polarized his sport, dies at 82</title>
      <description>Karolyi and his wife, Martha, came to prominence in their native Romania when Nadia Comaneci scored a historic perfect 10. Karolyi later led the United States to gymnastics superstardom with athletes such as Mary Lou Retton and Kerri Strug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3c0690-a491-11ef-929e-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 03:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump's Defense pick Pete Hegseth paid sexual assault accuser but denies wrongdoing, attorney says</title>
      <description>The lawyer said Hegseth paid an accuser as part of a nondisclosure agreement but maintained that their sexual encounter was consensual. President-elect Donald Trump's transition team has been unsettled by a memo shared with them by a woman who said she is a friend of the accuser, describing in detail the 2017 incident at a California hotel. Police investigated Hegseth on the sexual assault allegation but prosecutors did not file charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffdc040-a47a-11ef-9a89-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 00:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump chooses Chris Wright, an oil industry CEO and Trump donor who questions aspects of climate change, as energy secretary</title>
      <description>Wright, chairman of the board of Liberty Energy, runs a foundation focused on dispelling the conventional wisdom on climate change and promoting expanded fossil energy production. His views are at odds with many climate scientists and some top energy executives, who endorse curbing greenhouse gas emissions in tune with the Paris climate agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4aa7310-a466-11ef-92e6-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 22:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four nights a week, scientists go out to kill owls. Their goal: saving owls.</title>
      <description>The federal government plans to shoot up to nearly half a million barred owls throughout the West Coast. Scientists in Northern California who have been doing this nocturnal hunting for years say it is the only way to save the northern spotted owl from extinction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">083d07c0-a449-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 18:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My ex’s mom blackmailed him into breaking up with me</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My ex’s mom blackmailed him into breaking up with me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b2a0fa0-a43c-11ef-a976-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 17:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Jake Paul-Mike Tyson fight was a sad, silly spectacle, columnist Sally Jenkins writes</title>
      <description>The boxing charade had a lesson about true power vs. pixels, Jenkins writes, if you could get through all the nonsense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b507970-a434-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 16:03:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tell us how many people you’re cooking for and their preferences, and we’ll plan your Thanksgiving feast for you</title>
      <description>Whether you’re a first-time Thanksgiving host or just looking for a little recipe inspiration, our new holiday menu planner will help you build a meal to meet your needs. You can filter based on gathering size or dietary considerations and choose your recipes, and we’ll compile a printable grocery list to give you a head start on the holiday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c91ba350-a42d-11ef-9cad-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 15:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f102c70-a427-11ef-9705-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 14:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Gladiator II,’ ‘Wicked’ and 17 other movies everyone will be talking about this holiday season</title>
      <description>Whether your taste runs to Disney or more grown-up fare — terrorism, eros, triumph and pain — these are the movies people will be laughing, crying and chatting about between now and the new year, and their estimated opening dates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6e546b0-a3b0-11ef-8897-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 00:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Karoline Leavitt as White House press secretary</title>
      <description>Leavitt, who served in the same role on the 2024 presidential campaign and also worked in the White House communications office during the first Trump administration, steps into the role of the president's most visible spokesperson.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84072d61-a3ac-11ef-9eef-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin at his side, North Korea’s Kim Jong Un has never been more brazen — or in demand</title>
      <description>Donald Trump, who courted the North Korean leader during a first term that included two chummy summits, says Kim “misses” him. But as he returns to the White House, Trump will find Kim is much more confident, not least because he has a new alliance with Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8448b521-a3aa-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 23:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team weighs Pentagon pick after receiving details of past sexual assault claim</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump’s team debated the future of Pete Hegseth amid new revelations that police investigated an allegation that he sexually assaulted a woman in 2017.

Extensive details of the claim were shared with senior transition officials this week by a woman who said she was the accuser’s friend, who she said signed a nondisclosure agreement with Hegseth. Hegseth has denied wrongdoing and the police investigation did not result in charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e1a98d0-a39f-11ef-8719-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 22:18:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law makes a sexualized joke about his toddler niece</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother-in-law makes a sexualized joke about his toddler niece</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2a75280-a388-11ef-b3c0-0000a1ace0b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vaccines. Raw milk. Food dyes. Here are the changes RFK Jr. could make as the nation’s health secretary.</title>
      <description>If he is confirmed, Kennedy has pledged to pursue his “Make America Healthy Again” agenda to combat the causes of chronic disease and childhood illness. He has also discussed other goals, such as conducting more research on vaccines, revisiting federal vaccine requirements, taking fluoride out of public water, boosting access to raw milk, removing food dye and other ingredients and banning puberty blockers for children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">096179b0-a37c-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 18:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House speaker says he ‘strongly’ discourages release of ethics report on Matt Gaetz, Trump’s pick for attorney general</title>
      <description>Rep. Mike Johnson (R-Louisiana) said it would set a “terrible” precedent if the committee issued a report on its investigation into allegations that former congressman Matt Gaetz (R-Florida) engaged in sexual misconduct and illegal drug use and accepted improper gifts. Others, including some Republicans, have argued that the report should be considered as part of Gaetz’s confirmation process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e258db71-a375-11ef-a6ae-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 17:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">516bd750-a35e-11ef-9c6b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 14:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Trump’s controversial team. Tropical storm. Police chief. The Onion. Tyson vs. Paul. Bear disguise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24bad9a0-a349-11ef-8dbd-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks North Dakota Gov. Doug Burgum to lead the Interior Department</title>
      <description>The president-elect made the announcement, which he said would be made official on Friday, while speaking at the America First Policy Institute gala at his Mar-a-Lago estate in Florida.
The Interior Department oversees more than 500 million acres of federal land, managing oil, gas and mineral reserves that will be key to the Trump administration’s plans to boost U.S. energy production.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d145820-a2f7-11ef-8897-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 02:13:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If confirmed, Hegseth and Gabbard would do more to doom Trump's presidency than Democrats ever could, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>Neither is remotely qualified for two of the most important management jobs in government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef357640-a2ea-11ef-95cf-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:45:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names his personal lawyers from criminal cases for top Justice Dept. positions</title>
      <description>The president-elect announced that he would nominate Todd Blanche to serve as deputy attorney general, the second-most powerful position in the Justice Department. Emil Bove was chosen as principal associate deputy attorney general, and D. John Sauer will be nominated as solicitor general.
Blanche led Donald Trump’s defense in three of his four trials: the federal election interference case in D.C., the federal mishandling of classified documents case in Florida and the state-level hush money and business fraud case in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec676980-a2e7-11ef-85b4-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 00:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks former congressman Doug Collins to lead Veterans Affairs</title>
      <description>The Republican from Georgia is a longtime ally of the president-elect and was a staunch defender of Donald Trump during both impeachments.
The Veterans Affairs Department is the second-largest agency and oversees oversees health care, disability and other benefits for former service members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1e89ad0-a2e2-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 23:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go bags, passports, foreign assets: Prominent Trump critics are preparing to be a target of his revenge</title>
      <description>Such planning responds to a hypothetical worst case in which a second Donald Trump presidency ushers in systematic suppression of free speech and criminalization of dissent. Trump’s victory alone has set off alarms among some of his most outspoken critics, as well as within parts of the intelligence and national security communities he denigrated as the “deep state.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e05d4080-a2db-11ef-a15d-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 22:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump selects Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a vaccine skeptic, as health secretary</title>
      <description>Kennedy has pledged pursue a “Make America Healthy Again” agenda, which targets causes of chronic disease and childhood illness. Public health experts have warned that Kennedy, who has spent years repeating debunked claims about vaccines and who endorsed Donald Trump in August in hopes of a role in his future administration, could undermine vaccine oversight if he takes charge of the Department of Health and Human Services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2416b00-a2ce-11ef-978d-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 21:24:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if all you had to do was ask? Ask The Post AI delivers you AI-generated summaries from published Washington Post reporting.</title>
      <description>What if all you had to do was ask? Ask The Post AI delivers you AI-generated summaries from published Washington Post reporting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d3c7f20-a2ba-11ef-b00a-0000a1ace3fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 18:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband refuses to tell spouse why he’s unhappy in their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband refuses to tell spouse why he’s unhappy in their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9ee820-a2a9-11ef-97ee-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A small-town police chief was accused of paying $100 to rape a teen — then using his connections to try to cover it up</title>
      <description>In the tiny West Virginia town of Gauley Bridge, Police Chief Larry Clay Jr. “was the law.” Then a teenager reported that she’d been sex trafficked by her stepmother when she was 17 years old. The buyer, she told investigators, wasn’t just anyone — it was Larry Clay. Would a jury believe her?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5962030-a299-11ef-8248-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A controversial lunch item is removed from schools in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1158e500-a295-11ef-986d-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satirical news outlet the Onion wins auction to control Infowars, the far-right site founded by conspiracy theorist Alex Jones</title>
      <description>Jones was forced to sell Infowars and other personal assets in a court-ordered auction to pay the roughly $1.5 billion in damages he owes for claiming the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd145a40-a291-11ef-bf06-0000a1ace574</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 14:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz. House control. Trump and Biden. Cease-fire plan. Developing storm. Loneliness risk. Cancer experiment. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7f79940-a27f-11ef-bdb4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans are projected to retain a slim House majority, giving the GOP full control of Congress and the White House</title>
      <description>Republicans will remain the majority party in Congress’s lower chamber, the Associated Press reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09611e50-a239-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden endorses controversial road through wildlife refuge in Alaska</title>
      <description>The Interior Department recommended Wednesday a land-swap deal that could allow a road to be built through the Izembek National Wildlife Refuge. Supporters of the road say it could save lives. Opponents say it could undermine President Joe Biden’s environmental legacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95f8280-a210-11ef-9f51-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu readying Lebanon cease-fire proposal as ‘gift’ to Trump after election victory, Israeli officials say</title>
      <description>An Israeli minister discussed the plan with Trump and Jared Kushner at Mar-a-Lago on Sunday, three current and former Israeli officials told The Washington Post, hoping to deliver an early foreign policy win to the president-elect, who campaigned on ending the wars in the Middle East. But the evolving proposal has yet to be presented to Hezbollah and could face resistance in Lebanon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138fc7d0-a209-11ef-a744-0000a1ace931</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will nominate Rep. Matt Gaetz as attorney general and Tulsi Gabbard as director of national intelligence</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump announced plans Wednesday to nominate Gaetz (R-Florida) and Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman from Hawaii, to the respective posts.

Trump also confirmed he will nominate Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Florida) as secretary of state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79a25971-a1ff-11ef-9762-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio Spurs Coach Gregg Popovich suffered a mild stroke earlier this month, the team announced</title>
      <description>The 75-year-old Popovich, a Hall of Famer and the winningest coach in NBA history, has been away from the team since Nov. 2, when he suffered what the Spurs originally referred to as a medical incident.

The Spurs said Popovich has begun a rehabilitation program and is expected to make a full recovery, but it is unclear when he will return to the sideline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6caf90-a1f1-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans choose John Thune to replace Mitch McConnell as majority leader</title>
      <description>The leadership race, like much else, became a proxy battle over Republicans’ fealty to the president-elect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a71a8a70-a1e2-11ef-805e-0000a1ace245</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is 15 diners, 11 dogs and seating for 4 a Thanksgiving math fiasco?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is 15 diners, 11 dogs and seating for 4 a Thanksgiving math fiasco?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27d74e71-a1e1-11ef-8faa-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pledges smooth transition as he meets with Biden at White House</title>
      <description>During a cordial Oval Office meeting, President-elect Donald Trump said that “politics is tough,” but pledged a transition “as smooth as it can get.” In 2020, Trump did not invite Joe Biden to the White House after Biden won the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59f8c7f1-a1df-11ef-ab5f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re tracking Trump’s picks for his Cabinet and administration: Pete Hegseth, Kristi Noem and more</title>
      <description>Here are the people President-elect Donald Trump has picked or is considering to fill top positions in his incoming administration, based on our reporting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">842412b0-a1d4-11ef-a380-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The world knows where the sun is‘ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fac19b81-a1cb-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation picked up in October, as Americans prepared to vote on the economy</title>
      <description>Price increases have slowed significantly this year, but they weighed heavily on Americans who voted against incumbents in the November elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d01e5c40-a1c3-11ef-84d6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Trump’s return. Israel deadline. Discord leaks. Bird flu. Snow forecast. Lost luggage. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccee64f0-a1b6-11ef-9747-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 11:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump says Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy will run ‘government efficiency’ commission</title>
      <description>The president-elect said his billionaire ally and his former Republican primary rival would lead an external entity — what Trump called the “Department of Government Efficiency” — to come up with plans to slash regulations and waste and “restructure” federal agencies. It is not clear how such an effort would be funded or run because governmental spending decisions are up to Congress and the president, not outside groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d4aba1-a15b-11ef-9747-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 01:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump taps Pete Hegseth, an Army veteran and Fox News host, to be defense secretary</title>
      <description>Hegseth, who is a co-host on the weekend edition of "Fox &amp; Friends," has criticized the Biden administration’s approach to national security as weak and wrote a book describing the military’s leadership as more focused on diversity than confronting global threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a8030-a156-11ef-a85e-0000a1ace00f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump says John Ratcliffe is his nominee to become CIA director</title>
      <description>Ratcliffe, a former congressman from Texas, served as the director of national intelligence toward the end of Trump's first administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4eba70-a14b-11ef-b6bd-0000a1aceb7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 23:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord leaker Jack Teixeira sentenced to 15 years in prison for massive disclosure of U.S. secrets</title>
      <description>Teixeira was a member of the Massachusetts Air National Guard when he smuggled out images of hundreds of classified documents and posted them on Discord, a chat platform popular with video gamers. Those materials revealed government assessments of the war in Ukraine, plotting by terrorist groups and espionage efforts by China. His case shook the U.S. national security establishment, revealing the speed and ease with which top-secret materials can spread online, and upset Washington’s relationships with several international partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b32789f0-a13b-11ef-95f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA bans U.S. flights to Haiti for 30 days after Spirit plane was damaged by gunfire at Port-au-Prince airport</title>
      <description>The gunfire that struck Spirit Airlines Flight 951 on Monday came against a backdrop of political unrest and gang violence in Haiti after Prime Minister Garry Conille was fired over the weekend and replaced with Alix Didier Fils-Aimé.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62d29f00-a12f-11ef-bb0a-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 19:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will nominate Mike Huckabee, the former governor of Arkansas, as ambassador to Israel</title>
      <description>Huckabee served as Arkansas governor from 1996 to 2007 and has remained active in politics since then, running for president in both 2008 and 2016. He is an ordained Southern Baptist pastor. Huckabee’s daughter, Sarah Huckabee Sanders, was White House press secretary during Donald Trump’s first term and now serves as Arkansas governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39628130-a12a-11ef-98ff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend pins hopes on big family trip with teens who don’t get along</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend pins hopes on big family trip with teens who don’t get along</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d096a80-a11b-11ef-95f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury says defense contractor must pay $42 million over Abu Ghraib abuses</title>
      <description>A federal jury found that a Virginia-based defense contractor shared responsibility with the U.S. Army for abusing detainees at Abu Ghraib prison, awarding damages to three Iraqi men who said they were tortured there two decades ago. The verdict against CACI International marks the first time a civilian contractor has been held legally responsible for the inhumane treatment of detainees at the prison west of Baghdad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf879bf0-a117-11ef-b8d7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. gave Israel 30 days to surge aid to Gaza. The humanitarian situation there has only gotten worse, a Post analysis finds.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post analysis based on more than a dozen interviews with aid workers and officials found Israel has largely failed to comply with American demands outlined in an Oct. 13 letter, as humanitarian groups warn that parts of northern Gaza are edging closer to famine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5dbed0-a110-11ef-b5fb-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 16:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
