<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:09:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stock markets. Trump protests. Measles death. Israeli troops. Severe storms. March Madness. Alex Ovechkin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74c8cd50-139f-11f0-bdb7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian, European stock markets fall sharply as Trump tariffs spark recession fears</title>
      <description>Asian leaders have issued a flurry of statements to shore up confidence and attempt to avert crisis for their economies, with U.S. partners like Japan, South Korea and Taiwan striking a conciliatory tone and pledging to negotiate. Trump administration officials had spent the weekend defending the president’s tariffs on almost all trading partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f26f42e0-1398-11f0-b5ea-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut wins NCAA women’s basketball championship, beating South Carolina for its record-extending 12th title</title>
      <description>The Huskies routed the defending champion Gamecocks on Sunday in the national championship game in Tampa, securing their first title since 2016. South Carolina was trying to become the first repeat champion since Connecticut won four straight titles from 2013 to 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b71340-132b-11f0-8657-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Ovechkin scores his 895th career goal to pass Wayne Gretzky and set a new NHL record</title>
      <description>With his goal on Sunday afternoon, Ovechkin passed Gretzky to claim sole ownership of the record. It was a remarkable feat for Washington’s 39-year-old captain, who has long captured the hockey world’s attention with his sheer joy and relentless scoring ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e651ff1-130f-11f0-9aea-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 17:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The economy is about to collapse, and you idiots have no idea’: The 2008 weekend that shook the world, from leaders who lived it</title>
      <description>The weekend that shook the world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a4c55f0-1307-11f0-b3ac-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fdf68c0-1301-11f0-9e05-0000a1acef80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s National Park Service is rewriting the history of the Underground Railroad and other key events amid an anti-DEI push</title>
      <description>A Park Service webpage that previously called the smuggling network an effort “by enslaved African Americans to gain their freedom by escaping bondage” now emphasizes how it “bridged the divides of race,” according to a Washington Post analysis. Edits to the website of the Park Service — an agency charged with preserving American history — have changed how notable moments and key figures dating to the nation’s founding are described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f42e9140-12f7-11f0-a88c-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 15:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63b842c0-12eb-11f0-9c48-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes Alex Ovechkin’s shot so unstoppable?</title>
      <description>Ovechkin’s famous one-timer has been an NHL wonder for two decades. With the Washington Capitals star on the cusp of breaking the NHL’s career goals record, here’s a look at why his shot can be a goalie’s worst nightmare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e1a2ed0-1261-11f0-9588-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 21:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least two dozen D.C. police officers are a focus of broad pandemic fraud probe, two people familiar with the investigation say</title>
      <description>Federal prosecutors and the D.C. police internal affairs unit are scrutinizing whether the officers improperly pocketed pandemic relief funds that were aimed at offsetting covid-19 impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0eb6970-125c-11f0-848e-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 20:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This millennial voter marched against Trump in 2017. Now she feels helpless: ‘Fine, we’ll just let it all burn.’</title>
      <description>Democrats are struggling to match the massive resistance movement that sprang up in President Donald Trump’s first term — and battling cynicism among their own voters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">899faf11-122c-11f0-99e6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 14:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A young skier vowed to jump a highway to win a social media contest. His parents are left with regret.</title>
      <description>For many athletes like 21-year-old Dallas LeBeau, the ski industry has become an expensive, relentless chase to prove themselves in a social-media-driven world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea3c130-1226-11f0-848e-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 14:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4855b590-1222-11f0-a6a5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitals star Alex Ovechkin ties Wayne Gretzky's NHL career goals record with No. 894</title>
      <description>Ovechkin scored the 894th goal of his NHL career in the third period Friday against the Chicago Blackhawks to draw even with Gretzky. The 39-year-old racked up goals at a torrid pace this season before a broken leg in mid-November stalled his pursuit of Gretzky's record. The Russian superstar, who won a Stanley Cup with Washington in 2018, has long been a singular force in the sport and the face of hockey in the District.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45dc6181-11bc-11f0-8971-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 01:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House was hours from announcing a TikTok deal. Trump’s new tariffs wrecked it.</title>
      <description>The proposal to spin off the popular video app TikTok was shattered when the Chinese government said it would not approve any deal without discussing President Donald Trump’s tariffs and trade policy, three people close to the negotiations said. The reversal destroyed the Trump team’s hopes of moving toward a resolution on TikTok’s fate and underscores the sweeping fallout of Trump’s tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d04532b0-11a4-11f0-9742-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 22:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NIH prepares to launch new research into autism causes, a Trump priority</title>
      <description>Officials are weighing whether to hold a public competition and offer prizes or pursue a more traditional path of awarding research grants. The issue has been complicated by President Donald Trump and other officials repeating claims about the debunked link between immunizations and autism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a184000-11a1-11f0-8971-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 22:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump officials to freeze teacher training grants while legal challenges continue</title>
      <description>The justices split 5-4 on whether to reverse a lower court order that kept $65 million in funding in place for now. The Trump administration says the grant programs, which were created by Congress, promote diversity, equity and inclusion in ways that could violate federal law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">226b6f20-1199-11f0-a0e5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 21:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS layoffs underway as DOGE moves to eliminate 25 percent of the workforce</title>
      <description>The tax agency will lose roughly 20,000 jobs, including workers in its civil rights office, as part of the Trump administration's downsizing of the government, according to records obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22b14e90-1195-11f0-9bf3-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks tumble again after China matches U.S. tariffs, with the Nasdaq officially in a bear market</title>
      <description>The Nasdaq and the S&amp;P 500 are both down more than 10 percent since President Donald Trump announced new taxes on most imports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d94e530-1190-11f0-8971-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 20:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to negotiate return of man mistakenly deported to El Salvador.</title>
      <description>Federal officials have called the removal of Kilmar Abrego Garcia, who escaped death threats from gang members in his homeland, an “oversight.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcb5c5d1-1188-11f0-9260-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 19:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theodore McCarrick dies at 94. The disgraced ex-cardinal and former D.C. archbishop was found guilty of sexual abuse by the church.</title>
      <description>McCarrick was suspended from the ministry in 2018, amid accusations that he had sexually abused a teenage boy in the 1970s. The next year, he became the first U.S. cardinal or bishop defrocked by the Vatican.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5389aa0-1185-11f0-851d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Trump’s move to upend global trade, he resolved to follow his own instincts and was surrounded by officials who enabled him</title>
      <description>Inside and outside the White House, advisers say President Donald Trump is unbowed even as the world reels from the biggest increase in trade hostilities in a century.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa413310-1178-11f0-a7d0-0000a1ace940</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 17:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I feel ‘cheated’ by my wife that my life is changing after kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I feel ‘cheated’ by my wife that my life is changing after kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc76d0f0-1175-11f0-9018-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 16:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elena Delle Donne announces her retirement from the WNBA. The two-time league MVP led the Washington Mystics to the 2019 title.</title>
      <description>The 35-year-old Delle Donne, who made her announcement on Instagram on Friday, was a seven-time all-star and one of the most dominant players in the league during her prime. She was slowed by injuries late in her career and last played for the Mystics during the 2023 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03d0db70-115f-11f0-b83d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 14:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wall Street sell-off deepens as trade war escalates; major U.S. indexes slump</title>
      <description>Markets fell sharply as traders brace for more volatility after China announced new tariffs on U.S. goods, raising recession fears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29d20ae0-115c-11f0-848e-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:53:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91f0e310-1159-11f0-8a6a-000a1acedd51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 13:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 228,000 jobs in March, a stronger than expected showing despite growing uncertainty in the economy</title>
      <description>The Bureau of Labor Statistics jobs report showed a labor market in good shape, despite worries in March that Trump administration cuts to the public sector or anticipated tariffs could slow the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad0b56b0-1151-11f0-9810-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 12:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, retaliating against Trump's tariffs, imposes 34 percent levy on U.S. goods</title>
      <description>In announcing the tariffs, China, which exports far more to the United States than it imports, decried “unilateral bullying” by the Trump administration and said the U.S. tariffs were “inconsistent with international trade.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c157ef0-1146-11f0-8f69-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sliding stocks. Laura Loomer. Deadly storms. South Korea. Clean energy. Springsteen’s ‘lost’ albums. Tortoise mom. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8e9fa90-1143-11f0-9810-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Security Agency and Cyber Command chief Gen. Tim Haugh ousted as head of spy agency</title>
      <description>The director of the NSA, the powerful wiretapping and cyber espionage service, was fired Thursday, according to officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27a9cdf0-10ff-11f0-983a-0000a1ace2b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean court removes president from office after martial law decree, triggering election and more protests</title>
      <description>The Constitutional Court has upheld a parliamentary vote to impeach President Yoon Suk Yeol over his December attempt to impose martial law. An election will now be called, but the decision is likely to galvanize conservative factions and exacerbate political polarization.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">582a3710-10fc-11f0-a9f7-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 02:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One day into a widespread and marathon storm, tornadoes and floods have killed at least seven people across three states</title>
      <description>The days-long storm is expected to fuel more tornadoes Friday and heavy rains through the weekend. In Tennessee, where much of the damage has emerged, five have died, including two who were killed when a house was overturned. One person was killed in Indiana when they drove over a downed power line.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc19060-10e9-11f0-89a1-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:09:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where Americans could begin to see price hikes from Trump’s tariffs first, including cars and clothes</title>
      <description>Americans will bear the brunt of President Donald Trump’s latest tariffs on imported goods, economists say, with price increases kicking in almost immediately on these common items.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7495fe21-10d9-11f0-9a8e-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 22:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What just happened with Trump’s tariffs announcement? 5 experts explain.</title>
      <description>5 takeaways from Trump’s tariffs announcement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">102739d0-10d5-11f0-b843-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 21:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms Mehmet Oz to lead the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services</title>
      <description>The daytime TV star turned D.C. bureaucrat will be in charge of overseeing more than $1 trillion in annual spending for programs that include providing health insurance to over 130 million low-income and older Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc844350-10ca-11f0-9e90-0000a1aceddb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 sees its worst day since 2020 as Wall Street digests Trump’s global tariffs</title>
      <description>The Nasdaq composite index and S&amp;P 500 ended Thursday back in correction territory, defined as a decline of at least 10 percent from a recent peak, as investors, businesses and consumers fret about rising costs from an onslaught of new tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c525720-10c7-11f0-9f5e-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 20:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon inspector general will scrutinize Trump team’s use of unclassified Signal chat to coordinate military attack in Yemen</title>
      <description>The acting inspector general’s office said in a memo to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth and Deputy Defense Secretary Steve Feinberg that the inquiry will seek to determine whether Hegseth and his team “complied with DoD policies and procedures for the use of a commercial messaging application for official business.”

Republicans and Democrats in Congress had requested the watchdog’s involvement after top Trump officials inadvertently included a journalist on the highly sensitive Signal chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca1de480-10bf-11f0-a0e5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 19:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires senior National Security Council aides after far-right activist Laura Loomer visited him and pushed for ousters</title>
      <description>Loomer had urged President Donald Trump to purge staffers with foreign policy views deemed counter to his “America First” agenda, and the number of dismissals could grow, said people with knowledge of the shake-up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c202ff0-10b4-11f0-b2c0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 17:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House touted 72 recent immigration arrests. Half were behind bars before ICE apprehended them, a Post review found.</title>
      <description>In prison-orange boxes on social media, the White House highlighted immigration arrests made in communities in the early weeks of President Donald Trump’s second term. But many had been found in prisons, not American streets, and some have had their sentences cut short so they can be deported, worrying advocates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7c9330-10ac-11f0-a5f0-0000a1acebd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:57:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Her daughter, raised as her sister, finally learns the truth</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Her daughter, raised as her sister, finally learns the truth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12469830-10a5-11f0-a69b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 16:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bruce Springsteen will release seven ‘lost’ full-length albums in June</title>
      <description>The legendary rock singer announced the June 27 release of “Tracks II: The Lost Albums,” which will include seven albums recorded between 1983 and 2018. He also previewed the project with the song “Rain in the River.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e68c2720-109d-11f0-a4fc-0000a1acef21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 15:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are food prices really rising? Track the cost of a BLT to get a sense.</title>
      <description>We’re tracking inflation over more than 30 essential ingredients you may consume daily.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc6bdab0-1094-11f0-afa4-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Fantasy numbers’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaba6fe0-108f-11f0-9e05-0000a1acef80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Size of Trump tariffs stuns allies and threatens the global economic outlook as U.S. markets brace for volatility</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s trade war is sending global stocks lower and rattling business owners as they try to make sense of new tariffs that are taking hold. The rollout of the tariffs, which economists say will cost U.S. consumers and businesses billions of dollars more this year, threatens to radically alter the financial outlook.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">305d32a0-108e-11f0-9088-0000a1ace426</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 13:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Musk under pressure. Federal firings. Gaza war. Dangerous storms. Switch 2. Toddler archaeologist. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c747a060-107a-11f0-bbd4-0000a1aceb7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hungary to withdraw from the International Criminal Court, government says, after Orban ignored the court’s warrant for Netanyahu’s arrest</title>
      <description>The announcement by Prime Minister Viktor Orban’s chief of staff came during a visit by Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to Hungary. Leaving the court, which has accused Netanyahu of war crimes in Gaza, would require legislative approval and a withdrawal process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef78b81-1069-11f0-848e-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk and his PAC to keep spending on politics despite campaign loss in Wisconsin and doubts in the GOP</title>
      <description>The billionaire, whose network of allies poured more than $20 million into the Wisconsin Supreme Court race, will be heavily involved in elections going forward, according to two people familiar with the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c83e4290-1010-11f0-8101-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 10% tariffs on all imports and higher taxes on goods from about 60 countries, in sharp escalation of trade war</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump unveiled the details of the broadest import taxes in decades in a Rose Garden ceremony, the first of his second term. The tariffs will take effect immediately, the White House has said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaa20810-1002-11f0-ae31-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team has weighed deal to avert TikTok ban in U.S. that would leave algorithm in Chinese ownership</title>
      <description>The White House has considered a menu of options in recent weeks. They include a scenario where investors outside of China would increase their ownership of TikTok while Beijing-based ByteDance would retain ownership of the powerful algorithm that recommends what people see on the popular video app, according to two people familiar with the deliberations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e02b2750-0fe4-11f0-91bf-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claimed the Smithsonian is filled with ‘corrosive’ art. Monica Hesse found something different.</title>
      <description>What exactly does Trump think is in the Smithsonian?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91037f81-0fdd-11f0-ae56-0000a1ace06d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
