<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:10:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>White House budget office instructs agencies to prep for mass layoffs if the government shuts down</title>
      <description>The memo directs agencies to consider firing employees working on any program that is not funded by another law, such as Republicans’ One Big Beautiful Bill Act, and which does not align with the president’s priorities.

Government funding will run out next week if Congress doesn't act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f6a4441-9a02-11f0-b176-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Comey. ICE shooting. Tylenol pushback. FEMA delay. Kamala Harris. Huntington’s disease. Space weather. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6aaa360-99fe-11f0-8fda-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She shattered her elbow and ended up with a $97,000 bill</title>
      <description>Deborah Buttgereit struggled to afford health coverage after her husband’s death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">786c8090-999c-11f0-b7aa-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 23:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump should fix the U.N., not just grandstand, John Bolton writes</title>
      <description>Rhetorical digs won’t improve an institution in need of serious repair, Bolton writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35d40e10-9992-11f0-94e7-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department will seek to indict former FBI director James B. Comey, fulfilling a demand from Trump</title>
      <description>After the U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Virginia resigned under pressure, President Donald Trump replaced him with a White House aide and demanded that Attorney General Pam Bondi seek criminal charges against Comey. Virginia prosecutors plan to ask a grand jury in Richmond to indict him on allegations that he lied to Congress, people familiar with the matter say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5436060-998a-11f0-ae86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China, the world’s largest greenhouse gas emitter, pledges its first-ever reduction target</title>
      <description>China committed to reducing its greenhouse gas emissions by 7 percent to 10 percent over the next decade. Climate experts widely described China’s commitment as insufficient and said they hoped the country would out-perform its new target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c9f05a0-9981-11f0-b9e5-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationals to name Paul Toboni as head of baseball operations, tasking him with Washington’s teetering rebuild</title>
      <description>Toboni, 35, arrives in D.C. from the Boston Red Sox, where he helped oversee a stellar draft and player development system. The decision, confirmed by two people familiar with the situation, comes after the Nationals fired longtime general manager Mike Rizzo and manager Dave Martinez in July.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed726650-997b-11f0-8a51-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Texas flooded, key staff say FEMA’s leader could not be reached — part of a broader pattern of inaccessibility</title>
      <description>After the deadly July floods in Texas, key Federal Emergency Management Agency staff members say they could not reach acting administrator David Richardson for a period of roughly 24 hours as they scrambled to coordinate a response. The Washington Post reviewed internal records that support current and former FEMA officials’ claims that Richardson is frequently inaccessible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2922d801-9978-11f0-8187-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:56:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Kimmel and the upside of ignoring big-government coercion</title>
      <description>Trump, Kimmel and the upside of ignoring big-government coercion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8205e130-9967-11f0-8fc6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:57:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Planner is told to ‘chill’ when family’s lateness ruins plans</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Planner is told to ‘chill’ when family’s lateness ruins plans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb7c490-995f-11f0-a976-0000a1ace7dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anti-ICE messaging was found on rounds in Dallas ICE facility shooting that killed 1 person and injured 2, officials say</title>
      <description>No Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers were injured in the shooting, an ICE official said at a news conference. The shooter is also dead, officials say. The FBI is investigating the attack as an “act of targeted violence,” a Dallas special agent said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40da88b0-995c-11f0-8749-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 15:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not allowing a ‘shopping spree’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d3d09f0-994b-11f0-acfb-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:37:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denmark, hoping to reconcile, will apologize to Greenland over forced contraception</title>
      <description>Danish Prime Minister Mette Frederiksen is scheduled to formally apologize for forced contraception in Greenland. The public apology in Greenland’s capital comes as Denmark aims to repair colonial wounds amid attention from U.S. President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">798bb760-9948-11f0-83e6-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s U.N. speech. Jimmy Kimmel. USAID money. House margin. Deadly bacteria. Hurricane season. The rapture. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b316f30-9935-11f0-8fd1-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Kimmel delivers a passionate defense of free speech as his show returns to the air</title>
      <description>During his opening monologue, Kimmel thanked those who offered him overwhelming support after ABC temporarily pulled his show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">402ac150-9907-11f0-b02b-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 05:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What researchers suspect could be fueling cancer among millennials</title>
      <description>The rise in cancers in younger adults has drawn more scientists to investigate the ways modern life might be rewriting the body’s cellular fate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb7c790-98c4-11f0-b665-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Watch The Post’s Global AI summit on what’s next in the artificial-intelligence revolution</title>
      <description>As AI evolves at lightning speed, nations are racing to grasp its promise, confront its risks and shape its future. Follow along live as we explore how this technology is reshaping businesses, the workforce, education, health and humanity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbb04f20-98b2-11f0-818f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 19:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ryan Wesley Routh is found guilty of trying to kill Trump as he played golf at his West Palm Beach course last year, AP reports</title>
      <description>Routh, who represented himself in the two-week trial in Florida, faced five charges, including the attempted assassination of a major presidential candidate. He was arrested Sept. 15, 2024, when federal agents say he fled after setting up a “sniper’s nest” in the shrubbery outside Trump International Golf Club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1dbff40-98af-11f0-bcb4-0000a1ace7f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 19:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB will implement an automated umpire system to challenge ball and strike calls, starting in 2026</title>
      <description>The robotic umpires will arrive only partially next season, allowing batters, pitchers and catchers to challenge ball and strike calls in real time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eed2ef0-98aa-11f0-8415-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does cohabiting in his house mean they split his remodeling costs?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does cohabiting in his house mean they split his remodeling costs?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8d600a0-989f-11f0-b946-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I tried to protect my kids from the internet. Here’s what happened.</title>
      <description>Tech companies should be responsible for verifying the ages of their users.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9617bc0-989a-11f0-93e7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nexstar and Sinclair will not broadcast Jimmy Kimmel’s return to ABC, keeping him off air in D.C., Seattle and other major markets</title>
      <description>“Jimmy Kimmel Live!” will return to nighttime television Tuesday — less than a week after ABC suspended the show in response to the host’s comments on Charlie Kirk’s killing. But station owners Nexstar and Sinclair are refusing to air it, setting up a battle between the network and those who carry its programming in dozens of U.S. markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d43da0-9896-11f0-84d0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A toy company surges in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e95e3c0-9882-11f0-9580-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:34:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tylenol and autism. Jimmy Kimmel. Justice Department. Student loans. TikTok deal. Cancer risk. Fat Bear Week. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74c7b3a0-986c-11f0-b6e1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'An eye for an eye'? Erika Kirk did the remarkable.</title>
      <description>At the memorial service for conservative commentator Charlie Kirk, his widow forgave his killer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e79f4b81-97fa-11f0-930f-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 21:27:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France defies Trump administration, recognizing Palestinian statehood after U.S. attempts to quash effort</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio had tried to kill the initiative, issuing a cable to U.S. embassies and consulates in June to discourage attending France's meetings and publicly lambasting the effort as a “gift to Hamas.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7989191-97f6-11f0-ba96-0000a1ace6fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disney to bring back Jimmy Kimmel, sidelined after Charlie Kirk comments</title>
      <description>The late-night host will return to television Tuesday, nearly a week after ABC took him off the air under pressure from the Trump administration, station owners and conservative critics upset with his comments in the wake of Charlie Kirk’s killing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7931b40-97ed-11f0-ba5a-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 19:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to fire last Democratic member of Federal Trade Commission</title>
      <description>The justices overturned a lower-court injunction that reinstated Rebecca Slaughter to her position with the agency that oversees antitrust and consumer protection issues while litigation over her removal works its way through the courts. The high court also announced it will hear arguments on overturning a 90-year-old precedent that allows Congress to restrict a president's power to remove members of independent agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4610cbe0-97eb-11f0-b9ad-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 19:35:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is ‘workaholic’ boyfriend capable of loving their daughter?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is ‘workaholic’ boyfriend capable of loving their daughter?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5d4a4d0-97d2-11f0-9081-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Egypt’s president pardons Arab Spring activist Alaa Abdel Fattah, who spent more than a decade in prison</title>
      <description>Abdel Fattah, 43, was an icon of the 2011 uprising that ousted authoritarian leader Hosni Mubarak. He was arrested two years later, after Egypt’s current president, Abdel Fatah El-Sisi, seized power and launched a sweeping crackdown on dissent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0860ba2-97cb-11f0-8272-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A university under the spotlight in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4226d330-97b9-11f0-9a71-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk’s Christianity-infused politics appear poised to ascend within the GOP, and other takeaways from his memorial</title>
      <description>Kirk was not a household name before his death, but the right-wing movement he built could become a dominant part of the Republican Party, according to more than a dozen speakers and leaders of the Trump administration who memorialized him Sunday. Here are takeaways from the hours-long service in Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d33a6ec0-97a7-11f0-ac69-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk memorial. Trump targets. Palestinian state. Autism. Rising costs. Air traffic control. Build-a-Bear. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45d07c40-97a3-11f0-9b47-0000a1ace70b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, allies cast Charlie Kirk as ‘martyr’ whose legacy can shape GOP future at memorial that blended religious fervor, politics</title>
      <description>Republicans extolled conservative activist Charlie Kirk at a memorial Sunday as a religious leader of almost biblical stature who transformed the party and was critical to delivering the presidency to Donald Trump — and they predicted that Kirk’s slaying will galvanize their political movement for generations to come.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1961bdb0-974c-11f0-a642-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Donald Trump, Vice President JD Vance to speak at memorial for conservative activist Charlie Kirk. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The president, vice president and Kirk's widow, Erika, will speak to the tens of thousands of supporters gathered to mourn Kirk and highlight the contributions his organization, Turning Point USA, has made to the modern Republican Party. The scale and security of the event is on par with a state funeral, and the attendance of high-level political figures is notable, given that Kirk was a private citizen who was not well-known to a large swath of Americans until his death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d836470-9732-11f0-9097-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 21:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration set to tie Tylenol to autism risk, officials say</title>
      <description>Federal officials have been reviewing a possible link between Tylenol's early use in pregnancy and an increased risk of autism in children — a connection that researchers say needs more studies to draw conclusions. They are also expected to tout a lesser-known drug, leucovorin, as a potential treatment. President Donald Trump has prioritized the initiatives, although outside researchers have called for further study.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03879ee0-9721-11f0-b490-0000a1ace8fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 19:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 surprisingly hopeful things we learned about Alzheimer’s this year</title>
      <description>From a blood test to the unexpected role of lithium, these findings may lead to better diagnosis and treatment of the memory-robbing condition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4226790-9714-11f0-9e08-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 18:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1384bb0-9708-11f0-a1ac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 16:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">398752e0-96f1-11f0-b344-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 13:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K., Canada, Australia recognize Palestinian state, reversing decades-long positions in breaking with the U.S.</title>
      <description>British Prime Minister Keir Starmer said his government would formally recognize a state of Palestine, making good on a pledge to do so if Israel refused to implement a ceasefire in Gaza and commit to work toward a two-state solution. Canada and Australia also announced recognition of Palestine in statements issued Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b5c0890-96ed-11f0-a5b4-0000a1ace5f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 13:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His wife was dying, his federal job crumbling. It tested his faith — in God and Trump.</title>
      <description>One federal worker thought Trump represented his own conservative values. Then the government kept rejecting his attempts to resign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3f8df10-962e-11f0-af46-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 14:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ab408d0-9629-11f0-8938-0000a1aced50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA tells scientists to stop publishing research, requires new review process, employees say</title>
      <description>Staff from the EPA’s Office of Water were summoned to a town hall meeting this week and told by political appointees to pause the publication of most research, pending a review.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c992c1c0-9625-11f0-8938-0000a1aced50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 13:29:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal prosecutor in Virginia resigns after pushback from Trump over decision not to charge political foes</title>
      <description>Erik S. Siebert, the Trump-appointed U.S. attorney for the Eastern District of Virginia, had determined there was insufficient evidence to indict New York Attorney General Letitia James for alleged mortgage fraud. He also recently declined to prosecute former FBI director James Comey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff6fbf40-95b8-11f0-ba43-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:30:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump adds $100,000 fee to H-1B visas for skilled foreign workers and rolls out $1 million gold-card visas</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s visa overhaul is expected to constrain a program for highly skilled workers that is widely used in Silicon Valley while opening up immigration access to wealthy foreigners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e95d780-95ad-11f0-8db2-0000a1ace210</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 23:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.-appointed CDC panel ends broad endorsement of covid vaccines, voting to recommend medical consultations</title>
      <description>The federal vaccine advisory panel voted Friday to recommend that Americans get coronavirus vaccines only in consultation with their clinicians. The recommendation now goes to the acting Centers for Disease Control and Prevention director for final approval. It may create confusion, former health officials and public health experts warn, because of practical barriers to implementing the new guidance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b889c50-959f-11f0-9d83-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and China’s Xi bless long-awaited deal to create a U.S. version of TikTok</title>
      <description>An American version of the popular app will be partly owned by a consortium of investors allied with President Donald Trump, people familiar with the deal said, sidestepping a legally mandated ban the president has repeatedly pushed off.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ca74760-9580-11f0-8a0f-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when you purge the military lawyers</title>
      <description>Why has the military been so silent as the Trump administration has pushed the bounds of law by deploying troops to aid immigration enforcement actions at home and attacking alleged Venezuelan drug-smuggling boats abroad?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5379bb0-957a-11f0-9aa7-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m still sad over our breakup, and he has a new girlfriend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m still sad over our breakup, and he has a new girlfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95d53470-9577-11f0-8500-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:42:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge strikes down Trump’s $15 billion libel lawsuit against the New York Times</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Tampa, Florida, struck down President Donald Trump’s lawsuit, saying the 85-page complaint was “decidedly improper and impermissible.” A new complaint may be filed within 28 days but must be under 40 pages in length.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a80fb40-9575-11f0-8071-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
