<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 08:01:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Top FDA vaccine regulator hired under Trump ousted following conservative criticism</title>
      <description>Vinay Prasad, a physician and former medical professor, joined the administration after gaining prominence as a critic of coronavirus vaccine policies. His ouster follows criticism from conservative activists including Laura Loomer over his approach to drug approvals and past support for Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76866fa0-6cf3-11f0-938d-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 03:15:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tsunami alerts issued for U.S. West Coast and Japan after 8.7-magnitude quake in eastern Russia</title>
      <description>The quake ranks in the top 10 strongest earthquakes ever recorded. A tsunami watch is in place for the entire U.S. West Coast, and warnings have been issued in Hawaii and for Japan, where waves as high as 10 feet are forecast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d0eb173-6ce6-11f0-a831-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 01:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate confirms controversial Trump nominee Emil Bove as federal judge</title>
      <description>The Senate voted Tuesday night to confirm Emil Bove as a federal appeals court judge, ending a contentious confirmation in which the former attorney for President Donald Trump and top Justice Department official was the target of three whistleblower complaints.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eadea080-6ce3-11f0-8d24-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 01:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An op-ed from Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent: The road map to making America a crypto superpower</title>
      <description>The road map to making America a crypto superpower</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc42c921-6cd6-11f0-8e75-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 23:49:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. military is investing in this Pacific island. So is China.</title>
      <description>New U.S. radar sites on Palau are designed to keep China in check. But nearby Chinese tourism developments, some with questionable connections, could create vulnerabilities and enable Beijing to disrupt U.S. military activities in the Pacific.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68e846b0-6cc7-11f0-9568-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 22:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA announces proposal that would end virtually all of its climate regulations</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to rescind a landmark legal opinion that underpins virtually all of its climate regulations, including limits on car and power plant greenhouse gas emissions. EPA Administrator Lee Zeldin said if finalized it would be the largest deregulatory action in U.S. history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a97dc90-6ca7-11f0-9b4f-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ghislaine Maxwell wants immunity and a copy of House lawmakers’ questions before she testifies, her lawyer says</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee has subpoenaed Jeffrey Epstein’s imprisoned associate for a deposition Aug. 11. “Our initial reaction was that Ms. Maxwell would invoke her Fifth Amendment rights and decline to testify at this time,” her attorney wrote in a letter, saying Maxwell would be open to further cooperation if her requests are met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca224a0-6ca4-11f0-bec6-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 17:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whistleblower suggests Trump judicial nominee Emil Bove misled Senate about his role in dismissed case against NYC Mayor Eric Adams</title>
      <description>A third whistleblower has come forward to challenge the federal judicial nomination of Bove, sharing evidence with lawmakers suggesting the former attorney for President Donald Trump and current top Justice Department official misled lawmakers about his handling of the dismissal of public corruption charges against the New York mayor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1267a810-6c97-11f0-8c65-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:14:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Girlfriend’s fury at partner’s job is so raw they can’t discuss it</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Girlfriend’s fury at partner’s job is so raw they can’t discuss it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d34d3c0-6c95-11f0-9c3c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We texted nearly 1,100 Americans about Trump and the Epstein files. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post’s poll finds that Americans largely disapprove of how President Donald Trump is handling the issue, with most Democrats and independents disapproving and Republicans expressing a mix of approval and uncertainty. Most Americans strongly support releasing all files in the Jeffrey Epstein case and suspect the documents contain embarrassing information about Trump, Democrats and billionaires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5fe3d2-6c86-11f0-acf7-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 14:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A classic villain returns in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a388f180-6c80-11f0-9800-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan gunman left note referencing CTE, mayor says; one injured in deadly shooting is an NFL employee</title>
      <description>Mayor Eric Adams told MSNBC the gunman was not an NFL player but referenced a disease linked to head trauma in a note before killing four people, including a police officer.

NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell said in a staff message that an employee was "seriously injured."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baf81390-6c7c-11f0-9825-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 13:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manhattan shooting. Epstein poll. Whistleblower claim. Gaza aid. Planned Parenthood. Heat wave. Sydney Sweeney. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29b20b40-6c6b-11f0-a616-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza’s death toll passes 60,000, health officials say — a reminder of the human cost of Israel’s war as mass hunger takes hold</title>
      <description>The toll from Gaza’s Health Ministry does not distinguish between civilians and combatants but says the majority of the dead are women and children. Public health experts, doctors and conflict casualty monitors say the official figure is an incomplete count of the total number of people killed in Gaza since Hamas attacked Israel on Oct. 7, 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e77d870-6c64-11f0-866e-0000a1ace70d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least four killed, including an off-duty police officer, in Midtown Manhattan shooting, police say</title>
      <description>The gunman died from a self-inflicted gunshot wound, according to the police. The shooting happened inside 345 Park Ave., the tenants of which include the NFL and investment firm Blackstone Group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20a25800-6c27-11f0-85ae-000a1aced5db</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 02:52:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Álvaro Uribe, Colombia’s powerful former president, is convicted in bribery trial</title>
      <description>Álvaro Uribe was found guilty of bribery in criminal proceedings and procedural fraud on Monday, becoming the country’s first former president to be convicted in a criminal trial. The polarizing figure led Colombia from 2002 to 2010 and was credited with turning the tide of his country’s 52-year civil war against leftist insurgents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">947a5830-6c1e-11f0-b033-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 01:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to reduce your risk of heart disease, according to a cardiologist</title>
      <description>Heart disease is the leading cause of death in the United States. But about 80 percent of cases are considered preventable. There are many things you can do to protect your heart, and here are some evidence-based steps a cardiologist recommends to his patients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3da33850-6bf2-11f0-a820-0000a1ace377</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 20:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Without explanation, sister-in-law no-shows care for dying mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Without explanation, sister-in-law no-shows care for dying mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07891490-6bcc-11f0-b820-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is impacting 700 professions — and might impact yours</title>
      <description>How AI is impacting 700 professions — and might impact yours</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e881a290-6bc3-11f0-891e-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 15:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This person ‘will not be intimidated’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">704865c0-6bb9-11f0-9504-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:47:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA struggles to retain air traffic control recruits in a system with ‘hostile’ training</title>
      <description>One out of five trainees fail to get certified. In some cases, recruits failed their training and were dismissed. In others, they left of their own accord rather than endure what they described as haphazard instruction, organizational dysfunction and abusive conditions. “It’s this professional guild, but to me it also felt like a college hazing,” said a retired FAA psychologist. “It was hostile.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a0815c1-6bb5-11f0-9282-0000a1ace7f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 13:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thailand and Cambodia agree to ceasefire after days of border clashes</title>
      <description>The two sides agreed to “an immediate and unconditional ceasefire” starting at midnight, Malaysian Prime Minister Anwar Ibrahim said. President Donald Trump had spoken to both leaders to push for peace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77a59660-6ba2-11f0-957e-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 11:03:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza aid. Trump-Epstein. E.U. trade deal. Walmart stabbing. Plane evacuation. Walking benefits. Gwyneth Paltrow. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">061cf380-6ba2-11f0-8302-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fumes as Epstein scandal dominates headlines, overshadows his agenda</title>
      <description>The president's exasperation follows weeks of missteps and no clear strategy among top officials who underestimated the outrage, especially from the president’s base, and hoped the country would forget about the unreleased Epstein files and move on, according to nearly a dozen people close to the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef4a0780-6b4f-11f0-bcdd-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a microplastics researcher limits exposure to plastics in her day-to-day life</title>
      <description>Scientists have found microplastics in our livers, blood, brains and even placentas. And while more science is needed to fully understand how this affects our health, there’s enough evidence for us to be concerned, writes Tracey Woodruff, a professor at the University of California at San Francisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b77b0070-6b2c-11f0-b99c-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Lehrer dies at 97. The musician and satirist subverted clichés about romance, patriotism and small-town life.</title>
      <description>His astute social commentary, verbal dexterity and often academic subject matter differentiated him from mere novelty acts during the 1950s and 1960s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e60c6bd0-6b1e-11f0-8ae4-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:21:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces outline of tariff deal with European Union, saying he will impose 15% duty on imports</title>
      <description>Leaders around the world are rushing to strike trade agreements with President Donald Trump ahead of an Aug. 1 deadline, when the White House is expected to begin collecting new tariffs on imports from dozens of countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9171fd10-6b14-11f0-8f56-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 18:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>His son co-piloted the DCA-bound flight that crashed. Now Tim Lilley, also a pilot, is seeking answers.</title>
      <description>Lilley has found himself in two roles. He’s a dad in mourning. He’s also an aviation expert — one who has flown both types of aircraft in the Jan. 29 collision at Reagan National Airport — focused on finding answers and accountability for the families of all 67 people killed in the crash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22bbca30-6b0b-11f0-82ee-0000a1ace3d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0bd2da0-6b02-11f0-a0ef-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tour de France confronts a new threat: Are cyclists using tiny motors?</title>
      <description>After a doping scandal, professional cycling is pursuing the dual challenges of keeping the sport honest and convincing a skeptical audience it is.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd5e6590-6af1-11f0-bf2c-000a1aceddc6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">446134e0-6aed-11f0-be02-0000a1ace991</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel allows airdrops of food into Gaza amid international pressure over mounting starvation</title>
      <description>The first pallets of flour, sugar and canned food were dropped late Saturday. A growing number of foreign governments, including Jordan and Britain, have volunteered to airdrop food into Gaza to relieve a deepening crisis that has included deaths from starvation. Aid workers have said the approach is inefficient and inadequate to what's needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf4c5c40-6a63-11f0-bc3d-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 21:02:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth team told to stop using polygraph tests to root out people leaking to news media after complaint to White House</title>
      <description>The White House directed Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth to cease the use of polygraph tests after a senior adviser to Hegseth complained to senior officials about being targeted, U.S. officials and others familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef8ab7b0-6a57-11f0-ad67-0000a1ace84c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 19:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Roommate reacts with ‘bafflement and confusion’ every time I vent</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Roommate reacts with ‘bafflement and confusion’ every time I vent</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ca49190-6a39-11f0-a8df-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A timeless Chinese game is hooking people across D.C. and the nation</title>
      <description>Interest in mah-jongg is surging, thanks in part to a coterie of coaches and instructors, social media influencers, and luxe spaces to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">838b9180-6a2d-11f0-a4fe-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 14:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2770dbc0-6a24-11f0-a42d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From David Ignatius: The 12 days that turned back the clock on Iran’s nuclear program</title>
      <description>Israeli and American assessments agree Tehran’s infrastructure to finish a bomb is shattered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e27360-69ac-11f0-8acc-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 23:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge dismisses Trump administration lawsuit against Illinois and Chicago over 'sanctuary city' policies</title>
      <description>District Judge Lindsay C. Jenkins ruled that the Justice Department "lacks standing" to sue the state and city over what the White House has characterized as impeding its efforts to crack down on undocumented immigrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b65b74e0-69a6-11f0-aedf-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 22:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration releases billions it withheld from school programs, ending weeks of educators’ anxiety before academic year</title>
      <description>With the school year beginning in just weeks, lawmakers of both parties had lobbied the administration to release the funds, which support English-language learning programs, teacher training and academic enrichment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a47644b0-6980-11f0-b9bb-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 17:56:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Deadbeat dad’s parents want to give me money. I don’t want it.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Deadbeat dad’s parents want to give me money. I don’t want it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68d79930-6977-11f0-ad7a-0000a1aceff0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 16:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They’re rich. They’re anti-Trump. And they don’t want their big tax cut.</title>
      <description>Affluent voters have become more Democratic in recent years, opposing President Donald Trump’s policies that will make them richer. Many of the biggest beneficiaries of the GOP tax law say they are getting millions of dollars they don’t want or need.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52436870-6968-11f0-930f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 15:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple’s iOS 26 public beta is here. Here are the 4 biggest changes.</title>
      <description>iOS 26 is one of the most significant software overhauls the tech giant has made for the iPhone in years, and we’ve been testing it for weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41652550-6960-11f0-85cd-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 14:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a58c2150-695b-11f0-ac2c-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza talks. IRS changes. Ghislaine Maxwell. Paramount merger. Hulk Hogan. iPhone update. Tour de France. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84b33690-6946-11f0-bedb-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC approves $8 billion Paramount-Skydance merger after lengthy review marked by controversy</title>
      <description>The merger, which drew allegations of political pressure on Paramount-owned CBS News, was approved by a 2-1 vote, with Biden-appointed commissioner Anna M. Gomez voting against the transaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc2b2d60-68db-11f0-bbdb-0000a1ace0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:17:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs order pushing for more forced hospitalizations of homeless people with mental illness and addiction</title>
      <description>The White House said the move would shift people into long-term institutional settings and restore public order. Critics of the policy said it threatens to return the nation to an era when people were often unjustly locked away in mental health institutions and does nothing to help Americans afford housing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03c02a50-68da-11f0-b61e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 22:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France will recognize a Palestinian state, Macron says, calling for an urgent end to the war in Gaza</title>
      <description>In a statement, French President Emmanuel Macron said he would recognize Palestine at the U.N. General Assembly in September. “The urgent need today is to end the war in Gaza and to rescue the civilian population,” he said, adding that there is no other way to build lasting security in the Middle East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dc8f860-68d5-11f0-bbdb-0000a1ace0c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration sues New York City for using sanctuary city policies to impede immigration crackdown efforts</title>
      <description>The legal action comes days after an off-duty Customs and Border Protection officer was shot during an ambush robbery attempt in an upper Manhattan park, allegedly by a pair of undocumented immigrants.
The Justice Department says in its filing that the nation’s largest city has been flouting its obligations to assist in federal immigration enforcement by operating as a sanctuary city for decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9e71fe0-68d2-11f0-bdd0-0000a1ace430</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USDA will relocate most of its D.C.-based workforce and close several key facilities</title>
      <description>The agency will move about 2,600 employees to five other locations in the country and shutter some facilities in the capital region. The closures will include the Henry A. Wallace Beltsville Agricultural Research Center, a 6,500-acre operation that dates back 115 years and is one of the world’s largest facilities of its kind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eedd480-68cf-11f0-89d7-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass starvation is stalking Gaza as Israel restricts aid and deaths from hunger rise</title>
      <description>Testimonies from doctors, relief workers and Gazans make it clear that a worst-case scenario is unfolding: Nearly 1 in 3 people are going multiple days without eating, according to the United Nations, and hospitals are reporting rising deaths.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebf73930-68c1-11f0-9939-0000a1ace966</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 19:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
