<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 01:25:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Claims of sexual assault, violence: How the myth of Sean Combs came undone</title>
      <description>Diddy’s downfall built up slowly and then arrived dizzyingly fast, as rumors and accusations turned into lawsuits, raids and a decaying of Combs’s empire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34e80850-099a-11ef-a40f-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 22:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. tells Qatar to evict Hamas political leaders if militant group obstructs Israeli deal for Gaza cease-fire, hostage release</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken delivered the message to Qatar’s prime minister, Mohammed bin Abdulrahman Al Thani, last month, said a U.S. official. Diplomats familiar with the situation said the Gulf emirate, which has hosted Hamas’s political leaders for years at the United States’ request, has anticipated the request for months and advised them to devise a backup plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46789430-0991-11ef-b372-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 21:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada arrests three men in killing of Sikh separatist, an official says; Trudeau linked killing to Indian government</title>
      <description>The three men are Indian Canadians believed to be part of an organized crime network acting on the behalf of the Indian government and its intelligence apparatus, according to the official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive law enforcement matter.
Prime Minister Justin Trudeau told lawmakers in September that authorities were pursuing “credible allegations” that agents of the Indian government were behind the killing of Hardeep Singh Nijjar last June in Surrey, British Columbia. Nijjar, a Canadian citizen, advocated for an autonomous Sikh state in India.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">236171e0-097f-11ef-abb4-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:58:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Henry Cuellar (D-Tex.) and his wife charged with accepting $600,000 in bribes from foreign companies</title>
      <description>The congressman and his wife, Imelda Cuellar, are accused of setting up front companies that entered into sham contracts with an oil company controlled by the Azerbaijan government and a bank headquartered in Mexico. In a statement, Cuellar said he is innocent and will continue his campaign for another term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4edf0201-097b-11ef-b372-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 18:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My boyfriend’s closest confidante is his on-again, off-again ex</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My boyfriend’s closest confidante is his on-again, off-again ex</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d388d50-096e-11ef-b83e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutors question Hope Hicks on ‘Access Hollywood’ tape that they say helped lead to hush money payment. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Called as a witness in Donald Trump’s New York hush money trial, the former aide told jurors she was “stunned” by the release of a hot mic tape in which Trump made light of forcing himself on women.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7966000-096c-11ef-bd01-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 16:48:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas man’s ex-partner left the state to get an abortion. Now he’s asking a court for permission to investigate.</title>
      <description>The previously unreported legal action reflects a potential new antiabortion strategy to block women from traveling to end their pregnancies in states where abortion is legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7153530-095d-11ef-b0c7-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1b48cf0-0950-11ef-9a00-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 13:27:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added 175,000 jobs in April, as labor market growth slowed, compared to earlier in the year</title>
      <description>Despite high interest rates, the labor market continues to show resilience in 2024, according to the latest data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e030910-0949-11ef-a9c8-0000a1ace665</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 12:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Campus protests. Jobs report. Boeing whistleblower. Hottest April. Russian TikTok. Kentucky Derby. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b05c60-093c-11ef-abc9-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen A. Smith and his naked-as-ever ambition are testing just how much of the ESPN star America wants</title>
      <description>Sports, politics, sex, SpongeBob: There’s nothing Smith won’t argue about — as long as you keep listening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5dc6d80-08c8-11ef-937e-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 21:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Will request for a postnup offend much younger wife?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Will request for a postnup offend much younger wife?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76c9ec00-08a7-11ef-9b9b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 17:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden expands boundaries of two national monuments in California, protecting land that Native American tribes consider sacred</title>
      <description>President Biden signed two proclamations enlarging the San Gabriel Mountains National Monument and the Berryessa Snow Mountain National Monument, using his executive authority to protect vast swaths of land of cultural significance to tribes and nearby communities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e0c6e40-08a1-11ef-9548-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A botched drone strike in Syria killed a civilian, not a terrorist as the U.S. first claimed, Defense Department acknowledges</title>
      <description>The U.S. military’s findings, to be released later Thursday, follow a Washington Post investigation that cast doubt on its initial assertion the operation last year targeted a senior al-Qaeda figure. A Defense Department official said the real suspect got away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6983aea0-089d-11ef-a530-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 16:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden urges campus protesters to refrain from violence and says demonstrations have not changed his policies</title>
      <description>The president called on pro-Palestinian demonstrators at campuses around the country to avoid chaos and intimidation, saying that Americans have a right to peaceful protest but strongly condemning some of the tactics that have been used. “We’ve all seen the images, and they put to the test two fundamental American principles,” Biden said in quickly scheduled remarks at the White House. “The first is the right to free speech and for people to peacefully assemble and make their voices heard. The second is the rule of law. Both must be upheld.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad43571-089a-11ef-83f6-0000a1ace705</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 15:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wait, a baseball game was delayed by what?! Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c44a1c0-0888-11ef-aaf9-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 13:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of fifth victim in Baltimore bridge collapse has been recovered, authorities say</title>
      <description>The victim, one of six construction workers who died when the Key Bridge collapsed, was identified as Miguel Angel Luna Gonzalez, 49, of Glen Burnie, Md.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26c42af0-0879-11ef-b5ab-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:43:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCLA protests. Arizona abortion. Mike Johnson. Harvey Weinstein. Bird flu. Menopause drugs. Missing cat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f3f7b50-0873-11ef-bdda-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This middle school’s battle against cellphones yielded surprising results</title>
      <description>Illing Middle School in Manchester, Conn., navigated objections from students and some parents to lock up cellphones in a bid to improve focus and reduce social media-fueled conflicts. What unfolded reflects a broader struggle underway in education as some administrators turn to increasingly drastic measures to limit the reach of a technology that is both ubiquitous and endlessly distracting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3754b920-0806-11ef-b7d2-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes divisive antisemitism bill as Republicans seek to crack down on campus protests over Gaza war</title>
      <description>Critics of the Antisemitism Awareness Act, which has some Democratic support, call the legislation an effort to silence opinions of Israel and an affront to the First Amendment. It’s unclear what the bill’s prospects are in the Democratic-controlled Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">076ccb00-07ff-11ef-b3a8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-led Arizona Senate votes to repeal Civil War-era abortion ban. The Democratic governor is expected to sign it into law.</title>
      <description>The state’s highest court revived the ban on nearly all abortions in early April and it was set to take effect in June. The repeal is expected to be signed into law by Gov. Katie Hobbs in the coming days, but the state attorney general’s office said the repeal would not take effect until 90 days after the legislature adjourns for the summer. So, barring successful court challenges, the 1864 ban could take effect for a short time in the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb7582c0-07f6-11ef-8be6-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 20:10:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve leaves interest rates unchanged as rising inflation reduces pressure for cuts</title>
      <description>Since the start of the year, hotter-than-expected price data has complicated officials’ plans for taking pressure off the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d82dc1b0-07e4-11ef-b0bb-0000a1ace635</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 18:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Too late to accept a decade-old apology, accidentally left unread?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Too late to accept a decade-old apology, accidentally left unread?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe5d5c80-07d3-11ef-957d-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 16:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: Can a restaurant charge us $900 two months before dinner? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: Can a restaurant charge us $900 two months before dinner? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b1bc650-07d1-11ef-b93d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A landmark study scared women away from menopause hormone treatments. A 20-year follow-up has found fears were largely overblown.</title>
      <description>A new analysis published in JAMA found that for many younger menopausal women — typically those under 60 — the benefits of the drugs probably outweigh the risks for the short-term treatment of menopause symptoms. The analysis shows that younger women starting menopause and experiencing symptoms can take hormone treatments for several years with a lower likelihood of adverse effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a592121-07cd-11ef-b905-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 15:12:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despair at Florida clinic as 6-week abortion ban — expected to be the biggest jolt to access since Dobbs — takes effect</title>
      <description>At one Fort Lauderdale-area abortion clinic, women crowded the waiting room in the final hours Tuesday before the ban took effect. More than 80,000 women get an abortion in Florida in a typical year, accounting for about 1 in 12 abortions nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63b7c910-07c7-11ef-88f2-0000a1ace4c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 300 protesters were arrested at Columbia University and City College overnight, NYC Mayor Eric Adams says</title>
      <description>Officers in riot gear on Tuesday night cleared Hamilton Hall on Columbia’s campus, which was occupied by pro-Palestinian protesters, as demonstrators and authorities continue to face off on campuses across the nation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66d52090-07c5-11ef-a76a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 14:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A baffling artifact in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81b73ec1-07c0-11ef-919a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:41:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marjorie Taylor Greene says she will move to oust Speaker Mike Johnson. The House is likely to consider the motion next week.</title>
      <description>The move came after weeks of threats from Greene (R-Ga.), angry that Johnson (R-La.) has worked with Democrats to pass key legislation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba225e90-07be-11ef-9a5c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 13:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia arrests. Trump penalty. Florida abortion ban. Marijuana. Debt relief. Student phones. Roman mystery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd1e3ee0-07a9-11ef-955a-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York police enter Columbia University after pro-Palestinian demonstrators occupied a campus building. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Officers wearing riot gear were holding zip ties on their way to the encampment where students were demanding that the Ivy League university divest from Israeli-linked companies more than six months into that country's war with Hamas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e355a7a0-0759-11ef-97e3-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 01:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judges strike down Louisiana's new congressional map, saying second majority Black district is unconstitutional</title>
      <description>The panel ruled Tuesday that a newly redrawn congressional map, which added a second majority Black district, violated the Equal Protection Clause and blocked the state from using the map in upcoming elections. The Louisiana legislature approved the new map in January after a federal court found that the existing map probably illegally diminished Black voting power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd1e55a0-074b-11ef-9b50-0000a1acebf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 23:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hidden force supercharged this Alabama flood — and threatens the American South</title>
      <description>The U.S. Southeast and Gulf coasts are experiencing one of the world’s worst bursts of sea level rise, turning some storms into flooding disasters, a Washington Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94f0e730-073d-11ef-b661-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 22:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are most Americans getting more sleep than you? See how you compare.</title>
      <description>Americans gained 10 minutes of sleep per day, on average, between 2019 and 2022, but that extra time was not evenly shared. The biggest sleep gains were seen in younger adults between the ages of 25 and 34, men of all ages and people without children, according to a Post analysis of data from the American Time Use Survey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4dc24c0-072b-11ef-b6d7-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 19:57:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEA plans to reclassify marijuana as a lower-risk drug, officials say — a major move that would ease access nationwide</title>
      <description>The move by the Drug Enforcement Administration, first reported by the Associated Press, must receive approval from the White House Office of Management and Budget. Such a decision would not legalize marijuana at the federal level but could broaden access for medicinal use and boost the cannabis industry in states where the drug is legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f313810-071b-11ef-a502-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 17:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Her family left all the kitchen work to her, so she went on strike</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Her family left all the kitchen work to her, so she went on strike</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a65800-070a-11ef-a4e0-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 16:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli forces killed World Central Kitchen aid workers in Gaza. Here’s why we’re going back, chef José Andrés writes.</title>
      <description>We’re going back to Gaza to feed people. Here’s what we need from Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6785a20-0706-11ef-890b-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 15:32:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial finds the former president in contempt for his critical public statements</title>
      <description>Prosecutors had asked New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan to find former president Donald Trump in contempt for his public statements. Trump was under a gag order after being openly critical of various people — including Merchan’s adult daughter — on the campaign trail and on social media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7e9db20-06f7-11ef-bc5f-0000a1ace8f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rachel McAdams, Jeremy Strong and Jessica Lange are among the 2024 Tony nominees. Here is the full list.</title>
      <description>“Hell’s Kitchen,” “Illinoise,” “The Outsiders,” “Suffs” and “Water for Elephants” will contend for best musical at the June 16 ceremony in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9604790-06f5-11ef-8034-0000a1ace721</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A letter, and no resignation, in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19231b21-06f5-11ef-852e-000a1acecd15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA bans most uses of a toxic paint stripper tied to dozens of deaths</title>
      <description>The move bolsters the Biden administration’s broader crackdown on an array of chemicals known to cause serious health effects, despite their helpful applications in everyday life. Methylene chloride is suspected of causing cancer and has been linked to at least 88 accidental deaths since 1980.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d96ba450-06f1-11ef-a462-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 13:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia protest. Charlotte shooting. Trump trial. Gender care. Emergency brakes. Postpartum depression. Sleep. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6911cd1-06e0-11ef-bc5f-0000a1ace8f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia students occupy a university building as tensions continue to rise on campuses across the country</title>
      <description>Student protesters at Columbia University declared overnight that they had taken over a building near the campus’s South Lawn, hours after the Ivy League institution started suspending students who refused to leave a pro-Palestinian encampment on campus. At the University of Texas at Austin, police in riot gear arrested and pepper-sprayed protesters Monday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">092bc880-06e0-11ef-8294-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 10:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All new cars must have automatic emergency braking systems by 2029 under new federal safety rule</title>
      <description>The standards require cars to apply brakes automatically to avoid hitting pedestrians and other vehicles, even at higher speeds. Industry groups say the rule is impractical and that no currently produced vehicles can achieve the new standard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33968de0-0680-11ef-8793-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 officers fatally shot, 5 injured while serving warrant in Charlotte, N.C.</title>
      <description>Members of a U.S. Marshals fugitive task force were met with gunfire while trying to serve a warrant. The shooter was also killed, police said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7de832b0-067e-11ef-8774-0000a1ace886</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real Rick Steves is so much more complex than the travel host you see on TV</title>
      <description>At 68, America's favorite travel expert is still working hard and speaking out on ways to make the country a little more like his beloved Europe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a73f5e30-066b-11ef-b350-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump on trial: Personal anguish, political defiance and a loss of control</title>
      <description>Two weeks in, the first criminal trial of a former president has been personally taxing for Donald Trump and disruptive to his campaign for a return to the White House. The indictments that once helped Trump lock down the GOP nomination by firing up his base have become a serious constraint in the general election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05815f90-065b-11ef-b45d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appellate court rules state health-care plans must pay for gender-affirming surgeries, a major win for transgender rights</title>
      <description>The decision came from a set of cases out of North Carolina and West Virginia, where state officials argued that their policies were based on cost concerns rather than bias. The U.S. Court of Appeals for the 4th Circuit rejected that argument, saying the plans were discriminating against trans people in need of treatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aacf0f0-0648-11ef-9054-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is checking his phone the best way to prove he isn’t lying anymore?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is checking his phone the best way to prove he isn’t lying anymore?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f4e2280-0643-11ef-b401-0000a1acecd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All about open seating in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b93ec100-062c-11ef-bc15-0000a1ace8c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
