<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 12:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Cepeda dies at 86. The Hall of Famer was known as baseball’s ‘Baby Bull.’</title>
      <description>Cepeda, one of baseball’s most feared hitters in the 1950s and 1960s who played in three World Series, died Friday, according to a statement from his family released through the San Francisco Giants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dae4a7f0-35d1-11ef-a47b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2024 04:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s next for Biden and the Democrats? Our columnists discuss the aftermath of the first debate.</title>
      <description>President Biden’s debate performance has Democrats in a panic and Donald Trump supporters gleeful. Columnists Karen Tumulty, Dana Milbank and Jim Geraghty process how things feel the morning after, whether the president should step aside and how the truth was the night’s biggest loser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4208400-358f-11ef-ac39-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 20:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: Are my friends judging me because I don't have a maid?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: Are my friends judging me because I don't have a maid?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2acf22a0-356d-11ef-b0fa-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Could Democrats replace Biden at the convention? We’re answering your debate questions.</title>
      <description>Join Washington Post reporters Toluse Olorunnipa, Michael Scherer and Amy Gardner for a live chat on what President Biden and former president Donald Trump said — and didn’t say — during the debate along with what’s next for both candidates. Ask your question now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8a64cc0-3560-11ef-afc9-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says prosecutors improperly charged hundreds of Jan. 6 rioters</title>
      <description>After the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol, federal prosecutors charged more than 350 participants with obstructing or impeding an official proceeding. The Supreme Court had to decide the legality of that charge, which is also among the charges former president Donald Trump faces in his D.C. trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28b84e60-355e-11ef-ad16-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court overturns ‘Chevron’ precedent, a victory for conservatives eager to curb the power of U.S. agencies</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court curtailed the power of federal government agencies to regulate vast swaths of American life, overturning a 40-year-old legal precedent long targeted by conservatives who say the government gives unaccountable bureaucrats too much authority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2424f60-355a-11ef-aaf1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:29:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa’s Supreme Court approves six-week abortion ban passed by state lawmakers in 2023</title>
      <description>The measure enacted by the Republican-led legislature prohibits abortion at the point when fetal cardiac activity can be detected. A preliminary injunction from a lower state court had kept the procedure legal up to 22 weeks of pregnancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fcc1c00-3557-11ef-af63-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court says ban on homeless camping does not violate Constitution</title>
      <description>The court was reviewing a set of laws from Grants Pass, Ore., at a time when local and state leaders are struggling to deal with the growing number of unhoused individuals nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bac21c0-3557-11ef-a63e-0000a1ace569</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 14:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6a4ca80-3552-11ef-8eca-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democrats question whether Biden can recover from his damaging debate performance</title>
      <description>Democrats awoke Friday wondering whether President Biden can recover from what many judged as the worst performance by a presidential candidate in the modern history of politics. He has time to turn his campaign around, but he would need to persuade voters to forget what they saw Thursday night and reassess his fitness to serve a second term, chief correspondent Dan Balz writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bb67810-354f-11ef-b9cf-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 13:09:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post publisher’s role in Murdoch phone-hacking response comes into sharper focus</title>
      <description>William Lewis helped manage News International’s handling of the hacking scandal, a response that left some police officials and IT workers concerned the company was obstructing the inquiry. Former British prime minister Gordon Brown is now calling for Lewis to be criminally investigated. Lewis denies wrongdoing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49cfbf00-3542-11ef-9604-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debate fallout. Supreme Court. Bible lessons. Uvalde police. Bronny James. Gen Z creators. Pandas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9226d3b0-353d-11ef-af63-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Biden’s rough night, Trump’s false claims, and other takeaways from the first 2024 presidential debate</title>
      <description>The president’s performance did nothing to allay fears about his age, though he got some rare traction on Jan. 6 and Trump’s legal problems. And the former president finally took a position on an abortion question.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">632a2a60-34fe-11ef-a424-0000a1acec38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 03:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'This is excruciating to watch': Follow along with 12 columnists as they discuss the debate</title>
      <description>‘This is starting to get really hard to watch’: 12 columnists discuss the debate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c216240-34f0-11ef-afeb-0000a1aceb92</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 01:45:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Joe Biden and former president Donald Trump to face off in the first 2024 presidential debate. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Tonight’s highly anticipated debate, which holds high stakes for both candidates, is being hosted by CNN in Atlanta.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72516a50-34e8-11ef-a2e9-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Uvalde school district police chief indicted in connection with botched response to 2022 mass shooting</title>
      <description>The Texas attack was one of the deadliest school shootings in U.S. history. The 18-year-old gunman who stormed the school in May 2022 killed 19 students and two teachers before officers eventually shot him. In January, the Justice Department issued a scathing 575-page report that criticized local police commanders and state law enforcement for their actions that day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a9405a0-34e2-11ef-8427-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:08:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Lakers select Bronny James in second round of NBA draft, setting him up to be teammates with his father, LeBron</title>
      <description>The 19-year-old James was drafted Thursday despite a middling freshman season at Southern Cal, where he played after suffering cardiac arrest last summer. LeBron James can become a free agent this offseason, but the 39-year-old Lakers star has long expressed a desire to play with Bronny as the NBA's first father-son duo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54005860-34d2-11ef-b496-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 22:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: I’m ‘poopless’ after years of regularity. What are my options? Dr. Trisha Pasricha is taking your poop questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: I’m ‘poopless’ after years of regularity. What are my options? Dr. Trisha Pasricha is taking your poop questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd813861-34ab-11ef-b769-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 17:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Can this sibling salvage a brother’s relationship with their mom?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Can this sibling salvage a brother’s relationship with their mom?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe7559d0-34a0-11ef-8d8e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 21 questions will define the next 4 years. Do Trump and Biden have answers?</title>
      <description>We asked 21 Post Opinions columnists to pose one policy question that will define the next four years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">702a9252-349e-11ef-b15a-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court temporarily protects access to emergency abortions in Idaho, despite the state’s ban</title>
      <description>The Biden administration argued that Idaho’s strict abortion ban conflicts with federal law requiring hospitals to provide emergency medical care, including abortion, for non-fatal but threatening health conditions such as organ failure or loss of fertility. The court's ruling was accidentally posted on its website a day early but was not official until it was announced Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b7b94f1-3492-11ef-8606-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits SEC’s use of in-house tribunals, curbing power of a key federal agency in a win for conservatives</title>
      <description>The justices were reviewing a lower court ruling that found the Securities and Exchange Commission’s in-house tribunals, overseen by administrative law judges, violated the right to a jury trial guaranteed by the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8dd8700-3490-11ef-9c46-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court blocks Purdue Pharma bankruptcy plan that gives billions to address U.S. opioid crisis but would bar future lawsuits</title>
      <description>The fight, involving the maker of Oxycontin, has bitterly divided victims of the opioid crisis. Some said the settlement is the best and only way to get urgently needed funds for recovery and treatment, while others say it is unacceptable that a family blamed for helping ignite the opioid epidemic could escape additional responsibility in civil courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2e15650-348f-11ef-b111-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court blocks major EPA air-quality initiative while appeals continue</title>
      <description>The ruling impacts regulations that were scheduled to take effect in 2026 and would improve public health by requiring states, power plants and factories to reduce smog-forming pollution that blows across state lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d48f82b0-348e-11ef-8b35-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 14:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A former soccer captain left out of the Olympics in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b02a6f0-3489-11ef-951c-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How tonight’s Biden-Trump debate will work, including microphone muting and no audience</title>
      <description>The president and Donald Trump both previously agreed to participate in the CNN debate in Atlanta, and a Sept. 10 debate broadcast by ABC News. They are bypassing a decades-old tradition of three fall meetings organized by the bipartisan Commission on Presidential Debates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea8f1791-347c-11ef-a3ca-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential debate. Supreme Court. Bolivia unrest. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Green hydrogen. NBA draft. Sunspot. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c284b50-3474-11ef-bf79-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Hawks select Zaccharie Risacher with No. 1 pick in NBA draft; Washington Wizards take Alex Sarr with No. 2 pick</title>
      <description>The draft continues with the rest of the first round Wednesday night and the second round Thursday afternoon.
The class lacks any players who are considered generational prospects such as 2023 No. 1 pick Victor Wembanyama.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef6c770-341b-11ef-8339-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 00:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some people can’t stop worrying that everything that happens is good for Trump</title>
      <description>Most people recognize that getting convicted of felonies is bad. But try telling that to nervous anti-Trumpers who think the former president will benefit from each of his would-be catastrophes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fe2afe2-3407-11ef-a195-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soldiers breach Bolivian government palace in what officials call a coup attempt</title>
      <description>Videos showed a recently fired Bolivian Army general, Juan Jose Zuñiga, entering the Palacio Quemado government palace on Wednesday afternoon as Bolivian President Luis Arce ordered him to withdraw troops. “We denounce to the international community that in Bolivia there is a coup d’etat against our democratically elected government,” Vice President David Choquehuanca wrote on X.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2fb0240-3400-11ef-a195-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where 4.1 million immigrants in the U.S. came from and where they live now</title>
      <description>The immigration debate in the United States generally revolves around illegal crossings at the U.S.-Mexico border, but those numbers don’t indicate what happens to these and other migrants who stay in the country. A Washington Post analysis of U.S. immigration court records from the past decade reveals a population that has fanned out into every state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c83a8a0-33ee-11ef-b1ba-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 19:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court opinion posted prematurely shows the justices would allow emergency abortions in Idaho despite state’s strict ban</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court would allow emergency abortion care to prevent infertility, organ failure or other non-fatal health conditions, despite the state’s restrictions on the procedure, according to Bloomberg Law, which viewed a copy of a not-yet-released opinion that was briefly posted on the court’s website. It is extremely rare — perhaps unprecedented — for a ruling to be posted before the Supreme Court issues it. The opinion would be at least a temporary victory for the Biden administration, which has struggled to protect abortion access since the high court overturned Roe v. Wade two years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db678790-33e4-11ef-a5e9-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leads in 5 of 7 battleground states most likely to determine the election, according to The Post’s polling averages</title>
      <description>The Washington Post’s presidential polling averages, which will update daily, gather the best available national and state-level polling data and factor in how residents of each state voted in the past two presidential elections to calculate whom voters currently favor in the presidential race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0446a670-33de-11ef-8338-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 17:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: I’ve cooked with a gas range all my life. How can I replicate it with electric? We’re taking your questions.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: I’ve cooked with a gas range all my life. How can I replicate it with electric? We’re taking your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f87a5020-33d9-11ef-9182-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom badgers with loaded questions when she wants to make a point</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom badgers with loaded questions when she wants to make a point</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cee9711-33d5-11ef-9d30-0000a1ace5b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soccer star Alex Morgan left off the U.S. Olympic roster, a decision that comes amid a generational shift for the women’s program</title>
      <description>Morgan, who will turn 35 in July, was co-captain of the 2023 World Cup squad in New Zealand and Australia. She has long been considered a centerpiece of the U.S. women’s soccer team and is one of the program's greatest scorers, but her production has fallen significantly in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05824370-33cd-11ef-a216-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects limits on White House social media contacts, a win for the Biden administration</title>
      <description>The justices said challengers did not have standing to try to sharply limit what White House officials and other federal employees can say to tech giants about posts on public health, elections, national security and other topics that the government deems problematic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b0d7b0-33c5-11ef-ac80-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Yes, chef!’ It's time for today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c835eb0-33c0-11ef-9464-0000a1acebc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 13:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary results. Trump allies. Veteran pardons. Evan Gershkovich. Kenya protests. Spending habits. NBA draft. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31610200-33ab-11ef-b5e1-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Gershkovich’s espionage trial begins in Russia behind closed doors. The U.S. says the reporter was ‘wrongfully detained.’</title>
      <description>It is the first such trial for an American journalist since the Cold War. Gershkovich was arrested on a reporting trip over a year ago in Russia and faces 20 years in prison if convicted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9345a460-3380-11ef-b233-000a1ace8291</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Jamaal Bowman (N.Y.) loses Democratic primary to George Latimer in race that highlighted divisions over Israel, AP projects</title>
      <description>The race between Bowman and Latimer, which also included accusations of racism against Latimer, was the most expensive House primary in history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bebdf10-335d-11ef-ba98-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Lauren Boebert wins Republican primary in new Colorado district, AP projects</title>
      <description>Boebert, who has survived several controversies, prevailed in a crowded GOP contest in the state’s 4th Congressional District. She decided to run in the new district after a close general election against a Democrat in the 3rd District in 2022. The new district is more friendly to Republicans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">806c33b0-335b-11ef-86f5-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange pleads guilty to U.S. espionage charge, ending years of legal deadlock. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Assange, 52, will head to his native Australia after making a deal with U.S. prosecutors and admitting to publishing military documents about the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He had spent nearly seven years at the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, evading extradition for a Swedish sex assault investigation over allegations he denied, then for five years fought a bid to send him to the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">205e5980-334c-11ef-afb2-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Shouldn’t husband come home early, now that his mom is okay?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Shouldn’t husband come home early, now that his mom is okay?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d50fb5b0-330e-11ef-acc9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Southern’s decision to burn off toxic chemicals in Ohio derailment was unnecessary, NTSB investigators say</title>
      <description>The railway and its contractors disregarded signs that the train’s derailed tank cars posed little risk of exploding, yet went ahead with the venting and burning of toxic vinyl chloride, investigators from the National Transportation Safety Board said. The burn-off sent a towering black cloud of toxic fumes into the air following the accident, spreading contamination over a vast area. In addition, Norfolk Southern failed to communicate adequately with incident commanders, a decision that was unjustified, investigators said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0526dd0-330b-11ef-879e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An impending ban of these in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14e900a0-32f7-11ef-99e0-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Criminal Court issues arrest warrants for two top Russian defense officials, alleging war crimes in Ukraine</title>
      <description>According to the indictment, former defense minister Sergei Shoigu and Valery Gerasimov, chief of the staff of the Russian Armed Forces, were responsible for directing attacks at civilian objects and “causing excessive incidental harm to civilians or damage to civilian objects … and the crime against humanity of inhumane acts.” The court, to which Russia is not a signatory, has no powers of enforcement and relies on the 124 nations that are signatories to arrest those indicted for war crimes or crimes against humanity if they visit their territories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2d3f620-32eb-11ef-abd3-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. surgeon general calls gun violence a public health crisis in landmark declaration</title>
      <description>The advisory from Vivek H. Murthy says the nation must act with urgency to address death and injury caused by firearms, saying inspiration can be drawn from earlier campaigns to combat tobacco use and motor vehicle accidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a07d610-32e4-11ef-8300-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Julian Assange. Transgender case. Gun violence. Israel ruling. Student loans. Stanley Cup. Bathroom Picassos. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">064445b0-32e2-11ef-a665-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s Supreme Court rules that ultra-Orthodox must do military service, throwing Netanyahu’s government into turmoil</title>
      <description>The ruling on the controversial issue of the haredim engaging in compulsory military service could lead to the ultra-Orthodox parties quitting the ruling coalition and bringing down Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3af72500-32cb-11ef-ac84-000a1ace0258</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
