<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 12:01:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Iran poll. NYC primary results. Trump’s tax bill. ‘Alligator Alcatraz.’ Heat wave. Microplastics. Bezos’s wedding. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80e62e50-51b3-11f0-9610-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo concedes to Mamdani in New York City’s Democratic mayoral primary</title>
      <description>“Tonight was not our night,” the former governor told supporters. He said of Mamdani: “Tonight is his night. He deserved it. He won.” Mamdani, a democratic socialist, is now poised for a major upset in the Democratic race after jumping out to a lead after the first round of ballots were tallied Tuesday. Final results in the ranked-choice voting primary are expected to come next week. The Democratic nominee is expected to begin as a favorite in the general election in a heavily blue city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e51394c0-5173-11f0-b9cb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 03:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani leads Andrew M. Cuomo on 1st round of counting in New York Democratic mayoral primary</title>
      <description>Mamdani, who would be New York’s first Muslim mayor, didn’t break the 50 percent mark in the first round of counting, the Associated Press reported. But it was still a good performance for the 33-year-old democratic socialist state assemblyman, a relative newcomer who was facing off with a former governor with copious campaign cash and prominent endorsements. Under the city’s ranked choice system, officials will now drop the candidate who finished last and continue counting votes until a candidate bests 50 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13fd4760-5168-11f0-9610-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 01:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We texted 1,000 Americans about Trump’s Iran strikes. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post flash poll finds the airstrikes remain unpopular, but Republican support surged after President Donald Trump ordered the strikes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39076840-5147-11f0-8f0d-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. bombs set back Iran's nuclear program by months, but did not destroy it, say people familiar with secret Pentagon assessment</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and top aides have claimed that U.S. airstrikes obliterated Iran's nuclear program, but people familiar with an initial report by the Defense Intelligence Agency say that core components of Tehran's enrichment program remain intact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47778f61-5140-11f0-a92e-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend’s sudden death brings acute sense of last moments</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend’s sudden death brings acute sense of last moments</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">898fe4f0-5114-11f0-ac1b-0000a1ace99b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When heat rises, here are 3 ways to protect your mind and body</title>
      <description>Persistent heat can cause chronic health problems. Here's how to avoid heatstroke, manage summer depression and, when temperatures are not dangerous, enjoy nature's healing benefits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">343c8010-5102-11f0-a208-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new label law in todayʼs On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872c10e0-50ff-11f0-a208-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump accuses Israel and Iran of violating ceasefire hours after its start</title>
      <description>As Israel and Iran traded accusations, President Donald Trump said the two countries need to “calm down. Ridiculous.” Trump had announced the ceasefire deal on Monday as an end to what he said should be called the “12-day war.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db7e3560-50f0-11f0-bb5a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaky ceasefire. Supreme Court. New York primary. Abortion rights. Food labels. Humidity. Space images. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5642e7c1-50ea-11f0-8a8f-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel agrees to Trump’s proposed ceasefire with Iran</title>
      <description>Israel said it achieved its military goals in Iran and thanked President Donald Trump and the U.S. “for their participation in removing the Iranian nuclear threat.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bb47290-50c7-11f0-af4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims Iran and Israel have agreed to a ceasefire and an imminent end to their war</title>
      <description>In his announcement on social media, President Donald Trump congratulated both countries, saying the conflict “could have gone on for years, and destroyed the entire Middle East.” There was no immediate corroborating announcement from either the Israeli or Iranian governments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96c2f40-5083-11f0-a4e9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu decided on Iran war last year, then sought to recruit Trump</title>
      <description>The Israeli prime minister issued a general order in the fall to prepare for a strike, current and former officials say. Israel also tried to sway the U.S. with intelligence about Iran’s nuclear plans, but American analysts did not conclude Iranian leaders had decided to build a bomb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e214530-507e-11f0-bb98-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court for now allows Trump to deport migrants to ‘third countries’</title>
      <description>The six conservative justices cleared the way for the Trump administration to deport citizens of other countries to a third nation, temporarily blocking a decision by a lower court judge who said migrants must have a “meaningful opportunity” to contest their removal. The case is one of several testing the Trump administration’s aggressive efforts to ramp up deportations, in this case to conflict-ridden South Sudan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91386d50-5077-11f0-96b9-0000a1acecd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See images of faraway galaxies and nearby asteroids from the new Vera Rubin telescope and world’s largest digital camera</title>
      <description>The observatory, named for a pioneering American astronomer, will soon embark on a 10-year “deep and wide” survey of the entire sky in the Southern Hemisphere, promising to see more galaxies than ever seen before. The telescope features a 3,200-megapixel camera. See some of its first images here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c183fe11-5064-11f0-a4d3-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 19:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions reported near U.S. military base in Qatar after Iran vows to retaliate for Trump’s strike on its nuclear sites</title>
      <description>The development coincided with a warning from the U.S. Embassy in Qatar for American citizens there to shelter in place. Qatar also closed its airspace and suspended flights as a “precautionary measure” while the Middle East braces for a potential expansion of the fighting between Israel and Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6064550-5052-11f0-8a5c-0000a1ace1fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:54:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend cuts ties after being called on hurtful remark</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend cuts ties after being called on hurtful remark</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcca9db0-504f-11f0-b7c4-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 16:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘You have 12 hours to escape’: An Israeli warning to a top Iranian general reveals a covert campaign to destabilize Tehran</title>
      <description>An audio recording of a June 13 phone call obtained by The Washington Post offers a window into the stealth campaign by Israeli intelligence to threaten and divide Iranian military and government officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2b617d0-504a-11f0-add2-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An extreme heat warning covers the D.C. area today and tomorrow, with near-record highs expected. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>Temperatures are expected to reach the upper 90s to low 100s both afternoons and perhaps on Wednesday. When high humidity is factored in, it will feel as hot as near 110, and the National Weather Service has warned of risks of heat-related illnesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecb011a0-5046-11f0-ab0f-0000a1ace053</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard flouted the rules. Now, it’s getting a hard lesson, Secretary of Homeland Security Kristi L. Noem writes in an op-ed.</title>
      <description>Hosting foreign students is a privilege that comes with obligations, Noem writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd751741-503d-11f0-90b8-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 14:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pay raise in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c06ec92-5036-11f0-9818-0000a1ace131</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What satellite images reveal about damage to Iran’s nuclear sites</title>
      <description>The images provide the first glimpses of the aftermath of U.S. strikes on three sites said to be central to Iran’s nuclear program, revealing severe damage at aboveground facilities as well as the entry points left by bombs that burrowed deep underground to target some of the program’s most protected operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a926000-5033-11f0-bd48-0000a1ace06c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 13:08:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran’s response. Trump’s decision. Mahmoud Khalil. Minnesota suspect. Brutal heat. AI and jobs. NBA Finals. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b8f2670-5021-11f0-a1c5-0000a1ace210</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma City Thunder wins NBA championship, defeating Indiana Pacers in seven games to cap impressive title run</title>
      <description>The Thunder, led by NBA MVP Shai Gilgeous-Alexander, won a league-best 68 games during the regular season and remained the most complete team during the playoffs. This is the franchise’s first championship since it relocated from Seattle in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa22f600-4fdc-11f0-939e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 02:51:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bees are in trouble in the U.S., and a key to unlocking their secrets could disappear</title>
      <description>Native bees have been declining for years, and commercial honeybee keepers reported one of their biggest colony losses this year. Now the Trump administration plans to defund the federal government’s premier bee research lab, in Laurel, Md., putting its future in peril.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7059b441-4fb4-11f0-843d-0000a1ace3b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 22:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump and his inner circle threw Iran and the rest of the world off guard before the U.S. struck key nuclear sites</title>
      <description>Within a small circle of White House and administration officials, it was clear that even when President Donald Trump said he might not decide for “two weeks," an attack on Iran’s nuclear facilities was imminent, and the ruse was already underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91845b90-4f94-11f0-8969-000a1ace4566</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Suns agree to trade Kevin Durant to Houston Rockets for package of players and draft picks</title>
      <description>Durant, a 15-time all-star, will play for the fifth NBA franchise of his 17-year career as a result of the trade, which had been rumored for months after the Suns’ failure to make the playoffs in a disappointing season and will become official next week. The two-time Finals MVP joins a young Rockets team that won 52 games and earned the second seed in the Western Conference in 2024-25 before falling to the Golden State Warriors in the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">307e6c20-4f8d-11f0-ae68-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 17:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">663ff5f1-4f6e-11f0-a62e-0000a1aceb10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 13:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian nuclear sites sustained ‘severe damage’ in U.S. strike, Pentagon says, asserting mission was not about regime change</title>
      <description>Gen. Dan Caine, chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, said in a news conference Sunday that the Fordow, Natanz and Isfahan nuclear facilities “sustained extremely severe damage” but that it was too early to tell the scale of destruction. “This mission was not, has not been about regime change” but rather about addressing the threats posed by Iran’s nuclear program, Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0aa0531-4f67-11f0-939e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 12:53:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Any retaliation from Iran would be “met with force far greater than what was witnessed tonight,” Trump says on social media</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s warning followed the United States’ sweeping strikes on Iranian nuclear facilities that marked a major escalation for his administration and tethers the U.S. directly to a conflict with no clear outcome or end in sight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e6a6040-4f18-11f0-9605-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 03:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Donald Trump addresses the nation on U.S. strikes on Iranian nuclear sites. Watch our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Trump announced the targeted strikes on three nuclear facilities in Iran on social media earlier Saturday evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6aa777c0-4f0b-11f0-a943-0000a1ace981</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 01:51:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. warplanes carry out strikes on three nuclear sites in Iran, Trump says, calling the attack ‘successful’</title>
      <description>The strikes targeted nuclear facilities at Fordow, Natanz, and Esfahan, President Donald Trump said on social media Saturday evening. “A full payload of BOMBS was dropped on the primary site, Fordow. All planes are safely on their way home,” he said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62474b50-4efc-11f0-bf9f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 00:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What do young, single MAGA women want? It’s complicated.</title>
      <description>What, exactly, is the conservative culture in the age of President Donald Trump’s second coming, and what does it think right-leaning women should want? These were the questions facing the roughly 3,000 young women — mostly ages 16 to 26 — at the Turning Point USA Young Women’s Leadership Summit in Texas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d9c22e0-4ee7-11f0-be81-0000a1ace6fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 21:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Multiple’ B-2 bombers head west over Pacific, U.S. official says, as Trump considers whether to join Israel in striking Iran</title>
      <description>The B-2, based at Whiteman Air Force Base in Missouri, is the only U.S. aircraft able to carry the 30,000-pound bunker-busting bombs thought to be capable of penetrating Iran’s underground Fordow nuclear enrichment facility. President Donald Trump said Thursday that he would decide whether to strike within two weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d61b8652-4ec4-11f0-82d3-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My brother’s getting married, and my ‘volatile’ mom is getting meaner.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My brother’s getting married, and my ‘volatile’ mom is getting meaner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b997d5d0-4eb8-11f0-b2cf-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A farmer put faith in Trump to protect him and the migrant he hired. Now he’s struggling to pay the bills.</title>
      <description>With grants canceled and billions of dollars in jeopardy, President Donald Trump’s cuts are devastating American farmers and plunging families into uncertainty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e6d4210-4eac-11f0-a0ae-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7568bec0-4ea3-11f0-986f-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 13:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservation group's $60 million deal ends years-long fight over proposed mine near North America’s largest blackwater swamp</title>
      <description>The nonprofit Conservation Fund said it would acquire thousands of acres of land outside Georgia's Okefenokee Swamp, one of the South's last truly wild places. The agreement halts a plan for a titanium mine that had been the subject of years of legal and political battles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64fbae10-4e19-11f0-a9fb-0000a1ace27c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of U.S. citizens have fled Iran amid Israeli strikes, State Department says</title>
      <description>In a private diplomatic bulletin obtained by The Washington Post, U.S. government officials acknowledge that many Americans are in harm’s way as President Donald Trump contemplates ordering military action against Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13a7620-4e13-11f0-a9a9-0000a1ace9d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 20:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of Columbia protester Mahmoud Khalil after months in ICE detention</title>
      <description>Khalil, a prominent leader in campus protests over the war in Gaza, was the first high-profile noncitizen activist to be detained by the Trump administration as part of a crackdown on alleged antisemitism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d0d2c60-4e02-11f0-a9e3-000a1ace18b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6a1e620-4dda-11f0-84c6-000a1acebf5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s decision. Dodger Stadium. Threats to lawmakers. Listeria outbreak. Plastic bag fees. Roman puzzle. ‘Jaws.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad2d7960-4dc5-11f0-a44c-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allowed to keep California National Guard in Los Angeles, appeals court rules</title>
      <description>A federal appeals court in San Francisco said that President Donald Trump appears to have lawfully deployed the California National Guard in Los Angeles without consulting the state’s Gov. Gavin Newsom (D), delivering a win for the president as he aims to use the military to police protests against his deportation efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77526d60-4d92-11f0-a28b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Minnesota shooting suspect was found: A driver spotted a man hiding and waved down an officer</title>
      <description>Interviews with witnesses, victims’ friends and people who know the suspect, along with court records, provide an account of the days leading up to the attacks and more than 40-plus hour search for the suspect that followed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">788c15c0-4d59-11f0-aa18-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have knee pain? Here’s what really works.</title>
      <description>Knee braces, hydrotherapy and exercise are some of the most effective ways to address arthritis-related knee pain and stiffness, a new study shows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25982f42-4d48-11f0-a66d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will make a decision on striking Iran within two weeks, sees opportunity for negotiations first, White House says</title>
      <description>Trump’s statement Thursday, delivered by White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt, extends the timeline for a decision from days to weeks. In what she said was a direct quote from Trump, the president cited “a substantial chance of negotiations that may or may not take place with Iran in the near future.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1459d980-4d3a-11f0-a75b-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch in effect until 9 p.m.</title>
      <description>Storms capable of producing damaging winds and dangerous lightning are expected to come through the Beltway area between about 4 and 7 p.m. A flood watch is also in effect because of the possibility of torrential rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0a412f0-4d37-11f0-b0ca-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grieving a beloved dog is hard. The guilt is making it worse.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grieving a beloved dog is hard. The guilt is making it worse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a35fb5a0-4d26-11f0-88fb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the American Dream still alive? Test your knowledge of generational mobility with this quiz.</title>
      <description>There is widespread skepticism that the American Dream is still possible. Is it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53ee84e1-4d23-11f0-959f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 280,000 eggs were stolen in America’s scramble over prices and profit</title>
      <description>The shipment from egg giant Cal-Maine was supposed to travel from Maryland to Florida. Then came a ransom note from the supposed trucker: “You need to zelle or wire $7500 if you want your eggs.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">209c5490-4d1a-11f0-8112-000a1ace08bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
