<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:03:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels blindsided after overhearing husband’s therapy session</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels blindsided after overhearing husband’s therapy session</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c5a5970-2743-11ef-8268-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A wild upset in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9faff0-272d-11ef-942f-0000a1ace969</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel’s hostage rescue: Top-secret planning and a deadly ‘wall of fire’</title>
      <description>The military operation on Saturday that freed four Israeli hostages and killed more than 270 Palestinians, according to the Gaza Health Ministry, was one of the most dramatic and deadly episodes of Israel’s war against Hamas. This account is based on more than a dozen interviews with former and current Israeli military officials, family members of hostages and Palestinian eyewitnesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06179750-2724-11ef-9ab4-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil in Israel. European elections. Tax cuts. Tornadoes. At-home tests. Microplastics. D-Day marriage. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9848a210-2718-11ef-881b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home insurance was once a ‘must.’ Now more homeowners are going without.</title>
      <description>Experts say the trend in forgoing home insurance is driven by the growing impact of climate change — which has forced insurers to make larger and larger payouts — and skyrocketing housing prices. As the cost of insurance rises, more Americans have decided to expose themselves to risk rather than pay for it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85720541-26ab-11ef-953a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far right projected to make big gains in European Parliament; pending loss prompts France’s Macron to call legislative elections</title>
      <description>Early forecasts in the European Parliament elections show voters punishing ruling centrists and boosting nationalist parties that have made populist economic appeals and taken hard-right positions on immigration. After polls showed the far-right National Rally trouncing French President Emmanuel Macron’s centrist coalition, he dissolved the national parliament and set the first round of elections for June 30.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">371ab8b2-2697-11ef-8ec2-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions in taxpayer dollars are going to religious schools via vouchers as the separation between church and state erodes</title>
      <description>School vouchers can be used at almost any private school, but the vast majority of the money is being directed to religious schools, according to a Washington Post examination. The voucher programs, popular with conservatives, are rapidly growing in GOP-run states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27878bd0-2692-11ef-b4b0-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli opposition leader Benny Gantz announces departure from war cabinet, upending Netanyahu government</title>
      <description>The move by Gantz, a former general, may not bring down the government, but it destabilizes the emergency coalition formed after Oct. 7 and increases the political pressure on Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to accept a Gaza cease-fire proposal that would bring home the hostages still held by Hamas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f2e63c0-2688-11ef-8d94-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carlos Alcaraz wins French Open, continuing his ascent to the top of men’s tennis</title>
      <description>Alcaraz won the U.S. Open in 2022 on hard court and Wimbledon in 2023 on grass, so he is the youngest player to win majors on all three surfaces.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5689a870-2686-11ef-882a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 17:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">591eefc1-267a-11ef-ba2d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 16:07:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Has tipping gone too far? Here’s a guide on when to tip, according to our personal finance columnist.</title>
      <description>Many Americans have tipping fatigue, with 1 in 3 adults calling the practice “out of control.” With so much confusion about who and how much to tip, read this guide from The Post's personal finance columnist, Michelle Singletary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7606640-266d-11ef-a4e4-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 14:38:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e12d9cf1-2665-11ef-a114-000a1aced142</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 13:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephen Strasburg comes to terms with the end of his baseball career and what might have been: ‘I felt like I — you know, I failed’</title>
      <description>The former Washington Nationals star, whose retirement became official in April, said he struggles with the feeling that his career “wasn’t good enough.” But as he leaves Washington and moves back to his native California, Strasburg also reflected on the sparkling memories from his Nationals tenure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb91a3c1-25e6-11ef-95ff-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 22:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli forces killed at least 210 people in central Gaza on the same day four hostages were rescued, hospital officials say</title>
      <description>Al-Aqsa Hospital spokesman Khalil al-Degran in Deir al-Balah said 94 bodies had been counted there. Al-Awda Hospital administrative director Marwan Abu Nasser said 116 were counted at his medical center in Nuseirat. It was not immediately clear whether all of them were killed in the hostage rescue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1996f600-25ca-11ef-9066-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 19:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump loyalist is pushing a ‘post-constitutional’ vision that would be a broad expansion of presidential powers</title>
      <description>Russ Vought, the former president’s budget director, is laying the groundwork for a philosophy he calls “radical constitutionalism.” Vought envisions Donald Trump seizing new control over the military, federal agencies and spending — an agenda he is poised to steer from an influential perch if Trump is reelected, possibly as his chief of staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17d31500-25c1-11ef-ae99-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 18:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My mom wants me to forgive my estranged sibling she’s always favored</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My mom wants me to forgive my estranged sibling she’s always favored</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3ba95c3-25b6-11ef-b68c-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 16:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlin Clark, the rising star at the center of women’s basketball discourse, expected to be left off U.S. Olympic team</title>
      <description>The Indiana Fever rookie set NCAA records at the University of Iowa and has brought unprecedented attention to women’s basketball, but she is not expected to be included on the 12-player roster for this summer’s Paris Games, two people with knowledge of the decision confirmed. Team USA will feature a remarkable collection of decorated WNBA stars and will be heavily favored to win its eighth consecutive gold medal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca623b60-25ad-11ef-b68c-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 15:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iga Swiatek wins third consecutive French Open title, becoming the third woman to accomplish that feat in the open era</title>
      <description>Swiatek, a 23-year-old from Poland who is the top-ranked player in the world, beat No. 12 seed Jasmine Paolini of Italy in Paris to win her fourth career championship at Roland Garros and her fifth Grand Slam title overall. Swiatek joins Monica Seles and Justine Henin as the only women since 1968 to win the French Open in three straight years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14ca3d70-25a3-11ef-937d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 14:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bccc990-259b-11ef-a7cc-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Israeli military says four hostages have been rescued alive following an operation in central Gaza</title>
      <description>The four hostages are “in good medical condition” after being rescued Saturday morning, the Israel Defense Forces said. Those rescued include Noa Argamani, who was seen on video being driven into Gaza on a motorcycle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">783741a0-2585-11ef-9d9a-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 10:54:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panic over trans sports inclusion is forcing us to choose between extremes, columnist Jerry Brewer writes</title>
      <description>In the fight over transgender participation in U.S. sports, the right to play is simply an opening act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13a75b00-2524-11ef-a861-0000a1ace423</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 23:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A catastrophic earthquake and tsunami will one day hit the Pacific Northwest as tectonic plates slip</title>
      <description>Scientists have mapped one of the most hazardous spots on the globe in unprecedented detail: a 600-mile geologic boundary just off the coast. Along this fraught stretch, mapped in a study published Friday in the journal Science Advances, two pieces of the Earth’s crust slide against each other, building up stresses capable of unleashing a 9.0-magnitude earthquake and generating a tsunami, with waves as high as 40 feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63f1b2e0-2515-11ef-b21c-0000a1ace025</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 21:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Mother-in-law ‘bawled violently’ after finding out we don’t want kids. Do we sell the house she helped us buy?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Mother-in-law ‘bawled violently’ after finding out we don’t want kids. Do we sell the house she helped us buy?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ca079ad-24ec-11ef-9af8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court Justice Clarence Thomas acknowledges two 2019 trips paid for by Harlan Crow, adding them to annual disclosure forms</title>
      <description>Thomas acknowledged that the Texas billionaire who is his longtime benefactor paid for his 2019 visits to a resort in Bali and the private Bohemian Grove club in California. On their annual disclosure forms, Justices Brett M. Kavanaugh, Neil M. Gorsuch and Ketanji Brown Jackson reported lucrative book deals, and  Jackson reported concert tickets from Beyoncé. The justices' off-the-bench activities have been scrutinized and criticized in the past year following reports by ProPublica and other media outlets that Thomas failed to disclose years of luxury vacations and private jet travel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96174f12-24e7-11ef-b230-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 16:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz,</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ed8ae10-24d2-11ef-a0c9-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 13:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added a strong 272,000 jobs in May, but the unemployment rate edged up to 4 percent.</title>
      <description>The labor market continued to churn out jobs at a decent pace in May, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, even as higher interest rates weigh on the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aae5ef0-24ca-11ef-a837-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 12:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump campaign. Steve Bannon. Heat index. Rare cancers. Xylitol risk. Pat Sajak. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">176d4272-24bd-11ef-b3f1-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wendell Felder, ANC chair and former Ward 7 Democrats chair, projected to win Democratic primary for D.C. Council Ward 7 seat</title>
      <description>The race was the only open council contest on the ballot. The winner is likely to succeed Council member and former D.C. Mayor Vincent C. Gray (D), who is not running for reelection amid health issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b55e8540-2457-11ef-b2ef-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Unusual’ cancers have emerged since the pandemic. Doctors are asking whether covid is to blame.</title>
      <description>As some early national reports and large cancer institutions have confirmed an uptick in aggressive, late-stage cancers, there’s debate among doctors and public health experts about the cause. While some physicians say it is the consequence of disruptions to health-care services that began in 2020, others suspect a link to covid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">212c26e0-2450-11ef-ae37-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Clooney called White House to defend his wife’s work on ICC arrest warrants against Israeli leaders after Biden’s criticism</title>
      <description>The Academy Award-winning actor called one of President Biden’s top aides last month to complain about the president’s criticism of the International Criminal Court’s action against Israeli leaders — a case his wife, Amal Clooney, worked on, according to three people familiar with the conversation. His concerns spread throughout Biden’s orbit, leaving some officials to worry that the high-profile actor would withdraw from participating in a marquee fundraiser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">473327e0-243b-11ef-9424-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 19:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. area day after tornado outbreak</title>
      <description>Scattered storms could become severe, producing heavy rain, lightning and some damaging wind gusts through around sunset. However, a repeat of Wednesday’s tornado outbreak is highly unlikely.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a5f0950-2435-11ef-bccc-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 18:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Stephen K. Bannon, former Trump adviser, to report to prison by July 1 for contempt of Congress</title>
      <description>Bannon was sentenced to four months for refusing to provide documents or testimony to a House committee probing the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol. His sentence had been put on hold while he appealed his case, but a three-judge panel rejected his challenge last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66dcc5c0-2421-11ef-807f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 16:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse no-shows promised support for sick stay-at-home parent</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse no-shows promised support for sick stay-at-home parent</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">438bd0f1-241e-11ef-80d8-0000a1aced0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 16:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s how the unusual tornado outbreak in Maryland happened</title>
      <description>The swarm of tornadoes Wednesday in Maryland — among the most significant in years — took forecasters by surprise. Here’s why the tornadoes formed and how the ingredients came together.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c1e5270-241c-11ef-ae64-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 15:49:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris wants an Olympics without air conditioning. So visiting nations are getting their own.</title>
      <description>Organizers planned a 2024 Paris Olympics that would be more climate friendly and less reliant on AC. But some wealthy nations — uneasy about an unconventional cooling system in dormitories amid what could be the hottest year on record — are obtaining AC units to keep athletes cool, adding to the energy intensity of the games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c193cba0-2410-11ef-8985-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 14:26:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A shake-up in this country in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa0b2f30-2408-11ef-bd6f-0000a1ace521</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Central Bank cuts interest rates, after successfully bringing down inflation and ahead of the Federal Reserve</title>
      <description>The ECB, setting monetary policy for Europe, became the first major central bank to lower borrowing costs, cutting its main policy rate by one-quarter of a percentage point. The Fed is not expected to cut rates for months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c2da570-2400-11ef-882b-0000a1ace079</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 12:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump trial delay. Contraception vote. D-Day. Extreme heat. Spider invasion. Starliner. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea2b8340-23f3-11ef-bea9-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Particularly dangerous situation’ warning for confirmed tornado in Montgomery County</title>
      <description>Authorities advised people in the path of the storm to seek immediate shelter, and that there was a confirmed tornado near Poolesville and headed east.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97feeb60-2395-11ef-8bb9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 23:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Justice Alito’s account of the upside-down flag at his home doesn’t fully add up: A look at the major discrepancies</title>
      <description>Supreme Court Justice Samuel A. Alito Jr. has said that it was his wife who flew the banners, not him, and that she flew one of them after a neighborhood dispute. But his successive explanations have raised additional questions and, in some cases, conflicted with known facts, police records and accounts of neighbors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b1f5bd0-2388-11ef-aa50-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 22:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia appeals court pauses lower-court proceedings in Trump election case</title>
      <description>The order means the case against the former president and eight of his co-defendants, accusing them of a criminal conspiracy to overturn his defeat in the state, will almost certainly not be scheduled for trial before the fall election or even the new year. The appeals court is reviewing a request from the defendants to disqualify Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b55531-237e-11ef-9ca4-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 20:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birth control access could be threatened as conservatives mischaracterize IUDs and emergency contraception as causing abortions</title>
      <description>Since the Supreme Court overturned the right to abortion two years ago, far-right conservatives have been trying to curtail birth-control access by sowing misinformation about how various methods work to prevent pregnancy, even as Republican leaders scramble to reassure voters they have no intention of restricting the right to contraception, which polls show the vast majority of Americans favor.

Democrats are seeking to capitalize on the moment, with the Senate scheduled to hold a vote Wednesday on the federal right to contraception.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29302410-2363-11ef-a74c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 17:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: The garden’s overrun with basil. What are some really good recipes using it? Our food writers are taking your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: The garden’s overrun with basil. What are some really good recipes using it? Our food writers are taking your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9654f8a0-2358-11ef-89d1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth’s record heat streak has now lasted an entire year, pushing the planet closer to a dangerous climate threshold</title>
      <description>Scientists announced that it was the hottest May on record, marking an entire year of uninterrupted record warmth. It is now highly likely that there will be a year in which temperatures exceed the global target of limiting global warming to 1.5 degrees Celsius (2.7 degrees Fahrenheit) by 2028, the World Meteorological Organization said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b11abc0-2357-11ef-a579-0000a1aceb57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Ex offered son a loan — with strings that could trip up the family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Ex offered son a loan — with strings that could trip up the family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d480ca90-2354-11ef-8dfa-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing’s Starliner has entered orbit. Its first successful launch with astronauts on board came after years of setbacks.</title>
      <description>After multiple delays, the Atlas V rocket carrying Sunita “Suni” Williams and Barry “Butch” Wilmore entered orbit for an expected eight-day mission to the International Space Station.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eac0300-2350-11ef-89d1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 15:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing is making a third attempt to send Starliner into space for its first flight with astronauts aboard. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>If successful, the mission would mark the first time Boeing’s Starliner spacecraft has flown people, a key milestone for the company and for NASA, which is relying on the commercial sector to ferry its astronauts to space.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6325de0-2349-11ef-b643-000a1acefb8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youngkin says he’ll end Virginia’s participation in standards that zero-emission vehicles make up all new auto sales by 2035</title>
      <description>The standards were set by California and adopted by multiple other states. This marks at least the second time Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) has circumvented environmental standards passed by Democratic majorities in the Virginia legislature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ae2e352-2346-11ef-84c0-0000a1ace503</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 14:16:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This popular, mysterious soda is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13dba10-233f-11ef-a103-0000a1acecf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India’s election. Primary results. MDMA. Birth control. AI warning. Sinking city. Dr Pepper. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1321c21-232a-11ef-a5e6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
