<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:09:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Get the latest updates on tonight’s winners, surprises and snubs as ‘Oppenheimer’ vies for a record number of awards</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic-age biopic is poised to have a big night, while Lily Gladstone looks to make history as the first Native American to win an Oscar in an acting category. Join us for live coverage and analysis of the night’s biggest moments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df50260-df31-11ee-b49f-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign insider recounts failed hunt for 2020 fraud in new book</title>
      <description>Ken Block, an expert hired by the campaign, writes that he shot down false claim after false claim in an election that was not stolen. Emails from 2020 reviewed by The Washington Post show one tip was routed to the campaign via the manager of one of Donald Trump's golf clubs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068fc650-df1f-11ee-9c5c-0000a1ace007</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars could make history this year. Here’s everything you need to know about the frontrunners, how to watch and more.</title>
      <description>Will “Oppenheimer” dominate? What are the potential upsets and historic firsts? Is Ryan Gosling really performing as Ken? (Yes!) Here’s your complete rundown before the Academy Awards begin at 7 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ca04540-deff-11ee-93b4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">642e0511-def7-11ee-b59a-0000a1acebd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you tell which of these actors in Oscar-nominated films are wearing wigs? (It’s harder than it seems.)</title>
      <description>A good wig takes tons of time, money and a veritable encyclopedia of styling knowledge. These efforts will be recognized at tonight’s Academy Awards. Here’s the step-by-step process, plus a quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">104c9b30-deef-11ee-98f4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750dfc10-dee2-11ee-8455-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida has been ground zero for culture wars. But the pushback is growing as voters tire of DeSantis’s ‘war on woke.’</title>
      <description>Conservative lawmakers in the Sunshine State rejected a host of new culture war proposals, a change from past years when bills backed by Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) sailed through.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">995276e0-de5c-11ee-9f32-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 21:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Conservative parents don’t approve of Indian boyfriend I met online</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Conservative parents don’t approve of Indian boyfriend I met online</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8fa8490-de36-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How worried should we be about the Drunk Elephant tweens?</title>
      <description>Their much-publicized, pricey new skin-care hobby could be a symptom of our age-obsessed culture — or could be harnessed for good.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">615e83b0-de2e-11ee-97d7-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 16:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9168de00-de21-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The federal government won’t shut down this weekend. The Senate has passed spending legislation and will send it to Biden to sign.</title>
      <description>The measure had already passed the House. Another deadline awaits in two weeks for about 70 percent of federal agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11aeb600-ddac-11ee-ad82-0000a1ace6cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America is running out of electricity as tech companies sap the country’s aging power grid</title>
      <description>Vast swaths of the United States are at risk of running short of power as data centers and factories proliferate around the country. The growth is driven in part by the innovations in artificial intelligence and threatens to stifle the transition to cleaner energy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">426e9e51-dd97-11ee-a2a6-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novo Nordisk's blockbuster weight loss drug, Wegovy, may be prescribed to reduce heart attack risk in overweight people, FDA says</title>
      <description>The drug has the same active ingredient as the company’s diabetes drug, Ozempic. The approval is based on research showing that Wegovy reduced the risk of major cardiovascular events such as heart attacks and strokes by 20 percent, compared with a placebo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24327e81-dd82-11ee-b6c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Honduran president Juan Orlando Hernández is convicted of helping send tons of cocaine to the U.S.</title>
      <description>Hernández was treated as a U.S. government ally but secretly “paved a cocaine superhighway to the United States,” prosecutors said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9ccd5f0-dd7d-11ee-b39a-0000a1aced0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Katie Britt rebutted Biden’s speech from her kitchen. A lot of moms can’t see themselves in her place, our columnist writes.</title>
      <description>The Alabama Republican’s State of the Union rebuttal seemed aimed at suburban women whom Republicans have done little to win back, Monica Hesse argues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e5a31b0-dd75-11ee-bc91-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I fall out of love with a married man?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I fall out of love with a married man?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d2c7590-dd73-11ee-b81e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump posts $91M bond while appealing E. Jean Carroll defamation judgment. A judge had denied his request to delay payment.</title>
      <description>The former president and likely 2024 Republican nominee had until Monday to guarantee payment of an $83.3 million judgment to Carroll, a writer and columnist whom he defamed after she accused him of long-ago sexual assault. Trump also filed a notice saying he will appeal the judgment against him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee8c1b70-dd6c-11ee-a1d0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican National Committee installs Trump's chosen leaders, including his daughter-in-law, in merger with campaign</title>
      <description>Donald Trump, now the expected Republican nominee, picked Michael Whatley and Lara Trump to lead the party's central committee, which is facing a dramatic fundraising shortfall.

Whatley replaces outgoing RNC Chair Ronna McDaniel, who also was chosen by Trump but whose relationship with the former president and his allies had become strained in recent months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65066b30-dd6c-11ee-9773-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentagon’s long-awaited report on UFOs finds ‘no evidence’ of alien visits or hidden spacecraft. But will people believe it?</title>
      <description>Investigators from the Defense Department’s All-domain Anomaly Resolution Office debunked claims of secret military programs on extraterrestrial technology as “inaccurate,” and blamed a “consistent theme in popular culture” for the persistent suspicion of a government coverup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c537fb1-dd63-11ee-997b-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 15:47:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c03d680-dd58-11ee-af7b-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 14:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added 275,000 jobs in February, signaling continued strength in the labor market</title>
      <description>The labor market continues to add jobs at a healthy pace, even as interest rates remain high, according to the latest data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ecaca10-dd50-11ee-8f03-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the Union. Gaza port. Trump finances. NATO. MH370 mystery. Mike Tyson. The Oscars. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67857190-dd43-11ee-87b3-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 12:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden draws sharp contrasts with Trump in fiery State of the Union address</title>
      <description>In a speech befitting the political moment of an election year, President Biden loaded up on criticism of former president Donald Trump — without saying his name once. He dinged the Republican presidential front-runner for his coziness with Russia, the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol and Trump’s failure in his “duty to care” during the pandemic.
He also enthusiastically mixed it up several times with Republicans in the chamber, and at times he seemed to encourage the call-and-response with them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28bdd040-dd04-11ee-aef0-0000a1aced8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 04:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will this be more than a Biden campaign speech? Follow along with Post columnists as they watch the State of the Union.</title>
      <description>Follow our columnists as they discuss the State of the Union</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97779980-dcf5-11ee-8c45-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 02:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All eyes are on Biden’s last State of the Union before the election as he speaks on Gaza, the economy and reproductive rights</title>
      <description>The annual address to a joint session of Congress — which comes as Joe Biden’s 2024 rematch with Donald Trump kicks into high gear — also serves as a chance for the Democratic incumbent to reshape negative public perceptions of him and his presidency. Watch the speech live and follow along as Washington Post reporters offer commentary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f13d2460-dced-11ee-aef0-0000a1aced8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 01:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three men charged with murder in case of Virginia couple who were likely thrown off yacht in Caribbean</title>
      <description>The men, who had escaped custody in Grenada, probably threw Ralph Hendry and Kathleen Brandel off their boat on Feb. 18 as the 48-foot vessel sailed from Grenada to the neighboring island of St. Vincent, where they were recaptured, authorities have said previously.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42e305b0-dcc0-11ee-af6d-000a1ace5309</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 20:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is failing at the most important task of his presidency, Perry Bacon Jr. writes</title>
      <description>Even Democrats who are skeptical of President Biden’s chances of winning this November usually say he is doing a fantastic job, pointing to the strong economy and the long list of legislation that has passed in his tenure. The implication is that voters aren’t appreciating Biden as they should, perhaps because of his age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1003b840-dcb3-11ee-bbff-0000a1aced28</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronny Jackson, the former White House physician and Trump ally, was demoted by the Navy after a damaging misconduct investigation</title>
      <description>Jackson, who was the personal physician to Barack Obama and Donald Trump before becoming a GOP congressman, regularly refers to himself as a retired rear admiral. But in July 2022, the Navy reduced his retired rank to captain after a probe found he had berated subordinates, made inappropriate and sexual comments, and broke other rules on the job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf0605d0-dcaf-11ee-afe9-0000a1ace335</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 18:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. will build a temporary port on Gaza coastline for delivery of aid, Biden to announce in State of the Union</title>
      <description>With the Gaza Strip on the brink of famine, the United States will supply aid by ship to supplement deliveries by land and air, senior U.S. officials say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b405a10-dca9-11ee-b382-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to navigate and arrange end-of-life care for mom?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to navigate and arrange end-of-life care for mom?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ca96e91-dca4-11ee-96ce-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 17:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sweden joins NATO, completing a historic expansion of the alliance spurred by Russia’s war in Ukraine</title>
      <description>At a meeting in Washington, Swedish Prime Minister Ulf Kristersson deposited the final paperwork with U.S. Secretary of State Antony Blinken, the last step needed for the former militarily nonaligned nation to become NATO’s 32nd member. Sweden’s neighbor Finland joined last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31590620-dca0-11ee-8a49-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xcel Energy says its power equipment may have sparked the largest fire in Texas history</title>
      <description>Xcel Energy is a major electric company with operations in Texas and other states. The company, however, has rejected allegations it was negligent in maintaining its equipment, as a lawsuit claims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94a8df30-dc9f-11ee-a2ff-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 16:27:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A swoon-worthy shirt goes on sale in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6232e241-dc8f-11ee-ad45-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 14:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the Union. Alabama IVF. Affirmative action. ‘Rust’ shooting. Tainted cinnamon. Exercise benefits. Mammoths. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39b925a0-dc7a-11ee-820b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alabama’s governor signs bill to protect IVF after state Supreme Court ruling on frozen embryos</title>
      <description>State lawmakers passed the bill Wednesday to protect providers and patients doing in vitro fertilization from legal liability if embryos they create are damaged or destroyed. Gov. Kay Ivey (R) signed the bill into law less than three weeks after an Alabama Supreme Court ruling stated that frozen embryos are people and anyone who destroys them could be held liable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8b29130-dc36-11ee-8943-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 03:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia lawmakers to remove proposed sports arena from state budget, blocking best chance to bring Caps and Wizards to Alexandria</title>
      <description>For the plan to advance, Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) would have to send down a budget amendment or standalone bill resurrecting the project, call a special session or offer the measure up again during lawmakers’ one-day session in April. But leaving the arena out of the state budget makes it harder for Youngkin to win passage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba1e680-dc2a-11ee-98e3-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 02:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Rust’ armorer found guilty of involuntary manslaughter in fatal shooting of cinematographer on film set</title>
      <description>Hannah Gutierrez-Reed was accused of failing to ensure gun safety on the set of the low-budget Western movie in 2021. She was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter and not guilty of evidence-tampering charges, according to the Associated Press.
Alec Baldwin was rehearsing with a revolver on the set when the gun went off with live ammunition, killing cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and wounding director Joel Souza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8783ea10-dc14-11ee-8b71-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Founder of Casa Ruby, a D.C.-based nonprofit that supported homeless LGBTQ youth, charged with fraud and money laundering</title>
      <description>Ruby Corado is accused of diverting at least $150,000 of $1.3 million in money from Paycheck Protection and the Economic Injury Disaster Loan programs intended for Casa Ruby to bank accounts in El Salvador and hiding it from the IRS. Casa Ruby shuttered in July 2022 after it stopped paying employees and rent on properties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">355ea161-dc07-11ee-adf1-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 22:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who will Nikki Haley’s supporters vote for now that she has dropped out? We asked them.</title>
      <description>Haley, a former U.N. ambassador and governor of South Carolina, suspended her presidential campaign Wednesday.
The Washington Post spoke to nearly 40 Haley voters in four Super Tuesday states about how they would vote in a Donald Trump-Joe Biden rematch, a prospect that often elicited groans or hands thrown up in disappointment. Here’s what they said about their plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5341640-dc04-11ee-8a28-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A bill to avert a partial government shutdown heads to the Senate after the House approves funding through September</title>
      <description>The legislation wraps six appropriations bills into one measure totaling $459 billion. Congress must act before midnight Saturday to keep agencies open.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86f412b0-dbff-11ee-b98b-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 21:21:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dean Phillips ends long-shot bid for president, leaving Biden free of challengers</title>
      <description>The Minnesota congressman was Biden's last remaining notable Democratic primary challenger. He gained little traction in key early contests after entering the race with a pitch meant to convince Democrats that he would perform better than Biden in a race against former Republican president Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4b0f4a1-dbe5-11ee-baf8-0000a1aceb2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 18:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grandparent instructed to stop bringing bulky gifts for grandchild</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grandparent instructed to stop bringing bulky gifts for grandchild</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6382dff0-dbe1-11ee-af4a-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Houthi missile strike kills two civilians on commercial ship, U.S. officials say, marking first known deaths in militants’ campaign</title>
      <description>The missile struck the MV True Confidence at about 11:30 a.m. in Yemen, causing significant damage to the cargo ship. At least six other mariners were injured, and the crew has abandoned ship, one U.S. official said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0624a980-dbdf-11ee-af4a-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies must reveal key details about their role in causing climate change under a rule the SEC just approved</title>
      <description>The rule would also force public corporations to detail the threat that climate change poses to their operations. Industry groups are likely to challenge the policy in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4344c5e0-dbdd-11ee-b8e9-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why do your brownies get greasy? Our food writers are answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Food writers Aaron Hutcherson and Becky Krystal answer your cooking conundrums in their weekly chat — starting now. Today’s topics include perfecting brownies and shopping for spring produce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51f81e41-dbdb-11ee-b59e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 17:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. has quietly approved more than 100 weapons packages for Israel, amounting to thousands of munitions, since Gaza war began</title>
      <description>The triple-digit figure, which has not been previously reported, includes precision-guided munitions, small-diameter bombs, bunker busters, small arms and other lethal aid. The weapons transfers were processed without any public debate because each fell under a specific dollar amount that requires the executive branch to notify Congress, according to U.S. officials and lawmakers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10187f00-dbd2-11ee-9f3e-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 15:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McConnell endorses Trump after years of acrimony, telling The Post that the former president ‘has earned the requisite support’</title>
      <description>The Senate minority leader’s move could matter to major GOP donors, some of Donald Trump’s critics in the party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78396f80-dbce-11ee-af4a-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 15:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian missile strike hits near Ukrainian president’s motorcade in Odessa during visit by Greek prime minister</title>
      <description>Odessa in particular has been battered recently by missile strikes and Volodymyr Zelensky took the opportunity to call for more international support for Ukraine’s air defenses. He told the state broadcaster that there had been casualties but did not give details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f87bbb0-dbce-11ee-bd59-0000a1ace83d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 15:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules that federal agency created to help minority-owned businesses must serve all races, another blow for affirmative action</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Texas has ruled that the Minority Business Development Agency’s presumption of racial disadvantage is unconstitutional, siding with a group of White plaintiffs who argued that the agency discriminated against them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e0106c0-dbca-11ee-baf8-0000a1aceb2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet runs wild with conspiracy theories in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a541bb20-dbc6-11ee-a6de-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
