<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple leaders purged at NIH, CDC and FDA as massive layoffs begin at U.S. health agencies</title>
      <description>Senior leaders at the National Institutes of Health, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, and Food and Drug Administration have been put on administrative leave and some were offered reassignment to remote locations at the Indian Health Service. Meanwhile, federal employees have begun receiving layoff notices as part of a massive “reduction in force” at the Department of Health and Human Services, led by newly confirmed leader Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2f7250-0f07-11f0-9fa4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulling rabbits out of hats in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1daa120-0efd-11f0-ac6d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special elections. Trump’s tariffs. Harvard funding. Abortion ruling. Murder trial. Storm forecast. Hooters. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76e16590-0ee8-11f0-b626-0000a1ace9bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The women’s Final Four is set. South Carolina, UCLA, Texas and Connecticut will meet in Tampa for the national title.</title>
      <description>Three No. 1 seeds and No. 2 seed Connecticut advanced to the national semifinals of the NCAA women's basketball tournament, which has been short on major upsets. South Carolina will face Texas and UCLA will meet Connecticut on Friday before the winners play for the national championship Sunday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4c98b50-0ea9-11f0-be66-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 03:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily blocks Trump administration from ending deportation protection for about 350,000 Venezuelans</title>
      <description>The order prevents the Department of Homeland Security from allowing temporary protected status for Venezuelan migrants to expire on April 7. The decision comes as President Donald Trump has ramped up his efforts to quickly arrest and deport Venezuelans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfaa3e90-0e85-11f0-a4e6-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 23:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fast-food drive-throughs most likely to mess up your order, according to our Department of Data</title>
      <description>For almost a quarter-century, secret shoppers have been dispatched to each of the top 10 fast-food outlets throughout the United States, focusing on the lunch and dinner hours. Here’s the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3ae5190-0e73-11f0-863f-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration targets billions in federal funding to Harvard, saying the university mishandled campus protests, antisemitism</title>
      <description>The Education and Health and Human Services departments, along with the U.S. General Services Administration, announced a review of billions in contracts and grants to Harvard and its affiliates, a move that follows dramatic cuts at Columbia University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60eea790-0e6e-11f0-a8e3-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Technician sports dramatic new look. Does it warrant a comment?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Technician sports dramatic new look. Does it warrant a comment?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb27c580-0e4a-11f0-b04e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA beef in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3510340-0e34-11f0-a4e6-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right French leader Marine Le Pen convicted of embezzlement and barred from running in 2027 election, French media report</title>
      <description>Le Pen, the guiding force of the anti-immigrant National Rally party, has been regarded as a leading contender in France’s next presidential election. She accused prosecutors of seeking her “political death” in bringing charges that her party embezzled nearly $5 million of E.U. funds. Le Pen is expected to appeal the verdict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43141ea0-0e2b-11f0-9376-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s third term remarks. Elon Musk. Quake damage. West Bank. Air pollution. Richard Chamberlain. Final Four. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a0e46b0-0e1f-11f0-b3b4-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The men’s Final Four is set. Florida, Duke, Houston and Auburn will meet in San Antonio for the national championship.</title>
      <description>All four No. 1 seeds advanced to the national semifinals of the NCAA men’s basketball tournament for the second time in history and the first since 2008.
Duke will face Houston and Florida will meet Auburn on Saturday before the winners play for the national title next Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62bfa701-0dbe-11f0-b9b6-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50586271-0d80-11f0-998a-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craft distillers are hit hard as tariffs mix with 1930s rules for alcohol, making it more difficult to expand in the U.S.</title>
      <description>Alcoholic drinks have become the subject of dueling tariff threats between the United States and its neighbors, especially Canada. But some craft distillers say they feel particularly battered because they had seen these other countries as better targets for growth than parts of the highly regulated and crowded U.S. market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6738360-0d73-11f0-a5e5-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men’s basketball coach Kevin Willard is leaving Maryland to take Villanova job after leading Terps to NCAA tournament’s Sweet 16</title>
      <description>Rumors that Willard would soon be departing intensified over the past couple of weeks, after the coach declined to sign a contract extension and aired concerns about the school’s financial commitment to its men’s basketball program.

In three seasons at Maryland, Willard led the Terrapins to two NCAA tournaments, including this year’s run to the Sweet 16, their first since 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40de1290-0d6c-11f0-b147-0000a1ace1cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f82f300-0d6b-11f0-8aeb-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Chamberlain dies at 90. The TV heartthrob was ‘king of the miniseries,’ including ‘Shogun’ and ‘The Thorn Birds.’</title>
      <description>The 1960s TV series “Dr. Kildare” drew millions of viewers and made Chamberlain a household name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ca0bbc0-0d5f-11f0-9a11-000a1ace2140</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 12:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Trump administration has downplayed the Signal chat scandal</title>
      <description>“Mistake.” “Glitch.” “Entirely permissible.” “Hoax.” See the varied and shifting responses President Donald Trump and his allies have offered as they have reacted to this security breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">178cd360-0ce3-11f0-94fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 21:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Pentagon strategy memo on China and homeland defense has Heritage Foundation fingerprints</title>
      <description>Internal guidance from Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth is reorienting the Pentagon to deter China’s seizure of Taiwan and focus the military on homeland defense. According to a Washington Post analysis, in some instances, the planning document is a nearly word-for-word facsimile of a report from the conservative think tank behind Project 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5e1a3e1-0cd4-11f0-92ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 19:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I want to rekindle my bond with my sister, but she remains distant</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I want to rekindle my bond with my sister, but she remains distant</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbcd9901-0cb6-11f0-8ccf-0000a1ace7d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What legendary French chef Jacques Pépin taught our food writer about omelets and life</title>
      <description>It’s impossible to calculate how many classic omelets the beloved 89-year-old chef has prepared since dedicating himself to the art and technique of the dish. “There’s no failure,” he said. You eat your mistakes and move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e26b6cb0-0caa-11f0-8c76-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33694e60-0ca2-11f0-80d8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 13:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: At least 1,000 dead, 2,700 injured in Myanmar earthquake, according to country’s military. An earlier alert had an incorrect link.</title>
      <description>The powerful 7.7-magnitude earthquake struck Myanmar on Friday, killing at least 1,000 people, according to the country’s military junta, with deadly tremors felt hundreds of miles away in Thailand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c5e900-0c66-11f0-a131-000a1ace66fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 06:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 1,000 dead, 2,700 injured in Myanmar earthquake, according to country’s military</title>
      <description>The powerful 7.7-magnitude earthquake struck Myanmar on Friday, killing at least 1,000 people, according to the country’s military junta, with deadly tremors felt hundreds of miles away in Thailand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eee76390-0c64-11f0-9ea6-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 06:13:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. pushes out Peter Marks, nation’s top vaccine regulator, two people with knowledge of the decision say</title>
      <description>Marks, an architect of the Operation Warp Speed program to develop coronavirus vaccines, was given the choice to resign or be fired from the Food and Drug Administration, according to two people with knowledge of the request. Marks warned in his resignation letter that confidence in science is being undermined across the country, pointing to a worsening measles outbreak in Texas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b31af450-0c3a-11f0-87c2-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 01:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House kills plan for Maryland to receive elite D.C. fighter jet squadron</title>
      <description>The effort to acquire the jets after Maryland lost its own flying mission became linked with D.C.’s RFK Stadium deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92a1d140-0c2f-11f0-869a-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 23:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge makes it more difficult for the Trump administration to deport people to a country where they are not a citizen</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Boston issued an emergency order blocking the Trump administration from deporting people to so-called third countries where they are not a citizen before giving them a chance to seek humanitarian protection in the United States. The decision follows threats from Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem this week that anyone in the United States illegally could be sent to one of El Salvador's sprawling prisons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e04e991-0c2e-11f0-94a3-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 23:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFPB dissolution halted for now by federal judge’s preliminary injunction that orders the reinstatement of dismissed employees</title>
      <description>A federal judge on Friday temporarily blocked the Trump administration from dismantling the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau, a victory to employees of the financial watchdog roiled by efforts to shut down their agency. U.S. District Judge Amy Berman Jackson’s preliminary injunction bars the administration from imposing a work stoppage on the agency’s staff or forcing them to take leave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5266e8b0-0c23-11f0-a11c-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 22:23:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appeals court allows Trump to remove members of independent government boards for now</title>
      <description>A three-judge panel sided against members of the National Labor Relations Board and the Merit Systems Protection Board. The court is still weighing whether President Donald Trump has authority to fire the board members, but it upheld their removal while it considers the case, which could land before the Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ac6ff30-0c12-11f0-a89b-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 20:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Atlantic’s Jeffrey Goldberg made noise with a Signal chat scoop</title>
      <description>The Trump administration tried to paint the veteran journalist as a liar, so he felt compelled to prove them wrong — and he had the receipts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e02f4eb0-0c02-11f0-b3b0-0000a1ace1f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to formally abolish USAID, an action Congress has not yet authorized</title>
      <description>A letter sent to employees of the U.S. Agency for International Development said that most positions would be eliminated in coming months through reduction-in-force actions. Some functions of the agency, which administers foreign aid, will be transferred to the State Department, the letter said. The move is expected to draw lawsuits if the administration acts without congressional approval.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">842fa590-0bfa-11f0-950f-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 17:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 144 dead in Myanmar in 7.7-magnitude earthquake, junta says</title>
      <description>The earthquake hit 10 miles from the country’s second-largest city and also injured at least 732 people, according to Myanmar’s military junta. Buildings as far away as Bangkok collapsed, leaving at least eight people dead and dozens trapped, according to officials in Thailand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b42a00-0bec-11f0-83ec-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 15:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s cherry trees have reached peak bloom. The moment arrives earlier than normal for the sixth straight year.</title>
      <description>The blossoms at the Tidal Basin should remain near peak through the weekend. Boosted by unusually mild temperatures, the buds sped through the bloom cycle at near record speed. Because of human-caused climate change, the average peak bloom date is now about a week earlier than a century ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2cf7f20-0be1-11f0-a9c2-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 14:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0afdf670-0bd9-11f0-a455-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Myanmar quake. Federal layoffs. Vance in Greenland. Tariff impacts. Drying soil. March Madness. Partial eclipse. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3c521d0-0bc3-11f0-bba8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump executive order targets Smithsonian, directs Vance to remove what he deems ‘improper' ideology from museums and National Zoo</title>
      <description>The institution, the official keeper of the American story, has operated independently as a public-private partnership created by an act of Congress in 1846. The order comes as the institution has been expanding over decades to include a wider, richer and more diverse telling of the nation’s history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">280c2560-0b71-11f0-a33d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 5 words have killed millions in grants and advanced Trump’s agenda</title>
      <description>An obscure regulation covering federal grants is being deployed by President Donald Trump’s appointees to terminate them unilaterally across the government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c54f1540-0b57-11f0-9296-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 22:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal White House document shows federal agencies preparing to cut 8 to 50 percent of staff</title>
      <description>The details are still in flux, but the document obtained by The Post indicates that the Trump administration's push to shrink the government could have far-reaching effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">557cdd50-0b49-11f0-a913-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 20:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House withdraws Republican Rep. Elise Stefanik’s Cabinet nomination to protect narrow House majority</title>
      <description>Sen. James E. Risch (R-Idaho), who chairs the Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, said the White House notified him that her nomination to be U.S. ambassador to the United Nations was withdrawn.

"I have asked Elise, as one of my biggest Allies, to remain in Congress to help me deliver Historic Tax Cuts, GREAT Jobs, Record Economic Growth, a Secure Border, Energy Dominance, Peace Through Strength, and much more," President Donald Trump said in a post on Truth Social.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0451e511-0b3a-11f0-9c32-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department proposes merging ATF with DEA, among other major changes</title>
      <description>A memo from the office of Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche suggested merging the Drug Enforcement Administration with the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives. It also proposed transferring INTERPOL Washington, a part of the Justice Department that coordinates with law enforcement agencies around the world, to the U.S. Marshals Service. Justice officials said the proposals are under discussion and no decisions have been made.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb9b2200-0b2f-11f0-9637-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 17:20:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First pitches can go terribly wrong, columnist Thomas Boswell writes. Here’s hoping his goes right on Opening Day.</title>
      <description>Boswell is throwing out the ceremonial first pitch at Nationals Opening Day today — and he doesn’t want to become the next 50 Cent. In December, Boswell was named the 2025 winner of the Baseball Writers’ Association of America’s Career Excellence Award. He will be recognized during July’s induction weekend at the Baseball Hall of Fame in Cooperstown, New York, and included in an exhibit alongside other writers and broadcasters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fda10bc6-0b29-11f0-853b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 16:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Adult daughter still feels ‘in the way’ for not having been a boy</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Adult daughter still feels ‘in the way’ for not having been a boy</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32d571f0-0b25-11f0-9176-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 16:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Opening Day! Take George Will’s baseball quiz to see if you hit a home run — or strike out.</title>
      <description>Don’t get booed, get busy identifying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a022c800-0b18-11f0-9e48-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 14:34:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. announces cut of 20,000 positions to the Health and Human Services Department’s workforce</title>
      <description>The department — which includes the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, Food and Drug Administration, National Institutes of Health and other agencies — will save $1.8 billion annually, HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said, by reducing staff from 82,000 to 62,000. Half of those employees took buyouts and early retirement, while 10,000 will lose their jobs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83c2a0e0-0b13-11f0-89b1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadway’s hottest ticket in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Play now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edbfcb71-0b0f-11f0-8e21-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 13:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Signal transcript. Social Security. Ghost guns. Detained student. Hot weather. Fake job seekers. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9995f9d0-0afa-11f0-bc9f-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security backs off plan to cut phone services for disabled</title>
      <description>The changes announced Wednesday mean that those seeking disability benefits will continue to be able to verify their identity by phone, as all Social Security beneficiaries have been able to do for years. But those seeking retirement or survivor's benefits will no longer be allowed to do so, and will instead need to verify their identity online or in person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bae9f250-0a9e-11f0-8590-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:02:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 25 percent new tariffs on imported cars, which will probably raise prices for buyers</title>
      <description>The taxes will apply to finished automobiles, but not to auto parts. More tariffs are set to be announced next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05b8cd80-0a89-11f0-9227-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court upholds a temporary block on deporting Venezuelans under the Alien Enemies Act</title>
      <description>A federal appeals panel has rejected the Trump administration’s efforts to overturn a lower-court order that bars officials from deporting migrants under the wartime Alien Enemies Act while litigation on the matter continues. Judge James E. Boaseberg’s restraining order triggered enormous pushback from President Donald Trump and his allies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">027c4450-0a82-11f0-b435-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:36:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: High school couple hopes to stay together at separate colleges</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: High school couple hopes to stay together at separate colleges</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33eeea90-0a5c-11f0-a063-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 16:05:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
