<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:02:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Six of nine top colleges have rejected the Trump administration’s funding deal ahead of Monday deadline</title>
      <description>Despite strong pressure from the White House, including a Friday call, colleges and universities are largely rejecting President Donald Trump’s offer of preferential treatment for funding in exchange for compliance with his ideological priorities. On Monday, the University of Arizona and Vanderbilt University did not accept the deal, but said they were open to more discussion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5c80a50-ae09-11f0-b665-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 23:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James B. Comey asks judge to dismiss criminal case against him, calling it vindictive</title>
      <description>In court filings, Comey’s attorneys accused President Donald Trump of personally instigating the case against their client. When several prosecutors refused to proceed, the attorneys wrote, Trump installed a loyalist in a key position to ensure that charges would be filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7da94e0-adf5-11f0-b01b-0000a1ace171</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two more teens charged in August attack on DOGE staffer that propelled Trump’s D.C. takeover</title>
      <description>An 18- and a 19-year-old face charges including robbery and assault for their alleged role in the Aug. 3 attack on Edward Coristine — a 19-year-old software engineer known as “Big Balls” — and another person at a nearby gas station, U.S. Attorney for D.C. Jeanine Pirro announced Monday. Earlier this month, two 15-year-olds were sentenced to probation for their role in the incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5808e9d0-adf4-11f0-ba79-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 20:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump can deploy National Guard in Portland, appeals court rules</title>
      <description>A federal judge appointed by President Donald Trump had blocked him from sending federalized National Guard members to Oregon’s largest city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be2968b1-adeb-11f0-ae6a-0000a1ace57c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demolition of White House facade begins, contradicting Trump’s claim that addition wouldn’t interfere with current structure</title>
      <description>Construction teams Monday demolished a portion of the East Wing, with a backhoe ripping through the structure, according to a photo shared with The Washington Post and two people who witnessed the activity. The ballroom project, long desired by President Donald Trump, is estimated to cost $250 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08b9cb90-ade7-11f0-b622-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 19:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man was driving in reverse when he plowed through child’s party in Maryland on Saturday, killing 1 and injuring 13, police say</title>
      <description>The driver, identified Monday as 66-year-old Sunday Joseph, ran before turning himself in to authorities Sunday morning, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6647c160-ade5-11f0-9849-000a1ace2541</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He regrets not exploring his bisexuality before he married his wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He regrets not exploring his bisexuality before he married his wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6326f0d0-adce-11f0-9b15-0000a1acec62</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials and locals undercut Trump’s claims that boats off Venezuela are carrying deadly fentanyl to the U.S.</title>
      <description>Records and interviews with 20 people familiar with the route or the strikes show that the targeted passage in the waters between Venezuela and Trinidad and Tobago typically carries cocaine and marijuana to other continents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41402da0-adbb-11f0-bb35-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:47:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Mad Mike’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86e3a921-adb8-11f0-af5c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes. Marco Rubio. Military exercise. Inflation. Louvre heist. Parkinson’s prevention. Rare comets. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5f6ebc0-ada3-11f0-a35f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Stanford scientist and Berkshire Hathaway heir is on a mission to thwart redistricting efforts in California</title>
      <description>Charles Munger Jr. is the largest individual donor opposing the California ballot measure that would redraw the state’s congressional map to favor Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08517cd2-ad37-11f0-9c35-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 22:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These two infectious disease experts say this is when you should get covid and flu shots</title>
      <description>Flu season is here. The summer wave of the coronavirus has receded, but the winter uptick is likely around the corner. The Washington Post spoke to two experts about how they make their own decisions and how they talk about vaccines with friends and families.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d79e9c61-ad15-11f0-a35f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 18:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z slang is everywhere. Test your knowledge of teen talk with this quiz.</title>
      <description>Gen Z slang is everywhere. Do you understand it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d0a26e0-ad0b-11f0-8101-0000a1aced91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf03c2d0-ad04-11f0-b80f-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She spurned the concertmaster’s advance. Now she’s classical music’s #MeToo vigilante.</title>
      <description>Baltimore Symphony oboist Katherine Needleman’s online shaming campaign has sidelined several musicians — and outraged others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8f523b0-acf8-11f0-97b7-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9992590-acef-11f0-a048-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 13:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio promised to betray U.S. informants to get Trump’s El Salvador prison deal</title>
      <description>To secure Washington’s access to El Salvador’s most notorious prison, Secretary of State Marco Rubio made an extraordinary offer to President Nayib Bukele.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db3fed91-acea-11f0-a659-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 12:55:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thieves steal treasured jewelry from Louvre in daytime heist</title>
      <description>Thieves broke into the Apollo Gallery, which houses the French crown jewels, through an outside window and escaped on motorbikes, the interior minister said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b538f2c0-ace2-11f0-8efc-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 11:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He’s basketball’s next big thing — with a sports dad unlike any other</title>
      <description>Want a piece of Brigham Young’s AJ Dybantsa? “You have to go through” his father.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3551a6a0-ac75-11f0-8eca-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 22:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Street carnival atmosphere as huge crowds gather across U.S. for No Kings protests against Trump</title>
      <description>Demonstrators spoke out against President Donald Trump’s immigration crackdowns, domestic military deployments and efforts to sideline critics and political opponents. The nationwide protests appeared to be one of the largest mass demonstrations of recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47faee21-ac6f-11f0-8238-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 22:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin demanded Ukraine surrender key territory in call with Trump as condition for ending the war</title>
      <description>The Russian leader’s focus on Donetsk, a strategically vital region in eastern Ukraine, suggests he is not backing away from past demands that have left the conflict in a stalemate, despite Trump’s optimism about securing a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">685077e0-ac5f-11f0-a636-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to repatriate survivors of drug boat strike to Colombia, Ecuador</title>
      <description>It is unclear if the two surviving alleged drug smugglers have any links to Venezuelan criminal organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c54327d0-ac4c-11f0-a1c8-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With shutdown cuts, Trump moves closer to eliminating Education Department</title>
      <description>The administration is looking to shed workers and transfer some operations to other departments as it seeks to close the Education Department.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">119ae690-ac2f-11f0-827b-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63cf2ff0-ac27-11f0-8ee9-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 13:36:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani just played the greatest game in baseball history</title>
      <description>On a night of legendary excellence, Ohtani hit three home runs and pitched six-plus scoreless innings to lift the Dodgers to the National League pennant.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72647a00-ac1a-11f0-8882-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:03:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders disgraced former congressman George Santos released from prison</title>
      <description>In commuting his sentence, the president described Santos, who was expelled from the House after being accused of financial misconduct and telling myriad lies about his background, as “somewhat of a ‘rogue.'”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7d1a5e0-abac-11f0-a601-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Virginia turns down Trump deal for priority federal funding</title>
      <description>The state's flagship university joins MIT, Brown University, the University of Pennsylvania and the University of Southern California in refusing to sign the Trump administration’s proposed compact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">095ae230-aba5-11f0-909e-000a1aceb90b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks Supreme Court to let it deploy troops in Illinois</title>
      <description>Federal judges have so far declined to let the administration send the National Guard into the Chicago area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db14a4e1-ab97-11f0-867e-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Andrew to relinquish royal titles after fresh revelations tied him to Jeffrey Epstein and alleged Chinese espionage</title>
      <description>In a new book, one of Epstein’s victims wrote a lurid account of being sexually abused by Prince Andrew, a younger brother of King Charles III.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">210cbbf9-ab88-11f0-9157-0000a1acefcd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maine Senate candidate downplayed concerns about sexual assault in the military in deleted posts</title>
      <description>Democrat Graham Platner disavowed the comments in an interview with The Washington Post, saying, “I don’t want people to judge me off the dumbest thing I said on the internet 12 years ago.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4df870-ab81-11f0-8853-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband’s family disrespects me, and he does nothing about it</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband’s family disrespects me, he does nothing about it</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad170720-ab7b-11f0-a009-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Marjorie Taylor Greene is defending Obamacare subsidies</title>
      <description>Anyone surprised by her embrace of big government isn’t paying attention to how the GOP is changing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e28c7650-ab68-11f0-aa59-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:52:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9f13fe0-ab5d-11f0-8735-0000a1ace9b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump aide John Bolton to make first court appearance in classified documents case</title>
      <description>The former national security adviser surrendered to federal officials in Maryland on Friday, a day after his indictment on charges that he mishandled classified materials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b59c280-ab5c-11f0-858b-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Bolton. Trump-Zelensky meeting. ICE surveillance. Shutdown deadlock. Venezuela. Fertility drugs. Roman mystery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14187a80-ab4f-11f0-8e80-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These two quick tests can tell you if you’re as fit as an 80-year-old elite athlete</title>
      <description>The tests require only a chair, a willing helper, a stopwatch and few spare minutes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad18d50-aaed-11f0-b065-0000a1ace25c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Stamberg dies at 87. A ‘founding mother’ of NPR, she helped blaze a trail for women in broadcasting.</title>
      <description>As a host of “All Things Considered,” she was the first woman to anchor a national nightly news program in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54c24dc2-aae8-11f0-9070-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 23:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ace Frehley, the galvanizing guitarist who helped make Kiss one of the biggest rock groups of the 1970s and ’80s, dies at 74</title>
      <description>Taking the blues rock of his favorite bands, Frehley imbued the group with energy and leaned into the theatrics as a performer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c463b3b0-aae0-11f0-a8e0-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top military officer central to Trump’s drug war to step down early</title>
      <description>Adm. Alvin Holsey has served as the head of U.S. Southern Command for less than a year. The position typically rotates every three years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ba460e0-aade-11f0-8e19-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former national security adviser John Bolton indicted for allegedly mishandling sensitive documents</title>
      <description>Bolton is the third long-time target of President Donald Trump to be charged in a month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99b59140-aad3-11f0-82b6-0000a1acec03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chamber of Commerce sues Trump to block $100,000 fee for H-1B visas — its first legal action against the administration this term</title>
      <description>The powerful business group is alleging that President Donald Trump’s changes to the immigration pathway widely used by Silicon Valley are illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee9b7b30-aacd-11f0-bbdc-000a1acef288</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump unveils plan to make IVF and fertility drugs more accessible and affordable, a key campaign pledge</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump made broadening access to in vitro fertilization a 2024 campaign pillar as he looked to make up for losses among female voters in the aftermath of Roe v. Wade’s fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6a6d270-aacb-11f0-9458-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: How big will the ‘No Kings’ protests be this weekend? Our chief political correspondent takes your questions.</title>
      <description>Happening now: How big will the ‘No Kings’ protests be this weekend? Our chief political correspondent takes your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e5d6e40-aaae-11f0-a32e-0000a1ace0b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I resigned from the military because of Trump</title>
      <description>I could not swear to follow a commander in chief who seems so willing to disregard the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69f7ff90-aaad-11f0-aeb8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be dad goes bungee jumping, comes home to furious wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be dad goes bungee jumping, comes home to furious wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5265bec0-aaa9-11f0-a276-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Special Operations copters fly less than 90 miles from Venezuela, suggesting possible preparation for missions inside country</title>
      <description>The U.S. military’s elite Special Operations aviation unit appears to have flown in Caribbean waters near the coast of Venezuela in recent days, according to a visual analysis by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a456491-aaa0-11f0-ac88-0000a1ace758</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be ‘weak’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cbb0ed3-aa94-11f0-910d-0000a1aceb7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘It broke me’: Inside the FBI hunt for the online predators who persuaded a 13-year-old to kill himself</title>
      <description>How the suicide of a child from Washington state launched a years-long global investigation to find an elusive online user called “White Tiger,” with one FBI agent saying he encountered brutality and bureaucratic hurdles in the case that challenged him in ways he’d never faced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2051c050-aa8b-11f0-8dd6-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown layoffs. Voting maps. Pentagon. Venezuela pressure. Medicare portal glitches. ‘Quality’ jobs. Fitness test. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">518b2f50-aa7f-11f0-8dd6-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s team made a Medicare doctor directory a priority. It launched with errors, The Post found, setting off a scramble.</title>
      <description>The directory, intended to help older Americans navigate Medicare Advantage open enrollment, produces conflicting responses about which providers are covered by health plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aba10ea0-aa2b-11f0-853d-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
