<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 05:03:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Corman dies at 98. The low-budget filmmaker launched the careers of many actors and directors.</title>
      <description>While making films on the cheap, Roger Corman became a “cinematic godfather” to Jack Nicholson, Francis Ford Coppola and others whose careers he boosted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06f2a0a0-1010-11ef-a848-0000a1ace01f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2024 03:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists tracked a young whale’s journey before he vanished. What they learned could help save his species.</title>
      <description>Bishop was luckier than many in his family on his trip from Florida to Maine — a harrowing journey that has killed many other North Atlantic right whales. Bishop’s story shows the extreme danger facing right whales, which could be extinct in three decades if they continue to disappear at the present rate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88562cc0-0fde-11ef-9684-0000a1aced60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 21:36:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New book reveals how ‘Fat Leonard’ compromised two admirals in charge of Navy intelligence</title>
      <description>Confidential transcripts show prosecutors interrogated the Navy’s intelligence chief and a deputy about defense contractor Leonard Glenn Francis’s allegations that he provided them with meals, gifts and women. Both denied wrongdoing, but 10 other officers admitted to leaking military secrets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbdaac30-0fc9-11ef-86ea-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 19:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'There is an important message I am ready to scream out loud' this Mother's Day, writes Olena Zelenska, the first lady of Ukraine</title>
      <description>Six-year-old Renat and 10-year-old Varvara were living in Mariupol — the city wiped from the face of the Earth by Russian bombing — when they were sent to an orphanage in Russia. They were torn from their mother, who had been taken prisoner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3a35650-0fba-11ef-9c95-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 17:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My husband wants me to forget all about his emotional affair</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My husband wants me to forget all about his emotional affair</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61060890-0fb4-11ef-b444-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 16:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite warnings of violence at UCLA, police didn’t step in to quell attack on protesters for over 3 hours</title>
      <description>The delayed response prolonged an April 30 attack on a pro-Palestinian encampment on campus, one of the most violent altercations during this spring’s wave of campus protests. A Washington Post examination — based on more than 200 videos, emergency radio transmissions and other evidence — found that more than a dozen people were visibly injured before police stepped in. The Post also found that faculty had raised concerns for days about verbal and physical harassment directed at protesters, raising questions about whether the school should have had more police on hand to prevent an altercation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7cd2e80-0fae-11ef-851e-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security has to be fixed. But you still need your own savings, our personal finance columnist says.</title>
      <description>Congress needs to find a solution to Social Security's upcoming shortfall. In the meantime, here are three moves to get started on a retirement plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ef48f10-0fa5-11ef-8cbb-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e7a2541-0f9a-11ef-b444-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most extreme solar storm in 20 years brings beautiful northern lights</title>
      <description>An extreme geomagnetic storm hit Earth for the first time in over 20 years, causing stunning aurora displays across Europe and very low latitudes in the U.S.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37399c90-0f44-11ef-9bcb-0000a1ace463</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 03:11:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration says Israel may have violated humanitarian law using U.S. weapons but that conclusive evidence is lacking</title>
      <description>The Biden administration said it was “reasonable to assess” that Israel violated international law using U.S. weapons in its military campaign in Gaza but it found that it did not have enough information to draw a conclusion in any specific instances, meaning U.S. military aid could continue to flow to the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb104330-0f20-11ef-b3a6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 22:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New limits on credit card late fees won’t take effect as planned. A court issued a temporary injunction after banking groups sued.</title>
      <description>The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau had sought to cap most fees at $8 per month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b08f2701-0f1b-11ef-8e8e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 22:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A severe solar storm is hitting Earth. It could disrupt communications systems but show off the Northern Lights.</title>
      <description>The severe geomagnetic storm is the most intense in two decades and resulted from multiple solar eruptions that hurtled toward Earth. If the storm holds its strength, auroras could be seen with the naked eye at night as far south as Alabama and California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8155480-0f0c-11ef-92c4-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 20:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My dad and stepmom hate that I live with my mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My dad and stepmom hate that I live with my mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0d24460-0ee9-11ef-ae53-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 16:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s what actually happens within your lawn when you don’t mow it: An interactive guide</title>
      <description>Follow this step-by-step process to let your grass grow and discover why it helps flowers, birds and bees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db36f591-0ee0-11ef-ae53-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 15:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08bd4f00-0ed2-11ef-ada6-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Confederate leaders’ names will be restored to two Virginia schools, after school board reverses 2020 changes</title>
      <description>The Shenandoah County schools will once again be called Stonewall Jackson High School and Ashby Lee Elementary School. The move comes four years after the Confederate generals’ names were removed during the national reckoning about race sparked by the killing of George Floyd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b49334a1-0ecf-11ef-9009-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paul Manafort is poised to rejoin Trump world. But his global ties, including support for a Chinese media deal, complicate things.</title>
      <description>The former Trump campaign chairman, who’s likely to help manage this summer’s GOP convention, resumed consulting work after being pardoned in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">871b66b0-0ec9-11ef-800e-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 12:33:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels. U.S.-Israel rift. Police shooting. Deaf baby. iPad ad. Eurovision. Northern lights. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7130aa71-0ebc-11ef-94ac-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The saga of Kitty Snows, D.C.’s beloved blue-collar cat, and the neighbors who are fighting over her</title>
      <description>She belonged to everyone and no one. She crashed college house parties and slipped into homes and napped on couches. The Foggy Bottom Association sold her likeness on T-shirts, mugs and trucker hats. And then, this February, Kitty Snows vanished.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3db6ed00-0e47-11ef-b12e-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says Israel can ‘stand alone’ after Biden warning he could halt U.S. arms</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said Israel was strong enough to fight alone after President Biden threatened to halt the shipment of U.S. offensive weapons if the country moves ahead with its long-planned ground invasion of Rafah in the Gaza Strip. “If we have to stand alone, we will stand alone,” Netanyahu said in a video message ahead of Israel’s Independence Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d9fe4f0-0e2d-11ef-ac21-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veterans Affairs leaders improperly approved almost $11 million in bonuses for senior executives, watchdog finds</title>
      <description>The VA's inspector general has found that more than 180 senior executives received improper bonuses last fall, with several taking home more than $100,000. The bonuses came from money Congress had earmarked to recruit and retain specialists. VA executives have been ordered to repay the money, but some are challenging the ruling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8857e21-0e2b-11ef-b86a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 17:45:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. settles with two women who accused Mayor Muriel Bowser's former top aide of sexual harassment</title>
      <description>The terms of the settlement with the women, both of whom worked for the city, were not disclosed. The Mayor's Office of Legal Counsel had found John Falcicchio sexually harassed both of the women. Falcicchio, who was the chief of staff and former deputy mayor for planning and economic development, had resigned suddenly in March 2023 after the first accuser's complaint.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccf28ee0-0e22-11ef-a67c-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Was it wrong to approach late wife’s pal for no-commitment sex?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Was it wrong to approach late wife’s pal for no-commitment sex?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9be96760-0e1d-11ef-9ceb-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 16:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels spars with Trump lawyer during heated cross-examination. Follow live coverage in the hush money trial.</title>
      <description>The exchanges between Daniels and defense lawyer Susan Necheles grew increasingly tense Thursday morning. As the two traded verbal jabs, the jurors had to turn their heads quickly back and forth to track the testimony.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b625dd0-0e15-11ef-aa3a-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 15:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pantry staple with health benefits in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e82bda51-0e08-11ef-8f4b-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 13:34:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asked oil CEOs at Mar-a-Lago to raise $1 billion for his campaign, vowed to target EVs, say people who knew of meeting</title>
      <description>At a meeting last month at his Florida club, Donald Trump told some of the nation’s top oil executives they should invest in his presidential campaign instead of spending huge sums lobbying the Biden administration, according to people with knowledge of the meeting, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe a private conversation. Trump told the executives that if he returns to office, he would quickly reverse President Biden’s climate and energy policies. The result, Trump said, would be more offshore oil drilling, exports of liquified natural gas and support for gas-powered cars, instead of electric vehicles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1827740-0dfb-11ef-8ddf-0000a1ace69f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 12:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel weapons. Trump meeting. House speaker. Tornadoes. Brain worms. Pandemic risk. ‘The Office.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f6f040-0df3-11ef-96fb-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Social is relatively small. But Trump’s posts find enormous audiences anyway, thanks to an army of amplifiers and surrogates.</title>
      <description>Those concerned about the impact of Donald Trump’s incendiary and often inaccurate messages have long sought ways to limit his reach. A Washington Post analysis shows how those efforts have failed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdae0a60-0d98-11ef-9ec1-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Nuggets center Nikola Jokic wins NBA MVP award, becoming ninth player to receive the honor at least three times</title>
      <description>Jokic, 29, beat out fellow finalists Shai Gilgeous-Alexander of the Oklahoma City Thunder and Luka Doncic of the Dallas Mavericks to follow up his previous MVPs in 2021 and 2022. He finished second behind Philadelphia 76ers center Joel Embiid in 2023. The other players who have been named MVP at least three times are Kareem Abdul-Jabbar (six times), Bill Russell (five), Michael Jordan (five), Wilt Chamberlain (four), LeBron James (four), Moses Malone (three), Larry Bird (three) and Magic Johnson (three).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56e0490-0d93-11ef-9a2b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden says he will stop weapons shipments if Israel invades Rafah, the most direct threat he’s made since war started</title>
      <description>Biden said in an interview with CNN scheduled to air Wednesday that civilians in Gaza have been killed by U.S. weapons as Israel has gone after "population centers." Biden continued: "If they go into Rafah, I’m not supplying the weapons that have been used historically ... to deal with the cities." His acknowledgement that U.S. weapons have been used to kill civilians in Gaza and conditioning of support to the American ally is a notable change from his previous public comments on Israel's military operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e83b1270-0d8d-11ef-937e-0000a1ace8b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House overwhelmingly votes against ousting Speaker Mike Johnson, a blow to Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s efforts to remove him</title>
      <description>Democrats voted with most Republicans in support of a procedural motion that effectively ends the attempt of Greene (R-Ga.) to topple Johnson (R-La.). That means the House will not consider a “motion to vacate,” which would have been a direct vote on Johnson’s leadership. The speaker will keep his job for now, but future ouster attempts are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b90a6b0-0d87-11ef-a3bc-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do you get an air fryer to make food that’s actually crispy? We answered your cooking questions.</title>
      <description>How do you get an air fryer to make food that’s actually crispy? We answered your cooking questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9183af0-0d5e-11ef-bad6-0000a1ace97f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family pushes siblings to ‘make amends’ after their mother’s death</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family pushes siblings to ‘make amends’ after their mother’s death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbe3e9a0-0d54-11ef-90a9-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To please Putin, Russian universities purge liberals and embrace patriotism</title>
      <description>In a transformation of Russia’s education system, pro-Kremlin university administrators have ousted students and professors who oppose the war in Ukraine, slashed humanities programs with ties to the West, and rewritten curriculums to emphasize nationalism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">972a1960-0d53-11ef-99fb-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human disruptions to the planet have made it easier for diseases to spread — raising the risk of a new pandemic, study finds</title>
      <description>As humans degrade Earth’s environment, we have created a world in which diseases may be increasingly apt to fester and multiply. Climate change and biodiversity losses encourage disease to spread, according to research published Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5d19cd0-0d4f-11ef-94cb-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brittney Griner landed in Russia and wound up in prison. She details what happened in a new excerpt.</title>
      <description>This column — adapted from her memoir, “Coming Home” — is the story of how Griner’s ordeal began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9ae6e0-0d41-11ef-8022-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reelection bid in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c1d240-0d3e-11ef-874f-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels. Israel bombs. Zelensky plot. TikTok lawsuit. Michigan tornadoes. Olive oil. Whale speech. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207c2892-0d2a-11ef-a78d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police begin clearing, making arrests at George Washington University protest encampment</title>
      <description>The move on the pro-Palestinian encampment comes hours before the District’s mayor and police chief are set to testify on Capitol Hill about why they had for nearly two weeks declined requests from the university to clear it from the school’s grounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9a1ca00-0d21-11ef-9e11-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. paused shipments of thousands of bombs to Israel amid a rift over its battle plans for Rafah</title>
      <description>In an unprecedented move, the Biden administration paused a shipment of 2,000-pound bombs and other munitions bound for Israel last week as a result of mounting concern about the country’s plan to expand a military operation in southern Gaza that could dramatically increase the conflict’s death toll, senior administration officials said. It is the first known instance of a pause in U.S. arms transfers since the Oct. 7 Hamas-led attack. One U.S. official described the move as a “shot across the bow” intended to underscore the seriousness of Washington’s concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1274980-0ceb-11ef-b37b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 50 people are trapped inside a FedEx facility after a tornado hit Portage, Mich., county authorities say</title>
      <description>First responders were trying to get the people out but were waiting for the power company to clear downed wires blocking the way, Taylor Koopman, Kalamazoo County spokeswoman, said Tuesday evening. A nearby mobile home park was also hit hard, she said. No deaths had been reported in the city as of about 8 p.m., Portage Mayor Patricia Randall said, though crews were still assessing the damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a04401b0-0cda-11ef-b6a9-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final body found in Baltimore Key Bridge collapse, officials say</title>
      <description>Salvage crews have located the remains of the sixth and apparently final construction worker killed when the Francis Scott Key Bridge in Baltimore was struck by a ship and collapsed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c6edbd1-0cc9-11ef-b23c-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York judge was alarmed by Trump’s response to Stormy Daniels testimony, early trial transcripts show</title>
      <description>New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan called Trump lawyer Todd Blanche to a sidebar during a midday break to say the former president was “cursing audibly” and shaking his head, possibly intimidating adult-film actress Stormy Daniels as she testified in Trump's falsifying records criminal trial. “I am speaking to you here at the bench because I don’t want to embarrass him," Merchan said, according to transcripts. "You need to speak to him. I won’t tolerate that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72a12291-0cc8-11ef-b98c-0000a1ace4b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar and Drake’s rap feud has gotten ugly. Here’s a breakdown, track by track.</title>
      <description>Since Friday, Drake and Lamar have released songs with some serious allegations against each other, igniting pro-sports levels of spectating. Full of easter eggs (and probably misinformation), it’s a classic hip-hop feud with a very modern flavor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c703890-0cc1-11ef-918f-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's classified documents trial in Florida delayed indefinitely, judge says</title>
      <description>Judge Aileen M. Cannon canceled the May 20 start of Donald Trump's trial for allegedly withholding classified documents after leaving the White House and obstructing government efforts to get them back, saying she could not set a new date until myriad pre-trial issues are resolved. The decision increases the chances that Trump, who’s on trial in New York for allegedly falsifying business records connected to a hush money payment, will not face another criminal trial before the November presidential election in which he is the likely Republican nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a53f9ca0-0cb8-11ef-8879-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Stormy Daniels’s account of sex with Trump may be problematic, and other takeaways from today’s hush money trial testimony</title>
      <description>The first trial of a former U.S. president took an especially surreal turn, as adult-film actress Stormy Daniels told jurors about an alleged sexual encounter with Donald Trump that she did not want, prompting a call from defense lawyers for a mistrial. Read our takeaways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f335c30-0cb2-11ef-a60c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok files court challenge to law that could lead to its ban, setting up what could be an existential fight for the popular app</title>
      <description>The filing raises a variety of legal issues arguing that the law, signed by President Biden last month and which calls for TikTok’s sale within 270 days, was an unconstitutional overreach. It called for the court to block the law’s enforcement until it reaches a decision on the substance of the filing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8dd40c0-0c8d-11ef-8ef0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband admits to one-night stand, wants spouse to ‘let it go’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband admits to one-night stand, wants spouse to ‘let it go’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e69f3b70-0c8a-11ef-b7ab-0000a1ace835</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels, testifying now, recounts how she came to meet Trump in a hotel room — and the pajamas she said he was wearing</title>
      <description>Daniels, who alleged that she had a sexual encounter with Donald Trump years before he sought the presidency, is testifying this morning in his criminal trial. Trump faces 34 counts of falsifying business records related to his reimbursement of his then-lawyer Michael Cohen for a hush money payment made to the adult-film actress shortly before the 2016 election, which was meant to keep her from publicly sharing her story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3530d3e0-0c89-11ef-9de2-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 1,000 people, including 91 admirals, swept up in ‘Fat Leonard’ scandal, new book reveals. Yet only one admiral went to prison.</title>
      <description>Aides accused Rear Adm. Robert Gilbeau, known as “Crazy Bob,” of faking a mental breakdown in Afghanistan to avoid prosecution. He became the only admiral in history to be found guilty of committing a federal crime while on active duty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08351091-0c7f-11ef-aee0-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
