<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 03:04:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky judge shot and killed in his chambers by local sheriff following argument, state officials say</title>
      <description>Letcher County District Judge Kevin Mullins, 54, was fatally shot Thursday afternoon following an argument with the county sheriff, Shawn Stines, according to local officials. State police said Stines, 43, is in custody and has been charged with one count of murder in the first degree.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d37aa2c0-76e6-11ef-afae-0000a1ace38b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 00:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodgers slugger Shohei Ohtani becomes first player in MLB history with 50 home runs and 50 stolen bases in the same season</title>
      <description>Baseball’s biggest star became the founding member of the 50-50 club in his first season with the Dodgers, the latest breathtaking accomplishment in a historic career.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">754789c0-76dc-11ef-ab77-000a1ace47bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 23:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists have captured Earth’s climate over the past 485 million years. Here’s the surprising place we stand now.</title>
      <description>An effort to understand Earth’s past climates uncovered a history of wild temperature shifts and offered a warning on the consequences of human-caused warming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bdf1ba0-76d3-11ef-aff8-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 22:06:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Our leaders have turned their backs on us’: In Springfield, Eugene Robinson hears stories about strain, promise — and race</title>
      <description>In Springfield, I heard stories about strain, promise — and race</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17ed8820-76d1-11ef-9ba9-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 21:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.C. Republican nominee vows to continue campaign for governor as CNN report says he called himself ‘Black NAZI’ on porn site</title>
      <description>CNN reported that Mark Robinson, who has a history of incendiary remarks, also voiced support for bringing back slavery. Robinson denied making the comments and insisted he would stay in the race against Democrat Josh Stein in a battleground state key to the presidential race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab1b0960-76c7-11ef-9a14-0000a1ace727</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 20:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My friend just divorced a truly bad man. How do I help her move on? Our Well+Being editor is taking your questions about divorce.</title>
      <description>My friend just divorced a truly bad man. How do I help her move on? Our Well+Being editor is taking your questions about divorce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">668ed070-76ad-11ef-a88e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 17:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid was linked again to Wuhan market animals in a peer-reviewed paper. It’s unlikely to end debate over the pandemic’s origin.</title>
      <description>The new paper, which appears in the journal Cell, expands on findings from an informal 2023 report on the subject.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44adedc0-76a7-11ef-9e67-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Are post-breakup conversations with ex-boyfriend a bad idea?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Are post-breakup conversations with ex-boyfriend a bad idea?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d779e20-76a0-11ef-a2fe-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Chiles’s coach appealed Olympic score within required time, a Post analysis finds — contradicting ruling that revoked medal</title>
      <description>The Post’s review of audio and dozens of videos shows that the Court of Arbitration for Sport ruled against Chiles based on time markers that don’t precisely match the sport’s protocol for inquiries. Chiles is now suing in Swiss court to reclaim the bronze medal she was awarded last month at the Paris Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e183b431-769e-11ef-ac09-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alaska man charged with threatening to torture and assassinate six of the nine Supreme Court justices</title>
      <description>Panos Anastasiou, 76, was arrested after allegedly threatening six Supreme Court justices and their relatives, the Justice Department announced Thursday. Attorney General Merrick Garland said Anastasiou “made repeated, heinous threats to murder and torture Supreme Court Justices and their families to retaliate against them for decisions he disagreed with.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ff30991-769a-11ef-97f8-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 15:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah leader says device attacks are an ‘act of war’ against Lebanon, as Israeli warplanes fly over Beirut</title>
      <description>In his first remarks since thousands of electronic devices exploded across the country, Hasan Nasrallah said that Hezbollah suffered “a major blow,” but that his forces would not stop attacking Israel as long as the war in Gaza continued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42cee7d0-7697-11ef-b6d0-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 14:55:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big win for EVs in this country in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57d36c20-768b-11ef-a1d3-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris and Trump essentially tied in Pennsylvania one week after the debate, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris and former president Donald Trump are locked in a statistical tie in Pennsylvania, according to a Washington Post poll of a state that many analysts see as the battleground most likely to determine the outcome of the presidential election. One week after a debate that Pennsylvania voters widely say Harris won, she is favored by 48 percent of both likely voters and registered voters, while Trump is supported by 47 percent of voters in both categories. Third-party candidates are not a major factor in the race, The Post’s poll finds: After excluding minor candidates, Harris and Trump are both at 48 percent among likely voters, with Harris at 48 percent and Trump at 47 percent among registered voters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4378cf0-7679-11ef-ac5e-0000a1ace141</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 11:24:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding devices. Harris vs. Trump. Shutdown vote. Interest rates. Delta malfunction. Lingering storms. IRS reward. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">479db0f0-7676-11ef-95cb-0000a1ace98c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2024 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A journey from N.C. to Ukraine to suspect in apparent Trump assassination attempt</title>
      <description>Ryan Routh’s long and strange journey from running a roofing company to being the suspect in what the FBI has called an apparent assassination attempt in Florida left friends and acquaintances mystified. He could be odd, many of them said, and had a history of mostly minor run-ins with police, but wasn’t threatening. Still, in recent years, there were hints of a kind of unraveling, particularly since he went to Ukraine in 2022. While Routh saw himself engaged in a Manichaean battle of good evil, others found his activities there counterproductive and disturbing — so much so that they flagged him to U.S. government agencies, they said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ecc610-7616-11ef-af6f-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 23:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House fails to pass Speaker Mike Johnson’s government funding plan as Sept. 30 shutdown deadline nears</title>
      <description>Lawmakers want to extend operations at current spending levels but have yet to agree on how.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c9d6d30-7610-11ef-b4bd-0000a1ace26b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 22:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite more than two centuries of Haitian vilification, this moment feels particularly dangerous, author Edwidge Danticat writes</title>
      <description>This country should make no room for hate, the author writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bb745f0-7603-11ef-8473-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Fed’s half-point rate cut means for consumers, businesses and investors</title>
      <description>The Federal Reserve lowered rates for the first time in four years, a decision that will affect hiring, inflation, the housing market, stocks and borrowing costs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5993ad70-7601-11ef-baf8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 21:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More hurricanes are lingering for days, a new study found. Here are the places most at risk.</title>
      <description>The new research, published in the Journal of Applied Meteorology and Climatology, underlines growing risks that slow-moving tropical storms, even weaker ones, can unleash outsized impacts when they batter communities with uninterrupted downpours and unrelenting winds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4189a490-75fd-11ef-8873-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 20:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teamsters decline to endorse a presidential candidate for the first time since 1996, a blow to Democrats</title>
      <description>The International Brotherhood of Teamsters executive board voted to sit this election out, coinciding with new inroads Teamsters President Sean O’Brien has forged with the Republican Party. The powerful union has endorsed Democrats for president going back to the 1990s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">956acce1-75f0-11ef-b3df-0000a1ace808</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 19:02:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve cuts interest rates by a half-point, opting for a more aggressive move amid worries the job market is slowing</title>
      <description>The rate cut marks the first time since 2020 that officials have lowered borrowing costs, signaling a major shift in the central bank’s fight against post-pandemic inflation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13d98661-75e8-11ef-ba85-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 18:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government watchdogs are investigating Biden's weapons transfers to Israel after federal worker complaints, The Post has learned</title>
      <description>Inspectors general with jurisdiction over the State Department and Pentagon are preparing to publish the results of multiple investigations scrutinizing the Biden administration’s provision of U.S. weapons to Israel for its military campaign in Gaza, and “several” related inquiries are either underway or planned, their offices told The Washington Post. The forthcoming reports follow complaints from government employees who contend the export of billions of dollars in arms has violated U.S. and international law and received far too little oversight from watchdogs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b1a3b50-75de-11ef-983e-0000a1acebd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: How do you bring hardened honey back to life? Our food writers are answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: How do you bring hardened honey back to life? Our food writers are answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd81b071-75da-11ef-b65e-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The House GOP is a circus, Dana Milbank writes. The chaos has one source.</title>
      <description>The House GOP is a circus. The chaos has one source.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e0ffc20-75d9-11ef-ba1a-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:17:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: All the wives left her holiday feast to hang with husband’s ex-wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: All the wives left her holiday feast to hang with husband’s ex-wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a7a3280-75d7-11ef-bcad-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent NBA reporter Adrian Wojnarowski, known for his viral scoops, announces he is retiring from ESPN</title>
      <description>“I understand the commitment required in my role and it’s an investment that I’m no longer driven to make,” Wojnarowski, 55, said in a post on X. He has agreed to become the general manager of the St. Bonaventure men’s basketball program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a86300-75d3-11ef-a63d-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 15:35:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More deadly blasts, apparently linked to electronic devices, hit Lebanon a day after a pager attack targeted Hezbollah</title>
      <description>The new explosions, at least one of which occurred at a funeral held by Hezbollah in Beirut’s suburbs, killed at least one person and injured more than 100 people, according to Lebanon’s Ministry of Public Health. They come a day after a suspected Israeli attack on Hezbollah’s communications network caused thousands of the group’s electronic pagers to explode, killing 12 people and injuring nearly 3,000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">321f5911-75cf-11ef-a4fc-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 15:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dali owner knew of problems before cargo ship hit Baltimore bridge, U.S. alleges in a court filing</title>
      <description>The ship that hit the Francis Scott Key Bridge, killing six, had known issues that should have been fixed or reported before it set sail, the Justice Department said in a new court filing. Justice Department attorneys said the United States incurred more than $100 million in costs related to the collapse, and they believe the ship’s owner should have to pay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bd6c491-75cb-11ef-b1fd-0000a1ace53c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 14:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A great night for this TV drama in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fa66b02-75c2-11ef-a4fc-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploding pagers. Election violence. Sean Combs. Interest rates. Titan hearing. Instagram teens. Baby hippo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1dea6fb0-75ad-11ef-9bc9-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pager explosions in Lebanon possibly involved sabotage of the devices before they were delivered, experts say</title>
      <description>The suspected attack, which experts described as unprecedented in scope and apparent sophistication, appeared to be the latest salvo in the nearly year-long conflict between Israel and Hezbollah tied to the war in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7451a840-7540-11ef-b879-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 22:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At this ‘Disneyland for nerds’, the search is on for life on other planets. Dave Eggers takes us on a tour.</title>
      <description>Dave Eggers on NASA’s Jet Propulsion Lab</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac70e411-7514-11ef-8c51-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona election official to ask court to block nearly 100,000 voters with missing citizenship records from voting in state races</title>
      <description>A key election official in Arizona’s Maricopa County plans to ask the state’s highest court to prohibit nearly 100,000 longtime residents from voting in state and local races this fall after discovering the state does not have records that they proved their citizenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">523bf690-7511-11ef-9953-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:24:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Apologize to adult children for failing them ‘so completely’?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Apologize to adult children for failing them ‘so completely’?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fba9f960-750d-11ef-9406-0000a1ace075</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter registration deadlines are coming up fast. Here’s how to check your status.</title>
      <description>Even if you voted in a previous election, you’re not necessarily registered for this one, and the window to register closes early next month in some states. If you live in a place that doesn’t allow registration on Election Day on Nov. 5, you should make sure your registration is up to date before your jurisdiction’s deadline passes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb886470-7509-11ef-8ff5-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pagers carried by Hezbollah members explode across Lebanon, leaving a ‘large number of people’ injured, officials say</title>
      <description>A voice message circulated to members of the militant group urged them to throw away their devices, while health officials reported chaotic scenes at hospitals across the country as ambulances poured in. It was unclear what caused the blasts, which came as tensions between Israel and Hezbollah have soared after months of cross-border attacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6e72940-7503-11ef-9b7b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs indicted on racketeering and sex-trafficking charges</title>
      <description>The hip-hop impresario was arrested on a federal indictment in New York on Monday, according to the U.S. attorney’s office for the Southern District of New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e016cac0-74fe-11ef-8f52-0000a1ace661</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 14:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A statue gets ... mixed reviews ... in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df9e0002-74f8-11ef-9899-0000a1ace5d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 13:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump incident. Secret Service. Sean “Diddy” Combs. Heavy rain. Food chemicals. “Mom brain.” Harvest moon. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe0da500-74e3-11ef-ab4f-0000a1ace167</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French man accused of recruiting dozens to rape his wife tells court: ‘I am a rapist’</title>
      <description>Dominique Pélicot, 71, testified that he and “everyone else in this room” are rapists, contradicting earlier claims from others charged in the mass rape trial that they did not know the woman had not consented. Investigators said the alleged victim was raped while drugged and unconscious by at least 72 people; they have identified and charged 51 suspects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2179cb51-74d9-11ef-b50a-000a1acef879</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 09:42:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs arrested in New York after federal indictment</title>
      <description>The U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York said in a statement that Combs was arrested Monday evening, based on a sealed indictment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">656ccac0-74a1-11ef-9a87-000a1ace6486</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 03:03:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shots fired and ‘rather quick golf carts’: Donald Trump talks to Marc Thiessen about the West Palm Beach gunman</title>
      <description>The former president talks about the chaotic moments following the apparent second attempt on his life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d490ea60-7499-11ef-b21d-0000a1acedff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Sep 2024 02:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jordan Chiles appeals in Swiss court to reclaim Olympic bronze medal that was stripped over technicality</title>
      <description>Chiles won bronze in the women’s floor final in Paris last month, part of a historic all-Black medal podium. But a Swiss sports tribunal ruled the medal should be revoked because Chiles’s coach missed a deadline to challenge her initial score. Chiles is now taking her fight to Switzerland’s Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f45e150-7471-11ef-80f6-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service acting director says agency needs to ‘get out of a reactive model’ in protection plans after Trump incident</title>
      <description>Ronald Rowe Jr. said in a news conference Monday that the “paradigm shift” put in place after the assassination attempt on Donald Trump in July worked on Sunday when agents noticed what they thought was a man pointing a rifle toward the former President’s golf course where Trump was playing.
But the acting director said the agency is spread thin and needs Congress to give them funds to add personnel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b124b720-746f-11ef-aa31-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 21:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police released body-cam footage of Trump golf course suspect’s arrest. Records show he may have been in the area for 12 hours.</title>
      <description>Ryan Wesley Routh, who is suspected of a potential assassination attempt against Donald Trump, appears to have been in the area around the former president’s Florida golf course for 12 hours before a Secret Service agent spotted his rifle and opened fire, according to cellphone records included in a federal criminal complaint unsealed Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c510a30-7456-11ef-a9b4-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 18:07:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Will a friendly ex-spouse scare away future dates?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Will a friendly ex-spouse scare away future dates?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7124d761-7445-11ef-b7fb-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 16:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who was arrested in connection with potential Trump assassination attempt is charged with federal firearms crimes</title>
      <description>Ryan Wesley Routh appeared in federal court in West Palm Beach, Fla., on Monday. He was charged with possession of a firearm by a convicted felon and possession of a firearm with an obliterated serial number.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba71b70-743e-11ef-9c9b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 15:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A no good, very bad year for this company continues in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04533970-7430-11ef-8734-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 13:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Candice Bergen ends with a 'meow.' John Oliver eulogizes his dog. The best and most shocking moments at the Emmys.</title>
      <description>The generally surprise-free Emmys ceremony ended with a twist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3d904b1-7427-11ef-be48-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 12:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump incident. JD Vance. European floods. Taliban. Emmy winners. Tito Jackson. Caitlin Clark. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3029bf0-741a-11ef-aa3b-0000a1ace99f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
