<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 22:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A vaccine skeptic is hired to lead a government study of immunizations and autism. Public health experts fear the consequences.</title>
      <description>David Geier, who has long touted a debunked theory on vaccines and autism and was disciplined for practicing medicine without a license, will conduct the critical federal analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d95cd310-09c2-11f0-b94c-0000a1ace45b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 21:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Health warns of possible measles exposures after a person from Minnesota recently traveled in the District while contagious</title>
      <description>D.C. Health officials said the individual rode on an Amtrak train on March 19, walked through the concourse at Union Station and went to urgent care in Adams Morgan a few days later. The health agency is warning people of potential exposures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13ed2a60-09a1-11f0-b91b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia, Ukraine agree to expand partial ceasefire to include maritime traffic on Black Sea after Riyadh talks, White House says</title>
      <description>In a pair of joint statements, the countries agreed to “ensure safe navigation” and “eliminate the use of force” in the Black Sea, a key trade route for Ukrainian and Russian grain exports. The agreement also said that Russia would regain access to world markets for its food and fertilizer exports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">185d6481-099b-11f0-b621-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 17:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He tells his 39-year-old wife ‘not now’ to another baby</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He tells his 39-year-old wife ‘not now’ to another baby</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea3c9740-0992-11f0-b0bc-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 16:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic senators slam intelligence chiefs over Trump team’s Signal leak at hearing on worldwide threats. Watch it live.</title>
      <description>Director of National Intelligence Tulsi Gabbard and CIA Director John Ratcliffe — both of whom were involved in the discussion of sensitive war planning over a text message chain — claimed that messages shared on the leaked Signal group chat were not “classified.” The messages reportedly included detailed weapons and targeting information.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5b53760-098c-11f0-9661-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 15:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security is breaking down amid long waits, waves of calls, and web crashes</title>
      <description>A flood of cuts led by Elon Musk and the U.S. DOGE Service has sent the agency into meltdown as a new commissioner prepares to take charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a307c81-0983-11f0-a168-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 14:15:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A high-profile visit in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84c3ecc0-097d-11f0-aa57-0000a1ace6f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 13:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat leak. Lawyer crackdown. Columbia protester. Hamdan Ballal. Wildfires. 23andMe. Healthy eating. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4460aac1-0968-11f0-abf9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23andMe declared bankruptcy. Delete the DNA data it has on you right now, our tech columnist writes.</title>
      <description>California’s attorney general has issued a privacy “consumer alert.” Unless you take action, there is a risk your genetic information could end up in someone else’s hands and used in ways you never considered, Geoffrey A. Fowler writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75f5a5b1-08f8-11f0-87d5-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 21:39:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House acknowledges several top Trump officials plotted Yemen strikes in unclassified group chat that included Atlantic editor</title>
      <description>The group chat, over the messaging application Signal, appeared to involve a who’s who of key national security figures in the Trump administration, including Vice President JD Vance, White House national security adviser Michael Waltz, CIA Director John Ratcliffe and Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth, according to an extraordinary report Monday by the Atlantic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3704e2a2-08e7-11f0-b1f9-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 19:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does sibling love justify traveling to abusive mom’s deathbed?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does sibling love justify traveling to abusive mom’s deathbed?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80453d51-08cb-11f0-a2fd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 16:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another live-action remake in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca70c910-08b4-11f0-b2e8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland visit. Tax revenue. Gaza death toll. Pope Francis. JFK files. March Madness. Enduring lightbulb. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18650020-089f-11f0-93ca-0000a1ace581</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk once tacitly backed DEI. Now he’s focused on anti-White bias.</title>
      <description>Musk, who was raised during South African apartheid, used to steer clear of debate about race. But as he wields more power as head of the U.S. DOGE Service, part of his playbook now involves amplifying controversial opinions on racially sensitive topics — including what he sees as racism against White people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">794429f1-0833-11f0-86fe-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 22:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They were arrested during routine ICE check-ins. Then they disappeared.</title>
      <description>Family members, lawyers and the public can often get information on detained migrants’ location through an online database, contact with an official or direct phone calls with a detainee. But in the week since the Trump administration invoked the Alien Enemies Act to deport 137 Venezuelans to a mega-prison in El Salvador, detainees can no longer be found in that database.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40f113e0-0812-11f0-8b10-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 18:11:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian prime minister requests dissolution of Parliament and sets snap election as Trump’s threats loom over campaign</title>
      <description>Mark Carney, a former central banker, was sworn in as prime minister earlier this month, taking over as Liberal Party leader from Justin Trudeau. The campaign will take place against the backdrop of President Donald Trump’s trade war and repeated threats to use “economic force” to annex Canada and make it the 51st state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80631080-0805-11f0-8fcc-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:40:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11b2ad30-0800-11f0-a756-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 16:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland is hard to defend. As Trump threatens to ‘get’ the territory, the Danes are trying.</title>
      <description>Like Ukraine, Greenland possesses the critical and rare metals needed for electric vehicles, smartphones, medical imaging equipment, computer chips and wind turbines. But President Donald Trump’s comments have raised more questions than answers about defense of the world’s largest island.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a618b5d0-07f3-11f0-b7ed-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 14:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian death toll surpasses 50,000 in Israel’s war with Hamas, Gaza Health Ministry says</title>
      <description>More than 50,000 Palestinians have been killed in the war between Israel and Hamas, the Gaza Health Ministry said — a grim indicator of the conflict’s continued toll after Israel shattered a nearly two-month-old ceasefire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af8944d0-07d6-11f0-82df-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 11:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS nears deal with ICE to share addresses of suspected undocumented immigrants, ending years of assurances about privacy</title>
      <description>Under the draft agreement, Immigration and Customs Enforcement would be able to submit names and address to the IRS to cross-reference with confidential taxpayer databases, according to four people who spoke on the condition of anonymity out of fear of professional reprisals. The IRS has for years told undocumented workers that their tax information is confidential and that it is safe to file income tax returns without fear of being deported. About half — possibly more — of the roughly 11 million undocumented immigrants in the country file income tax returns to document their payments to the U.S. government, according to researchers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03b4b7d0-0762-11f0-871d-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 21:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I let go of the fear my family won’t approve of my partner?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I let go of the fear my family won’t approve of my partner?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">258f33e0-0752-11f0-b2a5-0000a1ace963</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 19:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump said he didn’t sign the Alien Enemies Act proclamation. So who — or what — did?</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump told reporters he did not sign the proclamation that he said authorized the rapid deportation of migrants he claims are violent gang members from Venezuela. So what did happen? Did Trump misspeak? Is he trying to deflect responsibility onto Secretary of State Marco Rubio? Did his officials use an autopen? The White House's response created more questions than answers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2c2e680-074f-11f0-8954-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 19:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis will be discharged from the hospital on Sunday, his doctors said, after five-week long health crisis</title>
      <description>“The good news that the world has waited for has arrived,” said one of the pope’s attending physicians. Francis will return to his home for what his doctors said would be a “convalescence” of at least two months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1b8edc0-0747-11f0-a9a0-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 18:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax revenue could fall 10% this year, according to projections, as changes at IRS may lead more filers to skip paying taxes</title>
      <description>Tax officials forecast a sharp drop in revenue because of changing taxpayer behavior, as many filers expect the Trump administration will be less likely to challenge suspected tax cheats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b184880-0734-11f0-8bec-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Hezbollah launchers after rockets were fired from Lebanon, killing two, in biggest exchange since ceasefire</title>
      <description>The Israeli Defense Forces and U.N. peacekeepers said projectiles were launched from Lebanon into Israel on Saturday morning. The IDF responded with strikes targeting “dozens of Hezbollah rocket launchers and a command center,” it said. At least two people, including a child, were killed and 10 wounded, according to the Lebanese Health Ministry. Hezbollah denied launching rockets and said the accusations were “merely pretexts” for “continued attacks on Lebanon, which have not ceased since the ceasefire was announced” in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c670a840-072d-11f0-9669-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:56:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0efd3e20-0724-11f0-8024-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kitty Dukakis dies at 88. She carved a distinct identity in public as her husband governed Massachusetts and ran for president.</title>
      <description>Dukakis, who was the wife of former Massachusetts governor and 1988 Democratic presidential nominee Michael Dukakis, spoke openly about her struggles with addiction and later promoted electroconvulsive therapy as a treatment for depression. She was a social worker, arts patron and activist on behalf of vulnerable populations, from the homeless to the stateless. She said she was “fiercely proud” of her Jewish background, playing a role in the creation of the U.S. Holocaust Memorial Museum in Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">853d55f0-0721-11f0-b6a3-0000a1ace8c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Foreman dies at 76. The heavyweight champion boxer was also a ubiquitous entrepreneur.</title>
      <description>Foreman died Friday while “surrounded by loved ones,” according to a statement on his verified Instagram account. Foreman defeated Joe Frazier to win his first heavyweight title in 1973, then became the oldest heavyweight champion in history when he reclaimed the crown two decades later at age 45. The Olympic gold medalist also became an ordained Christian minister and gained further fame for promoting the popular George Foreman Grill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc2f0b82-06c5-11f0-8674-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 02:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Wilson, transformative Washington police chief, dies at 96</title>
      <description>Wilson was a central player in a tumultuous period in the District’s history that encompassed the civil rights movement, anti-Vietnam War protests and the run-up to home rule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65f355c0-06a2-11f0-86c0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 22:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Department of Homeland Security shuts down three internal watchdog agencies, calling them 'roadblocks' to immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security ordered a “reduction in force” in three agencies that advocated for immigrants and investigated complaints, including about detention conditions and delays in processing green card and citizenship applications. The Office for Civil Rights and Civil Liberties, the Office of the Immigration Detention Ombudsman and the Office of the Citizenship and Immigration Services Ombudsman together had about 300 employees. They will be terminated within 60 days if they do not find another assignment inside DHS, a spokeswoman said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8c2ea60-0697-11f0-9cb0-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 21:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband says it’s ‘unacceptable’ to miss daughter’s college move-in</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband says it’s ‘unacceptable’ to miss daughter’s college move-in</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cff39c20-0673-11f0-b760-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 16:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6f85051-0659-11f0-a97b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 13:39:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel chaos. Elon Musk. JFK files. Gaza war. Deportation flights. Loneliest places. Deep-sea critters. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9972f9f0-0643-11f0-b3b4-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interior Department to open millions of acres in Alaska to drilling and mining</title>
      <description>Interior Secretary Doug Burgum announced the department would allow oil and gas leases in 82 percent of the 23 million acre National Petroleum Reserve-Alaska, overturning protections President Joe Biden finalized last year. The department will also reinstate a program to allow drilling in the 1.56 million acre Coastal Plain of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, the country’s largest preserve of its kind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be78d7e0-05dc-11f0-9422-0000a1ace530</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A huge iceberg broke off Antarctica. What scientists found under it startled them.</title>
      <description>After an iceberg 19 miles long cracked off an Antarctic ice sheet on Jan. 13, scientists began investigating a swath of ocean that had not seen daylight in decades. The researchers believe they will be able to identify dozens of new species from the expedition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ea3830-05d8-11f0-a0ad-0000a1ace082</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 22:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says detained Georgetown researcher cannot be deported for now. The government accused him of spreading ‘Hamas propaganda.’</title>
      <description>The order comes three days after Indian national Badar Khan Suri was detained at his Virginia residence by agents with the Department of Homeland Security, part of an increase in the Trump administration’s detentions of people with legal status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a24c1670-05cf-11f0-b3b4-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 21:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House says executive order will reduce the Education Department, rather than shut it down as Trump had promised</title>
      <description>White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters that the executive order President Donald Trump plans to sign Thursday will not completely shut down the Education Department, which would require congressional action. A smaller version of the agency will continue to administer its “critical functions,” she said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967044b0-05a8-11f0-8e36-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 16:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American prisoner held by Taliban for 2 1/2 years is released after first-known high-level U.S. visit to Afghanistan since 2021</title>
      <description>The news of George Glezmann’s release came the same day the Taliban announced that Adam Boehler, President Donald Trump’s interim envoy for hostage affairs, had visited Kabul for talks. The visit marked the highest-level, publicly known U.S. engagement with Afghanistan since the Taliban takeover in 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65a90b60-05a7-11f0-bd0e-0000a1ace773</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 16:21:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Happy in life — until rich surgeon-artist-athlete sister walks in</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Happy in life — until rich surgeon-artist-athlete sister walks in</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ea3380-05a5-11f0-b3b4-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 16:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unredacted details from the JFK files expose CIA agents and operations the agency kept secret for decades</title>
      <description>On Tuesday, the Trump administration unveiled more than 2,000 documents related to the assassination of President John F. Kennedy. The files are dense with information experts already knew, but there are gems: an unveiled American asset who spied on Castro, an award recommendation for a Watergate burglar and CIA plans to infiltrate “revolutionary Arab groups.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4ffa2c0-0597-11f0-bf49-0000a1ace540</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 14:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rare statement from this person in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88125390-058f-11f0-947d-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 13:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s orders. JFK files. Ukraine ceasefire talks. Ben &amp; Jerry’s. Greenpeace. March Madness. Cosmic surprise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70017ca2-057a-11f0-9573-0000a1aced9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgetown University researcher detained by immigration authorities, lawyer says</title>
      <description>Badar Khan Suri, an Indian national who was in the United States legally, was detained outside his home in Arlington, Virginia, on Monday night by agents who identified themselves as immigration officers, his attorney told The Post. Suri was then brought to a holding facility in central Virginia before being taken to Louisiana. Department of Homeland Security officials alleged Suri was spreading “Hamas propaganda,” though his lawyer said he was innocent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dafe030-0533-11f0-8fd7-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 02:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security numbers and other private information unmasked in JFK files</title>
      <description>The personal data of more than 200 former congressional staffers and others was made public Tuesday in newly unredacted documents related to the assassination of John F. Kennedy in 1963. Many of the people whose information was published are still alive and therefore vulnerable to privacy theft and doxing. Experts say the release of the information might violate privacy laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee942360-0525-11f0-841d-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:54:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans for U.S. military to hold migrants who cross border illegally — a potential major shift in enforcement</title>
      <description>The administration is evaluating a proposal for the Pentagon to take control of a buffer zone along the southern border and empower the active-duty troops deployed there to temporarily hold migrants who cross into the United States illegally, according to five U.S. officials familiar with the deliberations. If enacted, the move would mark a major shift, giving the military its most direct role yet in President Donald Trump’s expanding enforcement mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f17c6e0-0507-11f0-8f31-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Environmental group Greenpeace ordered to pay Dakota Access Pipeline operator hundreds of millions in high-stakes defamation suit</title>
      <description>Greenpeace defamed Dallas-based Energy Transfer during protests over the pipeline that drew thousands to Cannon Ball, North Dakota, in 2016 and 2017, a jury decided Wednesday. The ruling is a massive financial blow to Greenpeace that activists say could chill free speech.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d279760-0500-11f0-841d-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 20:25:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky agrees to 30-day partial ceasefire between Ukraine and Russia after conversation with Trump</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky said “we are ready to implement” a halt on energy infrastructure attacks, a first step in what he hoped would be “lasting peace” more than three years after his country was invaded by Moscow. Zelensky’s approval comes a day after President Donald Trump had a separate, lengthy conversation with Russian President Vladimir Putin in an attempt to broker a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff2c16e1-04fa-11f0-b163-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 19:47:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve holds interest rates steady as high tariffs and inflation blur path ahead</title>
      <description>Central bankers are dealing with more unknowns in steering the economy as President Donald Trump ignites a trade war and stubborn prices weigh on growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41b0bca1-04ec-11f0-a853-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife watches TV during work, then complains about her productivity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife watches TV during work, then complains about her productivity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1847cbc1-04dc-11f0-8965-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 16:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Two FaceTiming diners are shut down by an annoyed observer</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Two FaceTiming diners are shut down by an annoyed observer</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">944cb130-04d3-11f0-be28-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 15:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
