<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 08:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to press South African leader on ‘genocidal rhetoric’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is likely to ask the country to increase protections for its White ethnic minority and exempt U.S. companies from laws intended to boost the economic power of Black South Africans during a meeting with its leader on Wednesday, according to a White House official.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55b492a0-35dc-11f0-b9d4-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:41:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth may already be too hot for the survival of polar ice sheets</title>
      <description>If Earth stays at its current levels of warming — below policymakers’ goal of 1.5 degrees Celsius — polar ice sheets may melt, causing seas to rise and displacing millions in coastal communities, a new study finds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51b5ea90-35d8-11f0-b938-0000a1ace0f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fate of Trump’s agenda rests with House GOP factions that call themselves the ‘five families’</title>
      <description>This week will test whether the factions can find compromises on policies including Medicaid and Biden-era energy tax credits to advance President Donald Trump’s big bill. Our reporting found which caucuses each Republican belongs to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24854ee1-35be-11f0-baad-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 21:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More say Metro is safe from crime, especially higher-income riders, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>As more people return to working in person, opinions of the Metro system’s safety are on the rise, a Washington Post-Schar School poll finds. While there’s no shift among riders whose households make less than $100,000 a year, the poll records a dramatic upswing in safety perceptions among those making at least $200,000 a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">284cf120-35b1-11f0-99f6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 19:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom unhinges over daughter’s blue-collar boyfriend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom unhinges over daughter’s blue-collar boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c3e6720-3598-11f0-a434-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An artist wanted to make flood risk visible. So he painted a mural.</title>
      <description>With climate science under attack, artists and others must engage the public on these issues. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dbdc610-3596-11f0-bff0-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 16:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House officials wanted to put federal workers ‘in trauma.’ It’s working.</title>
      <description>In interviews, more than 30 former and current federal workers told The Washington Post that mass firings and chaos have left them feeling devalued, suicidal and scared for themselves and the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d30e211-358c-11f0-8f3f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 15:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration's ‘self-deport’ proposal for Ukrainians, Haitians would spend foreign aid funds, bypass U.N.-affiliated group</title>
      <description>Draft internal documents reviewed by The Washington Post show the administration devised plans to spend up to $250 million earmarked for foreign assistance to fund a program focused on removing immigrants who left active conflict zones, including 700,000 Ukrainians and Haitians, and returning them to their country of origin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72468ee0-3583-11f0-9b5c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 14:05:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An attempt at a quick ascent in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19662a51-357f-11f0-986f-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 13:34:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Putin. Supreme Court. Ashli Babbitt. Biden theories. Brain-dead woman. Hurricane season. Debating AI. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b098320-3569-11f0-b253-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. says it will charge Democratic Rep. LaMonica McIver after confrontation outside N.J. immigration detention center</title>
      <description>McIver will be charged with assaulting, resisting and impeding law enforcement officers, said Alina Habba, the interim U.S. attorney for New Jersey.
McIver, two other Democratic House members and Newark Mayor Ras Baraka clashed with Department of Homeland Security officers while visiting an immigration detention center in Newark on May 9. Trespassing charges against Baraka will be dropped, Habba said in a statement on X.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f6d92d0-3516-11f0-868d-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 01:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden cancer diagnosis draws well-wishes, questions — and conspiracy theories</title>
      <description>Some Republicans and right-wing activists wasted little time asserting without evidence that President Joe Biden and his circle covered up the diagnosis. It's a reflection of the harsh political environment as well as revived questions and debate about Biden’s initial decision to seek reelection last year, and whether his inner circle concealed information about his health and cognitive decline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae06ea10-3506-11f0-af31-0000a1ace080</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 23:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration allows massive New York offshore wind project to restart</title>
      <description>The Interior Department lifted the stop-work order on a nearly $3 billion wind farm off New York's coast on Monday, according to New York Gov. Kathy Hochul (D), following her direct appeal to President Donald Trump. Equinor Renewable Americas President Molly Morris had said last week the company would be forced to cancel the venture within days if there was no sign from the administration of a possible resolution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80916940-3504-11f0-a3b8-000a1ace105c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 22:56:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These crypto millionaires secured an exclusive dinner with Trump</title>
      <description>Most of the investors who won a chance to attend President Donald Trump’s dinner party on Thursday remain publicly unknown. Others say they are going in hopes of shaping his views.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa128e30-34f4-11f0-9a8b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 21:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retired four-star Navy Adm. Robert P. Burke found guilty of bribery, becoming highest-ranking military officer convicted of a crime</title>
      <description>Burke, former vice chief of naval operations, was found guilty of steering work to a New York company in 2021 in exchange for a $500,000-a-year postretirement job.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1d1d4c0-34df-11f0-aa34-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge rules Trump lacked the authority to dismantle the U.S. Institute of Peace</title>
      <description>Administration officials and members of billionaire Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service — aided by local and federal law enforcement agencies — seized the privately owned headquarters of the U.S. Institute of Peace in March and removed its leaders. U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell said the institute is created by Congress and not part of the executive branch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0863d2c1-34da-11f0-a1a0-000a1aceb799</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration is set to pay nearly $5 million to family of Jan. 6 rioter Ashli Babbitt, who died during the attack</title>
      <description>Babbitt was shot by police while climbing through a window into the House speaker’s lobby. Her family had filed a wrongful-death lawsuit in early 2024, seeking $30 million. Lawyers for both sides earlier this month told a judge they had reached a settlement in principle, reversing the Justice Department’s earlier opposition in the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c2f2be1-34d6-11f0-a48d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Salvadoran prison became a political human zoo</title>
      <description>How a Salvadoran prison became a political human zoo</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df85cdb0-34d2-11f0-936f-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 17:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to cancel temporary protected status for nearly 350,000 Venezuelans</title>
      <description>The Biden administration had created the status for Venezuelan migrants in 2021 and 2023, finding that economic and political turmoil under the regime of President Nicolás Maduro made it too risky to deport migrants back to their home country. The Trump administration rescinded the status, alleging that the Venezuelans were a strain on local resources and represented a public safety threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bf11cb0-34cf-11f0-8e39-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:37:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Her fiancé is a ‘torrent of hostility’ before his morning coffee</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Her fiancé is a ‘torrent of hostility’ before his morning coffee</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c37dbf0-34ca-11f0-a48d-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 16:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police secretly monitored New Orleans with facial recognition cameras, a scope of surveillance with no known precedent in the U.S.</title>
      <description>More than 200 cameras operated by a nonprofit scanned city streets in search of suspects. After records requests from The Washington Post, officials paused the first known, widespread live facial recognition program used by U.S. police. The program may have violated municipal guardrails around use of the technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f0708d0-34c8-11f0-a336-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:45:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Paying attention to our villains’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>‘Paying attention to our villains’ in today’s On the Record</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26950d00-34b6-11f0-8405-0000a1acec60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 13:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s cancer diagnosis. Trump’s bill. Bridge crash. Gaza. Fertility clinic blast. Deadly storms. Atomic clock. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ad3c300-34a0-11f0-bcde-0000a1ace41c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tax and immigration bill clears hurdle after late-night House committee vote</title>
      <description>House GOP leaders worked through the weekend to win over a quartet of fiscal conservatives who voted last week to block Trump’s “One Big Beautiful Bill Act.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbd09fe0-345a-11f0-9836-0000a1ace85d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 02:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-European centrist defeats right-wing populist in Romanian presidential vote</title>
      <description>Bucharest Mayor Nicusor Dan held off nationalist firebrand George Simion in an election Sunday that was watched closely in Western capitals. European officials feared that Simion, who spoke of ending Romania’s support for Ukraine, would disrupt E.U. and NATO unity on confronting Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54a99b20-3443-11f0-ba8a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 23:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Washington quashes DEI, Anna Wintour has emerged as an unlikely activist</title>
      <description>The longtime editor in chief of Vogue is the mastermind behind the Met Gala and remains one of the most recognizable faces of the fashion establishment. But fashion, at the level where Wintour has long served as gatekeeper, and with its subjective assessment of aesthetics, has struggled more than most industries with diversity and inclusivity. In recent years, she has committed to make change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a19725b0-342f-11f0-97f9-0000a1ace448</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 21:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former president Joe Biden has been diagnosed with a 'more aggressive form' of prostate cancer, a spokesman says</title>
      <description>Biden was diagnosed on Friday, his office said in a statement posted on X. The statement said the cancer "appears to be hormone-sensitive which allows for effective management."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f7d8720-3426-11f0-9e1d-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 20:27:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s actions are pushing thousands of experts to flee government</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s workforce policies are fueling a voluntary exodus of experienced, knowledgeable federal workers unlike anything in living memory. The scores of departures will have immediate and long-term consequences, employees predicted, imperiling the quality of government services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51fbf730-340a-11f0-b10a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 17:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99596670-3401-11f0-9137-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 16:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which breakfast is highest in sugar? Test your knowledge with our quiz.</title>
      <description>Some of the most popular packaged breakfast foods can harbor surprisingly large amounts of sugar. Can you guess how much? The answers might surprise you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75210030-33f0-11f0-83f1-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">556116d0-33ec-11f0-95e2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexican navy sailboat collides with New York’s Brooklyn Bridge, injuring at least 3, police say</title>
      <description>Several videos showed the Cuauhtémoc sailboat’s two masts snapping after hitting the bridge’s deck. The Mexican navy said the incident occurred during a training cruise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c71bc3a1-3393-11f0-b2db-0000a1ace321</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 02:57:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EXCLUSIVE: Trump Justice Department considers removing key check on lawmaker prosecutions</title>
      <description>For years, lawyers in the Justice Department’s Public Integrity section have reviewed cases against elected officials to ensure they are legally sound and not politically motivated. Trump administration officials are considering changing that rule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c452c621-3373-11f0-9d97-0000a1ace596</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff cuts forced this forecast office to shut overnight. Then, a tornado hit.</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service office in Jackson, Kentucky, is one of a growing number of local forecast stations that can no longer operate around-the-clock since the Trump administration significantly reduced staffing levels. But as dangerous weather loomed Friday, meteorologists there knew they'd have to scramble to have all hands on deck.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c318620-335f-11f0-9e1d-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:42:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DOGE’s grand plan to remake Social Security is backfiring</title>
      <description>The agency is abandoning an initiative aimed at preventing fraud, the latest example of a failed effort by Elon Musk’s disruptive cost-cutting team. Many of the major changes DOGE pushed at Social Security have been dropped or are being reversed after proving ineffective, while others are yielding unintended consequences and badly damaging customer service and satisfaction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1522990-3348-11f0-9be1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My parents didn’t respect me as a landlord. So I asked them to move out.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My parents didn’t respect me as a landlord. So I asked them to move out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e652f6a0-3337-11f0-97f9-0000a1ace448</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The media firestorm engulfing Bill Belichick and his 24-year-old girlfriend, Jordon Hudson</title>
      <description>Hudson, a former college cheerleader and philosophy major from New England, became famous for dating and advising the 73-year-old Belichick, a six-time Super Bowl winner with the New England Patriots and North Carolina’s new coach. Their personal and professional partnership, combined with the public’s appetite for any crumb of information about both, has vaulted Hudson into prominence and controversy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5dba0aa1-3327-11f0-9133-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ffff1b0-3322-11f0-96fb-0000a1ace730</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:26:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 16 people dead in Missouri and Kentucky as severe storms sweep central U.S.</title>
      <description>At least seven people have died in Missouri and nine in Kentucky, authorities confirmed, as tornadoes, hail and thunderstorms hit the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74d01132-3318-11f0-b5ae-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 12:14:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Moore, the country’s only sitting Black governor, vetoes reparations bill</title>
      <description>The bill would have required Maryland to recommend ways to fix the economic harms to Black descendants of enslaved people. The governor’s rejection of the bill dealt a blow to reparations supporters who counted on him to be an ally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3b2e8b0-32a0-11f0-97e9-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court maintains block on some Trump deportations of migrants under use of wartime power</title>
      <description>A divided Supreme Court on Friday continued to block the Trump administration’s use of the Alien Enemies Act to deport migrants from Northern Texas to El Salvador and said administration officials had not given those targeted for removal last month sufficient time to challenge their deportations.

President Donald Trump’s use of the wartime power to target a Venezuelan gang is one of the most controversial parts of his mass deportation efforts, which have spurred increasingly tense standoffs between his administration and the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf72c800-3294-11f0-a19e-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. region until 10 p.m.</title>
      <description>Scattered thunderstorms are likely to move through the D.C. region, most likely between about 4 and 7 p.m. Some storms could produce large hail and damaging winds in addition to heavy rain and lightning. Follow the Capital Weather Gang for the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c147b370-328b-11f0-8851-0000a1acecbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Cheating ex is mad you’re dating author of book on infidelity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Cheating ex is mad you’re dating author of book on infidelity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d983c1-3274-11f0-9283-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP hard-liners stall Trump’s legislative package on taxes and immigration</title>
      <description>Five fiscal hawks on the House Budget Committee joined Democrats to sink a procedural vote that would have advanced the measure over concerns the legislation did not impose deep enough spending cuts. The vote is a significant, but not fatal, setback to the legislation that President Donald Trump hopes will define his second term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0dab4e1-3272-11f0-9571-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d647c20-325a-11f0-acf3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tour. Tariff bills. Supreme Court. Cassie Ventura. Tornado threats. Siri settlement. Medical breakthrough. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2bbf8a0-3244-11f0-b87c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new pope confronts the Catholic Church’s sexual abuse scandal amid praise and scrutiny of his record</title>
      <description>Survivor groups say Pope Leo XIV must embrace transparency in investigations of priests accused of abuse. His handling of past cases has some worried.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e204170-31d8-11f0-be39-000a1ace7054</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price tag for Trump’s June military parade could reach $45 million. Soldiers will be bunked in government office buildings in D.C.</title>
      <description>A massive military parade planned in Washington next month will cost an estimated $25 million to $45 million and will involve dozens of war planes, hundreds of Army vehicles and thousands of soldiers from across the country sleeping in downtown government office buildings, an Army spokesperson said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67f01890-31c2-11f0-9857-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center employees announce plans to unionize after Trump’s takeover</title>
      <description>A group of workers asked the National Labor Relations Board to oversee a union vote. They criticized leaders at the arts center for layoffs and a lack of transparency under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">159e5d20-31bf-11f0-b22b-0000a1ace800</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be fooled. This is the calm before the AI storm.</title>
      <description>The lull in the artificial intelligence revolution, thanks to cultural lag, is just temporary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ff11ef0-31b3-11f0-9e4e-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
