<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 02:23:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>An ‘anonymous, unidentified’ body was returned by Hamas instead of the body of hostage Shiri Bibas, IDF says</title>
      <description>Hamas had promised the remains of three members of the Bibas family, who had been taken hostage: Shiri and her two young children. The Israel Defense Forces said it identified the two sons, but not their mother.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">613932b0-eff1-11ef-8bd4-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 01:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to fire Postal Service board and let his administration control the U.S. mail system, officials say</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is expected to issue an executive order as soon as this week to fire the members of the Postal Service’s bipartisan governing board and place the agency under the control of the Commerce Department. Experts call the move legally questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d9fb8b0-efec-11ef-874e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department deletes database tracking federal police misconduct after a Trump executive order undid a Biden-era program</title>
      <description>The database was first proposed by Donald Trump in 2020 after the police killing of George Floyd, but it was enacted by the Biden administration. The DOJ deleted the database, which included thousands of disciplinary records of federal officers, after a Trump executive order negated the Biden-era program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21cea130-efdf-11ef-9079-000a1ace80c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects unions’ request to pause federal worker firings, clearing roadblock for Trump administration as it makes sweeping cuts</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Christopher R. Cooper, who was appointed by President Barack Obama, declined to issue a temporary restraining order pausing President Donald Trump’s moves to fire thousands of employees who are on probationary status or deemed nonessential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebfa68a0-efcf-11ef-9cbe-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel narrowly confirmed as FBI director, putting Trump loyalist atop storied law enforcement agency</title>
      <description>Katel, a former White House aide, faced fierce opposition from Democrats over his history of incendiary rhetoric and his calls for retribution against perceived enemies of President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9904441-efc0-11ef-b522-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spurs star Victor Wembanyama will miss rest of NBA season because of blood clot in his shoulder</title>
      <description>The Spurs announced Thursday that their 21-year-old phenom was diagnosed with deep vein thrombosis in his right shoulder after returning to San Antonio from this past weekend’s All-Star Game.

Wembanyama is one of basketball’s brightest young stars and is widely considered the future face of the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06877910-efb7-11ef-b44b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York sues Puff Bar, MYLE and other popular vape brands, accusing them of deceptively marketing to young people</title>
      <description>State Attorney General Letitia James alleged that the 13 companies fueled a public health crisis by promoting “deceptive and misleading” messages about e-cigarettes’ safety and breaking a state law banning flavored vapes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb30b9c0-efb2-11ef-bca8-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s separation isn’t public, but husband’s new ‘friend’ is</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s separation isn’t public, but husband’s new ‘friend’ is</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36cf8dc0-efac-11ef-ad09-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mitch McConnell will not seek reelection next year, according to a speech preview, ending his decades-long tenure in chamber</title>
      <description>“Representing our commonwealth has been the honor of a lifetime. I will not seek this honor an eighth time,” McConnell (R-Kentucky) said in a preview of a Senate floor speech shared with the Associated Press. McConnell, first elected in 1984, relinquished his Republican leadership post after last year’s elections. He has faced health challenges in recent years, including injuries from falls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f80f3640-efaa-11ef-b206-0000a1ace257</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This senator stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbc8c0c1-ef9b-11ef-b094-000a1acec8c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many of Trump’s actions in his first month are unpopular among Americans, a Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has opened his second term with a flurry of actions designed to radically disrupt and shrink the federal bureaucracy. But reviews from Americans are mixed to negative on many of his specific initiatives, and 57 percent say he has exceeded his authority since taking office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2f757f0-ef91-11ef-833c-0000a1ace35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Ukraine. Federal firings. Israeli hostages. Delta payout. Tomb discovery. New iPhone. ‘Doomsday’ fish. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa8b0a0-ef82-11ef-ae21-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration orders Pentagon to make plans for sweeping budget cuts, exempting border security and a select few programs</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has ordered senior leaders at the Pentagon and throughout the U.S. military to develop plans for cutting 8 percent from the defense budget in each of the next five years, according to a memo obtained by The Washington Post and officials familiar with the matter — a striking proposal certain to face internal resistance and strident bipartisan opposition in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef3cab20-eefa-11ef-aa4c-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Transportation Department revokes approval of New York City congestion pricing toll on drivers</title>
      <description>Transportation Secretary Sean P. Duffy said the toll, which went into effect in January in an effort to cut planet-warming emissions and fund improvements to the city's transportation system, was a “slap in the face to working class Americans.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f18c24f1-eef0-11ef-97ea-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74733971-eee3-11ef-88e1-0000a1ace156</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, without evidence, accuses Zelensky of being a ‘Dictator without Elections’ — echoing rhetoric from Russia</title>
      <description>The outburst is President Donald Trump's latest attack on Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and Ukraine, which previously had U.S. support in its fight against Russia's invasion. Many of Trump's recent criticisms of Zelensky have been previously made by Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">301e2930-eee1-11ef-b6e6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059f0c60-eedc-11ef-94d5-0000a1acecbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across the breadth of Africa, Islamist extremism is spiking, military coups are spreading and Russian influence is on the rise</title>
      <description>As these ominous forces converge, the stakes are high for the region, and the reverberations could be felt beyond its borders. Read the stories of a jihadist, a Russian mercenary, a defiant broadcaster and others, both African and outsider, who are shaping this new chapter of African history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4d24c0-eed6-11ef-8807-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A long-time cast member in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fad9970-eece-11ef-9d81-0000a1ace814</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Musk. Free coronavirus tests. Jair Bolsonaro. Delta crash. Hostage releases. A$AP Rocky. Favorite child. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">015060a0-eeb9-11ef-827b-0000a1ace794</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil charges former president Jair Bolsonaro with leading plot to seize power, kill political rivals</title>
      <description>Bolsonaro is accused of leading an extensive plot to overthrow the Brazilian government following his 2022 electoral loss, including an attempt to poison Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the country's current president, and participation in an armed criminal organization. The charges are a historic rebuke of a politician whose brash and aggressive form of politics dominated the country for years and left it deeply polarized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea4d3250-ee65-11ef-8bdf-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky found not guilty of two counts of felony assault with a semiautomatic firearm</title>
      <description>Rocky, whose legal name is Rakim Mayers, was accused of shooting at his former childhood friend A$AP Relli (Terell Ephron) twice outside a Hollywood hotel in November 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">869a19b0-ee5d-11ef-9ef8-000a1ace5d0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA is losing hundreds of employees. That could slow disaster response.</title>
      <description>The job cuts at the Federal Emergency Management Agency, which come in addition to the firing of more than 200 employees last week, targeted probationary and contract workers, and could affect people across the country who are struggling to prepare for disasters or rebuild. The FEMA firings were part of a wave of terminations of federal workers that took place over the holiday weekend and Tuesday, according to agency officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">450502e0-ee52-11ef-9d24-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Trump administration’s error-plagued firing spree, which dismissed thousands for ‘performance’ reasons without evidence</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke to more than 275 federal workers and reviewed dozens of government records to compile an account of the chaotic process, which swept up some long-serving employees, military veterans and people with disabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ded7760-ee4e-11ef-aa0e-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs of probationary Defense Department employees are expected soon as team from Musk’s DOGE arrives at Pentagon, officials say</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has directed defense agencies to turn over a list of such employees by the end of Tuesday, with the expectation that many could be laid off as soon as this week, people familiar with the matter say. The directive coincides with the arrival at the Pentagon of personnel from Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service, which has overseen the firing of thousands of probationary employees in other federal agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">479a9c80-ee3f-11ef-8200-0000a1ace34f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis has pneumonia in both lungs, Vatican says, as concerns grow over ‘complex’ infection</title>
      <description>Francis, who had part of one lung removed in his youth, was admitted to the hospital Friday. He has suffered from declining health and mobility for years, and his current hospitalization is his fourth since ascending to the papacy in 2013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b635b20-ee2f-11ef-9d24-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 19:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did all 80 people survive after a plane flipped on the Toronto runway? What to know about ‘crashworthiness.’</title>
      <description>Aviation experts say aircraft design and a fast response from the cabin crew helped everyone aboard the regional jet escape after it flipped upside down in the snow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d0cca31-ee21-11ef-b286-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend talks about marriage, but where’s the engagement?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend talks about marriage, but where’s the engagement?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9bdc361-ee19-11ef-97b0-0000a1acec50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. federal prosecutor resigns after declining to take part in Trump administration plan to freeze EPA grant funding</title>
      <description>Denise Cheung, head of the criminal division in the U.S. attorney’s office in D.C., resigned in protest Tuesday morning after she refused to aid in freezing assets of a multibillion-dollar Biden administration environmental grant initiative, according to two people who spoke on the condition of anonymity because they weren’t authorized to discuss it publicly.

Cheung’s departure comes on the heels of prosecutor resignations after orders to dismiss corruption charges against New York Mayor Eric Adams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50ddbe70-ee18-11ef-a0a9-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 16:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing a dance in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67ff6fb0-ee07-11ef-b87d-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta crash. Elon Musk. Ukraine talks. Pope Francis. ‘Gulf of America.’ Snow forecast. Lincoln Memorial. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81f95d1-edef-11ef-b4b7-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sorrow, hope and longing of Japan’s ‘Missing Post Office’</title>
      <description>The old post office is a repository for 60,000-plus pieces of mail: letters, birthday cards and New Year’s greetings sent from all over Japan to those with no forwarding address: Lost friends and pets; past and future selves; and, most frequently, the dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036b84b0-ed96-11ef-88ca-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 01:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Social Security official exits after clash with Musk’s DOGE over attempts to access sensitive data, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Billionaire Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service has pushed for sensitive records at the Social Security Administration, leading to the departure of its acting commissioner. The agency is responsible for managing pension payments for more than 70 million American seniors and manages significant troves of personal data, including those related to Americans’ work history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d2df432-ed8d-11ef-be6f-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All 80 people on Delta flight that crashed and turned upside down at Toronto airport have been evacuated from the plane, FAA says</title>
      <description>The regional jet departed Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport on Monday morning. What caused the aircraft to flip upside down on the tarmac remains unknown, but weather conditions at the time were harsh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf634bd0-ed81-11ef-bd40-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50b667c1-ed51-11ef-beb3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was a Jan. 6 juror. What she learned surprised her.</title>
      <description>When the jury summons for federal criminal court arrived in my mailbox in November 2023, Lauren Ober knew she had to answer it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3a3c91-ed4d-11ef-af96-0000a1ace410</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 16:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Presidents’ Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c435100-ed3c-11ef-9440-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 highlights from ‘Saturday Night Live’s’ sprawling and unexpectedly poignant 50th anniversary special</title>
      <description>The three-hour-plus broadcast was packed with A-list stars including Eddie Murphy, Tina Fey, Paul McCartney, Adam Sandler and many more, who paid tribute to its five-decade run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2d78aa0-ed37-11ef-a842-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Trump’s firings. Ukraine talks. Freed hostage. Deadly storm. Healthy drinks. SNL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae77c641-ed26-11ef-ab97-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Saturday Night Live’ 50th anniversary special starts soon. Join our reporters and critics for live insights, analysis and more.</title>
      <description>Luminaries including Adam Sandler, Eddie Murphy and Tina Fey will be on hand as the NBC staple celebrates a half-century of comedy. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db03900-ecc9-11ef-83ac-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s DOGE seeks access to personal taxpayer data, raising alarm at IRS</title>
      <description>The unusual request would put sensitive data about millions of American taxpayers in the hands of Trump political appointees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b479dd0-ecc5-11ef-a5f5-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relatives and records cast doubt on Guantánamo migrants being ‘worst of the worst’</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke with family members of six Venezuelan men being held in Guantánamo. Despite the impression given by Homeland Security officials, the migrants were taken into custody after crossing the border — not during a targeted immigration operation in a U.S. city or at a jail or prison while serving a sentence. The relatives firmly deny they are members of the Tren de Aragua gang.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4123b6b0-ecb5-11ef-8d6b-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mountain by any other name should still be Denali, Alaskans say</title>
      <description>Denali means “the great one,” and those living in the snow-shrouded midst of North America's tallest peak question why one of President Donald Trump's first actions was to rename it for a 19th-century predecessor who never set foot in Alaska.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5176beb0-ec9a-11ef-9366-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9fc3e90-ec89-11ef-8bbd-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was the deadliest workplace in America. So why didn’t safety regulators shut it down?</title>
      <description>Inspectors issued more than 100 safety violations and millions in fines. Yet deaths and injuries continued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9def47b1-ec83-11ef-b0ff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f48b790-ec73-11ef-ae3f-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful, potentially damaging winds possible in D.C. area this afternoon</title>
      <description>After downpours exit midday, very strong winds are expected in the afternoon, potentially gusting to 50 to 60 mph. The National Weather Service has issued a high wind warning until 10 p.m. and cautions that power outages are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">525dd1e0-ec6f-11ef-96d1-0000a1ace502</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stunning pattern of suicide blights one of the Marines’ most iconic jobs</title>
      <description>Marine Corps drill instructors are a national symbol of discipline. But for some, their imposing persona belies a dark reality, a joint investigation by The Washington Post and Military.com found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b61b10-ebf3-11ef-ba5c-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 23:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfdc7130-ebc5-11ef-ac36-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rejects Trump request for half of its rare-mineral wealth in exchange for continued U.S. assistance</title>
      <description>The offer and Ukraine’s consideration of it rippled through European diplomatic circles not only for its audacity but also because the war-ravaged country appeared to be seriously considering how to reach a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92f03a40-ebc0-11ef-ab97-0000a1ace20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
