<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 23:02:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Parkinson’s may begin in the gut, study says, adding to growing body of evidence</title>
      <description>The study, published in JAMA Network Open, found that people with upper gastrointestinal conditions — in particular, ulcers or other types of damage to the lining of the esophagus, stomach or upper part of the small intestine — were far more likely to develop Parkinson’s disease later in life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28bed370-6bd7-11ef-8873-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 22:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden pleads guilty to federal tax charges, could face hefty fine and prison sentence</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden’s son entered a last-minute guilty plea on the day jury selection was supposed to begin in his federal trial. He could face up to 17 years in prison and fines of up to $1.3 million, a judge in Los Angeles said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff447940-6bcd-11ef-8dd8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 21:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How does divorced parent adjust to having less time with son?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How does divorced parent adjust to having less time with son?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">151054f1-6bb1-11ef-a495-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Times publisher A.G. Sulzberger writes in an op-ed: The quiet war against press freedom could come to America. Here’s how.</title>
      <description>Some foreign leaders have ruthlessly curtailed journalism. American politicians could draw from their playbook, Sulzberger writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">224aecd0-6bab-11ef-9cc0-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden offers plea in tax case, in effort to avoid second criminal trial</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden’s son Hunter tried to resolve his federal tax case Thursday morning as jury selection was about to begin, offering an Alford plea in which he maintains he is innocent but acknowledges that the prosecution’s evidence would likely result in a guilty verdict.

The judge adjourned the court proceedings until 11 a.m. Pacific time so prosecutors could consider the plea offer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4c1370-6ba0-11ef-ab71-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fictional train in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">197bbaa0-6b8b-11ef-8c12-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugandan Olympic runner Rebecca Cheptegei dies after she was set on fire by her ex-boyfriend</title>
      <description>Cheptegei is the third high-profile athlete to be killed in a domestic violence incident in Kenya, where she was based.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ac69bf0-6b8a-11ef-8dd8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia school shooting. Liz Cheney. Trump hearing. U.S. Steel. Toxic plastic. Space spectacle. ‘Game of Thrones.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff2f72a0-6b75-11ef-8453-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FBI learned of Ga. high school shooting suspect a year ago and sheriffs had questioned the teen and his father, agency says</title>
      <description>FBI agents received anonymous tips over a year ago about online threats allegedly made by the suspect now accused of killing four and injuring nine others at Apalachee High School. Jackson County Sheriff's officers interviewed the teen suspect and his father, who said hunting guns were kept in the house but his son did not have unsupervised access to them. Local schools were alerted about the tips, the FBI said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86862070-6b1f-11ef-bb0f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liz Cheney, in a break with the Republican Party, says she will vote for Democratic nominee Kamala Harris</title>
      <description>Cheney, the former congresswoman who served as vice chair of the House committee that investigated the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, made the announcement in North Carolina, which is considered to be one of the battleground states that could help decide the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1802e0-6b10-11ef-b589-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 22:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia school shooting suspect in custody is a 14-year-old student; two students and two teachers were killed, officials say</title>
      <description>Police identified a teenager as the suspect in a shooting at Georgia’s Apalachee High School that killed four people Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379cea91-6aff-11ef-ace2-0000a1ace897</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is preparing to block Nippon Steel’s purchase of U.S. Steel in stunning move, people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>The move would formally block Nippon Steel’s proposed $14.9 billion acquisition of U.S. Steel, according to three people with knowledge of the matter, who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The proposed deal has been under investigation by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e57c0520-6ae5-11ef-b32c-0000a1ace78b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least two killed and several wounded in Georgia high school shooting, according to a law enforcement official</title>
      <description>Several others were wounded in the shooting at Apalachee High School, about 35 miles northeast of Atlanta. A suspect is in custody, the Georgia Bureau of Investigation said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a707a030-6ae3-11ef-b014-0000a1aceddf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the asteroids that scare scientists. Are we prepared for them?</title>
      <description>These are the asteroids that scare scientists. Are we prepared for them?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afb52e81-6ae0-11ef-a8f5-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89f20890-6ada-11ef-a089-0000a1aceb59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6820140-6ad6-11ef-a0b7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta’s oversight body says ‘from the river to the sea’ isn’t necessarily hate speech, a decision likely to fuel Israel-Gaza debates</title>
      <description>The company-funded oversight body ruled the social media giant shouldn’t automatically take down posts using the phrase, a decades-old rallying cry for Palestinian nationalism that has reignited debate about the boundaries of acceptable speech. The clash has forced the company to closely examine its content rules amid scrutiny from Jewish groups that have accused it of allowing antisemitism to surge and criticism from pro-Palestinian groups, which argue Meta has stifled political critique amid a deadly war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">201ec341-6ad5-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was pitched as ‘an extraordinary opportunity’ to protect the planet and people. The Post found deep failures.</title>
      <description>C-Quest Capital said its stoves could improve people’s lives and reduce carbon emissions. But an investigation by The Washington Post in Mozambique reveals that the company promised more than it could deliver — a further hit to a troubled offsets market used by BP, Shell and other major corporations to meet their climate goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc82a752-6ac7-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unsettling new milestone for this city in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb86c81-6ac1-11ef-a59a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian strike. Trump vs. Harris. Gaza talks. School cop. Landslides. Cellphone study. Titanic. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca02062-6aac-11ef-882a-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Foreign Minister Dmytro Kuleba resigns amid government shake-up</title>
      <description>Kuleba’s exit follows those of other high-ranking officials in Ukraine this week. Kuleba, who has been in the role since 2020, has been a key voice in Ukraine’s drive to receive foreign weapons and to push allies to loosen restrictions on how they are used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413b7d20-6a8f-11ef-8149-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A louder voice in fighting abortion bans: Men in red states</title>
      <description>Two years after the Supreme Court overturned federal protections for abortion, growing numbers of men in deeply conservative states are speaking out in defense of reproductive rights because of the harrowing experiences they’ve seen wives or partners go through when pregnancies went tragically awry.

They have an integral role in the debate, a legal expert says: “Men telling their own stories … is going to be a big way to change hearts and minds.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a68d420-6a42-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. charges Hamas leaders with terrorism, citing Oct. 7 attack, and is investigating killing of Hersh Goldberg-Polin</title>
      <description>Attorney General Merrick Garland stressed that Hamas was responsible for the Oct. 7 deaths in southern Israel and said the United States will investigate the killing of Goldberg-Polin, 23, whose body was found in Gaza last week, as an act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5e906f1-6a3e-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A school resource officer admitted to sexually abusing two students. A South Carolina judge just sentenced him to probation.</title>
      <description>Richland County Sheriff's Deputy Jamel Bradley kept his job for years despite multiple complaints of sexual misconduct with teen girls, a Washington Post investigation found. The judge ordered Bradley to register as a sex offender, against the recommendation of prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">783b3240-6a2e-11ef-8990-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab9fcb30-6a0d-11ef-8557-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Opinions asked seven writers to find an amazing story from deep within government. First up, Michael Lewis’s discovery.</title>
      <description>The 2024 conversation has been driven by a handful of names. Trump. Harris. Biden. Vance. Walz. These individuals have put themselves forward to lead our government. But who really is our government? What is it made of? And what is at stake when politicians say they want to expand or dismantle it? To find out, we set seven stellar writers loose on the federal bureaucracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7677a8c0-6a0c-11ef-aef7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Post investigation into Xi’s visit to San Francisco reveals how China extended its repression into a U.S. city</title>
      <description>Chinese diplomats and pro-China diaspora groups based in the United States organized demonstrations in San Francisco that harassed and silenced protesters opposed to Beijing’s policies, including through violence, during Chinese leader Xi Jinping’s visit to the city in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e85495e0-69fb-11ef-a90d-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new take on a head-scratching story in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b11935c0-69f8-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian president says at least 41 people killed in Russian missile strike at the Communications Institute in Poltava</title>
      <description>President Volodymyr Zelensky said 180 people were injured when two ballistic missiles struck. The Defense Ministry said the time between the alarm and the impact was so short that many people were caught trying to reach shelters and were trapped under the rubble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2987d1e1-69ec-11ef-8fde-0000a1ace008</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 12:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris-Biden rally. Israel protests. Seized plane. China crackdown. Coronavirus shots. ‘Spy’ whale. Paralympics. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf413f0-69e3-11ef-bbf2-000a1acef238</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your ride is here. Take a trip with Uber driver Jon Rigsby in this comic from the Shifts series.</title>
      <description>The loneliness of the short-distance driver</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a84d3320-6970-11ef-aa6e-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 21:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump helped spark a culture war with his 1776 Commission on patriotism</title>
      <description>In his final months in office, President Donald Trump’s aides resisted as the president sought to ban the New York Times’ 1619 Project from the nation’s classrooms. Instead, he created a new commission on patriotism – and launched a culture debate that would reenergize his base after he left office. The little-noticed episode helps explain how Trump might view education if reelected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35dc1190-695b-11ef-a4cc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband declares daughter, 15, will ‘always be an underachiever’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband declares daughter, 15, will ‘always be an underachiever’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cfc0e60-6946-11ef-9f43-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash of ‘dark’ tanker exposes the dangers of China’s thirst for cheap oil</title>
      <description>To bypass Western financial systems and shipping services, China relies on a fleet of aging, substandard tankers that operate illicitly, analysts say. The ships pose major safety threats and have alarmed global shipping groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab0f44b0-6941-11ef-be82-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A school cop was repeatedly accused of sexual misconduct with female students. He kept his job for years.</title>
      <description>In South Carolina, Richland County Sheriff’s Deputy Jamel Bradley continued working as a school resource officer despite multiple complaints that he was preying on teenage girls at Spring Valley High. Bradley, a former college basketball star, is now facing sex crime charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac8e32a0-6938-11ef-9f43-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origins of Labor Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c0f1870-692f-11ef-916c-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostage deaths. Trump vs. Harris. Far-right victory. Hotel strike. Elon Musk. Hot summer. Cash incentive. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77dca5f0-691a-11ef-9bdb-0000a1acef07</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., with Qatar and Egypt, preparing final ‘take it or leave it’ deal between Israel and Hamas</title>
      <description>The effort was underway before Israeli officials discovered the bodies of six hostages. But U.S. officials said the discovery adds new urgency to striking a deal, and that if Israel and Hamas do not agree to their final proposal it could mark the end of American-led negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb9eaf50-68ab-11ef-bc44-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What it’s really like to take the train from California to New York</title>
      <description>This summer, comic artist Christine Mi rode two Amtrak trains across 12 states and 3,397 miles, meandering her way alongside deserts, forests, mountains, rivers; through coal plants, suburban backyards, vast cornfields, and the occasional Big American City. See her illustrated Amtrak journey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a7892a0-6895-11ef-999d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 19:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters flood the streets of Israel, labor union announces general strike after recovery of six dead hostages in Gaza</title>
      <description>Families of hostages and their supporters are trying to pressure Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to agree to a deal with Hamas to bring home the remaining captives. The six hostages recovered by the military Saturday, including Israeli American Hersh Goldberg-Polin, were killed by their captors shortly before troops found them, Israel’s Health Ministry said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5d228b0-687f-11ef-b5db-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 16:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ce05b70-687b-11ef-8f1c-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 16:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you spend money like a Gen Z-er, millennial or boomer? Take our quiz to see which generation you align most with.</title>
      <description>Your spending says a lot about your income bracket and whether you have kids. But there are also generational influences — and a growing gap between how older and younger generations spend money. Take this quiz to find out if you spend money more like an 18-year-old, a 78-year-old or somewhere in between.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">596f9c40-686f-11ef-9261-0000a1acec99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbbc36f1-6865-11ef-9489-0000a1aceb06</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 13:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass polio vaccinations begin in Gaza amid limited pauses in fighting, U.N. says</title>
      <description>The campaign to vaccinate more than 600,000 children against polio began in Gaza on Sunday, the U.N. agency for Palestinian refugees and the World Health Organization said. Israel said it would allow a "humanitarian corridor" for vaccination personnel and designate safe areas for administering the shots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af74f960-683c-11ef-87d6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 08:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli American hostage Hersh Goldberg-Polin confirmed dead by family and White House</title>
      <description>The family of Hersh Goldberg-Polin, 23, who was kidnapped by Hamas on Oct. 7, said he had been killed. Their statement came after the Israeli military announced it had located a number of dead bodies in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27b9bdd0-6819-11ef-8aff-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists are finding biases built into the Marshmallow Test and other common predictors of children’s success</title>
      <description>Developmental psychology aims to elucidate the “universals” in how the human mind develops but has often gleaned those insights by studying White, middle-class children from Western countries. So, if a child from a poor family or different culture doesn’t perform well, is the fault in the child or the test?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">906ec7e0-67dc-11ef-adb2-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 21:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sexual harassment scandal dogged Corey Lewandowski. Now he’s officially back in Donald Trump’s fold.</title>
      <description>Lewandowski, Trump’s first 2016 campaign manager, was reported to the police by three women who alleged unwanted physical contact, including a GOP donor in 2021 whose claims led Trump to call her directly, she said. Trump’s decision to bring back Lewandowski this month as a senior adviser shows his high tolerance for allies with political liabilities as long as they remain loyal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d41ec1-67b7-11ef-8d9e-0000a1ace01f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My dad says my brother gets the family estate because of ‘tradition’</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My dad says my brother gets the family estate because of ‘tradition’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d61143b0-67b2-11ef-b4f0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reporter detailed tennis star Alexander Zverev’s alleged abuse of women — and is paying for it</title>
      <description>Accusations of emotional and physical abuse by Zverev — which he has repeatedly denied — cast a shadow over his ascent. But the resulting stories may have created more troubles for their writer, Ben Rothenberg, as he grapples with a costly lawsuit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5bb8750-67a5-11ef-b4f0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 14:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e974e80-679d-11ef-8c6e-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
