<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 14:03:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9f13fe0-ab5d-11f0-8735-0000a1ace9b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump aide John Bolton to make first court appearance in classified documents case</title>
      <description>The former national security adviser surrendered to federal officials in Maryland on Friday, a day after his indictment on charges that he mishandled classified materials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b59c280-ab5c-11f0-858b-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Bolton. Trump-Zelensky meeting. ICE surveillance. Shutdown deadlock. Venezuela. Fertility drugs. Roman mystery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14187a80-ab4f-11f0-8e80-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 11:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These two quick tests can tell you if you’re as fit as an 80-year-old elite athlete</title>
      <description>The tests require only a chair, a willing helper, a stopwatch and few spare minutes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ad18d50-aaed-11f0-b065-0000a1ace25c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Susan Stamberg dies at 87. A ‘founding mother’ of NPR, she helped blaze a trail for women in broadcasting.</title>
      <description>As a host of “All Things Considered,” she was the first woman to anchor a national nightly news program in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54c24dc2-aae8-11f0-9070-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 23:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ace Frehley, the galvanizing guitarist who helped make Kiss one of the biggest rock groups of the 1970s and ’80s, dies at 74</title>
      <description>Taking the blues rock of his favorite bands, Frehley imbued the group with energy and leaned into the theatrics as a performer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c463b3b0-aae0-11f0-a8e0-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top military officer central to Trump’s drug war to step down early</title>
      <description>Adm. Alvin Holsey has served as the head of U.S. Southern Command for less than a year. The position typically rotates every three years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ba460e0-aade-11f0-8e19-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 22:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former national security adviser John Bolton indicted for allegedly mishandling sensitive documents</title>
      <description>Bolton is the third long-time target of President Donald Trump to be charged in a month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99b59140-aad3-11f0-82b6-0000a1acec03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:03:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chamber of Commerce sues Trump to block $100,000 fee for H-1B visas — its first legal action against the administration this term</title>
      <description>The powerful business group is alleging that President Donald Trump’s changes to the immigration pathway widely used by Silicon Valley are illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee9b7b30-aacd-11f0-bbdc-000a1acef288</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump unveils plan to make IVF and fertility drugs more accessible and affordable, a key campaign pledge</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump made broadening access to in vitro fertilization a 2024 campaign pillar as he looked to make up for losses among female voters in the aftermath of Roe v. Wade’s fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6a6d270-aacb-11f0-9458-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: How big will the ‘No Kings’ protests be this weekend? Our chief political correspondent takes your questions.</title>
      <description>Happening now: How big will the ‘No Kings’ protests be this weekend? Our chief political correspondent takes your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e5d6e40-aaae-11f0-a32e-0000a1ace0b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I resigned from the military because of Trump</title>
      <description>I could not swear to follow a commander in chief who seems so willing to disregard the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69f7ff90-aaad-11f0-aeb8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be dad goes bungee jumping, comes home to furious wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be dad goes bungee jumping, comes home to furious wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5265bec0-aaa9-11f0-a276-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Special Operations copters fly less than 90 miles from Venezuela, suggesting possible preparation for missions inside country</title>
      <description>The U.S. military’s elite Special Operations aviation unit appears to have flown in Caribbean waters near the coast of Venezuela in recent days, according to a visual analysis by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a456491-aaa0-11f0-ac88-0000a1ace758</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be ‘weak’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cbb0ed3-aa94-11f0-910d-0000a1aceb7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘It broke me’: Inside the FBI hunt for the online predators who persuaded a 13-year-old to kill himself</title>
      <description>How the suicide of a child from Washington state launched a years-long global investigation to find an elusive online user called “White Tiger,” with one FBI agent saying he encountered brutality and bureaucratic hurdles in the case that challenged him in ways he’d never faced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2051c050-aa8b-11f0-8dd6-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 12:24:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown layoffs. Voting maps. Pentagon. Venezuela pressure. Medicare portal glitches. ‘Quality’ jobs. Fitness test. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">518b2f50-aa7f-11f0-8dd6-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s team made a Medicare doctor directory a priority. It launched with errors, The Post found, setting off a scramble.</title>
      <description>The directory, intended to help older Americans navigate Medicare Advantage open enrollment, produces conflicting responses about which providers are covered by health plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aba10ea0-aa2b-11f0-853d-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 01:01:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public executions. Hunting rival gangs. Hamas launches a new, violent campaign to reassert control over Gaza.</title>
      <description>Amid the ceasefire with Israel, Hamas is sending a message that it remains the only visible authority in Gaza, with huge implications for President Donald Trump’s peace plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13aa4020-aa22-11f0-8739-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 23:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he has authorized covert CIA action in Venezuela</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Wednesday that he had authorized the Central Intelligence Agency to conduct operations in Venezuela, markedly escalating U.S. pressure on President Nicolás Maduro amid a string of lethal strikes against alleged drug trafficking boats in Caribbean waters off that country’s coast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0a182a0-aa1d-11f0-b1ff-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 23:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No amount of alcohol is safe if you aim to avoid dementia, a new study suggests</title>
      <description>The finding comes from the data of more than 550,000 adults and genetics information from 2.4 million study participants. It adds to emerging evidence that a drink or two a day isn’t risk-free.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">429ddaa1-aa12-11f0-b1cb-0000a1ace61b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 21:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teens avoided incarceration for attacking a former DOGE staffer. Trump officials quickly asserted the penalty was too lenient.</title>
      <description>Two teens arrested in connection with the attempted carjacking of a former U.S. DOGE Service staffer in August were sentenced to probation. White House press secretary Karoline Leavitt and U.S. Attorney for D.C. Jeanine Pirro swiftly revived the Trump administration’s criticism that young people who commit crimes in D.C. do not receive harsh enough punishments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07dc73f0-aa02-11f0-beb3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders Trump administration to pause layoffs during government shutdown</title>
      <description>Senior U.S. District Judge Susan Illston temporarily blocked the Trump administration’s plans to lay off thousands of federal workers during the shutdown, siding with unions that have argued the dismissals were illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1296d852-a9f6-11f0-bb89-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems open to limiting a key section of the Voting Rights Act that allows the use of race to draw legislative maps</title>
      <description>A ruling that eliminates or severely cuts back Section 2 of the Voting Rights Act would most likely lead to a decline in the number of minorities holding public office. It would also touch off a scramble to redraw electoral maps across the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4720d511-a9ee-11f0-9cb4-0000a1ace18b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:42:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgetown University names Eduardo M. Peñalver as its next president. Here are 4 things to know about him.</title>
      <description>Peñalver, 52, is the president of Seattle University, also a Jesuit institution. Georgetown’s board of directors chose him after a search to replace longtime president John J. DeGioia, who stepped down last November to recover from a stroke.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a3e45b0-a9e9-11f0-b5a5-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Will my husband’s long-distance job ruin our marriage? Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice.</title>
      <description>Will my husband’s long-distance job ruin our marriage? Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7c8a7f0-a9e0-11f0-acb1-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it America’s fate to decline and fall? History offers signs — and solutions.</title>
      <description>Is it America’s fate to decline and fall? Here’s what history says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35dff930-a9de-11f0-88e3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say goodbye to Post food critic Tom Sietsema in his final dining chat</title>
      <description>After 25 years, The Washington Post’s food critic is stepping down, so get in your last questions and comments now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">262f9cd0-a9d8-11f0-b16d-0000a1acef57</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A turtleneck kind of gal in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ffa3f72-a9cb-11f0-8b85-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza’s future. Venezuela strike. Charlie Kirk. Utility bills. Alcohol and dementia. D’Angelo. Uncrustables dupe. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18713620-a9b6-11f0-b117-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six recession warning signs to watch: Thrifting is up, but cardboard boxes are down</title>
      <description>The United States is not in — or even near — a recession, despite so many “indicators” online. But the economy is in an uncertain place. Here’s what you really need to pay attention to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dfb7f60-a94d-11f0-9a7e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 22:30:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. kills six alleged drug smugglers in new strike off Venezuela, Trump says</title>
      <description>The operation follows Senate Republicans’ narrow defeat of a measure that aimed to prevent the administration’s actions on legal grounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61ee8db1-a935-11f0-8415-0000a1ace235</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D’Angelo dies at 51. The visionary musician helped pioneer the neo-soul movement, releasing acclaimed albums such as ‘Voodoo.’</title>
      <description>The cause of death was cancer, according to a statement from his family. Born Michael Archer, D’Angelo helped launch a new era for R&amp;B, nodding to an old-school soul sound while incorporating notes of funk, hip-hop and jazz. Dubbed “neo-soul” by his music manager, the subgenre became a mainstay of 1990s pop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a995b880-a91e-11f0-b267-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it rude when one partner walks too fast for the other?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it rude when one partner walks too fast for the other?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c0dd360-a917-11f0-9a7e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gen Z slang is everywhere. Test your knowledge of teen talk with this quiz.</title>
      <description>Today’s teen slang is more absurd, global-reaching and irony-laden, thanks to TikTok.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec519380-a912-11f0-a3f4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects Alex Jones’s bid to set aside $1.4 billion verdict for defaming Sandy Hook families</title>
      <description>Jones, a conspiracy theorist and founder of InfoWars, had asked the justices to pause the award and take up an appeal of the civil case against him. He was found liable in 2022 of falsely claiming that the 2012 mass killing at Sandy Hook Elementary School in Connecticut was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57051d20-a90c-11f0-ac09-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:44:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterfly in the sky in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eee0010-a902-11f0-a734-0000a1ace51b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. saved him from the Taliban. Trump wants to send him back.</title>
      <description>He supported the American war, escaped Afghanistan and started a family in the United States. Then Immigration and Customs Enforcement arrested him, and if he is deported, he expects the Taliban to kill him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d7c9a90-a8f4-11f0-8b94-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 11:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s victory lap. Shutdown impact. Pentagon press. Heath insurance. Coastal storm. Pot science. Shoulder stretch. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee26e500-a8ec-11f0-86e7-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite reversal of hundreds of CDC layoffs, federal biodefense workers are among health staff who still lost jobs, officials say</title>
      <description>Officials have reversed more than half of the about 1,300 layoff notices sent to staff at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, sparing personnel who were leading the response to measles outbreaks in the United States and an Ebola outbreak abroad. But details emerged about the other health workers who lost their jobs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cecfd460-a88c-11f0-95c3-0000a1ace322</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microplastics are everywhere. You can do one simple thing to avoid them.</title>
      <description>The biggest sources of microplastics have one thing in common, scientists say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed41c9b0-a87f-11f0-8a31-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prominent news outlets reject Pentagon’s press policy before signing deadline</title>
      <description>The Washington Post joined the New York Times, CNN and the Atlantic in refusing to sign the policy, which says that reporters cannot obtain or solicit any information that the Defense Department does not explicitly authorize.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47654651-a868-11f0-aa48-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A surge in retirements is putting huge strains on the government as it deals with a shutdown and layoffs</title>
      <description>The mass exodus — unprecedented in its scale — includes 154,000 federal employees who accepted buyout offers and were largely removed from the payroll as of the end of last month. Some of those are among nearly 105,000 employees who took regular retirement during the fiscal year that ended in September, an 18 percent surge from the previous year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f734f1d0-a844-11f0-a453-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 14:57:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remembering Sister Jean in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">155464e0-a839-11f0-8956-000a1acedd61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 13:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declares 'dawn of a new Middle East,' celebrating return of all living hostages to Israel</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is addressing the Israeli parliament after Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu called him “the greatest friend that the state of Israel has ever had in the White House.” All 20 living hostages have been returned to Israel from Gaza, and Israel has begun releasing Palestinian prisoners and detainees. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5822f6d0-a828-11f0-be19-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 11:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostage release. Shutdown impacts. Blue states. Deadly explosion. Gender pay gap. AI videos. Longevity tips. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5000540-a823-11f0-b976-0000a1ace930</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel prize in economics awarded to trio for their work explaining creative destruction in innovation, growth</title>
      <description>The Nobel Memorial Prize in Economic Sciences was awarded to Joel Mokyr of Northwestern University, Philippe Aghion of College de France, INSEAD and the London School of Economics, and Peter Howitt of Brown University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd8bb080-a81c-11f0-81fc-0000a1acec81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 10:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas releases first seven Israeli hostages as swap brokered under ceasefire deal gets underway</title>
      <description>The group, who were handed over to the International Committee of the Red Cross, are among the last living captives in Gaza about two years after Hamas-led militants attacked Israel, unleashing Israel’s destructive war in the Gaza Strip</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4a43800-a7fa-11f0-a643-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 06:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A conservative influencer was arrested in Portland. The president was watching.</title>
      <description>After Nick Sortor was arrested earlier this month outside an Immigration and Customs Enforcement facility in Portland, Oregon, President Donald Trump latched on to justify a federal crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d88c1e0-a7b6-11f0-a9c2-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 21:56:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The pain from the government shutdown is about to hit the public</title>
      <description>Americans are bracing for the worst effects of the ongoing shutdown to collide with the U.S. economy this week as missed paychecks and the absence of billions of dollars of government services sink in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b250f40-a791-11f0-b844-0000a1ace9f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 17:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
