<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 04:01:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Moore, the country’s only sitting Black governor, vetoes reparations bill</title>
      <description>The bill would have required Maryland to recommend ways to fix the economic harms to Black descendants of enslaved people. The governor’s rejection of the bill dealt a blow to reparations supporters who counted on him to be an ally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3b2e8b0-32a0-11f0-97e9-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 21:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court maintains block on some Trump deportations of migrants under use of wartime power</title>
      <description>A divided Supreme Court on Friday continued to block the Trump administration’s use of the Alien Enemies Act to deport migrants from Northern Texas to El Salvador and said administration officials had not given those targeted for removal last month sufficient time to challenge their deportations.

President Donald Trump’s use of the wartime power to target a Venezuelan gang is one of the most controversial parts of his mass deportation efforts, which have spurred increasingly tense standoffs between his administration and the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf72c800-3294-11f0-a19e-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 20:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. region until 10 p.m.</title>
      <description>Scattered thunderstorms are likely to move through the D.C. region, most likely between about 4 and 7 p.m. Some storms could produce large hail and damaging winds in addition to heavy rain and lightning. Follow the Capital Weather Gang for the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c147b370-328b-11f0-8851-0000a1acecbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 19:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Cheating ex is mad you’re dating author of book on infidelity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Cheating ex is mad you’re dating author of book on infidelity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d983c1-3274-11f0-9283-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP hard-liners stall Trump’s legislative package on taxes and immigration</title>
      <description>Five fiscal hawks on the House Budget Committee joined Democrats to sink a procedural vote that would have advanced the measure over concerns the legislation did not impose deep enough spending cuts. The vote is a significant, but not fatal, setback to the legislation that President Donald Trump hopes will define his second term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0dab4e1-3272-11f0-9571-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 16:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d647c20-325a-11f0-acf3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tour. Tariff bills. Supreme Court. Cassie Ventura. Tornado threats. Siri settlement. Medical breakthrough. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2bbf8a0-3244-11f0-b87c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new pope confronts the Catholic Church’s sexual abuse scandal amid praise and scrutiny of his record</title>
      <description>Survivor groups say Pope Leo XIV must embrace transparency in investigations of priests accused of abuse. His handling of past cases has some worried.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e204170-31d8-11f0-be39-000a1ace7054</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 22:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Price tag for Trump’s June military parade could reach $45 million. Soldiers will be bunked in government office buildings in D.C.</title>
      <description>A massive military parade planned in Washington next month will cost an estimated $25 million to $45 million and will involve dozens of war planes, hundreds of Army vehicles and thousands of soldiers from across the country sleeping in downtown government office buildings, an Army spokesperson said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67f01890-31c2-11f0-9857-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center employees announce plans to unionize after Trump’s takeover</title>
      <description>A group of workers asked the National Labor Relations Board to oversee a union vote. They criticized leaders at the arts center for layoffs and a lack of transparency under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">159e5d20-31bf-11f0-b22b-0000a1ace800</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 19:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t be fooled. This is the calm before the AI storm.</title>
      <description>The lull in the artificial intelligence revolution, thanks to cultural lag, is just temporary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ff11ef0-31b3-11f0-9e4e-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 17:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears divided over limiting block on Trump’s birthright citizenship order</title>
      <description>It remains unclear how the high court will resolve the issue, with several liberal justices asserting that President Donald Trump’s order to deny automatic citizenship for U.S.-born babies is blatantly at odds with more than 100 years of Supreme Court precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">778ce130-31ad-11f0-b145-000a1ace00cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:55:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How does she tell her boyfriend he needs to make his own friends?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How does she tell her boyfriend he needs to make his own friends?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fc20091-31aa-11f0-a9fb-0000a1ace028</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:32:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former interim D.C. U.S. attorney Ed Martin is under an ethics investigation in D.C., he says in officewide goodbye email</title>
      <description>On Wednesday, his last day before starting a new job at the Justice Department, Martin alerted his office’s roughly 350 attorneys and 400 staff members to the matter while claiming his confidentiality had been violated. President Donald Trump last week announced he was replacing Martin with Fox News host Jeanine Pirro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15836f00-31a7-11f0-bb63-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court is hearing arguments on lower-court rulings blocking Trump’s birthright citizenship order. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has asked the justices to scale back the nationwide injunctions to apply only to the pregnant women, immigrant advocacy groups or states that challenged the ban — which opponents say conflicts with the Constitution, past court rulings and the nation’s history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb415890-3197-11f0-a60c-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin judge pleads not guilty, seeks to throw out charges that she interfered with an immigration arrest</title>
      <description>Milwaukee County Judge Hannah Dugan entered her not guilty plea to charges that she blocked the arrest of a Mexican immigrant as she argued that federal officials had no power to prosecute her. FBI Director Kash Patel announced her arrest last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d578050-3196-11f0-b6ef-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 14:09:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another name change in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef55e1c0-3190-11f0-8bfb-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 13:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden book. Trump’s tour. Supreme Court. Cassie Ventura. Overdose deaths. Wildfire smoke. Chimp first aid. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bddfbae0-317b-11f0-b68e-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA is offering to pay weather forecasters to fill critically understaffed teams as hurricane season looms, emails show</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service is scrambling to fill 155 vacancies, including in coastal Texas and Louisiana, according to notices obtained by The Washington Post. An estimated 500 agency employees have been fired or taken early retirements this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8350dc0-30f9-11f0-b241-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 19:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland’s credit rating drops amid worries about the impact of federal spending cuts and an economic slump</title>
      <description>The downgrade of the state's triple-A bond rating by Moody's comes after a similar downgrade of D.C.'s bonds in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c231890-30f2-11f0-8a5d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:38:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders release of Georgetown University researcher who Trump administration alleged was a threat to foreign policy interests</title>
      <description>Badar Khan Suri has been held in a Texas immigration detention center since his arrest in March. He is expected to be returned promptly to Virginia after the ruling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14349d60-30e2-11f0-8a32-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House bans U.S. from any work related to G-20 in South Africa after Trump threatens boycott over unfounded 'genocide' claims</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump had already publicly threatened to boycott the summit of the world's largest economies over claims of persecution against White South Africans. The South African government has rejected the Trump administration’s accusations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd0997f1-30df-11f0-a92b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom worries about older neighbor kids who misbehave around her own</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom worries about older neighbor kids who misbehave around her own</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d32d38e0-30dc-11f0-b6a6-0000a1ace589</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotline between National Airport and Pentagon has been disconnected since 2022, FAA official says at air safety hearing</title>
      <description>A hotline connecting air traffic controllers at Washington National Airport and their counterparts at the Pentagon has been “inoperable” since March 2022, Franklin McIntosh, the Federal Aviation Administration's deputy head of air traffic control, testified at a Senate committee hearing Wednesday. Questions of coordination between the airport and the Defense Department have been a key focus since the Jan. 29 midair collision of an Army helicopter and passenger jetliner that killed 67 people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cff0a850-30d8-11f0-a601-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:33:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Are headsets a solution to noisy restaurants? Debate with others in our chat.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Are headsets a solution to noisy restaurants? Debate with others in our chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfca0a51-30d4-11f0-a65f-0000a1acecdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 15:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star witness Cassie Ventura testifies about alleged beatings by Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs as his trial continues. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Ventura is back on the stand to deliver more testimony about alleged physical abuse and sexual assault by her ex-partner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3213350-30ce-11f0-b83a-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 14:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The land of the midnight sun’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05cbcc1-30c7-11f0-8bb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 13:32:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump in Qatar. Tariff rollback. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Menendez brothers. Combs trial. Storms. Cannes red carpet. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">941213d0-30b2-11f0-b209-0000a1ace492</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA plans to weaken rule curbing 'forever chemicals' in drinking water</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to rescind and reconsider limits on four different “forever chemicals” under a landmark drinking water standard implemented last year by President Joe Biden, according to documents reviewed by The Washington Post. The limits were adopted as part of the Biden administration’s efforts to limit public exposure to per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances (PFAS), hazardous chemicals linked to a range of serious illnesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e90ae4f0-3069-11f0-9fec-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 02:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Buttigieg, eyeing a presidential run, says ‘maybe’ Biden hurt Democrats</title>
      <description>The former Biden administration official spent Tuesday in Iowa, where he suggested he would look at running in 2028. In his highest-profile public appearance since leaving government, Buttigieg also warned not to “hang back” against President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcd827e0-3068-11f0-a72b-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 02:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Menendez brothers resentenced to 50 years to life with immediate parole eligibility</title>
      <description>A state parole board will consider whether to recommend that Erik and Lyle Menendez be released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d14d6f11-305d-11f0-b594-00000a1ace07</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 00:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cassie Ventura recounted coercive ‘freak-offs’ with escorts, and other key moments from Day 2 of the Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs trial</title>
      <description>Ventura testified that Combs coerced her into participating in days-long drug- and sex-fueled parties with male escorts, which Combs allegedly filmed and directed down to the smallest details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932727f0-304c-11f0-9e7a-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 22:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB reinstates Pete Rose, ‘Shoeless’ Joe Jackson and other deceased players, making them eligible for Hall of Fame</title>
      <description>Commissioner Rob Manfred ruled that MLB’s punishment of banned individuals ends with their deaths. The decision comes months after President Donald Trump said he would issue a “complete pardon” to Rose, who died last year at 83.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13cc5501-303a-11f0-91a2-0000a1ace0df</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The big changes in Trump and Republicans’ giant tax and immigration bill, from Medicaid cuts to taxes on college endowments</title>
      <description>Hearings are underway in House committees as the GOP tries to move ahead with legislation to extend tax cuts, reshape the economy and fund the White House’s immigration crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a993e10-3025-11f0-90c5-0000a1acef6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces U.S. will remove all sanctions against Syria to give the country ‘a chance at a greatness’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s remarks, delivered from Saudi Arabia, garnered a standing ovation from Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman and others. “Oh, what I do for the crown prince,” Trump mused after some of the applause had died down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12050580-3019-11f0-878f-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:41:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Career-dazed college student wonders how people choose their jobs</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Career-dazed college student wonders how people choose their jobs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0a42f31-3014-11f0-8466-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What these Pennsylvania factory workers are saying about Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Business is flourishing at this furniture maker, but even here workers want certainty — and lower prices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e897cde0-3013-11f0-8fa5-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 16:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star witness Cassie Ventura testifies that arguments with Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs often ended in physical abuse. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Ventura has alleged years of abuse and sexual exploitation during her relationship with Combs, who faces 15 years to life in prison if convicted on all counts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff4b4870-300c-11f0-8c52-0000a1ace502</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 15:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving away money in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac6c9042-2ffe-11f0-a12e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 13:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation rose in April compared to March but the annual pace eased, in a first test of Trump’s economic policies</title>
      <description>The consumer price index rose at an annual rate of 2.3 percent for April, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics. Inflation has eased in recent years but remains above the Federal Reserve's goal of 2 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a297ec0-2ff7-11f0-bc7b-0000a1ace820</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatar's gift of luxury jet to Trump would be a security problem, experts say</title>
      <description>The luxury jet was moved five weeks ago to San Antonio International Airport, suggesting that preparations for improvements to the plane might already be underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3f5f1b0-2ff3-11f0-9062-0000a1ace349</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Middle East trip. Trade war. White South Africans. Hostage release. Diddy trial. Humidity. Biological age. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68b39391-2fe9-11f0-a422-0000a1ace182</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>French film star Gérard Depardieu found guilty in sexual assault case</title>
      <description>The 76-year-old actor was convicted of groping two women during the filming of “Les Volets Verts” (“The Green Shutters”) in 2021 in a landmark moment for France’s #MeToo movement. Depardieu had rejected the accusations during the four-day trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">193ecc40-2fd9-11f0-b35e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:03:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mavericks win NBA draft lottery, earning right to select top prospect Cooper Flagg with No. 1 pick next month</title>
      <description>Dallas won the lottery drawing in Chicago on Monday night, and it is widely expected to draft Flagg, the 18-year-old Duke product who has long been considered the best draft-eligible player available this year. The draft is June 25 and 26 in New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08ad3740-2f89-11f0-b662-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 23:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hidden ways Trump and DOGE are shutting down parts of the federal government</title>
      <description>Limits on spending have incapacitated parts of agencies as varied as the National Park Service and the Pentagon, according to interviews with federal employees and records reviewed by The Washington Post. At the Environmental Protection Agency, according to three employees, research at 11 laboratories has ground to a halt because of a requirement that Trump officials must approve all new lab purchases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4a0f30-2f74-11f0-9127-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 21:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-China tariff reprieve powers Wall Street, lifting the S&amp;P 500 more than 3 percent higher</title>
      <description>Markets are “uttering a huge sigh of relief” after the two nations agreed to lower most tariffs for 90 days and signaled plans for continuing talks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">322f27d0-2f6c-11f0-9cdd-000a1ace0145</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 20:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hidden engine behind American innovation is being destroyed. We might not notice until it’s gone.</title>
      <description>Why destroy the funding that made the U.S. a leader in technology and invention?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b4c2bc0-2f66-11f0-bdc1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 19:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White South Africans arrive in U.S. to resettle across 10 states as refugees, a status Trump has suspended for all other groups</title>
      <description>The order allowing Afrikaners to enter the United States on allegations of racial discrimination restarts a refugee resettlement program that has seen most funding halted in recent months. They landed at Dulles International Airport and will board connecting flights to be resettled in various states, according to three government officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">230d1f30-2f5a-11f0-b7fc-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 17:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas releases last living U.S. hostage Edan Alexander from captivity in Gaza</title>
      <description>The 21-year-old dual national was abducted while serving in the Israeli military on Oct. 7, 2023. Hamas said it was releasing Alexander as a step toward a lasting ceasefire with Israel, following talks with the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e536c8a0-2f4f-11f0-b2bb-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:41:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to shut down an in-law who thinks her meanness is funny?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to shut down an in-law who thinks her meanness is funny?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58481611-2f4a-11f0-bdf9-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 16:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
