<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Harris’s interview. Trump campaign. FBI problems. Polio vaccinations. Covid risk. College football. Chatty monkeys. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">013e9500-66bf-11ef-b9cd-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris pledges to name a Republican to her Cabinet if elected in her first major interview since Biden dropped out of the race</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris said such a move would reflect her interest in a variety of views.

“I have spent my career inviting diversity of opinion,” Harris told CNN in an early excerpt of an interview that was set to air in full later Thursday night. “I think it’s important to have people at the table when some of the most important decisions are being made that have different views, different experiences.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b24fb40-6650-11ef-b96c-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 21:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches are in effect for large parts of the area into tonight</title>
      <description>Storms could produce damaging wind gusts, hail and areas of flooding. The severe thunderstorm watch covers much of the area, while the risk of flooding is highest west of Fairfax and Montgomery counties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ecdaae0-6643-11ef-8116-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Divorce complicates kids’ visits to their dying grandfather</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Divorce complicates kids’ visits to their dying grandfather</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0273b9e0-6620-11ef-9bb0-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army defends Arlington National Cemetery staffer who it says was ‘abruptly pushed aside’ by Trump campaign aides</title>
      <description>In a statement Thursday, Army officials said the employee “acted with professionalism” when she sought to enforce regulations that prohibit partisan political activity on cemetery grounds. The employee has decided not to press charges, Army officials said.

The former president was at the cemetery to mark the third anniversary of a suicide bombing that killed 13 U.S. troops in Afghanistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f2b4970-661d-11ef-b69f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years after Larry Nassar scandal, FBI is still falling short at handling child sex abuse cases, internal Justice Dept. report finds</title>
      <description>A new inspector general report found the FBI still often fails to quickly notify local authorities about alleged sexual abuse cases in their jurisdictions. In one especially egregious example, a suspect allegedly victimized another minor for 15 months after the FBI became aware of the allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98b2cb70-6617-11ef-a0db-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vladimir Kara-Murza’s first column since release from Russia: ‘My first thought was that I was going to be led out to be executed’</title>
      <description>Kara-Murza, who won the Pulitzer Prize for commentary in 2024, was imprisoned in Russia in 2022. He was released this month as part of the largest international prisoner exchange since the Cold War.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49036b20-6612-11ef-bf2c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 14:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A gut-sy solution that could help the environment in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0078b9c0-660b-11ef-aabf-0000a1acec38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 13:31:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump at Arlington Cemetery. Student loans. Telegram. Listeria. Hurricane season. Emmett Till. Venomous sea worms. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da2f4aa0-65f5-11ef-8391-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police officer critically wounded in shooting near DC-295 in Northeast Washington, authorities say</title>
      <description>The officer was shot in the head and remained in critical condition on Wednesday after attempting to retrieve a firearm from around a storm drain on DC-295 South, according to two public safety officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba25820-65a6-11ef-90b3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 01:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Trump visit sparked turmoil at America’s most sacred cemetery</title>
      <description>Federal law specifically prohibits election-related activities at military cemeteries. But during a visit, former president Donald Trump's aides pushed past an Arlington National Cemetery official to film footage they later released as a campaign video on TikTok.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c43f020-659d-11ef-842b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 00:24:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Journalist withheld details about Emmett Till’s killing, according to documents shared with The Post ahead of their public release</title>
      <description>William Bradford Huie’s research notes, newly released to The Washington Post and Mississippi Today, show he suspected more than two men tortured and killed the 14-year-old, but suggest that he left out those details when they threatened his story published in Look magazine in 1956.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83341f40-658d-11ef-bb75-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 22:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. soars to record high of 101 degrees, one of the three hottest days so late in the season on record</title>
      <description>The high of 101 broke the previous Aug. 28 record of 99 from 1948 amid the District's third hottest summer to date. Only two other days on record have reached at least 101 later in the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18fce801-6588-11ef-a3aa-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 21:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram CEO Pavel Durov is indicted on charges of complicity in distributing child porn and is forbidden to leave France</title>
      <description>French prosecutors indicted the chief executive of popular messaging service Telegram Wednesday on charges including complicity in the distribution of child sex abuse images, aiding organized crime and refusing lawful orders to give information to law enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fbf5390-657c-11ef-bdf6-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 20:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-politician found guilty of murdering Las Vegas Review-Journal reporter Jeff German</title>
      <description>Robert Telles was accused in the September 2022 stabbing of German, who had reported stories critical of Telles’s performance as Clark County public administrator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c565aee0-6571-11ef-a79b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 19:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court refuses to allow Biden’s latest student loan repayment plan as litigation continues</title>
      <description>The justices declined to clear the way for the Biden administration’s new student loan repayment plan for now, adding to uncertainty about the future of a program that would affect millions of borrowers. Biden introduced the program, Saving on a Valuable Education, last fall after a divided high court rejected a different effort by his administration to offer student debt relief.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">139c52e0-656c-11ef-a020-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 18:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Scofflaw in-law is ‘outraged’ to be banned from family lake house</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Scofflaw in-law is ‘outraged’ to be banned from family lake house</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5ee9780-6556-11ef-a4a6-0000a1ace9c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 16:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medics say at least 10 Palestinians have been killed during a major Israeli military operation in the West Bank</title>
      <description>Israeli officials said counterterrorism operations began overnight in several areas of the occupied West Bank, including the city of Jenin. Residents in the area of the raids described drones overhead, armored personnel carriers on the streets and Israeli forces making house-to-house arrests.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac20f761-6552-11ef-bbee-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why does it always take forever to get my check? Our food critic is taking your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why does it always take forever to get my check? Our food critic is taking your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">530e8650-654e-11ef-ae5c-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheating at the Paralympics? Athletes say some competitors lie about their levels of disability.</title>
      <description>As the Paralympic Games begin in Paris today, athletes say the system that is intended to ensure equitable competition is easily manipulated and that the governing bodies charged with oversight are more concerned with silencing allegations of dishonesty to preserve the inspirational themes of the Paralympics than they are with safeguarding fair play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9a3ca0-654a-11ef-a79b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 14:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Something's rumbling in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de996850-6541-11ef-a23f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 13:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump charges. Presidential debate. West Bank. Mosquito virus death. ISP hack. Mask ban. Paralympics. Catch up now</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c83779e0-652c-11ef-ae3a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden approved troubled Gaza pier mission despite internal pushback and warnings, inspector general finds</title>
      <description>The humanitarian operation, halted last month after numerous setbacks, was set in motion earlier this year despite warnings from within the U.S. government that rough seas could pose significant challenges, and objections from officials who feared it would detract from a diplomatic campaign to make Israel open additional land routes into the war zone, according to an inspector general report published Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff352bd0-64ce-11ef-ad49-0000a1ace1c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 23:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas calls itself the ‘most pro-life state’ in the country. But moms there keep dying.</title>
      <description>The challenges to maternal and infant health in Arkansas, a state that strictly bans abortion, are particularly daunting in its southeast corner. There, in timber country, doula Hajime White is among the women trying to help both newborns and their mothers survive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18e9b160-64c8-11ef-9ba8-0000a1ace593</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 23:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat advisory and air quality alert for D.C. area on Wednesday</title>
      <description>Temperatures could climb to record-challenging highs of close to 100 degrees and it will feel as hot as 105 to 109 with the humidity, according to the National Weather Service.
In addition, the Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments has issued a code orange air quality alert, which means the air is expected to be unhealthy for sensitive groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d7506f0-64bc-11ef-9b14-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 21:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith files new indictment against Trump in case involving alleged conspiracy to obstruct 2020 election</title>
      <description>The move comes in the wake of a Supreme Court ruling granting broad immunity to presidents for official acts, and just before a window when Justice Department policy would counsel against such a move so close to the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d92a1ee0-64b1-11ef-8b58-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 20:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adulteration and mislabeling are rampant in the avocado oil industry, scientists say, including brands sold at large retail chains</title>
      <description>Scientists at the University of California at Davis found that at least 21 products labeled as avocado oil — nearly two-thirds of the 36 bottles they tested— were adulterated, in some cases with other oils that could pose a hazard to people with food sensitivities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">283bc0f0-64a9-11ef-9ed2-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 19:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.H. resident dies from mosquito-borne eastern equine encephalitis, or EEE, as some New England towns restrict activities</title>
      <description>The death from the viral illness is the first in New Hampshire since 2014. In neighboring Massachusetts, some towns have closed parks after dusk and limited outdoor events because of the threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7612e40-64a2-11ef-8527-0000a1ace7d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 18:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What if AI helped artists make music? Listen to some of the ways it can provide inspiration.</title>
      <description>Here's why musicians are smart to embrace AI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e175e450-6491-11ef-b330-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump adds Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and Tulsi Gabbard, two former Democrats, to his transition team</title>
      <description>Kennedy ended his independent presidential campaign Friday and endorsed Donald Trump, appearing with him at a rally in Arizona. Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman from Hawaii, backed Trump during a joint appearance Monday in Michigan. She ran for the Democratic presidential nomination in 2020 but left the party two years later. Both will help prepare for a possible second Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1410a1f1-648f-11ef-b330-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:11:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family leaves Thanksgiving invitation hanging for months</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family leaves Thanksgiving invitation hanging for months</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4d13f0-648d-11ef-ae63-0000a1ace59c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese government hackers have penetrated several U.S. internet providers to spy on users</title>
      <description>The unusually aggressive and sophisticated attacks on at least two major providers with millions of customers suggest Beijing has “dramatically stepped up” its hacking efforts, a former top U.S. cybersecurity official said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f51151d0-647c-11ef-b73e-000a1ace384b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 14:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropping out in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81138d10-6478-11ef-8cec-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli troops have rescued a hostage held in Gaza since Oct. 7, military says</title>
      <description>Kaid Farhan al-Qadi, 52, was kidnapped from his security job at Kibbutz Magen’s packing factory during Hamas’s attack on Israel. The Israeli military said Qadi is being transferred for medical checks at a hospital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d91ab50-6476-11ef-8cec-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 13:14:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris endorsements. Trump cases. Gaza aid. Telegram arrest. Yacht investigation. Oasis reunion. World records. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a17eb3f0-6463-11ef-8527-0000a1ace7d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the 50 megadonors pumping $1.5 billion into the election</title>
      <description>From billionaire investors to shipping magnates and cryptocurrency firms, these megadonors skew Republican, though they affiliate with both parties. Here are the people and groups making the biggest donations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">999afa30-63f6-11ef-b502-0000a1acecfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Smith appeals Judge Cannon’s decision to toss out Trump indictment in classified documents case</title>
      <description>Jack Smith’s appeal said U.S. District Judge Aileen M. Cannon’s ruling “conflicts with an otherwise unbroken course of decisions, including by the Supreme Court ... and it is at odds with widespread and longstanding appointment practices in the Department of Justice and across the government.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca089fa0-63e8-11ef-9265-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 20:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Russia invaded Ukraine, a crew of workers spent three weeks trapped at Chernobyl. Serhii Plokhy tells their story.</title>
      <description>When a 12-hour shift turned into three weeks at Chernobyl</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ee9f2c0-63dc-11ef-a336-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 18:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Prince George’s County Council member Mel Franklin pleads guilty to theft scheme and perjury</title>
      <description>The Democrat faces up to one year of incarceration under a plea agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1bacab0-63cf-11ef-aa88-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 17:23:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: When parents divorce, does school-year timing matter for the kids?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: When parents divorce, does school-year timing matter for the kids?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a851b50-63c4-11ef-a0b4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram founder Pavel Durov’s arrest is linked to site’s inability to moderate ‘child sex crimes,’ French police say</title>
      <description>Durov was arrested in France for allegedly failing to moderate illegal child abuse activity on the messaging app, according to a police official. His arrest renews ongoing debate over free speech on social media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3bc714d1-63c3-11ef-9666-0000a1ace59f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some new flight attendants face homelessness and hunger: ‘You’re just barely surviving’</title>
      <description>In interviews with 18 current or former flight attendants, workers recounted dire financial situations, with starting salaries as low as $23,000. They shared similar stories: Earning much less than expected. Quickly falling behind on bills. Spiraling into debt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c4d4e20-63bd-11ef-ad99-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 15:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singing goodbye to Sphen in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Hed: Singing goodbye to Sphen in today’s On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2de2620-63af-11ef-8b1d-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Harris debate. Hezbollah. Germany stabbing. Yacht probe. Mosquito disease. Stranded astronauts. Cow burps. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">618cb720-639a-11ef-a578-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump event at a border wall built during the Obama administration highlights an unkept promise</title>
      <description>Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump came to Montezuma Canyon in Arizona on Thursday to heap praise on “the Rolls-Royce of walls,” as he called it. But the partition he praised was actually built during the Obama administration. Nearby lay piles of extra rusting pieces procured during the Trump administration but never erected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dadf220-632c-11ef-bf13-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 21:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists may have found a radical solution for making your hamburger less bad for the planet</title>
      <description>Cows produce more greenhouse gas emissions than the entire aviation industry. These researchers believe they can slash those emissions using gene editing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7212371-6313-11ef-bf33-000a1ace5f8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 18:55:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These jobs didn’t exist a generation ago. What can they tell us about the future? Get Shifts, a new comic series, to find out.</title>
      <description>An illustrated history of the future of work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77b1ebf1-6305-11ef-9a67-0000a1ace3c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 17:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ee40f0-62fb-11ef-bab3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:04:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Europe’s most dangerous volcano reawakens, Italians wonder if they need to flee</title>
      <description>Scientists are debating the peril posed by the Phlegraean Fields volcano, thought to have caused the most violent eruption of prehistoric Europe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8afa2900-62f3-11ef-a9b3-0000a1acedd3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 15:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a89a6f2-62e6-11ef-bf53-0000a1ace761</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
