<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39a80a92-d1e7-11f0-b0b8-000a1ace43bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netflix to buy Warner Bros. Discovery in $83 billion cash-stock deal</title>
      <description>The largest streaming network says it will purchase Warner Bros.’ studios and streaming assets after winning a bidding war with Comcast and Paramount.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">709c57f0-d1dc-11f0-a2cf-0000a1ace4d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat strike. Redistricting fight. Pipe bomb suspect. Trump’s ballroom. Pesticides. Social media ban. Black Death. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e510f830-d1d1-11f0-a431-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video shows a second U.S. military strike on alleged drug smugglers hit before survivors could flip boat, lawmakers say</title>
      <description>The footage was shown on Capitol Hill, where Adm. Frank M. Bradley faced a day of difficult questions about the deadly operation he oversaw.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8c17480-d16c-11f0-aab1-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court hands Trump a victory in fight over Texas congressional map</title>
      <description>The court has cleared the way for a voting map in Texas that could allow Republicans to win up to five additional seats in the House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9247e850-d16a-11f0-9259-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury refuses to reindict Letitia James in mortgage fraud case</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had sought a new indictment in Virginia after a judge had dismissed a case against the New York attorney general last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3f36af0-d168-11f0-841b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 23:28:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland House speaker steps down from role where she made history</title>
      <description>Adrienne A. Jones was the first Black person and first woman to lead the Maryland House of Delegates. She said it was time for a new generation to lead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80632b50-d15a-11f0-841b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 21:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Signalgate’ report contradicts Hegseth’s claim of ‘total exoneration’</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s actions “created a risk to operational security,” according to an independent assessment publicly released Thursday by the Pentagon’s inspector general.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff5cca40-d152-11f0-a3f8-0000a1ace0b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump replaces architect he handpicked to design his $300 million White House ballroom</title>
      <description>It is unclear whether James McCrery II stepped back voluntarily. The president has chosen architect Shalom Baranes, who has been designing and renovating government buildings in Washington for decades, to continue the project, according to two people familiar with the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06b98080-d14e-11f0-a3c5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 20:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ominous maps of a falling fortress city reveal a change in Ukraine war</title>
      <description>Putting Russia’s campaign to capture Pokrovsk into perspective.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4bc40f0-d13a-11f0-82db-0000a1ace604</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:57:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friends refuse to disclose why they’re divorcing after 20 years</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friends refuse to disclose why they’re divorcing after 20 years</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b24c8c0-d133-11f0-8dd5-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing a fashion deal in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">222985a1-d12f-11f0-ae7a-0000a1acefdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kiss’s Gene Simmons: Congress, I have a plea for you</title>
      <description>Long ago, broadcast radio helped bands like Kiss break through. Today, that business model is broken.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4641b30-d127-11f0-b896-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 15:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI arrests suspect in investigation of pipe bombs planted near RNC and DNC headquarters night before Jan. 6</title>
      <description>Federal officials have arrested a man who is believed to have planted the pipe bombs, according to three people familiar with the matter. The arrest could bring closure to a mystery that has vexed law enforcement for five years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a8ed6e0-d11e-11f0-855c-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 14:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s road safety plan has failed. This woman’s death reveals why.</title>
      <description>U.S. officials encouraged cities to adopt Vision Zero to save lives, but driver opposition and a lack of money derailed it. The program has foundered in city after city, according to an examination of pedestrian death data by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33cf1df0-d117-11f0-9311-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth scrutiny. Trump pardon. Vaccine vote. Syria brutality. Pedestrian deaths. Amazon delivery. Airport pajamas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba51ec40-d108-11f0-acac-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data management giant Palantir deepens its ties to ICE as its CEO forms an alliance with Trump on immigration</title>
      <description>Palantir’s software is helping U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement track undocumented immigrants and deport them faster, according to federal procurement filings and interviews with people who have knowledge of the project. CEO Alex Karp, formerly an outspoken Democrat who a decade ago said that he respected “nothing” about Donald Trump, has staunchly defended the president’s immigration policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6442a40-d0a8-11f0-8ad6-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dozen former FDA commissioners condemn plans to tighten vaccine approvals, warning of risks to Americans’ health</title>
      <description>The former Food and Drug Administration leaders wrote they were “deeply concerned” with new plans the nation’s top vaccine regulator, Vinay Prasad, laid out in a leaked internal email Friday. They argued that his approach could delay the arrival of vaccines better matched for evolving viruses, make it too expensive for new shots to come to market and slow the expanded approval of vaccines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1019d130-d094-11f0-8f63-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor sentenced to 30 months in prison over Matthew Perry’s death from ketamine</title>
      <description>Salvador Plasencia, who pleaded guilty in July to multiple drug charges in connection to the “Friends” star’s death, was sentenced Wednesday. He was initially charged alongside four others in 2024 after an investigation into Perry’s fatal overdose at age 54 the previous year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad8b7031-d090-11f0-8ac5-0000a1ace08b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 21:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth violated security protocols designed to protect U.S. troops in ‘Signalgate’ affair, top Pentagon watchdog finds</title>
      <description>The inspector general inquiry centers on Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s use of the unclassified commercial messaging app Signal to share highly sensitive U.S. attack plans, according to four people familiar with the findings. The report, due to be released Thursday, appears certain to reignite an issue that has dogged Hegseth for much of his tenure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">364cc330-d08a-11f0-8c32-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 20:54:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will pardon Democratic Rep. Henry Cuellar of Texas. He was charged with bribery, money laundering and conspiracy.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump says he will also pardon Cuellar’s wife, Imelda. The couple’s indictment detailed a bold corruption scheme in which Henry Cuellar, one of the most conservative Democrats in the House, allegedly promised to wield his power to advocate for his benefactors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35f39bf0-d064-11f0-be61-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 16:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security launches immigration sting in New Orleans, the latest in a series of sweeps nationwide</title>
      <description>City residents had anticipated the operation, particularly immigrants. Some businesses had closed while others posted signs saying, “ICE not welcome here.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58711850-d060-11f0-9f69-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:54:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College football drama in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa98cfd0-d05e-11f0-b1bc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 15:42:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration pause. Pete Hegseth. Special election. Kids’ vaccines. Cold records. Lonely Americans. Blocking the sun. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ffc9ea0-d03f-11f0-987d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican wins Tennessee special election in Trump country, as Democrats gain ground</title>
      <description>GOP nominee Matt Van Epps defeated Democrat Aftyn Behn in Tennessee’s ruby-red 7th Congressional District, the Associated Press projected. The contest, which became more competitive than initially expected, was the latest test of voter attitudes about President Donald Trump’s agenda and Democrats’ response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee5a5210-cff1-11f0-8177-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 02:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holocaust museum gets the pen that was used to save dozens of children at Auschwitz</title>
      <description>Erno Spiegel’s fountain pen was a subtle weapon in the fight for survival in a Nazi concentration camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68dc6d42-cfd7-11f0-89c1-0000a1ace580</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 23:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump rails against Somali migrants: ‘I don’t want them in our country’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump ended a Cabinet meeting Tuesday with a rant against Somali migrants, accusing them of having “ripped off” Minnesota and using dehumanizing language to attack a group he has increasingly targeted in recent weeks. The president’s comments came amid reports that his administration is ramping up immigration enforcement efforts targeting undocumented Somali immigrants in the Minneapolis-St. Paul area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70d01b10-cfcc-11f0-b361-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 22:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This moral slum of an administration is sickening, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Regarding Venezuela, Ukraine and much more, Trump and his acolytes are worse than simply incompetent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71a634f0-cfba-11f0-956e-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard shooting suspect charged with murder, assault offenses</title>
      <description>U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro has said the suspect, Rahmanullah Lakanwal, will face additional charges as the investigation continues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07126d80-cfaf-11f0-b84e-0000a1ace080</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents at odds over ‘wicked smart’ teen who’s behind in four APs</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents at odds over ‘wicked smart’ teen who’s behind in four APs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77fd35a1-cfa2-11f0-bcc3-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A D.C. wedding in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff0ca0a0-cfa0-11f0-96d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.’s vaccine advisers plan biggest change yet to childhood schedule</title>
      <description>The new chair of the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices says the panel is preparing this week to vote to end universal hepatitis B vaccination at birth and to examine whether childhood shots are triggering allergies and autoimmune disorders. Public health groups accuse the group of spreading misinformation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b42f670-cf97-11f0-92be-000a1ace15b3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former president of Honduras freed from U.S. prison after Trump pardon</title>
      <description>Juan Orlando Hernández had been sentenced last year to 45 years in prison after being convicted in a U.S. court of running a “narco-state” that helped send South American cocaine to the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4468ece0-cf91-11f0-ba66-000a1ace0166</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:12:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth. Alina Habba. D.C. shooting suspect. ‘Everywhere chemicals.’ TSA fee. Buy now, pay later. Olivia Nuzzi. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">668d6b43-cf76-11f0-9d6e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth tries to distance himself from boat strike fallout as White House emphasizes admiral’s role</title>
      <description>The Washington Post reported exclusively Friday that Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth gave a spoken order to kill the entire crew of a vessel thought to be ferrying narcotics in the Caribbean Sea. When two survivors were detected, the military commander overseeing the operation, Adm. Frank M. Bradley, directed another strike to comply with Hegseth’s order that no one be left alive, people with direct knowledge of the matter told The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9826ad20-cf20-11f0-9c56-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 01:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House revealed its pared-back Christmas display — with a Trump LEGO portrait and ‘Be Best’ baubles</title>
      <description>In her first holiday back in charge of White House decor, first lady Melania Trump presented a straightforward, even understated — at least by White House standards — look. The tour route differs from years past because the traditional entrance has been leveled to build President Donald Trump’s 90,000-square-foot ballroom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0114b2a0-cf12-11f0-96d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TSA will begin charging a $45 fee for travelers without a Real ID or passport starting Feb. 1</title>
      <description>Monday’s announcement urges travelers to pay the $45 fee online before they travel. The Transportation Security Administration is working with partners to offer pay-in-advance options, the news release says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbbf0b40-cefb-11f0-bb7b-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 21:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The alleged National Guard shooter once served in an elite CIA-backed unit. But his life unraveled as a refugee in the U.S.</title>
      <description>The course of Rahmanullah Lakanwal’s journey from a trusted U.S. battlefield ally to the suspected shooter of two National Guard members on the streets of downtown D.C. remains unclear, in part. But like many Afghans who had worked for the United States and came to this country after the chaotic August 2021 U.S. withdrawal from Afghanistan, he appeared to struggle to adapt to his new circumstances.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">825dbea0-cef0-11f0-9c56-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 20:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Gay parents of biracial child ‘overthink’ a private school option</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Gay parents of biracial child ‘overthink’ a private school option</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e0805f1-ced8-11f0-83cf-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump unlawfully appointed his former attorney Alina Habba to serve as top prosecutor in New Jersey, appeals court rules</title>
      <description>The decision could have far-reaching implications for other controversial Trump appointments that have been challenged in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a845eb0-ceca-11f0-a0f7-0000a1ace187</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A top aide resigns in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a51d6a0-cec2-11f0-96d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ozempic is changing how we spend money and time, plus what we eat</title>
      <description>As people’s bodies change through the use of GLP-1s, so does their spending across industries including fashion, restaurants, gyms and travel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3732ce70-cebe-11f0-80cb-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth. ICE raids. California shooting. Deadly floods. Vaccine approvals. Ozempic habits. Hungry microbes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a5023c0-cead-11f0-a070-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lane Kiffin will take over as LSU's football coach following days of drama</title>
      <description>He became a hovering theme of the latter part of the college football season as his future at Mississippi became uncertain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56052a20-ce2b-11f0-8873-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 20:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5115e9e0-ce0e-11f0-b3a1-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 17:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under Pete Hegseth, the Defense Department has been pulled into Trump’s efforts to punish political foes</title>
      <description>In threatening to deploy the military justice system against Democrats, the secretary of defense has joined President Donald Trump’s norm-shattering bid to punish adversaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f76f24e0-ce05-11f0-a40a-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4afb2850-cdf9-11f0-b36e-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House panel joins Senate in launching bipartisan inquiry of Pentagon over Hegseth's order to kill boat strike survivors</title>
      <description>The Senate and House armed services committees’ pledge followed a Washington Post report revealing that Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth ordered that a U.S. strike leave no survivors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01fb6940-cd8a-11f0-baad-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playwright Tom Stoppard dies at 88. His works were among the most acclaimed and oft-performed of the past half-century.</title>
      <description>Stoppard, a Czech-born British dramatist, explored political, artistic and scientific questions — often with mash-ups of high and low culture. His most popular works include Tony Award-winning plays “Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead,” “Travesties” and “The Real Thing.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcd24950-cd49-11f0-80b0-0000a1ace17d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my parents I didn’t dump my boyfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my parents I didn’t dump my boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09fe2220-cd46-11f0-baad-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
