<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 00:03:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will seek to define his legacy and explain his campaign exit in an Oval Office address. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Speaking to the nation for the first time since leaving the presidential race, President Biden plans to defend his record and describe his vision for his remaining six months in office.

The speech also will allow Biden to more fully explain his decision to step aside in the 2024 election and endorse Vice President Harris to lead the Democratic ticket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecb43130-4a17-11ef-a16c-0000a1ace6f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 23:53:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies producing millions of dollars of carbon offset credits in the Amazon routinely use public land they have no right to</title>
      <description>A six-month Washington Post investigation reveals that many carbon credit ventures have repeatedly and, authorities say, illegally laid claim to publicly protected lands, generating enormous profits and then failing to share the revenue with those who protected or lived on the land. The use of such lands to sell credits also contributes little to reducing carbon emissions, even though carbon credits are considered one of the world’s most important tools in the fight against climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09cb58d0-4a08-11ef-b13d-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 21:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lewis H. Lapham dies at 89. The innovative editor revived Harper’s magazine and wrote books and essays skewering upper-class excess.</title>
      <description>During two stints as the top editor at Harper’s, he turned the magazine into what he called a “theater of ideas,” promoting emerging voices such as David Foster Wallace, Christopher Hitchens and Fareed Zakaria. After retiring from the magazine in 2006, he founded his own publication, Lapham’s Quarterly, devoting each issue to a single subject.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d93d4e60-49fa-11ef-ba97-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 20:25:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu addresses a Congress divided on Israel-Gaza war as event draws throngs of protesters. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s speech spotlights the disagreement between Republicans and Democrats in their approach to one of America’s closest allies amid a devastating war in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d4d0f90-49e7-11ef-b38d-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 18:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump gunman Googled ‘how far away was Oswald from Kennedy’ before rally shooting, FBI director says in testimony</title>
      <description>FBI Director Christopher A. Wray told lawmakers the gunman who tried to assassinate former president Donald Trump had conducted a Google search seeking information on John F. Kennedy’s assassination. Wray also said the gunman used a rifle with a collapsible stock, which may have helped him conceal the weapon until he was on the roof where he opened fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2480ac60-49dc-11ef-9e25-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents’ clash over child’s screen time is affecting their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents’ clash over child’s screen time is affecting their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fb4f080-49d6-11ef-9a26-0000a1ace833</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Can Trump stop Biden’s campaign funds from going to Harris? Our politics reporters are taking your 2024 questions.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters Colby Itkowitz, Tyler Pager, Yvonne Wingett Sanchez and Michael Scherer are answering your questions about what’s next for Vice President Harris and the Democratic Party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d150741-49ce-11ef-b8a8-0000a1ace5cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 15:07:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: 7 options for Kamala Harris’s VP pick, in rough order of who makes the most sense for the ticket</title>
      <description>There will be a premium on a proven commodity and someone who can help Harris. That points to a handful of names, including Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro, Arizona Sen. Mark Kelly and North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61d91170-49c7-11ef-8986-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 14:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An album and a presidential candidate in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f97e9e0-49c1-11ef-b5ae-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris campaign. Secret Service. Netanyahu visit. Delta chaos. Carbon credits. Yellowstone eruption. ‘Dark oxygen.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db190520-49ab-11ef-8d9e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Mayall dies at 90. Known as the godfather of British blues, he helped shape 1960s rock through his band the Bluesbreakers.</title>
      <description>A multi-instrumentalist who sang and played guitar, keyboards and harmonica, Mayall was better known as a bandleader who had a superb eye for talent and a steadfast devotion to the purity of the blues. No fewer than seven members of his groups have been named to the Rock &amp; Roll Hall of Fame, which announced in April that Mayall would be inducted this fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f1fabe0-4954-11ef-9518-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service asks Trump campaign to stop holding outdoor rallies, following assassination attempt in Pennsylvania</title>
      <description>Donald Trump's campaign is scouting indoor venues, such as basketball arenas and other large spaces where thousands of people can fit, said people familiar with the request who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe private discussions.
But those indoor events would be a marked change for Trump, who has held hundreds of outdoor rallies since launching his first presidential bid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abf20660-493e-11ef-88f2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years after Larry Nassar scandal, top gymnastics coaches remain in the sport despite allegations of physical and emotional abuse</title>
      <description>Gymnastics officials promised reform. But gymnasts’ allegations of abuse in their clubs have been met largely with inaction, an investigation by The Washington Post found, including in one California gym that still produces elite gymnasts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04dcc4d0-493b-11ef-8bb3-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 21:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Maine writer set out on the Appalachian Trail with his son. Mistakes were made.</title>
      <description>When you’re heading into 100 miles of wilderness, sometimes you have to start with a pause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bb8d2a0-4932-11ef-b18f-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:28:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.) says he’ll step down, ending long political career amid pressure from his party over bribery conviction</title>
      <description>His decision to resign, effective Aug. 20, will allow New Jersey Gov. Phil Murphy (D) to appoint a temporary replacement to serve until January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24ec6491-492e-11ef-816b-0000a1acec61</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris said 19 words in 2018 that taught us all we need to know about the kind of candidate she’ll be, our columnist writes</title>
      <description>Harris’s question at Justice Brett Kavanaugh’s confirmation hearing is worth a rewatch, columnist Monica Hesse says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">496a8201-4921-11ef-8b02-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 18:27:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Bob Menendez plans to resign, effective Aug. 20, after bribery conviction, according to two people briefed on the decision</title>
      <description>Menendez, a Democrat from New Jersey, faced calls for him to leave the Senate following his conviction on federal bribery and corruption charges.

A Manhattan jury found the 70-year-old guilty on 16 felony counts in a case in which he was accused of taking bribes from three businessmen who showered him and his wife with cash, gold bars and a Mercedes-Benz, an extravagant bounty for his help securing deals with foreign officials and trying to derail several criminal investigations in New Jersey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47ff19e0-491b-11ef-b966-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:44:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunday was the hottest day ever recorded on Earth, scientists say</title>
      <description>Preliminary data from Europe’s top climate monitor shows the planet’s average temperature on July 21 was 17.09 degrees Celsius (62.76 degrees Fahrenheit) — breaking a record set only last year. Researchers say that evidence suggests Sunday was the hottest day on Earth since the start of the last ice age more than 100,000 years ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e88c4e0-4919-11ef-9e4a-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 17:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Was it wrong to box out sisters-in-law to focus on mom’s funeral?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Was it wrong to box out sisters-in-law to focus on mom’s funeral?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eebff40-490d-11ef-a103-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 16:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to give speech Wednesday about his decision to end reelection campaign, people familiar with his plans say</title>
      <description>Biden announced he would withdraw from the race in a letter to Americans on Sunday, promising he would “speak to the Nation later this week in more detail about my decision.” Vice President Harris, having secured pledges of support from a majority of Democratic National Convention delegates to be the party’s  likely presidential nominee, is heading to the battleground state of Wisconsin for a rally Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43849041-4905-11ef-8790-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 15:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service Director Kimberly Cheatle resigns amid criticism for security failures at Trump rally shooting</title>
      <description>Cheatle, a veteran Secret Service agent who became director in 2022, had called the security failure — involving a gunman shooting from an apparently unsecured roof at a July 13 Trump campaign rally — unacceptable. She faced increasing calls from Republican leaders to step down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b5cfc1-4901-11ef-8674-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another stunning political announcement (five decades earlier) in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd40e941-48f7-11ef-8b02-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What voters in key states think about Kamala Harris replacing Joe Biden as the likely Democratic nominee</title>
      <description>The Washington Post and George Mason University’s Schar School asked 152 registered voters from six battleground states to share their reactions to President Biden’s abrupt decision to end his presidential candidacy and endorse Vice President Harris. The responses were decidedly mixed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8dfb990-48f2-11ef-b5fc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 12:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris. Donald Trump’s age. Body-cam video. Israel-Gaza war. Climate fight. Test scores. ‘Twisters.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b653aac0-48e2-11ef-a83c-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A majority of Democratic delegates have pledged their support for Harris, signaling she is likely to secure the party’s nomination</title>
      <description>These pledges are a symbolic show of support for Vice President Harris. She would not officially become the party’s nominee for president until delegates formally vote next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">822403a0-4895-11ef-8004-0000a1ace472</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2024 01:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers summon CrowdStrike CEO to testify on Friday’s massive computer outage</title>
      <description>Republican leaders of the House Homeland Security Committee demanded that George Kurtz appear on Capitol Hill to explain how the outage happened and what the cybersecurity company is doing to prevent future incidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa420d91-486e-11ef-a8b6-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 21:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi endorses Harris as Democratic Congressional leadership prepares to sit down with vice president ‘in short order’</title>
      <description>Vice President Harris picked up key endorsements for her White House bid on Monday, including from Rep. Nancy Pelosi (D-Calif.). House Minority Leader Hakeem Jeffries (D-N.Y.) said he and Senate Majority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-N.Y.) plan to meet with Harris “in short order” and will have more to say then. He said Harris’s candidacy has “excited the country.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4106c7a0-4858-11ef-8160-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 18:28:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Presidential candidate RFK Jr. floated taking a job in a Trump White House as he weighed an endorsement for the Republican nominee</title>
      <description>Independent candidate Robert F. Kennedy Jr. suggested being given a senior job overseeing a portfolio of health and medical issues, an idea that the Trump campaign rejected, according to several people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1b72990-484a-11ef-a005-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 16:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris calls Biden’s record ‘unmatched’ in first public appearance since endorsement. She heads to Delaware today. Follow updates.</title>
      <description>Vice President Harris made her comments at the start of an event honoring championship college athletes at the White House. She is heading to campaign headquarters in Delaware later Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2737a970-4844-11ef-814b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 16:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Biden tried to hold back the tide of history, David Von Drehle writes. The flood came anyway.</title>
      <description>Time has cast its vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4027cd90-483d-11ef-a594-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 15:15:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kamala Harris performs against Donald Trump in election polls</title>
      <description>Even though President Biden has endorsed Vice President Harris to replace him at the top of the ticket, recent polls find little difference between how she and Biden stack up against Donald Trump. In a Washington Post average of 11 post-debate polls, Trump edged out Harris by 1.5 percentage points, only slightly less than his 1.9-point lead over Biden in the same polls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5912cc20-4837-11ef-a620-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 14:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Tornadoes on fire’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>‘Tornadoes on fire’ in today’s On the Record</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d22859d0-482e-11ef-926d-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 13:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s exit. Kamala Harris. Trump’s reaction. Netanyahu visit. Listeria outbreak. Retirement. ‘Magical’ painting. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">898a28d0-4819-11ef-bd2f-000a1acedf53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Joe Manchin (I-W.Va.) is considering re-registering as a Democrat to compete for the party’s presidential nomination</title>
      <description>Manchin is weighing his options following President Biden’s withdrawal Sunday afternoon from the presidential race, according to an adviser. Some in the party establishment coalesced behind Vice President Harris, who announced she is seeking the presidential nomination, in the immediate wake of Biden’s exit.


Manchin is the only elected official besides Harris who as of Sunday night had signaled an interest in seeking the Democratic nod. Motivational speaker Marianne Williamson also says she is vying for Biden's delegates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31c85ed0-47c1-11ef-9dcf-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Democrats can pick a new candidate, a step-by-step visual guide</title>
      <description>There are two paths for replacing Biden at the top of the Democratic ticket: a virtual vote that would lock in a new nominee in early August or an “open” convention starting Aug. 19. Here’s how they work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">600b0690-47b6-11ef-a658-0000a1acefcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 23:10:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden dropped out of the 2024 presidential race. Here is how the historic weekend played out.</title>
      <description>The president had all but made up his mind Saturday night. By midday Sunday, the Zoom calls began informing staff that Joe Biden would bow out of the race against Donald Trump and would endorse Kamala Harris as his successor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8707d0e0-47af-11ef-8c82-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s exit could help his party hold the White House. But Democrats need to proceed carefully, the Editorial Board writes.</title>
      <description>With Biden stepping aside, Democrats must now embrace an open process</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66641e91-47a8-11ef-8b79-000a1acebc1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 21:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vice President Harris says she will ‘earn and win’ presidential nomination</title>
      <description>“I am honored to have the President’s endorsement and my intention is to earn and win this nomination,” Harris said in a statement Sunday.
President Biden announced his withdrawal from the race and endorsed Harris to lead the Democratic ticket earlier on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a2ac081-47a2-11ef-98b7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 20:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden backs Harris as Democratic Party nominee</title>
      <description>Biden said he gives his “full support and endorsement for Kamala to be the nominee of our party this year. Democrats — it’s time to come together and beat Trump.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fcb0930-478f-11ef-911c-0000a1aceb07</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 18:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden to end reelection bid, the president announced in a letter</title>
      <description>A growing number of Democrats for weeks had called on the president to withdraw from the race after his performance in a June debate with Republican nominee Donald Trump. Biden said in a letter he would address the nation later this week regarding his decision to end his campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54b97041-478b-11ef-bbe7-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 18:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xander Schauffele wins the British Open, capturing his second major championship of the year</title>
      <description>Schauffele, 30, also won the PGA Championship at Valhalla in May and became the first player to win two majors in the same year since Brooks Koepka in 2018. He entered the day one shot off the lead and tied for second place before moving up the leader board to win his second career major. American men won all four majors this year for the first time since 1982.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d44e6800-4787-11ef-829d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 17:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a945c980-477a-11ef-8adb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 16:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School turned him liberal. His mom loves Fox News. Will their bond survive?</title>
      <description>After a conservative mother sent her son to a new school, his views shifted left — bringing the nation’s political division home. As claims of school indoctrination are surging, can their family find a way to heal?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd30b900-4771-11ef-85ce-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba260410-4764-11ef-a381-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 13:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic donors are funding a preliminary vetting process for running mates should Harris replace Biden as nominee</title>
      <description>The effort, described by four people familiar with the process, suggests that influential figures in the party are growing increasingly restless and concerned about the time remaining to mount a national campaign.

In recent days, people involved in the effort have contacted the teams of top Democratic figures, including Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro and Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear, the people said, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive effort. The donors are also interested in vetting North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper, Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer and Arizona Sen. Mark Kelly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fa1ebc0-46f1-11ef-bd1c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service said to have denied requests for more security at Trump events</title>
      <description>Top officials repeatedly rejected requests from Donald Trump’s security detail for more personnel and gear at events before attempted assassination, at times citing lack of resources at short-staffed agency, person familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">993c4450-46ea-11ef-b36c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A double life: The cocaine kingpin who hid as a professional soccer player</title>
      <description>Sebastián Marset used his vast drug proceeds to buy and sponsor soccer teams in South America and Europe, investigators say. And then, to fulfill a boyhood fantasy, inserted himself under false identities into the starting lineups — even though he’s not good enough to play at the professional level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c5c1821-46e1-11ef-9f34-0000a1aceb12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When should you salt food while cooking? Here’s what’s best for meat, eggs, vegetables and more.</title>
      <description>When you add salt to a recipe can be just as important as how much you add, and that timing impacts more than flavor. Depending on the food, salting before, during or after cooking will yield optimal results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779b52d0-46ce-11ef-a03c-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli jets strike Houthi targets in Yemen, military says, one day after a drone attack in Tel Aviv</title>
      <description>The strikes in the port city of Hodeida hit an oil depot and power station, a Houthi spokesman said. Israel launched the attack after a drone attack claimed by the Houthis hit a building in central Tel Aviv early Friday, killing one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd9c6730-46bc-11ef-aa77-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: After so many racist incidents, I’m afraid White people think I’m ugly</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: After so many racist incidents, I’m afraid White people think I’m ugly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65d8d6c1-46b1-11ef-8902-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
