<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:11:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown endgame. Venezuela. Extreme rain. Bridge collapse. ChatGPT conversations. Cancer symptoms. Devil bee. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15a72660-bfbf-11f0-b51a-000a1aceb455</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela placed on high alert with massive mobilization of soldiers and militia, defense minister says</title>
      <description>The move comes as the USS Gerald R. Ford aircraft carrier enters waters near Latin America amid speculation that the Trump administration intends to escalate its deadly counternarcotics campaign there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac936020-bf6f-11f0-981a-000a1ace7b51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 02:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How this major city became one of America’s most affordable for home buyers</title>
      <description>While there are many yardsticks for calculating housing affordability, Pittsburgh stands out as uniquely livable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d75400-bf5e-11f0-80d6-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court extends pause on order requiring Trump administration to pay full SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>The ruling comes in a high-stakes battle over funding that helps about 1 in 8 Americans afford groceries — and amid signs the issue could soon be resolved on Capitol Hill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8948d920-bf5a-11f0-b894-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Still forced to parent a ‘man-child’ ex so he shows up for the kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Still forced to parent a ‘man-child’ ex so he shows up for the kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c6296e0-bf20-11f0-83cc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:04:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. aircraft carrier nears Latin America as naval buildup fuels speculation that Trump intends to escalate antidrug campaign</title>
      <description>The USS Gerald R. Ford and its three accompanying warships arrived in the region Tuesday, the Navy said. Since early September, the Trump administration has directed the killing of at least 75 people in its counternarcotics campaign. President Donald Trump has been particularly fixated on Venezuela and its leader, Nicolás Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c51be870-bf1e-11f0-b53f-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing Supreme Court cases in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15028ec1-bf0b-11f0-a8c7-0000a1ace30b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ByHeart recalls all baby formula amid botulism outbreak</title>
      <description>This marks a significant expansion of the organic baby formula company’s weekend recall of two batches after federal health officials said they were investigating 13 botulism hospitalizations potentially linked to its formula.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70a7a050-bf09-11f0-a532-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 14:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How women feel about Trump’s presidency: Heartbreak, fatigue, gratitude</title>
      <description>We asked women how they felt about Donald Trump right after he won the election. One year later, we caught up with them to see what they think now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fadbea0-bf04-11f0-991f-0000a1ace13c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown bill. Supreme Court. Tariff rebates. ICE incident. Oil drilling. Hormone therapy. AI-designed viruses. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb5e5be1-bef5-11f0-8349-0000a1acedcb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deal to end longest-ever government shutdown passes Senate, heads to House</title>
      <description>The House will return to Washington to vote on the plan to reopen the government later this week, after more than 50 days away from the Capitol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16484910-bea6-11f0-b42d-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 02:28:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the dementia crisis grows, D.C. turns to a Dutch model for answers</title>
      <description>In D.C., which has one of the nation’s highest dementia rates, health advocates are pushing for earlier detection and alternative care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33262420-be89-11f0-aad1-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:01:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How different are urban and rural Americans? Take our quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>How different are urban and rural Americans? Take our quiz to find out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fea642e1-be77-11f0-82af-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 20:58:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA will remove warning on hormone therapy for menopause, potentially widening access</title>
      <description>Since 2003, the drugs have included a black-box warning that they may increase the risk of heart attacks, strokes, blood clots and certain cancers. Some doctors say the labels have long prevented women from taking medications aimed at treating the symptoms of menopause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbca07e0-be58-11f0-a9ab-0000a1ace31d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:15:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to brush off Mom’s critiques behind her fake praise?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to brush off Mom’s critiques behind her fake praise?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd800730-be56-11f0-a19a-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Post’s new food critic is Elazar Sontag — and he won’t be anonymous</title>
      <description>For the past three and a half years, Sontag was the restaurant editor at Bon Appétit magazine, where he searched for the best new dining spots in the United States. He won’t try to keep his face off the internet, but he will cover D.C.-area restaurants with the rigor and attention that locals deserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aca1730-be4a-11f0-b83d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court won’t hear challenge to its landmark same-sex marriage ruling</title>
      <description>The announcement indicates there is not an appetite among the high court’s conservative majority to revisit the case known as Obergefell v. Hedges, one of the court’s most significant decisions in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0999de0-be43-11f0-96e7-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the best place to raise kids? See how your county ranks.</title>
      <description>Find where to move based on your priorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46de4990-be41-11f0-8cd7-0000a1ace386</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:26:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Justice Department is struggling as thousands of experienced attorneys exit and few are replaced</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has backfilled only a fraction of open jobs, with the process snarled by a lack of qualified candidates, bureaucratic delays and hiring freezes, according to people familiar with Justice Department hirings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ee120f1-be34-11f0-8495-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown vote. BBC resignations. DOJ vacancies. Anti-vaccine event. Hiring slowdown. Sports betting. Walking study. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf8eca50-be2c-11f0-849d-0000a1ace30f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate takes key vote toward ending government shutdown after group of Democrats strikes deal with Republicans</title>
      <description>Seven Democratic senators and one independent joined with almost all of the chamber’s Republicans to take the first step toward reopening the government. Sunday’s vote is the first of many that will be necessary to pass the agreement in the upper chamber.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1f1ea40-bde8-11f0-8ec1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 03:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to declutter with the 90/90 rule and 8 other numerical guides</title>
      <description>Like recipes, organizing systems often rely on numbers to make decluttering more straightforward. “Saying ‘If you have not used it in 90 days and you will not in the next 90, let it go’ makes it clear,” one home refresh expert says. Try this menu of numerically oriented methods to help you start your cleaning journey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f9c3270-bda4-11f0-9c8b-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 19:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former NFL commissioner Paul Tagliabue dies at 84. He led the league from 1989 to 2006.</title>
      <description>The apparent cause of death was heart failure complicated by Parkinson’s disease, according to Tagliabue’s family, who said he died at his home in Chevy Chase, Maryland. He succeeded Pete Rozelle as commissioner and was succeeded by Roger Goodell.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fe40b11-bd96-11f0-9b73-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 18:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd3fd180-bd8d-11f0-9dc6-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 17:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration orders states to pause efforts to pay full November SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>The White House is instead asking states to issue partial payments, which are about 65 percent of a usual Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program benefit. An Agriculture Department memo warns states that if they fail to comply, they will face consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ea631a0-bd88-11f0-b24f-0000a1ace947</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 16:20:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a childhood virus can contribute to dementia later, and what you can do about it</title>
      <description>A new study suggests that the shingles vaccine may help prevent dementia by reducing the risk of varicella-zoster virus reactivation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1411e6f0-bd7b-11f0-95bb-0000a1ace5df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 14:47:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5894f90-bd78-11f0-a803-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2025 14:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secret history of how Thomas Jefferson’s words were doctored inside his memorial</title>
      <description>This installment of The Post's seven-part series explores how Jefferson's great-great-grandson pushed to portray him as an abolitionist, leaving a misleading impression about his actions on equality and slavery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68e5be00-bcfd-11f0-93ad-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 23:48:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right provocateur Nick Fuentes is triggering a MAGA civil war</title>
      <description>Once barred from nearly every social media platform, Fuentes’s resurgence is driving a wedge through President Donald Trump’s MAGA movement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76142710-bcda-11f0-b865-0000a1ace913</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 19:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Congress spars over shutdown, ACA premium costs are rising. These 8 Americans showed us how much.</title>
      <description>Premium costs for health insurance sold through the Affordable Care Act are soaring because of the expiration of enhanced subsidies at the heart of the government shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59a6c610-bcc0-11f0-9529-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc834520-bcb1-11f0-ad34-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:48:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Take On Me,’ the ultimate synth-pop hit song, has been stuck in our heads since the 1980s. Here’s how it got there.</title>
      <description>The full story of how A-ha emerged from the Norwegian tundra with the ultimate pop song — and its unexpected afterlife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a88ba940-bcab-11f0-8512-0000a1aceb1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 14:03:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court temporarily blocks order on releasing SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>The order pauses, for now, a lower court ruling that would have required the Trump administration to release November benefits in full.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f59810a0-bc4e-11f0-a7bc-0000a1aceb98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Trump from deploying National Guard in Oregon</title>
      <description>District Judge Karin J. Immergut, who was appointed by President Donald Trump, said the attempted deployment in Portland exceeded his authority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb5a5b50-bc4a-11f0-ba8f-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 02:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The states where more people are likely to die before turning 65</title>
      <description>A new study reveals an increase in premature deaths among 18- to 64-year-olds, with Black adults and certain states disproportionately affected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64503e20-bc3e-11f0-bfdd-0000a1aced49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks Supreme Court to block order on releasing SNAP benefits</title>
      <description>A federal judge had directed the administration to release full benefits for November. The administration said Friday it was working to release those benefits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f817ae10-bc37-11f0-817b-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel-winning scientist James Watson dies at 97. He helped reveal the structure of DNA, illuminating the genetic blueprint for life.</title>
      <description>The discovery of DNA’s double helix structure — made with his research partner, Francis Crick, and collaborators Maurice Wilkins and Rosalind Franklin — forever altered the study of biology and influenced modern life in ways that extended far beyond the academic. His reputation was later tarnished when some of his writings were condemned as racist and sexist.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3a35ca1-bc13-11f0-bd04-0000a1acec93</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:56:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. steps up presence in Gaza to support ceasefire, replacing Israel as administrator of humanitarian aid</title>
      <description>The move relegates Israel to a secondary role in determining how and what humanitarian relief can enter Gaza as the U.S. takes the lead, according to several people familiar with the transition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f588bb10-bc11-11f0-bff6-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cornell University agrees to pay $60 million in agreement with Trump administration that restores the university’s research funding</title>
      <description>The deal closes federal investigations into Cornell, which is the fourth Ivy League university to reach an agreement with the administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96edea0-bc00-11f0-9aff-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:41:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sabrina Carpenter, Lady Gaga, Bad Bunny lead nominations from the Recording Academy</title>
      <description>New categories were added this year, including for traditional country album. Here’s the list of the top nominees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d67475a1-bbfa-11f0-9a78-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068f75f0-bbe7-11f0-8b2f-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:35:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second woman says U.S. Anglican Church archbishop sexually harassed her</title>
      <description>A new allegation adds to a crisis facing the denomination founded by conservatives who split from the Episcopal Church in the early 2000s over an openly gay bishop.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">837664b1-bbe3-11f0-9408-0000a1ace749</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight cuts. Voter shifts. Supreme Court. ‘Sandwich guy.’ Climate talks. Bari Weiss. Better aging. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41992580-bbd1-11f0-b789-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heritage Foundation staff in open revolt over leader’s defense of Tucker Carlson</title>
      <description>The recent departures and condemnations stemmed from increasing frustration with Kevin Roberts’s handling of Project 2025 and internal sexism allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c5baec0-bb73-11f0-b2ce-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk wins $1 trillion pay package, tying him to Tesla for a decade and setting him up to be world's first trillionaire</title>
      <description>In an era of skyrocketing CEO pay, the award is unprecedented. The decision passed with more than 75 percent of the vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">568206c0-bb5d-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to release full SNAP benefits by Friday</title>
      <description>In his ruling, Judge Jack McConnell said the USDA was causing “irreparable harm” by not releasing full funding. “The evidence shows that people will go hungry,” he added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eda51610-bb5c-11f0-9ee9-0000a1ace890</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 22:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional Budget Office believed to have been hacked by foreign actor, people familiar with the situation say</title>
      <description>The nonpartisan office makes economic projections for lawmakers and evaluates legislation for how much it would add or subtract from the national debt. The breach potentially exposes key financial data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e105490-bb55-11f0-ac62-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:14:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to end policy of self-identifying gender on passports</title>
      <description>The justices overturned for now a lower-court decision that blocked an executive order by President Donald Trump that required passports to reflect a person’s sex as listed on their birth certificate. The decision is the latest in a string of orders by the high court rolling back gay and transgender rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50ec3302-bb50-11f0-851a-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury finds D.C. ‘sandwich guy’ not guilty of assaulting officer</title>
      <description>Sean C. Dunn admitted he flung the hoagie at a federal agent. His attorneys called it a “harmless gesture” of protest as Trump commandeered D.C. police.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5927fb70-bb47-11f0-826e-0000a1ace6bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia teacher shot by 6-year-old student wins $10 million in lawsuit against former assistant principal</title>
      <description>Abby Zwerner was a teacher at Richneck Elementary School when she was shot by her first-grade student in 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff3b65c0-bb3c-11f0-89ca-0000a1ace577</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
