<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:03:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: National Park Service to remove 140 cherry trees for D.C. sea wall project. A previous alert said 300.</title>
      <description>The removal of the iconic Japanese flowering trees between the Thomas Jefferson Memorial and the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial will begin in May, the Park Service said.

In all, about 300 trees of different varieties, including cherry trees, will be removed from the Tidal Basin and West Potomac Park during a three-year project to rehabilitate crumbling sea walls in the area. When work is completed, the Park Service said, it will plant hundreds more trees.

An earlier version of this alert misstated the number of cherry trees that would be removed. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61f3d810-e15e-11ee-9657-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 17:23:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Park Service to cut down 300 cherry trees over a 3-year span for D.C. sea wall project. Most will be replaced.</title>
      <description>The removal of the first 140 of the iconic Japanese flowering trees between the Thomas Jefferson Memorial and the Franklin Delano Roosevelt Memorial will begin in May, the Park Service said.

Ultimately, 300 cherry trees around the Tidal Basin and West Potomac Park will be removed during a three-year project to rehabilitate crumbling sea walls in the area, but 274 of the trees will be replaced, according to the Park Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b326711-e154-11ee-87f7-0000a1ace202</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother is a risk to ‘cut and run’ on his premature newborn twins</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother is a risk to ‘cut and run’ on his premature newborn twins</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8d994d0-e152-11ee-a874-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 16:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia judge drops a small number of the charges against Trump in sweeping election interference case</title>
      <description>The judge overseeing the election interference case against former president Donald Trump and several allies dismissed six counts of the 41-count criminal racketeering indictment, ruling that the charges lacked specific detail, but he declined to dismiss the case.

In a nine-page order issued Wednesday morning, Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee dismissed six charges alleging Trump and five co-defendants had illegally urged elected officials in Georgia to violate their oaths of office in their attempts to overturn Trump’s 2020 election loss in the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e36eaa0-e14b-11ee-aed9-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:08:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the best way to split the bill at a restaurant? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>Post food critic Tom Sietsema answers your restaurant-related questions, solves your dining dilemmas and gives suggestions on the best places to eat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2214cf51-e14b-11ee-94ff-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 15:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The House overwhelmingly passed a bill that could ban TikTok in the U.S. Its fate in the Senate is uncertain.</title>
      <description>The legislation, approved less than a week after advancing out of committee, would force TikTok to split from its parent company or face a national ban — a sweeping bipartisan rebuke of the popular video-sharing app. It now goes to the Senate, where some lawmakers have expressed concern it may run afoul of the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87b97530-e147-11ee-ba83-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 14:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Predatory groups are coercing children into violent and degrading acts on popular online platforms, then boasting about it</title>
      <description>An emerging network of groups motivated by cruelty seeks out children with mental health issues and blackmails them into self-harm, in some cases pressuring them to take their own lives, a global examination by The Washington Post and several media partners found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f49a82a0-e13f-11ee-8a5a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘A pivot out of nowhere’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef302ab0-e13d-11ee-9ac0-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexei Navalny’s widow, Yulia Navalnaya, writes: Putin isn’t a politician, he’s a gangster</title>
      <description>Putin isn’t a politician, he’s a gangster</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bf3d640-e13c-11ee-93fa-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 13:21:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden vs. Trump. Robert Hur. TikTok ban. Ukraine aid. Andrew Tate. Trailblazing pilot. Fox disguise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cce894c0-e128-11ee-a811-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officially wins the GOP nomination for president, AP projects, setting up a rematch with Biden</title>
      <description>Donald Trump secured the 1,215 delegates needed to make him the party’s official nominee, the Associated Press reported. He is set to be formally nominated at the Republican National Convention from July 15-18 in Milwaukee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42cb9710-e0e7-11ee-86fd-0000a1acec72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 03:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden formally gains enough delegates to secure the 2024 Democratic presidential nomination, AP projects</title>
      <description>President Biden clinched the 1,968 delegates needed to earn the 2024 presidential nomination, the Associated Press reported, setting up a likely rematch with former president Donald Trump.
He is set to be formally nominated at the Democratic National Convention from Aug. 19-22 in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">003856b0-e0c7-11ee-a3ca-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 23:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. will send Ukraine $300 million in weapons as Biden’s request for more aid remains stalled in the House</title>
      <description>The emergency package, announced by the White House on Tuesday, will be funded by “unanticipated cost savings” from contracts the Pentagon had brokered to replace weapons previously provided to Ukraine, national security adviser Jake Sullivan said. President Biden’s request for billions of dollars in additional funding has been stalled for months amid a broader political dispute that includes aid for Israel and U.S. border security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3647ad1-e0a2-11ee-8bc3-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Podcast. Subtweet. If you’re still using these dated words, you’re not alone, Benjamin Dreyer writes.</title>
      <description>If you’re still using these dated words, you’re not alone</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a82820-e08f-11ee-b1aa-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband mulls unemployment as preferable to a ‘step down’ job</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband mulls unemployment as preferable to a ‘step down’ job</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0e52fe0-e089-11ee-85e4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Robert Hur will testify to Congress that he did not ‘disparage the president unfairly.’ Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Hur is testifying before Congress this morning about why he did not recommend seeking charges against President Biden for his possession of classified documents after Biden’s vice presidency ended. The former prosecutor’s description of Biden’s memory lapses during an interview has become fodder for Republicans in the 2024 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7f00850-e079-11ee-9643-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 14:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My eyes see ... today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4c5720-e074-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump last year asked Elon Musk if he wanted to buy Truth Social, a sign they continue to communicate more than previously known</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump’s overture to the billionaire did not lead to a deal. But the two have had other conversations, too, Trump advisers say, about politics and business.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26b7fe30-e072-11ee-80d3-0000a1acef5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 13:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The annual inflation rate rose in February, underscoring concerns prices could be heating up again despite the Fed’s efforts</title>
      <description>The central bank is eyeing multiple interest rate cuts this year — but only if progress on inflation keeps up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d736d9d0-e06c-11ee-88a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transcript of Biden’s interview paints nuanced portrait of his cognitive abilities ahead of Robert Hur’s congressional testimony</title>
      <description>The president doesn’t come across as absent-minded as Hur has made him out to be — and Hur doesn’t appear as crass as Biden has made him out to be. Hur is slated to testify about his probe into Biden’s handling of classified documents today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e39fe20-e06a-11ee-88a4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 12:18:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 election. Special counsel. Haiti violence. LGBTQ+ law. Boeing whistleblower. Airbnb cameras. Sycamore Gap tree. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1725880-e05f-11ee-9384-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a doctored photo of the Princess of Wales triggered a media crisis</title>
      <description>Celebrities aspire to look perfect. Journalism aspires to tell the truth. But those two standards clashed when Kensington Palace released its first photo of Catherine since her abdominal surgery, with obvious manipulations that may have exacerbated a royal PR crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc04d121-e000-11ee-a8ae-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 23:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RNC fires dozens of employees after Trump-backed leadership takes over</title>
      <description>Communications and political staff members were fired from the party’s central committee, according to three people familiar with the firings but who weren’t authorized to speak publicly. The staffing changes came just days after Michael Whatley and Lara Trump, former president Donald Trump’s chosen candidates, were elected to head the RNC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15204b00-dffa-11ee-8b84-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 22:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Biden’s $7.3 trillion budget proposal would raise taxes on the wealthy to cover health and child care. A previous alert said $7.2 trillion.</title>
      <description>The White House proposal is unlikely to become law due to Republican control of the House. Aides say it would lower the soaring national debt by $3 trillion over 10 years.

An earlier version of this alert misstated the cost of the proposed budget. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85fa6360-dfc3-11ee-b517-0000a1ace62c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden’s $7.2 trillion budget proposal would raise taxes on the wealthy to cover health and child care. It’s unlikely to be approved.</title>
      <description>The White House proposal is unlikely to become law due to Republican control of the House. Aides say it would lower the soaring national debt by $3 trillion over 10 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">226af0a1-dfc1-11ee-b13f-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 16:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NATO members must raise their defense spending to 3 percent of GDP, Polish President Andrzej Duda writes</title>
      <description>On March 12, 1999, Poland realized its dream of joining NATO. Twenty-five years later, we know that strengthening the alliance is vital amid rising threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed70d220-dfb6-11ee-9d5c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest moments at the Oscars, including ‘Oppenheimer,’ Emma Stone, Ken and a naked John Cena</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic biopic dominated the Oscars, and the best actress category held the biggest surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7471b070-dfb0-11ee-81e0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 14:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sink your teeth into today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c983b6a0-dfae-11ee-8260-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest moments of the Academy Awards, including ‘Oppenheimer,’ Emma Stone, Ken and a naked John Cena</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic biopic dominated the Oscars, and the best actress category held the biggest surprise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a62040b0-dfaa-11ee-9ed0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 13:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oscar winners. Trump and Biden. Shutdown deal. Ramadan in Gaza. Kate Middleton. Small houses. Aliens. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d6232a1-df96-11ee-91ac-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine, Princess of Wales, says she altered official photo and apologizes after some photo agencies removed it from circulation</title>
      <description>Princess Catherine posted on social media that she was experimenting with photo editing and apologized for the confusion caused by the family photograph. Several news agencies suspended use of the photo after determining that parts of it had been digitally edited.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fc6b6b0-df95-11ee-ac2d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 10:53:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Oppenheimer’ wins best picture at the Oscars, nabbing seven Academy Awards</title>
      <description>The ceremony looked back on a year in which audiences and critics found a lot to love.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72521851-df4e-11ee-ad37-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 02:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get the latest updates on tonight’s winners, surprises and snubs as ‘Oppenheimer’ vies for a record number of awards</title>
      <description>Christopher Nolan’s atomic-age biopic is poised to have a big night, while Lily Gladstone looks to make history as the first Native American to win an Oscar in an acting category. Join us for live coverage and analysis of the night’s biggest moments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df50260-df31-11ee-b49f-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 22:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign insider recounts failed hunt for 2020 fraud in new book</title>
      <description>Ken Block, an expert hired by the campaign, writes that he shot down false claim after false claim in an election that was not stolen. Emails from 2020 reviewed by The Washington Post show one tip was routed to the campaign via the manager of one of Donald Trump's golf clubs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068fc650-df1f-11ee-9c5c-0000a1ace007</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 20:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Oscars could make history this year. Here’s everything you need to know about the frontrunners, how to watch and more.</title>
      <description>Will “Oppenheimer” dominate? What are the potential upsets and historic firsts? Is Ryan Gosling really performing as Ken? (Yes!) Here’s your complete rundown before the Academy Awards begin at 7 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ca04540-deff-11ee-93b4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:59:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">642e0511-def7-11ee-b59a-0000a1acebd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you tell which of these actors in Oscar-nominated films are wearing wigs? (It’s harder than it seems.)</title>
      <description>A good wig takes tons of time, money and a veritable encyclopedia of styling knowledge. These efforts will be recognized at tonight’s Academy Awards. Here’s the step-by-step process, plus a quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">104c9b30-deef-11ee-98f4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 15:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750dfc10-dee2-11ee-8455-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2024 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida has been ground zero for culture wars. But the pushback is growing as voters tire of DeSantis’s ‘war on woke.’</title>
      <description>Conservative lawmakers in the Sunshine State rejected a host of new culture war proposals, a change from past years when bills backed by Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) sailed through.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">995276e0-de5c-11ee-9f32-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 21:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Conservative parents don’t approve of Indian boyfriend I met online</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Conservative parents don’t approve of Indian boyfriend I met online</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8fa8490-de36-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 17:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How worried should we be about the Drunk Elephant tweens?</title>
      <description>Their much-publicized, pricey new skin-care hobby could be a symptom of our age-obsessed culture — or could be harnessed for good.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">615e83b0-de2e-11ee-97d7-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 16:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9168de00-de21-11ee-b00b-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 14:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The federal government won’t shut down this weekend. The Senate has passed spending legislation and will send it to Biden to sign.</title>
      <description>The measure had already passed the House. Another deadline awaits in two weeks for about 70 percent of federal agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11aeb600-ddac-11ee-ad82-0000a1ace6cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:29:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America is running out of electricity as tech companies sap the country’s aging power grid</title>
      <description>Vast swaths of the United States are at risk of running short of power as data centers and factories proliferate around the country. The growth is driven in part by the innovations in artificial intelligence and threatens to stifle the transition to cleaner energy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">426e9e51-dd97-11ee-a2a6-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Novo Nordisk's blockbuster weight loss drug, Wegovy, may be prescribed to reduce heart attack risk in overweight people, FDA says</title>
      <description>The drug has the same active ingredient as the company’s diabetes drug, Ozempic. The approval is based on research showing that Wegovy reduced the risk of major cardiovascular events such as heart attacks and strokes by 20 percent, compared with a placebo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24327e81-dd82-11ee-b6c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 19:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Honduran president Juan Orlando Hernández is convicted of helping send tons of cocaine to the U.S.</title>
      <description>Hernández was treated as a U.S. government ally but secretly “paved a cocaine superhighway to the United States,” prosecutors said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9ccd5f0-dd7d-11ee-b39a-0000a1aced0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 18:58:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Katie Britt rebutted Biden’s speech from her kitchen. A lot of moms can’t see themselves in her place, our columnist writes.</title>
      <description>The Alabama Republican’s State of the Union rebuttal seemed aimed at suburban women whom Republicans have done little to win back, Monica Hesse argues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e5a31b0-dd75-11ee-bc91-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I fall out of love with a married man?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: How do I fall out of love with a married man?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d2c7590-dd73-11ee-b81e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump posts $91M bond while appealing E. Jean Carroll defamation judgment. A judge had denied his request to delay payment.</title>
      <description>The former president and likely 2024 Republican nominee had until Monday to guarantee payment of an $83.3 million judgment to Carroll, a writer and columnist whom he defamed after she accused him of long-ago sexual assault. Trump also filed a notice saying he will appeal the judgment against him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee8c1b70-dd6c-11ee-a1d0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:57:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican National Committee installs Trump's chosen leaders, including his daughter-in-law, in merger with campaign</title>
      <description>Donald Trump, now the expected Republican nominee, picked Michael Whatley and Lara Trump to lead the party's central committee, which is facing a dramatic fundraising shortfall.

Whatley replaces outgoing RNC Chair Ronna McDaniel, who also was chosen by Trump but whose relationship with the former president and his allies had become strained in recent months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65066b30-dd6c-11ee-9773-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:53:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
