<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he spoke with Putin in their first known call since he took office and they agreed to visit each other’s countries</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has previously demanded that Russian President Vladimir Putin put an end to the war in Ukraine, but Trump has offered few concrete indications of how he would foster a breakthrough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c68118e0-e966-11ef-9a42-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard is confirmed by the Senate as Trump’s director of national intelligence, overcoming stiff opposition</title>
      <description>The nomination of Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman turned supporter of President Donald Trump, stirred fierce debate. But she managed to assuage the concerns of a handful of Republicans skeptical about her qualifications and past behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdd076f1-e961-11ef-bfbd-000a1ace5295</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Can I tip less to eat out more? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Can I tip less to eat out more? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b4b2850-e95f-11ef-99f7-000a1ace6903</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth calls Ukraine’s peace goals ‘unrealistic’ in meeting with allies</title>
      <description>Hegseth on Wednesday called Ukraine’s desire to recover all of the territory it has lost to Russia since 2014 an “unrealistic objective” while pledging that the Trump administration will pursue peace negotiations to end war between the two nations. Any deal, Hegseth added, must come with “robust security guarantees,” international oversight of the boundary between Russian and Ukrainian forces, and no NATO membership for Ukraine — something that would require other countries to defend Ukrainian territory in any future conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6e2a2d0-e951-11ef-b806-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:59:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Put your common cents to the test in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5fee110-e94d-11ef-b538-0000a1ace49b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 14:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation increased more than expected in January as prices heated up for Americans</title>
      <description>Price increases eased throughout much of 2024, but progress on inflation slowed in the past few months, partly due to housing costs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04e258e1-e946-11ef-bfbd-000a1ace5295</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Musk. Prisoner release. Health agencies. Rising prices. Fire insurance. Tuna recall. Giant Schnauzer. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1be24f0-e938-11ef-a2e3-0000a1ace016</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monty, a Giant Schnauzer, wins best in show at Westminster dog show</title>
      <description>The world's most prominent dog show gave its highest honor to Monty, a three-time winner of the Working Group, on Tuesday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ce7f530-e8f9-11ef-bf00-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 04:24:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top ICE officials removed from jobs amid scramble to meet Trump's ramped-up goals for arrests and deportations</title>
      <description>Two of the top officials at U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement have been reassigned from their jobs amid frustration among Trump officials that immigrant detainees have been released and that officers aren’t ramping up arrests and deportations fast enough to meet the president’s goals, according to three people with knowledge of the move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6719f150-e8db-11ef-b34f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Post Next 50, a list of fascinating people expected to make an impact in 2025</title>
      <description>Journalists across The Washington Post newsroom selected 50 people who reflect a range of viewpoints and whose work will be significant in society. The list isn’t an award or honor. The goal is to look forward, not backward. Who do you think is “next”?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33d16cb1-e8cc-11ef-b34f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 23:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snow is starting in the D.C. area. Follow Capital Weather Gang’s live updates.</title>
      <description>The heaviest snow is expected this evening when visibility will drop and roads may become hazardous. About 3 to 6 inches could fall by morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ab627f0-e8ad-11ef-9b72-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:22:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces release of Marc Fogel, an American imprisoned in Russia, as part of deal with Kremlin</title>
      <description>As a result of the deal, Fogel has been released and is returning to the United States, National Security Adviser Michael Waltz said in a statement. Fogel was detained by Russian officials in August 2021 and charged with smuggling into the country a small amount of medical marijuana, which was prescribed in the United States for back pain but is banned in Russia. Waltz called the deal with Russia an “exchange” but provided no information on what the United States offered in return. It was negotiated by President Donald Trump’s special envoy to the Middle East, Steve Witkoff, he said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb747d80-e8a8-11ef-b719-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel will end Gaza ceasefire if Hamas does not return hostages Saturday, Netanyahu says</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said in an address Tuesday that Israel would "gather forces inside and around the Gaza Strip" in preparation to resume war if hostages held by Hamas are not returned Saturday. It was not immediately clear if he meant the three hostages whose release had been agreed on or all remaining hostages.

Hamas said Monday it would delay the release over accusations of Israeli ceasefire violations. Netanyahu's remarks come after President Donald Trump said "all hell is going to break out" if hostages are not released.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ce64f80-e8a1-11ef-9f37-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders CDC to restore websites that were taken down after Trump’s executive order on gender</title>
      <description>A judge ruled that the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention must restore online access to websites with data and guidance on HIV monitoring, health risks for youths and assisted reproductive technologies. President Donald Trump had ordered federal agencies to recognize only male and female genders, leading health officials to take down the websites to review their content.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0982b5e2-e89f-11ef-b325-0000a1ace724</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s processed foods are catching on with the kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s processed foods are catching on with the kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cfcd80-e89d-11ef-8c06-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National parks can be dangerous. So Trump made a hiring freeze loophole.</title>
      <description>The exemption comes after congressional Democrats warned that national parks could be short-staffed during the summer season. Conservation groups also raised concerns that a shortage of law enforcement workers could prevent park visitors from receiving lifesaving medical evacuations and care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">208f6ca0-e89b-11ef-b430-0000a1acef41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Islamic State has regrouped in Somalia — and has global ambitions</title>
      <description>The Post ventured to the front lines of an offensive against the Islamic State in northern Somalia, where the group has built an international terror hub. As foreign fighters flow in and money flows outward to other militant cells, local forces have launched a grinding fight against the group despite a lack of Western support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">276ceb51-e897-11ef-8479-0000a1ace239</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 16:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seal as a seal in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccaeaa90-e888-11ef-98ad-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 14:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pushback. Israeli hostages. Elon Musk. Eric Adams. Flu outbreak. Winter storms. Earth’s core. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd8e05b1-e86f-11ef-84e5-0000a1ace7d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 12:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department tells prosecutors to drop corruption charges against New York Mayor Eric Adams</title>
      <description>Adams was indicted in September for allegedly accepting bribes through campaign donations and luxury travel perks. President Donald Trump has expressed sympathy for the mayor even as many officials and residents in New York said the charges made Adams unfit for office. The Justice Department said the case should be dropped because Adams is seeking reelection and should focus on fighting crime and illegal immigration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74611e50-e80f-11ef-a5d4-0000a1aceb72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:30:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Trump’s move to slash NIH funding in 22 states that sued</title>
      <description>The lawsuit came after the Trump administration on Friday announced changes to how it would pay universities and research organizations to cover costs related to administration and infrastructure. The announcement sparked alarm among academic leaders who said it would cut billions of dollars in biomedical research funding, imperil their universities and medical centers, and threaten research into cancer, Alzheimer’s and other diseases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3d58b90-e806-11ef-b5d3-0000a1ace825</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 25% tariffs on steel and aluminum imports, dealing blow to Canada and Mexico</title>
      <description>Canada, the No. 1 foreign supplier to U.S. buyers, will feel the brunt of the tariffs. But the tariffs target China, which is a smaller U.S. supplier but accounts for more than half of global steel output.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1decaa50-e803-11ef-8a21-0000a1ace013</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 23:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump expected to issue executive order targeting D.C. crime, homeless encampments and graffiti</title>
      <description>The directives targeting D.C. could come in an executive order as early as this week and emphasize public safety and beautification of the city, according to three people who spoke on the condition of anonymity because they weren’t authorized to discuss private conversations between the White House and D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser’s administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3069d8c0-e7fd-11ef-839f-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 22:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk-led group launches $97 billion bid for ChatGPT-maker OpenAI</title>
      <description>A group of investors led by Elon Musk sent a $97.4 billion offer to buy the artificial intelligence company to OpenAI’s board. OpenAI CEO and board member Sam Altman has rebuffed the idea in a post on X.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3293540-e7fb-11ef-a6a7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 22:09:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter storm warnings have been issued for the D.C. area for up to 4 to 8 inches of snow</title>
      <description>Snow is forecast to begin between late morning and late afternoon Tuesday with deteriorating conditions by the evening commute. The heaviest snow is forecast Tuesday night and in the southern half of the area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ac1e20-e7eb-11ef-b9b6-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 20:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to talk about a second child when wife is leaning no?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to talk about a second child when wife is leaning no?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a63981-e7d1-11ef-8707-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 17:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Palestinians would not have the right to return to Gaza under his proposal to take over the enclave</title>
      <description>In an interview with Fox News, President Donald Trump said “no” when asked whether Palestinians displaced by his plan to “own” the territory would be allowed to come back.

“No, they wouldn’t because they’re going to have much better housing,” he said in a clip of the interview that aired Monday, adding that he would “make a deal” with Egypt and Jordan to build “a permanent place” for Palestinians in those countries. American allies in the Middle East have angrily rejected Trump’s proposal, and the United Nations and legal experts say it probably violates international law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e46a20-e7c7-11ef-afa1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 15:57:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Bowl 2025 commercials: Our picks for the best, worst and weirdest</title>
      <description>Dunkin’ brought back Ben Affleck, the one true DunKing. Meg Ryan and Billy Crystal reunited to persuade “When Harry Met Sally” fans to buy Hellmann’s mayonnaise. Mountain Dew scarred everyone by putting the singer Seal’s face on a literal seal. Here are all of the standout commercials from Super Bowl LIX.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6802a121-e7be-11ef-a465-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 14:50:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The QB in the booth in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c3ca520-e7bb-11ef-a5eb-0000a1aced16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 14:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Mahomes never saw his worst loss coming. The Eagles did.</title>
      <description>On Sunday night at the Super Bowl, Mahomes’s inevitability collided with a ferocious, profoundly talented defense. The Philadelphia Eagles clobbered the Kansas City Chiefs, 40-22, and bullied Mahomes into a brand of turnover-streaked, almost helpless football that had been foreign to him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d71770c1-e7b1-11ef-8d6e-000a1acec17d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 13:20:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Federal workers. Biden officials. Hostage release. Fire recovery. Multilingual kids. Super Bowl. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">976e9990-e7a6-11ef-998d-0000a1ace19c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At the Super Bowl, Kendrick Lamar came ready to play with a stylish, nonstop halftime show</title>
      <description>The visionary rapper had a subtle message for our political moment — and an unsubtle one for his rival Drake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4062ec40-e766-11ef-9ff8-0000a1ace773</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 04:19:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eagles rout Chiefs, 40-22, in Super Bowl LIX, denying Kansas City's bid for a historic three-peat</title>
      <description>The Eagles won the Super Bowl for the second time in eight seasons and they did it in commanding fashion, never trailing against Patrick Mahomes and the Chiefs. President Donald Trump, former first lady Jill Biden and music star Taylor Swift all attended the game in New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b697ef40-e75d-11ef-9e87-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 03:18:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrected link: The Chiefs meet the Eagles in Super Bowl LIX, with a chance at a three-peat on the line. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Kansas City has won the past two Super Bowls and three of the past five, including a 38-35 win over Philadelphia two years ago, and has not lost in the postseason in over three years. The Eagles, led by NFL offensive player of the year Saquon Barkley, are seeking their second Super Bowl title and enter tonight's matchup having won 15 of their past 16 games. A previous alert was sent with the wrong link. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">637e0800-e73d-11ef-a5eb-0000a1aced16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chiefs meet the Eagles in Super Bowl LIX, with a chance at a three-peat on the line. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Kansas City has won the past two Super Bowls and three of the past five, including a 38-35 win over Philadelphia two years ago, and has not lost in the postseason in over three years. The Eagles, led by NFL offensive player of the year Saquon Barkley, are seeking their second Super Bowl title and enter tonight's matchup having won 15 of their past 16 games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caaa7470-e73b-11ef-b5cd-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 23:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A health board’s ban on coronavirus shots in its Idaho clinics offers a glimpse of RFK Jr.’s vaccine-skeptical America</title>
      <description>An Idaho health district banned its public health clinics from distributing the coronavirus vaccine last fall. Public health experts fear other boards across the country could follow as scientifically inaccurate information about vaccines swirls from the top of President Donald Trump’s potential health administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e2e8950-e727-11ef-bb4f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 20:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some of Elon Musk’s old employees have a warning for federal workers</title>
      <description>Even among hard-driving tech workers, Musk is known for his unusual and often erratic management tactics. Now former employees predict the Silicon Valley billionaire will cause friction as the shadow boss of a federal bureaucracy where many workers trade the higher pay and longer work hours of corporate America for job security.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">190fec40-e718-11ef-9b91-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 19:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edb0ef60-e715-11ef-ac94-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 18:44:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the era of Trump trad</title>
      <description>This president’s aesthetic combines classical architecture and cartoonish virility with WWE alternative reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4730bfb0-e703-11ef-b032-0000a1aceb3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 16:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Four big Super Bowl LIX predictions — including who will win</title>
      <description>From Kansas City’s defense to the Eagles’ A.J. Brown to Chiefs tight end Travis Kelce, The Washington Post’s Adam Kilgore provides the Super Bowl’s most important factors to watch, plus a final score pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f021e3a0-e6fa-11ef-8b15-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 15:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df50bfe1-e6f2-11ef-88a6-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 14:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In chaotic Washington blitz, Elon Musk’s ultimate goal becomes clear</title>
      <description>In one federal agency after another, Musk and a coterie of aides are moving to control, automate — and substantially diminish — hundreds if not thousands of public functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ee51910-e66c-11ef-8979-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 22:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 underrated destinations to add to your travel wish list</title>
      <description>Our picks for where to go without crowds this year include the forests of Transylvania, a “mini New Orleans” in another southern state, a tranquil Brazilian beach and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1abbc90-e652-11ef-a473-0000a1ace055</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:28:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Cleavage’: A single word can have so many meanings. So can life.</title>
      <description>It’s what linguists call a “contronym,” a word with two opposite meanings. It also describes my life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab163d90-e648-11ef-b8d7-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 18:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The only Super Bowl recipe roundup you need — including wings, dips, chili and pizza</title>
      <description>For the many millions of people without a rooting interest in the Kansas City Chiefs’ dynastic aspirations or the Philadelphia Eagles’ run to redemption, the main event will play out on a coffee table rather than the football field. Peruse our top recipes, broken down by “food group,” and supplement with store-bought essentials as needed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1bcb170-e643-11ef-8676-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration cut billions in biomedical funding. Researchers say it imperils work on cancer and other illnesses.</title>
      <description>The NIH said that, effective immediately, it will cut more than $4 billion in what it calls overhead expenses, and it singled out large universities. Researchers say that will hurt small and large facilities alike that work on medical issues such as cancer research and heart disease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e18dc1-e63e-11ef-b248-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 17:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74dd4300-e629-11ef-865e-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Musk’s DOGE from access to Treasury Department material</title>
      <description>A federal judge temporarily blocked Elon Musk’s Department of Government Efficiency early Saturday from accessing sensitive Treasury Department information for millions of Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">243e0210-e5f0-11ef-b806-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 07:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will fire Kennedy Center board members, appoint himself chairman</title>
      <description>President Trump did not say which board members he plans to terminate. It is unclear whether the president has the power to make such changes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f86c190-e5ae-11ef-a4f0-0000a1ace6d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 23:49:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI director nominee Kash Patel was paid $25,000 by Russian filmmaker tied to Kremlin, documents show</title>
      <description>Patel received the money from Global Tree Pictures, a Los Angeles-based company run by Igor Lopatonok, who holds both Russian and U.S. citizenship. Lopatonok’s previous projects include a pro-Russia influence campaign that received money from a fund created by Russian President Vladimir Putin, the documents show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">232ef3f0-e5ac-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 23:34:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
