<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 17:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Second-grader feels ‘neglected’ during Mom’s time with teen sisters</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Second-grader feels ‘neglected’ during Mom’s time with teen sisters</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f5b1721-7f45-11ef-a9da-0000a1ace549</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Completely and entirely erased’: How Helene swallowed one mountain town</title>
      <description>Scenes of destruction and suffering lay almost everywhere in Swannanoa, N.C. — cars in tree limbs, mangled homes, mud-choked roads, and people desperate for water and food after Helene devastated western North Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb3474a0-7f41-11ef-bdb9-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dikembe Mutombo dies at 58. The basketball Hall of Famer dominated on defense at Georgetown and in the NBA.</title>
      <description>The all-star center for the Denver Nuggets, Atlanta Hawks and Philadelphia 76ers — who also played for three other teams during an 18-year NBA career — built an off-court legacy through his humanitarian work in central Africa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44962d40-7f3d-11ef-a59c-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel has told U.S. it is planning a limited ground operation in Lebanon that could start imminently, U.S. official says</title>
      <description>The American official said Israel’s planned campaign would be smaller than its last war against Hezbollah in 2006 and would focus on clearing out militant infrastructure along the border to remove the threat to Israeli border communities. On Monday, Israeli forces carried out limited raids in Lebanon, according to an Israeli familiar with the operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c641e1f1-7f37-11ef-81e4-000a1acebfc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A legend of the stage and screen in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53e180e0-7f30-11ef-bdb9-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helene’s damage. Vance vs. Walz. Hezbollah leader. Port strike. Kris Kristofferson. AI veto. Earth’s atmosphere. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2519d830-7f1b-11ef-917c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how Helene left a trail of devastation from Florida to the Carolinas, killing at least 87 in its path</title>
      <description>Videos show the massive swath of destruction from the storm, with its devastating combination of water and wind that hit hundreds of miles from Florida to the Southern Appalachians. Entire communities were flooded; some were cut off with no way in or out. Homes and vehicles have been swept away, and hundreds of roads have been washed out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddec1f60-7ebe-11ef-b7ba-0000a1acebc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 23:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kris Kristofferson dies at 88. The singer-songwriter was a rugged but tender-hearted star of song and screen.</title>
      <description>His trove of country-pop hits such as “Me and Bobby McGee” and “Help Me Make It Through the Night” pushed him to the forefront of American popular composers. His sophisticated compositions juxtaposed freedom and loneliness, romance and loss, tenderness, and a degree of carnality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af99b30-7eb6-11ef-a1d4-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 22:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under a Texas sun, agrivoltaics offer farmers a new way to make money</title>
      <description>Solar grazing helps farmers feed their flocks while the expanding solar industry provides more clean energy to the grid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81173070-7eac-11ef-99e1-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria’s Freedom Party on track to win the national parliamentary election, an unprecedented far-right victory in the post-war era</title>
      <description>If election projections hold up, the win would be the first national victory for the country’s far right since World War II. But the anti-immigration Freedom Party may not be able to find coalition partners to form a government under provocative leader Herbert Kickl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">930b32b0-7e9b-11ef-a3a4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 19:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mark Robinson’s campaign for North Carolina governor came crashing down and induced GOP panic</title>
      <description>Top Republicans, including Donald Trump, long championed or enabled Robinson. Then came a CNN report tying Robinson to an old account on an obscure online porn forum. This was not a failure to vet their candidate, critics said — it was a conscious decision to look away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d611e80-7e8c-11ef-b7ba-0000a1acebc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 17:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">220608c1-7e7c-11ef-987d-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 16:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flooded North Carolina towns continue to struggle with communication problems as relatives search for loved ones after Helene</title>
      <description>The true extent of the storm’s toll remains unknown in western North Carolina, where cell phone and internet signals have been spotty. Buncombe County has received more than 1,000 reports of people looking for loved ones, the county manager said Sunday. But the number is expected to decrease as signals are restored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b13926b0-7e79-11ef-97db-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1372da00-7e67-11ef-a3bb-0000a1ace568</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a phone call, Arizona’s top three Democrats debated how to handle 98,000 voters with no record of providing citizenship proof</title>
      <description>Their predicament was “an urgent, a dire situation,” Gov. Katie Hobbs said, according to audio of the call obtained by The Washington Post. Secretary of State Adrian Fontes said critics would “beat us up no matter what the hell we do.” Attorney General Kris Mayes worried they would be accused of rigging the 2024 election in a crucial state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aea5501-7df7-11ef-a13e-0000a1acec60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why millions of Americans give up control of their thermostats</title>
      <description>Power companies are tapping into customers’ smart thermostats, EV chargers and home batteries to prevent blackouts when the grid is strained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11685e10-7de5-11ef-bb33-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Biblical devastation’ in North Carolina towns flooded by Helene</title>
      <description>The death toll from Helene climbed as emergency responders rushed to rescue residents in small mountain towns that have been cut off from communication. Rescuers said they were struggling to respond to the high number of calls reporting emergencies. Anxious relatives took to Facebook to search for loved ones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fab11b51-7ddd-11ef-8213-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 21:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private messages sent in 2020 show JD Vance harshly criticizing Trump’s record</title>
      <description>In messages sent near the end of President Donald Trump’s time in office, Vance wrote that Trump had “thoroughly failed to deliver on his economic populism.” The timing contrasts with Vance’s explanation for how he transformed from an anti-Trump critic in 2016 to a supporter in 2020, saying that he was converted by Trump’s success as president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7891b00-7dc9-11ef-a657-000a1ace0d80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 18:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My daughter is a harsh parent. I’m worried for my granddaughter.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My daughter is a harsh parent. I’m worried for my granddaughter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32bd5211-7db7-11ef-95e4-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 16:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half the U.S. has banned trans girls from girls sports. A mom may be among the first to face a penalty.</title>
      <description>When Jessica Norton let her trans daughter play volleyball, the school district accused her of breaking Florida law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ba72d80-7db0-11ef-a525-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 15:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4dcd900-7d9d-11ef-8cc6-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah chief Nasrallah’s power spanned the Middle East. His death is a blow to Iran and could plunge Lebanon into crisis.</title>
      <description>Hasan Nasrallah, a Shiite cleric, was born in a shantytown in Beirut and rose through Hezbollah’s ranks in the 1980s. He strengthened ties with Tehran and transformed the group into a sprawling political, military and social movement, with considerable power both inside Lebanon and in countries such as Syria and Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17d71f90-7d98-11ef-8cc6-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military says Hezbollah leader Hasan Nasrallah is dead; militant group has not confirmed</title>
      <description>The Shiite cleric was one of Israel’s archfoes for decades and led one of the most powerful militant groups in the region with backing from Iran. His death could sharply escalate the risks of a wider Middle East war nearly a year after Hamas’s deadly raid from Gaza touched off Israeli attacks that have claimed tens of thousands of lives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba86f01-7d74-11ef-848d-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago White Sox set modern MLB record for futility with their 121st loss</title>
      <description>The White Sox lost to the host Detroit Tigers on Friday night to fall to 39-121 with two games to play. They eclipsed the 1962 New York Mets, who went 40-120-1 in their first season as a major league franchise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">642faf01-7d35-11ef-a941-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 01:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah’s leader was target of Israeli strike, says person familiar with information shared by Israel. His condition is unknown.</title>
      <description>Hasan Nasrallah, the head of Hezbollah, was the target of an Israeli strike in Beirut on Friday, according to a person familiar with information provided by Israel to the United States after the attack, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss sensitive matters. Residents of Lebanon’s capital reported large blasts and pillars of smoke billowing over neighborhoods in the city’s south.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8642f7b0-7d0c-11ef-9673-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 20 killed in three states as Helene’s devastating flooding continues. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>More than 4 million are without electricity in a swath of the country as Helene continues its northward path, leaving a deadly and destructive trail from Florida through Georgia and into the Carolinas. As severe floodwaters swept through one North Carolina town, knocking out communication, the mayor there described the scene as “simply apocalyptic.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df9adc60-7cf3-11ef-a660-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department charges three men in alleged Iranian plot to hack into email accounts of Donald Trump's campaign staff</title>
      <description>Masoud Jalili, Seyyed Ali Aghamiri and Yasar Balaghi “prepared for and engaged in a wide-ranging hacking campaign” targeting current and former U.S. officials, political campaigns, members of the media, and others, the indictment charges. The plot allegedly included an effort to try to share campaign documents with news organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be95efe0-7cef-11ef-933c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: ‘My wife’s brother told her he hates me’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: ‘My wife’s brother told her he hates me’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">374c7400-7cef-11ef-9f37-0000a1acef9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:40:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Mayor Eric Adams pleads not guilty to bribery, corruption charges</title>
      <description>Adams, a Democrat and former police officer, has vowed to stay in office and fight the federal charges he faces, which include bribery, wire fraud and taking illegal campaign donations. He is accused of a years-long scheme to accept improper gifts and payments from foreign benefactors and hide it from the public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70f013d0-7ced-11ef-9500-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:27:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Symphony Orchestra goes on strike, citing pay disparities with other major American orchestras</title>
      <description>The union representing the NSO voiced disapproval of compensation terms proposed by the John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts. The strike, the first since 1978, will disrupt the orchestra’s 94th season that included an opening gala performance scheduled for Saturday, which has been canceled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8a21d40-7ce6-11ef-9a66-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:40:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge strikes down Arlington’s ‘missing middle’ policy, restoring single-family-only zoning in the Northern Virginia county</title>
      <description>A group of homeowners had sued Arlington last year, charging that the county had not followed required procedures or done enough to ensure this zoning change would not negatively impact their suburban neighborhoods. The much-debated policy allowed the construction of multiunit buildings in any residential area — including those that had long required one house with a yard on each lot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11760670-7ce4-11ef-93c9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 15:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says Israel’s assault on Hezbollah will continue, defying U.S. cease-fire demands and issuing a sharp warning to Iran</title>
      <description>In an address to the United Nations General Assembly, Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu signaled there would be no immediate truce in his country’s rapidly escalating conflict in Lebanon, and he warned Iran that Israel's military could strike its assets anywhere in the Middle East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1896f6c0-7ce0-11ef-848d-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 14:52:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4314ca0-7cd4-11ef-b897-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maggie Smith dies at 89. The Oscar-winning British actress enchanted audiences in the Harry Potter films and ‘Downton Abbey.’</title>
      <description>For most of her multiple decades in show business, Maggie Smith defined herself mainly as a theatrical actress. But she also won Oscars for “The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie” and “California Suite,” and Emmys for her portrayal of the disapproving aristocrat Dowager Countess of Grantham in “Downton Abbey.” She was also praised by devoted Harry Potter fans for her portrayal of Professor Minerva McGonagall in the Warner Bros. film series.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b0a21e0-7cd3-11ef-928f-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 13:22:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Helene leaves over 3 million without power in Florida, Georgia and Carolinas. Torrential rain expected to continue Friday.</title>
      <description>Rising waters topped 10 feet in parts of Florida’s Big Bend area after the storm made landfall there. Farther north, excessive rain led to widespread flash flooding in spots from Florida through Georgia and into the Carolinas, with more expected. The Atlanta area was placed under a flash flood emergency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0d32360-7cce-11ef-8fc4-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:48:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Md. Gov. Moore’s approval rises but Bronze Star controversy draws criticism, Post-UMD poll finds</title>
      <description>The approval rating of Maryland Gov. Wes Moore (D) among registered voters has risen seven percentage points since March, and he wins high marks for his response to the Francis Scott Key Bridge collapse, according to a Washington Post-University of Maryland poll. But the poll finds many voters are skeptical of his response to a recent Bronze Star controversy.
One of the nation’s rising Democratic stars, the first-term governor saw his overall job approval climb in the past six months, with 60 percent of registered voters now rating him positively, up from 53 percent in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17e06f70-7cc9-11ef-841b-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 12:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helene’s landfall. JD Vance’s DMs. Eric Adams. Netanyahu speech. Executions. Schizophrenia drug. Climate discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6197a20-7cbf-11ef-be62-0000a1ace516</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan’s ruling party selects Shigeru Ishiba, outspoken former defense minister, as new prime minister</title>
      <description>Ishiba, 67, has been chosen as the Liberal Democratic Party’s new leader and will officially become the prime minister next week, succeeding Fumio Kishida. Ishiba has proposed creating an “Asian NATO” to counter security threats from China and North Korea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">264ec900-7c9a-11ef-8214-0000a1ace429</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 06:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Helene makes landfall in Florida as a Category 4 storm with winds up to 140 mph. The storm surge could reach 20 feet.</title>
      <description>The dangerous storm comes ashore in Florida’s Big Bend region as power outages are mounting throughout the state. Flooding that had already drenched much of the Southeast and southern Appalachians will continue into Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25fedda1-7c81-11ef-848d-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 03:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA approves new kind of antipsychotic drug to treat schizophrenia, a disease that afflicts about 24 million people globally</title>
      <description>The new drug, Bristol Myers Squibb’s Cobenfy, targets a different area of the brain than traditional drugs to relieve symptoms such as delusions without causing patients to gain weight, fall asleep or experience involuntary muscle jerking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2350b10-7c5e-11ef-82c9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 23:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to meet with Zelensky on Friday, the first between the two since 2019. The Ukrainian leader met with Harris on Thursday.</title>
      <description>Donald Trump earlier this week criticized Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky, saying, “We continue to give billions of dollars to a man who refuses to make a deal.” Trump’s remarks came after Zelensky’s events at the White House on Thursday with President Joe Biden and Vice President Kamala Harris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9af94b0-7c54-11ef-93b5-0000a1ace890</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 22:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How far can Jayden Daniels take these Commanders? Our sportswriters are answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>For the first time in years, Washington's NFL team is generating real optimism. Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier are answering readers' questions about the team, which will try to win its third straight game Sunday at Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21cd1c70-7c21-11ef-b76c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Lack of focus at work sends new parent into spiral of self-hate</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Lack of focus at work sends new parent into spiral of self-hate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8452a0a0-7c20-11ef-9415-000a1ace6279</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Mayor Eric Adams charged with bribery, wire fraud and seeking campaign funds from a foreign national, indictment says</title>
      <description>The indictment reveals a lengthy list of accusations that grew out of what prosecutors called “corrupt relationships" with rich foreigners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72ee64a0-7c18-11ef-8e76-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans can order free rapid coronavirus tests by mail starting today, ahead of an expected winter covid wave</title>
      <description>The Biden administration will begin shipping four free at-home tests per household on Monday. People can order the tests through covidtests.gov.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f04ebb60-7c0f-11ef-b57f-0000a1aceccd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A torch goes out in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65d02900-7c0b-11ef-a350-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoda Kotb says she’ll leave ‘Today’ show early next year</title>
      <description>“I realized that it was time for me to turn the page at 60, and to try something new,” Kotb said on air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60963a70-7c0a-11ef-9415-000a1ace6279</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Helene, now Category 2, likely to intensify before pummeling Florida and the Southeast. See forecasts and live updates.</title>
      <description>As the massive storm moves toward Florida’s Gulf Coast, its sheer size means dangerous tropical storm-force winds will reach hundreds of miles from the storm's center. The Big Bend area, where the state’s peninsula meets the Panhandle, could see rising water up to 20 feet. And some areas of the United States, including places well beyond Florida, could see over a foot of rain and threats of life-threatening flash-flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c6c7540-7c08-11ef-90e2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angela Alsobrooks pulls ahead of Larry Hogan in Maryland’s must-win Senate race, poll finds</title>
      <description>Alsobrooks, the Democratic Prince George’s County executive, has pulled clearly ahead in Maryland’s unusually competitive U.S. Senate race with a double-digit lead among likely voters, according to a Washington Post-University of Maryland poll, in a contest critical to deciding control of the chamber next year.

Alsobrooks leads Hogan — a Republican former governor elected twice in the deep-blue state — by 11 percentage points among likely voters, even though the poll shows Hogan has won over a sizable portion of Democrats and remains about as popular with voters as his rival.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cac17381-7bfe-11ef-a6e5-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s meetings. Hurricane Helene. Eric Adams. Lebanon. Shutdown bill. AI Judi Dench. Constitution copy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cc066d0-7bf6-11ef-9410-0000a1aceb4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
