<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 12:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s speech. Republican split. Liverpool car incident. Gaza school. Cancer risk. Hot weather. Mysterious bucket. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc7ac9c0-3ae9-11f0-b3bb-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81 years after he died in World War II, a young aviator was buried in his California hometown</title>
      <description>Second Lt. Thomas V. Kelly Jr. was 21 when he perished with 10 other men on a B-24 bomber shot down near New Guinea on March 11, 1944. Two years ago, his remains and those of three other crew members were recovered from the underwater crash site. Kelly was buried Monday beside family members in Livermore, California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1178a7f1-3a75-11f0-847c-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 21:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you understand your dog’s emotions? Here’s what research tells us.</title>
      <description>Dog owners don’t understand their pet’s emotions as well as they think they do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef605c30-3a5b-11f0-a834-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Rangel dies at 94. He was the first African American chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee.</title>
      <description>The New York Democrat was a powerful voice for Harlem in Congress but was forced to relinquish his chairmanship because of a series of financial transgressions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611a2990-3a4e-11f0-847c-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Stepparent resents husband’s ex over teen’s support agreement</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Stepparent resents husband’s ex over teen’s support agreement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d75d4411-3a4a-11f0-b4e9-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See what happened when these Post readers stopped mowing their lawns</title>
      <description>Whether you have a small yard or acres to spare, these reader-submitted photos show that retiring your lawn mower can mean less work, more wildlife and a display of blooms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41efe6f0-3a3e-11f0-bfd6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six veterans reflect on Memorial Day — and 364 other days we should not forget</title>
      <description>How to honor Memorial Day? Reach out to veterans’ families. Honor the Constitution. Remember the privilege as well as the sacrifice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b87752e1-3a39-11f0-8451-0000a1acef62</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy long weekend! Play today’s On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Memorial Day points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">444329f0-3a37-11f0-9442-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump scolds Putin. Tariff delay. Elon Musk’s future. Firebomb plot. Credit scores. Vaccine rules. Beauty ratings. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3d19f0-3a20-11f0-bfd6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s been five years since George Floyd’s murder. Much of the promised ‘racial reckoning’ never emerged.</title>
      <description>His murder by Minneapolis police in 2020 set off a summer of protests and promises to address the country’s racial inequality. Five years later, many of those efforts have either been reversed or never materialized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf5c73f0-39b2-11f0-86ca-0000a1ace341</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This teen lost her mother and sister in the DCA crash. They’d wanted her to win an upcoming piano competition. And so she played.</title>
      <description>For Anne Valerie Ter, the piano was an extension of herself, from the time she first laid eyes on the instrument as a 1-year-old. After the death of her mother and sister, she pounded her grief into the piano keys as she faced Rachmaninoff’s daunting Piano Concerto No. 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee688960-3984-11f0-8130-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7b0b120-3981-11f0-975e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 16:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where do you stand on this fierce generational divide? Swipe through our test to find out.</title>
      <description>A breakdown of why young people insist on recording videos vertically — and why older folks hate it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd430141-3974-11f0-b060-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 14:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ddcdb0-3970-11f0-89e2-000a1ace4d5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 13:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This scientist spent years studying ‘super agers.’ Here’s the lifestyle change he focuses on most.</title>
      <description>Cardiologist Eric Topol, 70, previously emphasized aerobic exercise. His research led him to significant changes in his routine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4ca9d20-38e9-11f0-86ca-0000a1ace341</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kansas family farm, barely getting by, grapples with Trump’s cuts</title>
      <description>Farmer Jacob Thomas was “barely making it” before the federal cuts this year. Then he and his wife lost 10 percent of their business when the Agriculture Department cut a billion dollars from funding to grow local food for schools and food banks. Other grants they hoped to use to expand are up in the air or have evaporated.
“For the first time in my life,” Thomas said, “I don’t trust the government is going to follow through on their word.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">637ee190-38ae-11f0-84c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6647eda0-38a3-11f0-8b38-0000a1aced7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant arrests at courthouses signal new tactic in Trump’s deportation push</title>
      <description>U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers have been instructed to arrest people immediately after a judge has ordered them to be deported or after prosecutors move to drop their cases. The coordinated operation is the government’s latest attempt to quickly remove people from the country — even if officials have to bypass the courts — as concern grows in the White House that President Donald Trump won’t be able to fulfill his campaign promise to remove millions of undocumented immigrants from the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03985390-38a1-11f0-99af-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House abruptly dismisses NSC staffers in significant reorganization</title>
      <description>The dismissals, part of a plan to downsize the coordinating body, follow President Donald Trump’s recent ouster of his national security adviser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fff59220-3823-11f0-8bfd-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge strikes down Trump's executive order targeting Jenner &amp; Block law firm</title>
      <description>It is the second time a federal judge has ruled that President Donald Trump's unprecedented actions to punish a law firm are unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40371e50-3818-11f0-b7de-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks Trump administration’s effort to ban Harvard University from enrolling international students</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Massachusetts granted Harvard an order on Friday that prevents the Department of Homeland Security from revoking the school’s certification to enroll international students. The decision comes one day after DHS told the school that foreign students must transfer from the university or risk losing their visa status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7f8be91-37f1-11f0-ab79-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body slamming? Officer aggression? The clash with ICE that led to charges against a Democratic congresswoman.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post analyzed hours of witness video to assess conflicting accounts of a tussle this month involving Rep. LaMonica McIver (D-New Jersey) and Immigration and Customs Enforcement at a Newark detention center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6f0d730-37e6-11f0-af42-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55380be0-37da-11f0-93bd-0000a1ace9f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes 50 percent tariff on European Union, takes aim at Apple</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump proposed a 50 percent tariff on all goods from the European Union, declaring that trade negotiations with the E.U. were “going nowhere.” 

In a separate media post, Trump threatened Apple with a minimum 25 percent tariff if the tech giant did not make iPhones for American customers in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef065eb0-37d1-11f0-a8da-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard suing Trump administration over the abrupt revocation of its ability to enroll international students</title>
      <description>The university said it was filing a lawsuit Friday morning against the administration, challenging its decision Thursday to block the school’s certification to admit foreign students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c9f69c0-37d1-11f0-a6b8-0000a1aceb26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harvard. Budget bill. Crypto dinner. D.C. shooting. Supreme Court. Vitamin D. Bear cub. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11776e10-37c5-11f0-a20a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to fire independent regulators for now, casting doubt on 90-year-old legal precedent</title>
      <description>The order, which drew a sharp dissent from the three liberal justices, powerfully endorsed President Donald Trump’s authority over the federal bureaucracy. But the court said it would not impact the independence of the Federal Reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">031a2131-3754-11f0-a48e-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI says suspect in D.C. Jewish Museum shooting confessed to killings</title>
      <description>Elias Rodriguez, 31, faces murder and firearms charges in the killings of two Israeli Embassy workers. The charges could carry the death penalty, but interim U.S. attorney Jeanine Pirro said it's too soon to decide whether to pursue capital punishment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63489600-3753-11f0-9de1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 21:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration revokes Harvard’s ability to enroll foreign students</title>
      <description>In a letter, Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem said her agency had revoked Harvard’s Student and Exchange Visitor Program certification. The move means the university may no longer enroll foreign students, and existing foreign students must transfer or risk losing their legal status, DHS said, adding that Harvard had created an "unsafe campus” by allowing anti-American agitators, many of them foreign students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e19f0b0-373a-11f0-9ec5-0000a1ace3b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband brushes off his side texts to a female co-worker</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband brushes off his side texts to a female co-worker</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">063ad810-3726-11f0-8023-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 16:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate votes to block California’s EV rule, sending measure to Trump. The move could affect car sales in a dozen states.</title>
      <description>The Senate voted to block California from enforcing a rule that would ban sales of new gasoline-powered cars in the state by 2035. The vote marks the GOP’s latest effort to curtail state-level efforts to tackle climate change, even as President Donald Trump and congressional leaders have empowered states to set their own education policies and abortion laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">540879b0-3723-11f0-a9b4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks layoffs at Education Department, stalling Trump’s effort to close the agency</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Boston directed President Donald Trump’s administration to reinstate federal employees who were terminated so the department can continue to carry out its statutory functions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d78330-3721-11f0-a9b4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former British prime minister Liz Truss: ‘Elites killed my pro-growth agenda. Trump can’t let them stop his.’</title>
      <description>The White House’s proposed tax cuts, tariffs and spending reforms are showing the West the way forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">758655d0-371e-11f0-978a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court deadlocks, blocking creation of nation’s first public religious charter school</title>
      <description>With only eight justices voting, the Supreme Court’s 4-4 tie leaves in place an Oklahoma state Supreme Court decision that blocked the creation of the Catholic school and said it would be unconstitutional. A ruling for St. Isidore of Seville Catholic Virtual School would have for the first time allowed direct and complete taxpayer funding to establish a faith-based school, allowing government sponsorship of a curriculum that calls for students to adhere to Catholic beliefs and the church’s religious mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a05ab20-3718-11f0-b7cf-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds fraud conviction of government contractor</title>
      <description>The case involved Alpha Painting &amp; Construction and a project manager, Stamatios Kousisis, who was sentenced to 70 months in prison for obtaining a multimillion-dollar contract under false pretenses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca78fbe0-3716-11f0-bd4e-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 14:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dale Earnhardt Sr. was 49 when he died. As his son neared that age, he went looking for answers.</title>
      <description>Reporter Kent Babb, whose dad died at 51, always dreaded turning that age. Babb wondered how Dale Earnhardt Jr., the iconic NASCAR driver, was coping as he approached 49. “God, I wish he was here for me,” Junior told Babb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4d71601-3710-11f0-9f07-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A night to remember for this actor in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6583f7f0-370f-11f0-9d28-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 13:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. shooting. Oval Office confrontation. Budget bill. Deportation flight. Lonely men. Nor’easter. Lincoln’s gloves. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef0be230-36fb-11f0-bc30-0000a1ace93c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House narrowly passes Trump’s sweeping tax and immigration bill, sending the measure to the Senate</title>
      <description>The bill would extend tax cuts from 2017 that are otherwise set to expire, create some new tax breaks, and spend billions on deportations and defense. Congress’s nonpartisan bookkeeper says it would add $2.3 trillion to the national debt over 10 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4e222a0-36fb-11f0-b153-0000a1ace01c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Israeli Embassy staff killed near Capital Jewish Museum in D.C.</title>
      <description>The two diplomatic staff were shot late Wednesday, Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7976ec0-36bf-11f0-8cdb-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 03:50:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma City Thunder guard Shai Gilgeous-Alexander wins his first NBA MVP award</title>
      <description>Gilgeous-Alexander led the NBA in scoring and guided the Thunder to a league-best 68-14 record in the regular season. He is the third Oklahoma City player to win the league’s top individual award, joining Kevin Durant and Russell Westbrook, and the second Canadian-born player, joining Steve Nash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27cb0c80-3699-11f0-b34e-0000a1acefc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 23:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blasts prosecutors for ‘embarrassing retraction of charges’ against Newark Mayor Ras Baraka</title>
      <description>The Justice Department dropped trespassing charges against Baraka after a clash outside an ICE detention facility. Rep. LaMonica McIver (D) faces two charges of assaulting a law enforcement officer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9b0a9a0-367d-11f0-bf7b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:56:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge says Trump’s decision to remove several immigrants to South Sudan violates his previous court order</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Brian E. Murphy said the Trump administration “obviously” violated his previous order to give immigrants a meaningful opportunity to challenge their removal to a country where they are not citizens. He said the government notified the immigrants the day before they were deported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7d8cee0-3675-11f0-afb6-0000a1ace1fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 19:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump confronts South African president over violence against White farmers in extraordinary Oval Office meeting</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump made no mention of the nation’s long-standing epidemic of violence against both White and Black people, nor its violent and discriminatory history of White rule. South African President Cyril Ramaphosa acknowledged a violence epidemic in his nation but denied a “genocide,” as Trump claimed, and said it was an issue of “criminality.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ffcf420-366d-11f0-819b-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon takes possession of Qatari luxury jet sought by Trump for use as Air Force One</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has praised Qatar for offering the $400 million plane to his administration, but a raft of national security experts have panned the idea, saying it raises significant cost and security concerns, while members of Congress have questioned whether the deal is ethical.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ecc9e3e0-366b-11f0-a4e0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 17:49:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida prosecutors investigate nonprofit linked to initiative led by Casey DeSantis and championed by husband Gov. Ron DeSantis</title>
      <description>Hope Florida Foundation has been mired in controversy since state Republicans began examining why the nonprofit received a $10 million payment from a Medicaid settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bbacd40-365e-11f0-b952-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:12:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé wants her parents, who don’t work, to pay for their wedding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Fiancé wants her parents, who don’t work, to pay for their wedding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a958e50-365d-11f0-8fa5-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Tom Sietsema’s take on a critic nearly getting booted from the French Laundry</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Tom Sietsema’s take on a critic nearly getting booted from the French Laundry</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">128bfe90-3655-11f0-9fdb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 15:05:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. abandons police accountability efforts in Louisville, Minneapolis days before 5th anniversary of George Floyd’s death</title>
      <description>The new civil rights chief at the Justice Department said the government will drop out of reform agreements negotiated during the Biden administration, undoing a signature effort to reshape local law enforcement after high-profile killings by officers ignited widespread outrage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b688abf1-364c-11f0-b8bd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 14:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you tell me how to get to today’s On the Record?</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1e14460-3647-11f0-9795-0000a1ace9cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
