<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 19:02:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Alito says he will not recuse from Jan. 6 cases, offers new details on politically charged flags raised at his homes</title>
      <description>Justice Samuel A. Alito Jr. faced calls from Democratic lawmakers and some legal experts to recuse from two Supreme Court cases related to efforts to overturn the 2020 election results after reports that an upside-down American flag and a religious flag — both of which have been embraced by election deniers — flew outside the homes owned by him and his wife. Alito said his wife is “fond of flying flags” and was responsible for the raising of these flags. He also said he asked her to lower the upside-down American flag but she initially refused to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd0070b0-1de3-11ef-b875-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says it has military control of a buffer zone on the border between Gaza and Egypt</title>
      <description>The Israel Defense Forces said Wednesday that it had gained “tactical control over the Philadelphi corridor,” a narrow strip of land separating Gaza from Egypt, and a key target of Israel’s offensive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6910b5b0-1ddf-11ef-b5f8-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:18:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecutor drops charges against golfer Scottie Scheffler after traffic-related incident near PGA Championship</title>
      <description>Scheffler was arrested on May 17 and booked on four charges, including second-degree assault of a police officer, while driving toward Valhalla Golf Club in Louisville, site of the PGA Championship. Scheffler, the world's top-ranked golfer, called the incident "a big misunderstanding." Louisville's mayor and police chief said last week that the officer who arrested Scheffler failed to activate his body camera, in violation of policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c9b0df1-1dde-11ef-94d5-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 17:10:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Turns out their 40-year ‘secret’ was out of the bag the whole time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Turns out their 40-year ‘secret’ was out of the bag the whole time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab267030-1dd4-11ef-adf2-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury deliberations have begun in Trump’s hush money trial. Here’s what he could face if he’s convicted.</title>
      <description>Twelve New Yorkers will weigh whether former president Donald Trump, the presumptive Republican White House nominee, falsified business records connected to a hush money payment to an adult-film actress before the 2016 election. If convicted, he’s in for a mix of routine court processing and extraordinary logistical considerations, legal experts say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11dd4960-1dd1-11ef-9e82-0000a1ace929</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: Is it safe to eat at a restaurant after it was closed by the health department? Our food critic answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: Is it safe to eat at a restaurant after it was closed by the health department? Our food critic answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">520b9ab0-1dd0-11ef-bdd3-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native American children suffered pervasive sexual abuse at the Catholic-run boarding schools they were forced to attend</title>
      <description>The U.S. government took Native American children from their families and sent them to live at remote boarding schools, some of which were operated by the Catholic Church or its religious affiliates. A Post investigation uncovered decades of abuse — Catholic priests, brothers and sisters raped and molested more than 1,000 Native American children in their care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0233a090-1dc7-11ef-95ec-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Washington-area sports fans dislike or hate the Washington Commanders’ name, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Schar School poll finds that 54 percent of Washington-area sports fans say they either dislike or hate the local NFL team's name. Among just local Commanders fans, the antipathy toward the name is even more stark; 58 percent say they don’t like the name. The franchise unveiled the Commanders name, logo and uniforms in February 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a161321-1dc4-11ef-a91b-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 14:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A celebrity mountain lion’s legacy in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b91ba350-1dbf-11ef-bced-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giant pandas are returning to D.C. this year, the Smithsonian’s National Zoo announces, after reaching a lease agreement with China</title>
      <description>The new pandas — Bao Li, 2, a male, and Qing Bao, 2, a female — are coming on a 10-year lease, during which the zoo will pay the China Wildlife and Conservation Association $1 million a year, the zoo said in its announcement.

Bao Li is the son of Bao Bao, a female giant panda born at the zoo in 2013, and the grandson of Mei Xiang and Tian Tian, the panda couple whose departure from the zoo last year broke hearts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">964ec1b3-1db3-11ef-879e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump jury. Gaza pier. Pope Francis. Texas storms. Child abuse. Baseball history. Wu-Tang Clan. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d40cc10-1daa-11ef-bddd-0000a1ace7b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico City and millions of its residents could run out of water in weeks</title>
      <description>The metropolitan area gets about a quarter of its water from a system that could be unable to provide water by June 26 because of decreased rainfall and the recent El Niño pattern. Rain would help alleviate the strain, but it could also “cause a false sense of security,” one expert said, as the city grapples with poor water management and infrastructure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a0fde0-1d35-11ef-ad6a-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 21:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon suspends aid deliveries to Gaza civilians after repeated mishaps and weather damage to floating pier</title>
      <description>A U.S. service member was critically injured, four U.S. military vessels were beached, and sections of the structure were ripped free in bad weather. The pier will be towed to the Israeli port of Ashdod for repair and reassembly — a process that will take “at least a week,” according to a Pentagon official.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c896e630-1d26-11ef-b655-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 19:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family clown hopes to pivot by offering sincere support</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family clown hopes to pivot by offering sincere support</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">921748e0-1d0b-11ef-acba-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 16:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia enacts Russian-style ‘foreign agent’ law despite mass protests — a victory for Moscow</title>
      <description>The Georgian Dream party overrode a presidential veto, so now the law — which critics warn will be used to restrict free speech and squash political dissent — will pass. Georgia’s future as being part of either Moscow’s orbit or that of Western Europe hangs in the balance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01c8a5a0-1d0a-11ef-9696-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 15:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis issues a rare apology after he was accused of using a slur to refer to gay men in a closed-door session with bishops</title>
      <description>The pope’s choice of words appeared to run counter to his efforts to thaw the Catholic Church’s relationship with the LGBTQ+ community.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ad80e90-1cfd-11ef-b64f-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A famous documentary is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5d64000-1cfa-11ef-aaca-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 14:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing arguments are underway in Trump’s New York hush money trial. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>In the New York court system, the defense gives its closing argument first, followed by prosecutors. After that, jurors will get instructions from New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan and begin deliberations over whether Donald Trump, the first former U.S. president charged with a crime, falsified business records related to a payment to an adult-film actress ahead of the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">997a9730-1cf8-11ef-a96b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 13:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s trial. Rafah strike. Tornadoes. Deadly landslide. Bill Walton. Wildlife bridge. Orcas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fe34780-1ce1-11ef-80f6-000a1aced053</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid will still be here this summer. Will anyone care?</title>
      <description>Despite “FLiRT” variants, this may be the first covid wave with little federal pressure to limit transmission or data to even declare a surge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a309ebb0-1c81-11ef-8722-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 23:34:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I saw with my own eyes someone burning’: Eyewitnesses describe Israeli strike on Rafah tent camp</title>
      <description>At least 45 people were killed and dozens wounded in the Israeli airstrike late Sunday, according to the Gaza Health Ministry, which said about half of the victims were women and children. Israel’s Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu called it a “tragic accident” and promised an investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">516c88f0-1c7a-11ef-8cfd-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 22:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado watch issued for D.C. area until 11 p.m.</title>
      <description>Thunderstorms, some of which may be severe, are most probable in the Washington region between about 5 and 8 p.m. A couple tornadoes cannot be ruled out, although heavy rain, lightning and strong winds will be most widespread.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d96c3770-1c64-11ef-8179-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 20:08:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Walton dies at 71. The Basketball Hall of Famer went on to a colorful career as a commentator.</title>
      <description>Walton, a dominant college player at UCLA and a two-time NBA champion whose professional career was affected by injuries, died after a prolonged battle with cancer, the NBA announced in a statement.

“Bill Walton was truly one of a kind,” NBA Commissioner Adam Silver said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872cc950-1c52-11ef-bfaa-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:57:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It's time to shake up America's national holidays, starting with Memorial Day, Daniel Pink writes.</title>
      <description>Why not shake up America’s national holidays?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb06c1b1-1c4a-11ef-9379-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 17:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekend storms kill at least 22 people as severe weather heads toward East Coast. Here’s where it could hit next.</title>
      <description>Deadly storms producing destructive tornadoes slammed Texas, Oklahoma, Arkansas and Kentucky. Areas from Alabama to New York could see severe storms on Memorial Day afternoon and evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb19050-1c41-11ef-9d66-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 15:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunters killed off most of Florida’s wild flamingos. Now the fluorescent fowl appears to be making a comeback.</title>
      <description>Few animals are more closely associated with Florida’s iconography than the flamingo, but its numbers plummeted by the 1920s. Then Hurricane Idalia blew in several flamboyant flocks last year. Scientists feared they might fly back home, but a new Audubon Florida survey indicates they could be planning to stay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11f8be91-1c3a-11ef-a0ac-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 15:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re not messing up your shine in today’s holiday On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c8a0c90-1c2d-11ef-9ff2-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 13:29:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch in effect until midnight as potentially damaging storms approach D.C. area</title>
      <description>These storms have a long history of bringing down trees and will blast through much of the metro region between 10 p.m. and midnight. Follow the Capital Weather Gang for the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e803951-1bc8-11ef-80be-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 01:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Pretty gross’: The toxic mix of fast-rising seas and septic systems</title>
      <description>In the American South, septic systems are creating serious threats to public health and the environment as the region grapples with one of the most rapid sea level surges on Earth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f878270-1b9b-11ef-a4b5-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 20:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 26 most anticipated movies of the summer</title>
      <description>The surf is up, bringing what board riders might call a “set” of cinematic waves to theaters: Two Kevin Bacon movies! Two Shyamalan movies — a father and daughter affair! And two Kevin Costner movies! But there’s something for everyone, including, for the mavericks among us, more than a few one-offs: stories that showcase originality, verve, surprise and eccentricity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">265dcba4-1b8b-11ef-9c11-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 18:09:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08f17790-1b79-11ef-bf85-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When open houses get weird: Real estate agents dish on the horrors they’ve seen, from the gross to the dangerous</title>
      <description>Industry experts are split on whether open houses actually help sell homes, but there seem to be two universal truths about them: The practice helps agents expand their client base, and, when you welcome large numbers of random people to view a listing, extremely strange things can happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">771b0000-1b70-11ef-b9eb-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 14:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a007f90-1b64-11ef-8396-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small tortilla shops are being shaken down as Mexican cartels create vast extortion networks, expanding their grip on the economy</title>
      <description>At least 15 percent of tortillerías in Mexico — about 20,000 storefront businesses — are regularly extorted, according to the industry trade group. A decade ago only a tiny percentage were threatened. What has happened is emblematic of the criminal penetration of industries from agriculture to construction across Mexico and Latin America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0437c1-1af5-11ef-a852-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:21:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Black rising star lost his elite orchestra job. He won’t go quietly.</title>
      <description>Josh Jones, an acclaimed young classical percussionist, thinks the Kansas City Symphony dismissed him unjustly. Now he is breaking the orchestra world’s “code of silence” about hiring, firing and promotion to share his grievances. Symphony officials deny he was unfairly treated. But other musicians say he has launched a much-needed conversation about an outdated system they believe thwarts many talented young artists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d6ed2a0-1ac5-11ef-8540-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 18:35:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Sister-in-law inserts herself into our kids’ playdates. Do I say something?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Sister-in-law inserts herself into our kids’ playdates. Do I say something?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12c09800-1ab1-11ef-ace5-0000a1aceff9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 16:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Milwaukee patio becomes a battleground for Black public housing tenants, some of America’s most talked-about voters</title>
      <description>College Court Apartments residents, exasperated by the problems in their building, proposed solutions to local leaders. Instead of a response, tenants awoke a few days later to find a padlock on the gate to the patio. Recent polling suggests low-income Black voters like the ones at College Court are disappointed in Joe Biden’s presidency — but he desperately needs their votes, especially in swing states such as Wisconsin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b8c2f70-1aa4-11ef-9fa7-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 14:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efff81c0-1a9a-11ef-a706-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uvalde families announce new lawsuits alleging ‘Call of Duty’ studio, Meta and gunmaker all helped ‘groom’ shooter</title>
      <description>The lawyer who won a record-breaking settlement for Sandy Hook families alleges Daniel Defense, Activision and Meta are responsible for pushing the Robb Elementary shooter to acquire the AR-15 style weapon he used in the Texas attack. Victim relatives are intensifying their quest for accountability in civil court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42b0d6b0-1a0c-11ef-ac17-0000a1ace503</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 20:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three missionaries were killed by a gang in Haiti, an Oklahoma-based group says. Two were relatives of a Missouri lawmaker.</title>
      <description>Missouri state Rep. Ben Baker identified two of the victims as his daughter Natalie and son-in-law Davy Lloyd. They were coming out of a church Thursday evening when they were ambushed by “a gang of 3 trucks full of guys,” Missions in Haiti Inc. said on its Facebook page. A U.N.-approved international police force, led by Kenya and funded and trained largely by the United States, is preparing to deploy to the Caribbean nation to help its security forces confront gangs that now control an estimated 80 percent of the capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">995ecde0-19ef-11ef-9b0a-0000a1ace636</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 17:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some high-tech U.S. weapons in Ukraine are being defeated by Russian jamming, documents obtained by The Post show</title>
      <description>The percentage of some GPS-guided munitions, including Excalibur artillery shells, successfully hitting their targets plummeted after Russian forces deployed sophisticated electronic warfare capabilities, prompting Kyiv to abandon some Western weapons altogether. Russia’s successful jamming could serve as a blueprint for other adversaries, including China and Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3c1f520-19e3-11ef-8a4b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 15:40:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Morgan Spurlock dies at 53. His documentary ‘Super Size Me’ skewered the fast-food industry and tackled the epidemic of obesity.</title>
      <description>Spurlock’s family confirmed the Oscar-nominated director died from cancer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c44c1f30-19db-11ef-9401-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 14:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">200feb10-19d4-11ef-8297-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:47:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.N.’s top court rules that Israel must ‘immediately halt’ its military offensive in Rafah</title>
      <description>International Court of Justice rulings are legally binding but require the U.N. Security Council to enforce them. Israel’s war to destroy Hamas in the Gaza Strip has leveled large sections of the territory, killed tens of thousands of people, mostly civilians, and brought the population to the brink of famine, according to health officials. In a preliminary response to the case filed by South Africa, the ICJ in January ordered provisional measures to prevent further harm to civilians.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c25ee10-19d1-11ef-a289-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 13:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>East Coast abortion clinics have seen a surge in traffic since a Florida law banning most abortions went into effect</title>
      <description>New survey data collected by researchers at Middlebury College offers a first-of-its-kind look at the practical impact of the Florida law that banned most abortions on May 1, showing wait times at clinics increased in multiple states though a collapse in care many had predicted before the law passed has not so far materialized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84875530-19c8-11ef-a5d1-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 12:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voting map. Israel ruling. Ticketmaster lawsuit. College athletes. Hurricanes. Food prices. Holiday weekend travel. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5dfa890-19bc-11ef-a464-0000a1ace460</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges are set to pay their athletes directly after NCAA and power conferences vote to settle landmark amateurism lawsuits</title>
      <description>The NCAA’s board of governors and college athletics’ five power conferences voted to approve a settlement in the House v. NCAA case that involved former athletes suing over not being compensated for the use of their names, images and likenesses. Two related cases also would be settled under the agreement.
The terms of the settlement, which is still pending plaintiff approval and additional steps in the legal process, include a framework for revenue sharing that would lead to athletes being paid by their schools beginning in the 2025-26 school year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eca0102-1960-11ef-b637-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 23:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternate electors who tried to reverse Trump’s 2020 defeat are poised to serve as electors again in at least three states</title>
      <description>Their eagerness to serve — and encouragement to do so from their parties — reflects a widespread belief among Republicans that the electors did nothing wrong in 2020, raising the question of what they might do or say if former president Donald Trump once again loses any of those states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b8d8000-194d-11ef-bea2-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Baltimore prosecutor Marilyn Mosby sentenced to 12 months of home detention, 2 years of supervised release for fraud and perjury</title>
      <description>Mosby, who gained national prominence for charging police officers following the death of Freddie Gray, had been convicted in federal court in Maryland for lying to mortgage lenders in the process of buying two Florida vacation homes and falsely claiming financial hardship to access retirement money. Mosby has continued to deny wrongdoing, saying she was the target of a politically motivated prosecution, and has been campaigning for a presidential pardon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60fec1f0-193e-11ef-b0b1-0000a1ace832</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750f7cf1-191d-11ef-b252-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
