<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My son’s 5-month relationship ended 3 years ago. He’s still reeling.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My son’s 5-month relationship ended 3 years ago. He’s still reeling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">000bc410-f431-11ee-8900-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the war in Ukraine worsens and Russia advances on battlefield, Zelensky faces terrible options</title>
      <description>Short of soldiers, weapons and ammunition, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has no way out of a worsening war — unable to advance militarily and unwilling to surrender occupied territory to Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">078725e0-f42c-11ee-b8e0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She failed to terminate her unwanted pregnancy. It changed another woman’s life.</title>
      <description>Evelyn desperately tried to terminate her pregnancy in three states before ultimately choosing adoption. Would a long-planned reunion with her 1-year-old offer the healing she needed?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aecbe770-f425-11ee-ac84-000a1acef853</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb559bc0-f419-11ee-a052-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa beats Connecticut in women’s Final Four, will face South Carolina for national championship</title>
      <description>The Hawkeyes, led by record-setting guard Caitlin Clark, reached the national final for the second consecutive year after beating the Huskies on Friday night in Cleveland.
Earlier in the evening, South Carolina remained undefeated and secured its spot in Sunday’s final with a victory over North Carolina State.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d537c460-f3c6-11ee-9ee8-0000a1ace78d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House and Senate leaders are nearing agreement on a landmark bill aimed at protecting Americans’ privacy online</title>
      <description>The expected deal would vault Congress closer to a historic agreement lawmakers have sought for decades. It would create a mechanism to allow individuals to sue companies that violate their privacy, among other provisions, according to a person familiar with the negotiations who spoke on the condition of anonymity. Further details are expected to be announced next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26fd28b0-f3a6-11ee-81bf-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 23:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See what the solar eclipse will look like in your city</title>
      <description>Whether you see a total or partial eclipse all depends on where you are. The difference is enormous.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7365880-f38f-11ee-ba2d-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The nation’s largest assisted-living chain uses a staffing algorithm; some managers say it left facilities dangerously short-handed</title>
      <description>Brookdale Senior Living, the leading operator of senior homes with 652 facilities, acquired the algorithm-based system and used it to set staffing at its properties across the nation. But as Brookdale’s empire grew, employees complained the system, known as “Service Alignment,” failed to capture the nuances of caring for vulnerable seniors, documents and interviews show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baa2f290-f36d-11ee-a1d1-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: How do I ask my wife for an open marriage?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: How do I ask my wife for an open marriage?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c239f80-f369-11ee-9242-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.7-magnitude earthquake hits New York City area, according to USGS</title>
      <description>The small quake was centered in suburban Lebanon, N.J., according to the United States Geological Survey. Social media users reported feeling it from New England to Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4586710-f35b-11ee-aefd-0000a1ace909</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5350c70-f350-11ee-b016-0000a1ace334</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added 303,000 jobs in March, reflecting a surprisingly booming labor market that continues to beat predictions</title>
      <description>The labor market continues to churn out jobs at a healthy pace, thanks in part to the leisure and hospitality sector, even as interest rates remain high, according to the latest data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfaf2160-f348-11ee-b807-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump case. Gaza aid. Airport security. ALS drug. Snowstorm. Final Four. Salmon crash. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a69b7510-f33b-11ee-a736-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli investigation finds the strike that killed seven World Central Kitchen aid workers was in ‘serious violation’ of procedures</title>
      <description>The Israeli Defense Forces said the decision to strike the vehicles was made in error and came after the IDF misidentified vehicles in the aid convoy as carrying Hamas operatives. It also found the IDF drone operators were not made aware of the aid convoy’s coordination plan, and the aid group’s logo was not visible to the cameras tracking the vehicles at night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91216911-f33b-11ee-8418-000a1ace137f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel announces new Gaza aid routes after Biden demands more humanitarian relief in call with Netanyahu</title>
      <description>Israel’s war cabinet announced new measures to allow more aid into Gaza, including the opening of the Erez border crossing, after a call between President Biden and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Thursday morning. Biden warned that U.S. policy toward Israel could change if Israel did not take steps to protect noncombatants and boost aid to Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1429aa0-f2f0-11ee-96c3-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What starvation is doing to Gaza’s children</title>
      <description>Hundreds of thousands of children in Gaza are going hungry. Even if more aid arrives, experts say the damage will be lasting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd302970-f2d2-11ee-b755-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where, when and how to watch the solar eclipse — and what it will look like: Your ultimate guide</title>
      <description>On Monday, a total solar eclipse will sweep across North America, blocking out the sun momentarily for millions of viewers along a path stretching from northern Mexico to Maine. We won’t see another until 2044. Here’s everything you need to know to prepare for this rare celestial phenomenon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a24069b0-f2ca-11ee-85d9-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Cannon rejects Trump’s bid to dismiss classified documents case based on Presidential Records Act</title>
      <description>The ruling could avert a looming standoff between special counsel Jack Smith and Judge Aileen M. Cannon. It comes two days after Smith said the judge was pursuing a legal premise that was “wrong,” and urged her to rule quickly so that he would have the option of appealing before trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcb36911-f2b6-11ee-b984-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist group No Labels says it will not field a ticket in the 2024 presidential election</title>
      <description>The group said in a statement that it had not identified candidates “with a credible path to winning the White House” and that the “responsible course of action is for us to stand down.” Allies of President Biden sought to discourage the group from moving forward with a ticket they feared could help Donald Trump at the polls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d3511b1-f2b5-11ee-aec1-0000a1ace470</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. policy toward Israel will change unless it heeds Biden on Gaza aid and civilian protections, Blinken suggests</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken spoke to reporters following President Biden’s call with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. The warning lacked specifics and came as the Biden administration continued to approve the transfer of thousands of bombs to Israel despite calls to condition aid in the aftermath of the Israeli airstrike that killed seven aid workers with the World Central Kitchen charity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baccef30-f2b1-11ee-898b-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to resist the burn of a caustic sense of humor?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to resist the burn of a caustic sense of humor?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b73444a0-f29c-11ee-974d-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 16:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasters warn of an ‘extremely active’ Atlantic hurricane season this year, with 23 named storms</title>
      <description>The hurricane season could be one of the busiest in years because of record warm oceans and the expected demise of the El Niño climate pattern. The forecasters at Colorado State University also said the conditions raise the odds for storms to hit the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b3ae040-f298-11ee-92b7-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 15:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a rare move, the maker of a failed ALS drug removes it from the market weeks after disappointing trial results</title>
      <description>Amylyx Pharmaceuticals said it had started the process to remove its drug, called Relyvrio in the United States and Albrioza in Canada, adding that it will not be available for new amyotrophic lateral sclerosis patients effective immediately while existing patients can be transitioned to a “free drug program.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e478170-f28d-11ee-8c6c-0000a1ace1bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 14:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. proceeded with approval of thousands of more bombs to Israel on same day of strike that killed 7 World Central Kitchen workers</title>
      <description>The decision to green light the arms demonstrates President Biden’s determination to continue the flow of lethal weaponry to Israel despite the widely-condemned incident he said he was “outraged and heartbroken” about.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9cce0f0-f288-11ee-8fee-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A book bound in what?!? Play today’s On the Record to find out</title>
      <description>Earn your Thursday points now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">956e88e0-f287-11ee-9c1a-0000a1ace98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. awards $20 billion to help finance clean-energy projects, with a focus on disadvantaged communities</title>
      <description>The action by the Environmental Protection Agency is one of the Biden administration’s largest investments in combating climate change and promoting environmental justice. Because of the money involved, it is sure to be closely watched by opponents and supporters of the nation’s energy transition.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0beb8e31-f27b-11ee-9432-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 12:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza aid. Taiwan quake. Snowstorm. Green banks. Sepsis test. AI comedy. Moon time. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8075a050-f272-11ee-a205-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Food and dietitian influencers are pushing ‘anti-diet’ advice even as obesity rises</title>
      <description>The anti-diet movement, which began as an effort to combat weight stigma and an unhealthy obsession with thinness, is now drawing global food marketers. One company in particular, General Mills, maker of Cocoa Puffs and Lucky Charms cereals, has launched a multi-pronged campaign that capitalizes on anti-diet teachings, an investigation by The Washington Post and The Examination, a nonprofit newsroom that covers global public health, has found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8699b520-f1e1-11ee-8aa7-0000a1acecb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Ignatius and Jim Geraghty just visited Ukraine. Listen to them describe what they saw in the latest episode of ‘Impromptu.’</title>
      <description>What we saw on the ground in Ukraine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7725790-f1dd-11ee-8b90-000a1ace17c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: How do you keep salad from wilting so quickly in the refrigerator? Our food writers answer your questions.</title>
      <description>Food writers Aaron Hutcherson and Becky Krystal answer your cooking conundrums in their weekly chat. Today’s topics include cooking wines and garlic clove sizing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20d3de91-f1d8-11ee-ad26-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith fires back at Judge Cannon’s order that could disrupt Trump classified documents case</title>
      <description>The prosecutor asked U.S. Judge Aileen M. Cannon to rule quickly on Donald Trump's claim that he is protected by the Presidential Records Act, so the government can appeal before trial. The filing represents the most stark and high-stakes confrontation yet between Cannon and the special counsel, illustrating the extent to which a ruling that legitimizes Trump's position could eviscerate the historic case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed104aa8-f1d5-11ee-bc44-000a1ace7d81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How do you get over someone you don’t want to get over?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How do you get over someone you don’t want to get over?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc76570-f1d3-11ee-8fa1-000a1ace4fbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Name that coach in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">528b86a0-f1be-11ee-b348-000a1ace2984</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan earthquake. Israeli strike. Trump rebuke. Russia warning. Bird flu. Keto diet. Eclipse lawsuit. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52010670-f1a9-11ee-bc4e-0000a1ace3d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 7.4 earthquake prompts tsunami alerts in Taiwan, Japan</title>
      <description>The earthquake off the east coast of Taiwan was the largest recorded in 25 years and was followed by several aftershocks, leading authorities to tell people on Taiwan's east coast and one of Japan's southern islands to take shelter and seek higher ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9efe4710-f156-11ee-bd39-0000a1ace581</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 01:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council votes to spend $515 million to modernize Capital One Arena after Ted Leonsis agrees to keep Wizards, Caps in the city</title>
      <description>The move is separate from a nonbinding, 14-page term sheet detailing the more specific elements of an agreement signed last week between D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) and Leonsis, the teams' owner, to keep the teams playing downtown. The funds, which will be spent over the next three years, also will go toward helping Leonsis’s company expand into part of the area surrounding the arena.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d1a6011-f13c-11ee-b10c-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft faulted by government review board for a ‘cascade’ of failures in Chinese hack</title>
      <description>The independent Cyber Safety Review Board’s report knocks the tech giant for shoddy cybersecurity practices, lax corporate culture and a deliberate lack of transparency in obscuring the origins of the breach that targeted Cabinet and top State Department officials, including the U.S. ambassador to China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e187da0-f139-11ee-bcf2-0000a1ace01b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gave Russia a specific warning about terrorist plot against concert hall over two weeks before the attack, officials say</title>
      <description>More than two weeks before the bloody assault at Crocus City Hall in suburban Moscow, the U.S. government shared highly specific information about the possible location of a terrorist plot, according to people familiar with the outreach. That directly contradicts Russia’s claims that the warning was too general to prevent an attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c38e8a0-f134-11ee-9fbe-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: The relative he’s avoiding happens to be Black. Coincidence?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: The relative he’s avoiding happens to be Black. Coincidence?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85c110d0-f10f-11ee-84a4-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Moore, a rising Democratic star, showcases his ‘won’t flinch’ attitude amid the Key Bridge crisis</title>
      <description>The freshman Maryland governor was an ascendant figure for Democrats who had already faced high expectations. Now he tackles his first major test in a moment of crisis. A behind-the-scenes look at how a rising political star confronted a catastrophe — and the bigger challenge that lies ahead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53170000-f109-11ee-8585-0000a1aceb9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some chatter about a magpie in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58110bf0-f0f5-11ee-95e7-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says Israeli forces ‘unintentionally hit innocent people’ after World Central Kitchen says strike killed 7 workers</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s comments were the first in which Israel directly took responsibility for the attack. “Unfortunately, there was a tragic incident in which our forces unintentionally hit innocent people in the Gaza Strip,” Netanyahu said. “As it happens in war, we are investigating the matter fully, we are in contact with the governments, and we will do everything possible to prevent this from happening again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">643f72b0-f0e9-11ee-937f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump bond. Abortion ban. Alex Murdaugh. Bird flu. Google data. Caitlin Clark. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26633340-f0e0-11ee-8d08-0000a1acedc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Central Kitchen suspends aid operations in Gaza, says 7 workers killed in Israeli strike</title>
      <description>The food aid nonprofit said in a statement that the dead included a U.S.-Canada dual national. The Israel Defense Forces said earlier it was aware of reports of the incident and was conducting a “thorough review.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93760fd0-f0bc-11ee-9c43-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The women’s Final Four is set: Connecticut, Iowa, South Carolina and North Carolina State will play for a national championship</title>
      <description>Undefeated top overall seed South Carolina will face No. 3 seed N.C. State in one national semifinal Friday in Cleveland, and No. 1 seed Iowa will meet No. 3 seed Connecticut in the other.
The semifinal winners will play Sunday afternoon for the national title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42e23300-f0a3-11ee-b919-0000a1ace729</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military launches investigation after reports of World Central Kitchen aid workers killed in Gaza strike</title>
      <description>The food aid nonprofit’s founder, celebrity chef José Andrés, said that several employees had been killed in an Israeli strike. The Israel Defense Forces said it was aware of the allegations and would conduct “a thorough review” after photos appearing to show the killed aid workers circulated on social media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae5d5e0-f08a-11ee-a653-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump posts $175 million bond to keep N.Y. authorities from seizing his property after civil fraud judgment</title>
      <description>The former president’s posting of the bond was necessary to keep New York Attorney General Letitia James from initiating legal steps to take over his properties, including Trump Tower. An appeals court panel recently ruled to reduce the bond from $464 million in the massive civil fraud judgment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6fcc340-f087-11ee-8dc5-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rematch of 2023 title game, Caitlin Clark and Iowa face Angel Reese and LSU for spot in Final Four. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>After their epic, taunt-filled matchup in last year’s national championship game, Clark’s Hawkeyes are about to take on Reese’s Tigers in the NCAA women’s basketball tournament’s Albany Region 2 final.
Follow our coverage for live updates, highlights and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b5cd4e1-f07b-11ee-a5d0-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our reporters went into Gaza’s largest hospital for the first time in months. Mass destruction and the smell of death awaited them.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters were among a handful of foreign journalists taken inside al-Shifa hospital in Gaza City by the Israeli military on Sunday after two weeks of heavy fighting with militants. The hospital, once Gaza’s premier medical facility, has been destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ce8d21-f06f-11ee-90a5-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Supreme Court allows strict state abortion ban to take effect, but greenlights putting the issue on the November ballot</title>
      <description>Florida’s conservative high court ruled that the state’s constitution does not protect abortion rights. But in a separate decision it also ruled that voters can decide in November whether an amendment enshrining the right to an abortion should be approved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d289dbf0-f064-11ee-b815-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
