<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 13:03:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Jan. 6 case. Ukraine aid. ‘Rust’ sentencing. Coral bleaching. Caitlin Clark. Abba and Biggie. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7af6ba20-fbe0-11ee-969e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They were liberal public school teachers. Now they teach kids to be anti-‘woke.’</title>
      <description>Kali and Joshua Fontanilla taught English in a deep-blue California district — but quit their jobs and moved to Florida to start their own school after growing convinced the curriculum was left-wing propaganda. While the claim that public schools promote left-wing “indoctrination” has become a commonplace on the right, it’s not usually an allegation repeated by teachers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24f6cbc0-fb85-11ee-981d-0000a1aced49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fever selects Caitlin Clark with first pick in WNBA draft, officially launching her professional basketball career</title>
      <description>Clark, a record-setting guard at the University of Iowa, was virtually certain to be taken with the No. 1 pick once she announced in February that she would enter this year’s draft. She joins the WNBA shouldering unprecedented expectations to increase its visibility after her college games drew sellout crowds and record television ratings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d631b981-fb81-11ee-99d0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 23:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Idaho ban on gender-affirming care for minors to take effect as case continues</title>
      <description>While the underlying case concerns the constitutionality of a ban on gender-affirming medical care for minors, the court’s order did not address the merits of the issue – only whether the law could take effect for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85622ae0-fb76-11ee-8348-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 22:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for region until 10 p.m.</title>
      <description>Hit-or-miss storms could produce large hail and damaging wind gusts, in addition to dangerous lightning. The threat for storms gradually shifts southward through the region during the afternoon and into the evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86d6fe20-fb56-11ee-ad8b-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Rust’ armorer sentenced to 18 months for involuntary manslaughter in fatal on-set shooting of cinematographer</title>
      <description>Hannah Gutierrez-Reed was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter in June. She was accused of failing to ensure gun safety on the set of the low-budget Western movie in 2021. Alec Baldwin was rehearsing with a revolver on set when the gun went off, killing cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and wounding director Joel Souza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">192ae410-fb54-11ee-bb3f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you afford to buy a house? Take our quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>Homeownership is how many Americans accumulate wealth, but affording a home is a growing challenge for many. Mortgage rates have more than doubled and are now at nearly 7 percent on a typical 30-year loan. So, should you buy a home right now? To help you decide, take this quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3f17d0-fb4a-11ee-840c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27864bb0-fb42-11ee-9eed-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This should be a global wake-up call’: Corals are bleaching in every corner of the ocean, threatening its web of life, scientists say</title>
      <description>The fourth-ever bleaching event in history, declared by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration and International Coral Reef Initiative, is the second in a decade. More than 54 percent of all the reef areas on the planet have experienced bleaching-level heat stress in the past year, and the overall amount could soon pass a record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bb41d0-fb39-11ee-a5c4-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla to shed more than 10 percent of its workforce as EV demand cools</title>
      <description>The move by CEO Elon Musk comes after the company, which employed more than 140,000 as of December, reported a sharp decline in vehicle deliveries in the first quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5664cd01-fb31-11ee-ac6b-0000a1ace217</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A historical location hosts a film festival in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bff74450-fb2c-11ee-9274-000a1aced311</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump arrives for the start of his hush money trial, the first criminal prosecution of a former U.S. president. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Jury selection is set to begin this morning in Manhattan, where Donald Trump is charged with falsifying business records ahead of the 2016 election to hide payments made to keep an adult-film actress quiet about an alleged sexual tryst.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2d784b1-fb29-11ee-bc53-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal criminal investigation opened into crash that brought down Baltimore’s Key Bridge</title>
      <description>Six construction workers died after the container ship Dali lost power and slammed into a pillar of the Francis Scott Key Bridge on March 26 in the Port of Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a69a7a80-fb19-11ee-ac8d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s lawyers have done all they could to delay his criminal trials. The first one is set to start today.</title>
      <description>The former president's lawyers have pledged to argue every motion and request every possible document, hoping to delay his trials beyond November's election, people familiar with the strategy say. They have succeeded so far with pushing back Trump's trials in D.C., Florida and Georgia. But jury selection in the New York hush money case is slated to begin this morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d89de00-fb17-11ee-aa43-000a1ace4f60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Iran attack. Sydney stabbing. Trans bill. Tax Day. Scottie Scheffler. Pompeii paintings. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4da4f561-fb17-11ee-84cf-0000a1ace681</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottie Scheffler wins the Masters, securing his second green jacket in the past three years</title>
      <description>The world's No. 1 player finished the job Sunday after beginning the final round with a one-shot lead and holding off challenges by Ludvig Aberg and Max Homa. It was the second career major title for Scheffler, 27, who captured his first green jacket in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f62a10-fab4-11ee-a369-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could you judge Trump impartially if you were on his hush money trial jury? Here’s what 12 New Yorkers said.</title>
      <description>When Donald Trump walks into a Manhattan courtroom on Monday, it will kick off a process unprecedented in American history: jury selection for a former president’s criminal trial. He is facing 34 felony charges for allegedly falsifying business records related to a hush money payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels during the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2770da10-faa1-11ee-8ba6-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 20:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This senator wants an online privacy law. She has slowed efforts for years.</title>
      <description>Sen. Maria Cantwell (D-Wash.) has been a primary reason for an impasse on legislation, according to more than a dozen current and former congressional aides in both parties, and others familiar with the dynamics of the committee she chairs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2641ea40-fa91-11ee-b2c7-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 18:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-time investors in Trump’s Truth Social see their share values plunge — and see it as a test of faith</title>
      <description>The company has lost $3.5 billion in value since its public debut last month. But for some investors, the stock is a badge of honor — a way to show their devotion beyond buying Donald Trump’s merchandise, visiting Trump golf courses or donating to Trump’s presidential campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18c5b021-fa84-11ee-9510-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3b32000-fa7f-11ee-8ac5-0000a1acecc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now it’s up to Israel: De-escalate or retaliate against Iran? Max Boot writes about what could come next.</title>
      <description>Tehran’s barrage of drones and missiles was a face-saving maneuver, successfully repulsed. But the possibility of matters spinning out of control still looms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b082360-fa7a-11ee-8719-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 16:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas county at center of the border fight is overwhelmed by migrant deaths</title>
      <description>Record-level migration has brought record-breaking death to Maverick County, a border community that is ground zero in the feud between Texas and the Biden administration over migration.

First responders have run out of body bags and burial plots. Their rescue boats and recovery trucks are covered in dents and scratches. County officials say they don’t have the training or supplies to collect DNA samples of each unidentified migrant as required by state law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f59cd000-fa70-11ee-b239-0000a1acecb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 15:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48be9560-fa63-11ee-bea3-0000a1acebf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 13:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. forces have shot down Iranian attack drones targeting Israel, officials said</title>
      <description>The United States, attempting to walk a line of helping its ally without getting pulled deeper into a regional war, has targeted and downed some of the Iranian drones fired at Israel on Saturday, two U.S. officials confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab2af31-f9eb-11ee-b3d6-000a1ace491b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 23:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military says multiple drones launched from Iran now headed toward Israel. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The drones would take several hours to reach Israeli territory, a military spokesman said in a statement. Israel and the United States had braced for the attack after an Israeli strike in Damascus killed senior members of Iran’s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bac06ce0-f9d4-11ee-bc70-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our reviewer tried living with a $699 AI device on his chest. You probably shouldn’t bother with the Star Trek-style pin.</title>
      <description>If you’ve ever watched Star Trek characters tap their badges to communicate, you basically know how to use the AI Pin, meant to be worn on a shirt as it answers questions and sends messages. There’s a glimmer of a good product here, but using it can quickly get frustrating, Chris Velazco writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">791febc1-f9c6-11ee-87af-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 18:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cheating scandal rocked the D.C. bar trivia scene. Here’s how it unfolded — and why so many people care.</title>
      <description>A team that won Red Bear Brewing Co.’s Wednesday trivia night several weeks running was found to be cheating using an Apple Watch. We had to investigate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d429b60-f9bc-11ee-adf2-000a1ace1bd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I want to move out. My parents might guilt me into staying.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I want to move out. My parents might guilt me into staying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71224b50-f9af-11ee-a79a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We mapped nature across the U.S., neighborhood by neighborhood. Look up where you live.</title>
      <description>Spending time in nature is linked to a longer, healthier life. But nature is not distributed fairly across the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c29de1-f9a7-11ee-ab49-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today?</title>
      <description>Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">135743f0-f99a-11ee-8482-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it has seized a Portugal-flagged ship near the Strait of Hormuz, saying the vessel is ‘connected to’ Israel</title>
      <description>Iranian state media shared a video that appeared to show a person rappelling from a helicopter to board a ship, which the report identified as the MSC Aries. The region has been on alert for Tehran’s promised retaliation to an Israeli strike near Iran’s embassy in Syria that killed two senior members of Iran’s Revolutionary Guard this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3cf7f50-f987-11ee-b69b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A man killed five in a stabbing attack at an upscale mall in Sydney’s Bondi Junction before being shot dead, Australian police said</title>
      <description>Several are injured, including a small child, police said, adding that the attacker is not known to the police, and the motive is not clear. Police are carrying out a critical incident investigation and say they have not ruled out terrorism as a motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">112f96e0-f977-11ee-8ba6-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mysterious condition is striking young, highly trained athletes</title>
      <description>First described more than 150 years ago, POTS has proliferated since the coronavirus pandemic. The syndrome tends to strike suddenly, leaving previously healthy people unable to function, with no clear cause. In recent years, doctors have noticed a curious and disproportionate subset of patients: female athletes at peak fitness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d394140-f900-11ee-a372-0000a1aceb39</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Shellfish could kill me. My dad’s family doesn’t care.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Shellfish could kill me. My dad’s family doesn’t care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a30988c0-f8ee-11ee-b242-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 17:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert MacNeil dies at 93. The broadcast journalist helped start what is now ‘PBS NewsHour.’</title>
      <description>MacNeil and co-anchor Jim Lehrer formed one of television journalism’s most successful and enduring partnerships in 1975, when they launched what became “The PBS NewsHour.” For two decades, MacNeil served as an urbane, evenhanded co-anchor, maintaining a reputation for sober, straightforward reporting and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a599a650-f8ea-11ee-b53e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. hikes cost of oil drilling on federal lands for first time in decades, a bid to generate more money for taxpayers</title>
      <description>The Interior Department rule represents the first comprehensive update to the federal oil and gas leasing program in more than 30 years. It will force oil companies to pay at least 10 times more to drill on U.S. lands — $150,000 up from $10,000 — plus higher royalties. The rule also aims to prevent taxpayers from footing the bill for cleanup of abandoned oil and gas wells.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">169b0a10-f8e6-11ee-90ce-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 16:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels’s other court battle: A multimillion-dollar horse feud</title>
      <description>As Stormy Daniels prepares to take center stage in Donald Trump’s New York hush money trial, she’s also embroiled in a far less high-profile legal battle in Texas: a clash in the horse world that has ensnared some of the top officials in the rarefied world of competitive English riding. That bitter dispute shows the same dynamics that have defined Daniels’s existence on the national stage — questions about her credibility, the adulation of supporters who say she’s standing up for the truth and a large amount of money at stake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">465a54d0-f8dd-11ee-8f7e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 14:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.

URL:</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d19457b0-f8d0-11ee-9115-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A narco revolt takes a once-peaceful nation to the brink</title>
      <description>Ecuador’s young president declared war on the country’s powerful drug gangs after they sparked a wave of violence, including killings, kidnappings and car bombs. The Post has reconstructed the day Ecuador nearly collapsed when organized-crime groups, which have vastly expanded their influence across Latin America, launched attacks on the police, seized a TV station and rioted in prisons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f2198a0-f8cc-11ee-8cb4-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O.J. Simpson. Student debt. Israel-Gaza war. Harvard tests. Shohei Ohtani. iPhone repairs. Castaways. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce436480-f8bb-11ee-a20c-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What O.J. Simpson and his murder trial told us about race in America</title>
      <description>The nation’s view of Simpson's 1995 acquittal in the murders of his ex-wife, Nicole Brown Simpson, and a friend, Ronald Goldman, largely fell along racial lines, though time has bridged some of the gap.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c04080c0-f857-11ee-bedd-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 23:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the massive Baltimore bridge cleanup works, step by step</title>
      <description>Using massive barges and floating cranes, crews are clearing the hulking pieces of steel and hunks of concrete that have crippled the Port of Baltimore and spread economic pain locally and nationally. Here is exactly what they’re doing in the water.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d118b2c0-f846-11ee-b6b4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 21:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women in states with bans often take abortion pills alone and afraid. They share their experiences.</title>
      <description>Overwhelming evidence shows that taking abortion pills is safe and effective. But as more women in states where abortion is illegal choose to end their pregnancies on their own, without directly interacting with a medical professional, they are thrust into a largely ad hoc, unregulated system of online and grass-roots abortion pill distributors. The experience can be confusing, scary and, at times, deeply traumatic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0afbf4a0-f83a-11ee-a458-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 19:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani’s ex-interpreter faces federal charges for allegedly stealing $16 million from MLB star to cover gambling debts</title>
      <description>Federal prosecutors announced Thursday that they have charged the interpreter, Ippei Mizuhara, with bank fraud, alleging he impersonated the Los Angeles Dodgers star to access his bank accounts and pay off illegal gambling debts, a major turn in a scandal that rocked baseball. Ohtani “is a victim,” prosecutors said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21dade40-f82e-11ee-946a-0000a1ace994</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 18:05:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plans to expand two national monuments in California, a victory for tribes and environmentalists</title>
      <description>President Biden plans to enlarge the boundaries of two national monuments near Los Angeles and the Bay Area in the coming weeks, aiming to bolster his conservation record and increase access to nature for disadvantaged communities, according to two people briefed on the matter. Biden is expected to sign proclamations expanding the San Gabriel Mountains National Monument and the Berryessa Snow Mountain National Monument. The exact timing has not been finalized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dc92b40-f821-11ee-8930-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She makes liberal use of silent treatment in her friend group</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She makes liberal use of silent treatment in her friend group</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1234fa0-f81c-11ee-bc9d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Longest-serving liberal on Wisconsin Supreme Court won’t run again, potentially upending swing-state court after $50 million race</title>
      <description>Justice Ann Walsh Bradley’s retirement gives conservatives their last chance in the coming years to win a majority after losing last year’s race, the most expensive judicial contest in U.S. history. The court with 4-3 votes upheld Joe Biden’s win and ended a GOP gerrymander. It could soon decide whether abortion remains legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">404998e0-f819-11ee-a7ec-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 15:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>O.J. Simpson dies at 76. His murder trial led the former NFL star to become a symbol of domestic violence and racial division.</title>
      <description>Simpson died of cancer on Wednesday, his family announced on X. In a trial that riveted the nation, Simpson was found not guilty in 1995 of murdering his ex-wife and her friend, though he was later found liable in a civil judgment. He spent years in jail on unrelated charges — a stunning downfall for a man who had risen from a San Francisco slum to become one of the greatest running backs in football history, an actor in more than 20 movies, a corporate pitchman and a TV sports commentator.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15c795e0-f814-11ee-a29f-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 14:59:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The anniversary of a record-breaking moment in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e659120-f807-11ee-834d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: The Post’s climate summit with John Podesta, Maryland Gov. Wes Moore, Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala and many more leaders</title>
      <description>Record-breaking temperatures, massive investments in clean energy and a growing public recognition of the effects of global warming are ushering humanity into a new climate era. Join The Washington Post for powerful conversations about the tipping points shaping the future of the planet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6dacb710-f803-11ee-ac3b-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 13:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
