<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 04:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Former Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro must begin 27-year sentence for coup attempt after he exhausted all appeals, court rules</title>
      <description>In a final ruling, Brazil’s Supreme Court upheld Bolsonaro’s conviction for attempting a coup, attempting the violent abolition of the democratic rule of law and other charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37d3e770-ca3f-11f0-b4b3-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) will not run for fourth term, a decision bound to usher in a competitive mayoral race</title>
      <description>Bowser’s seismic decision will bring to a close more than a decade in leadership overseeing some of the city’s most booming times and also its most turbulent crises this century. In an interview Monday night with The Washington Post, Bowser, 53, said that “we’ve accomplished what we set out to accomplish.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bde37e0-ca33-11f0-ab64-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC’s new top deputy had ordered his state health department to stop promoting mass vaccinations amid a flu surge</title>
      <description>Ralph Abraham, who is Louisiana’s surgeon general, has been hired as the principal deputy director at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, according to a spokesperson for the Health and Human Services Department. The CDC currently has no permanent director, so Abraham would essentially be running the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f74de290-ca26-11f0-8f1f-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA will abandon air pollution rule that the agency has said would prevent thousands of U.S. deaths</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency will no longer defend Biden-era limits on fine-particle pollution, which causes heart and lung disease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">539894e0-ca23-11f0-8bab-0000a1ace676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After he postponed wedding, fiancée split and took the sympathy with her</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After he postponed wedding, fiancée split and took the sympathy with her</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">734a9fc0-ca20-11f0-8bab-0000a1ace676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan’s president: I will boost defense spending to protect our democracy</title>
      <description>An unprecedented military buildup by Beijing threatens peace and stability in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44ec10c1-ca19-11f0-b577-0000a1ace712</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s going on with Trump’s gold ‘Oval Office’ sign?</title>
      <description>Online, naysayers have compared the ornate font to the one used in the Cheesecake Factory logo or the fanciful typefaces used to make “Live, Laugh, Love” signs. A White House spokesperson swiped back: “President Trump is making the White House beautiful and giving it the glory it deserves. Only people with a severe case of Trump Derangement Syndrome would find a problem with that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e55bbc40-ca0f-11f0-b487-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sudden resignation in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76f3de30-ca0b-11f0-9281-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey case. Ukraine talks. Oval Office sign. Gaza winter. AI hiring bias. Sleep apnea. Thanksgiving cost. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cbafab0-c9f6-11f0-9698-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 33 definitive rules of road trips</title>
      <description>A manual for drivers and passengers who want to get along.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22ace1e6-c999-11f0-9cb8-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says it will investigate Sen. Mark Kelly (D-Arizona) after controversial video</title>
      <description>The announcement Monday follows a viral video posted last week in which Kelly, a combat veteran, and five other Democratic colleagues reminded U.S. service members of their duty to disobey unlawful orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">795a3771-c969-11f0-9cd7-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses cases against James Comey and Letitia James, rules prosecutor appointment unlawful</title>
      <description>The decision disqualifying Lindsey Halligan as U.S. attorney sets back Trump’s efforts to use the Justice Department to target perceived rivals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b7c4350-c95f-11f0-820e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Two affairs and a big lie later, can their marriage be saved?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Two affairs and a big lie later, can their marriage be saved?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56999993-c957-11f0-b19b-0000a1ace85c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A witness exposes unusual tactics used to prop up mortgage fraud cases</title>
      <description>The witness in the Sen. Adam Schiff (D-California) case exposed surprising revelations about Trump officials and their attempts to reach an indictment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3fdb620-c94f-11f0-9894-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chatting with AI bots in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79428931-c947-11f0-9f69-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Andy Beshear: This slap in the face to rural America is a chance to turn it blue</title>
      <description>Democrats should be the party of aspiration — and talk like normal human beings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2e630a1-c93f-11f0-b6a1-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Cliff, Jamaican reggae star with global following, dies at 81</title>
      <description>His lead performance as a singer turned outlaw in the 1972 film “The Harder They Come” helped introduce reggae to the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b00da7e1-c935-11f0-8127-0000a1ace7c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:01:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. MAGA divide. Power shutoffs. ICE raids. ‘Forever chemicals.’ Cancer screening. Visual effects quiz. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11345900-c92d-11f0-ae7a-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s resignation is a sign of a possible turning point for Trump’s term</title>
      <description>Recent developments suggest a potential rebellion within the Republican Party as President Donald Trump struggles with low poll numbers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c46d8e91-c8b7-11f0-a0ff-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 22:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hulking home addition in Virginia is dividing neighbors and stumping officials</title>
      <description>The construction has driven a split into a leafy neighborhood of mostly one- and two-story homes, and the bad feelings have spilled out into Facebook screeds, awkward encounters and in-person harassment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4203a3b2-c8a1-11f0-87bf-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 19:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">557b71b0-c88e-11f0-8e3e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 17:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent writes: It’s time to end the filibuster</title>
      <description>Senate Republicans should not shy from doing what Democrats are certain to do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4b1bdc1-c881-11f0-9582-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2055b050-c879-11f0-a3a9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These people had near-death experiences. Here’s how it changed their lives.</title>
      <description>No experience is exactly the same, but there are some commonly reported features, such as seeing a brilliant light, feeling a sense of peace, or having the sensation of leaving one’s body or being drawn into a tunnel. However it might look, these events can permanently affect a person’s life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0dcd4d60-c876-11f0-a0a4-0000a1ace444</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:09:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spirit falls in NWSL final as Rose Lavelle powers Gotham to title</title>
      <description>The Washington Spirit lost, 1-0, to Gotham FC in the NWSL final Saturday night in San Jose. Gotham won its second title in three years. Washington was seeking its second league championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41bb5c10-c81d-11f0-8a4f-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 03:34:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine’s Zelensky faces an agonizing choice. David Ignatius has the latest from the Trump administration’s new push for peace.</title>
      <description>U.S. officials tell me Trump’s peace plan is flexible, but a painful decision lies at its core.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7862d00-c804-11f0-b38f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez built her own political machine. Now she’s deciding her next move.</title>
      <description>Seven years after she leapt onto the national stage as an outsider, the New York Democrat is considering a run for Senate or president and has become one of the party’s most significant leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34eaebc0-c7e3-11f0-b67c-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 20:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House blew past legal concerns in deadly strikes on drug boats</title>
      <description>The Trump administration sidestepped skeptical lawyers across national security agencies as it pursued a military campaign against alleged narcotraffickers, according to multiple current and former officials familiar with the debates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33c37d60-c7d0-11f0-9f6a-00000a1ace8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N. climate talks fizzle out 10 years after Paris accord</title>
      <description>Nearly 200 countries reached an agreement in Brazil Saturday that makes no mention of curtailing the use of fossil fuels, the main drivers of climate change. The deal represents a win for the oil, gas and coal industries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42abfe40-c7c8-11f0-99c7-0000a1ace378</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:25:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our top 10 favorite books of the year, as selected by the staff of The Washington Post’s Book World</title>
      <description>The list includes debut novels by Kate Riley and Lucas Schaefer, nonfiction about the American Revolution and women in the Soviet Union, and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ca73cb0-c7b4-11f0-a1f5-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:03:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a11bdf0-c7b1-11f0-b780-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene announces she is resigning from Congress in the wake of a feud with Trump</title>
      <description>The longtime MAGA supporter says she is stepping down as of Jan. 5.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9774750-c743-11f0-975d-0000a1aced15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 01:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court justice temporarily pauses order blocking Texas map favoring GOP</title>
      <description>The order will give the high court time to consider an appeal by Texas, which is seeking to overturn the ruling by a panel of federal judges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea2c6350-c73f-11f0-bbce-0000a1ace5f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 01:09:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top FDA drug regulator raises alarms about expediting approvals, arguing they could threaten Americans’ safety</title>
      <description>Richard Pazdur, who assumed his new role this month, has warned that new Trump administration initiatives could be illegal and pose a risk to public health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f26a0b10-c737-11f0-8bd3-000a1ace6340</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 00:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former U-Va. student given five life sentences in shooting that killed three classmates</title>
      <description>Christopher Darnell Jones Jr. pleaded guilty last year to three counts of first-degree murder in the 2022 shootings on the University of Virginia campus. Two other students were injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08d108c0-c730-11f0-9f2b-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks IRS from sharing data with DHS for immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>Immigration officials had asked the tax agency for help locating 1.2 million suspected undocumented immigrants in August.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4025481-c72e-11f0-ab85-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 23:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pivots from bashing Mamdani, predicting he will ‘do a great job’ as New York City’s mayor</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump warmed to Mayor-elect Zohran Mamdani, even declaring he would finally feel comfortable moving back to the city with the 34-year-old democratic socialist running city hall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56744dc0-c727-11f0-927c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:13:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This is not regime change’: María Corina Machado’s message to Americans</title>
      <description>‘This is not regime change’: María Corina Machado’s message to Americans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dad5be80-c71f-11f0-927c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Evict ‘at risk’ sister from family home you inherited?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Evict ‘at risk’ sister from family home you inherited?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59ff0ce0-c700-11f0-ae93-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the ultrarich seized unprecedented power over American politics</title>
      <description>The concentration of wealth among the richest Americans is unlike anything in history — and so is billionaires’ influence in politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">084788e1-c6ed-11f0-8eb6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b571e00-c6e7-11f0-b310-0000a1ace87d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pushing Ukraine to sign peace deal by Thanksgiving or lose support</title>
      <description>The U.S. is now sending signals that everything could be off the table if Kyiv does not quickly sign a proposal that was drawn up by special envoy Steve Witkoff, according to two officials familiar with the talks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d99ede0-c6da-11f0-b9eb-0000a1aceffc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In reversal, Coast Guard classifies swastikas, nooses as hate symbols</title>
      <description>The new order came hours after The Post initially reported the service no longer planned to classify the swastika as a hate symbol but instead as “potentially divisive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d346780-c6d6-11f0-bd69-0000a1ace53b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire donors. Trump’s ‘treason’ claim. Swastika rules. Drilling. Musk chatbot. Flight ‘civility.’ Frida Kahlo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92f35350-c6d1-11f0-bc0e-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC in turmoil after agency backpedals on debunking vaccines’ link to autism</title>
      <description>Sen. Bill Cassidy (R-Louisiana), who voted to confirm Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. after Kennedy pledged not to remove language stating vaccines do not cause autism from the CDC website, condemned the change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ddca00-c656-11f0-8e85-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to halt ‘unlawful’ Guard deployment in D.C. while lawsuit plays out in court</title>
      <description>A judge granted an injunction in D.C.’s lawsuit against Trump’s National Guard deployment, but it won’t take effect for 21 days so the government can appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">617c0bb0-c653-11f0-aa26-0000a1ace4f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Coast Guard will no longer classify swastikas, nooses as hate symbols</title>
      <description>The military service, which falls under the Department of Homeland Security, has drafted a new policy that classifies such items “potentially divisive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">957a2f10-c63e-11f0-8f71-0000a1acec26</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend just found out he’s the father of his ex’s baby</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend just found out he’s the father of his ex’s baby</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afb6e9b0-c632-11f0-a843-0000a1acec21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 5 cities help explain why homicide rates are down across the U.S.</title>
      <description>Homicides are down nearly 20 percent this year in 52 of America’s largest cities, according to a Washington Post analysis, a decline that spans both red and blue states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3eb9a10-c62f-11f0-a5d0-0000a1ace3b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing the Epstein files in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6df3b9d0-c62e-11f0-a317-0000a1ace398</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
