<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 23:01:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift bought the full rights to her music. So what do ‘Taylor’s Versions’ mean now?</title>
      <description>There’s still a point to her project of rerecording albums — at least to her die-hards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bf23570-3f2d-11f0-8e23-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 21:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What food expiration dates and best-by labels really mean: Busting 5 persistent myths</title>
      <description>What food expiration dates and best-by labels really mean: Busting 5 persistent myths</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9fadbb0-3f13-11f0-8f49-0000a1acef44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 18:11:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">913719f0-3f01-11f0-9521-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bd918d0-3eeb-11f0-a1ac-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 13:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran dramatically increases stockpile of near weapons-grade enriched uranium, according to IAEA report</title>
      <description>In just three months, Iran produced 300 pounds of uranium enriched to 60 percent, a step away from weapons-grade, a classified International Atomic Energy Agency report said. The report comes as President Donald Trump pursues negotiations with Tehran over its nuclear program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebfe5fd0-3e69-11f0-bc62-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:55:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 ways women are physically stronger than men</title>
      <description>Generally, discussions of “strength” have meant brute force and speed over short distances — qualities historically associated with male physiology. But stamina, recovery, resilience and adaptability are also essential to athletic performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6615bb0-3e66-11f0-9a18-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 21:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pick for NASA administrator told by White House that nomination will be rescinded, source says</title>
      <description>Billionaire entrepreneur Jared Isaacman has ties to SpaceX and Elon Musk, whose influence is waning as he steps away from his role as head of the U.S. DOGE Service. The full Senate was preparing for a vote on Isaacman's nomination as early as next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fbf1270-3e5d-11f0-a504-0000a1acef95</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 20:26:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s called the Library of Congress. But Trump claims it’s his.</title>
      <description>The attempt to take over the legislative library is the latest example of efforts by the Trump administration to erase the traditional lines that separate the branches of government. Resistance from the GOP-controlled Congress has been limited, but there has been some pushback to the president’s plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03e00280-3e55-11f0-b47e-0000a1ace68f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 19:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration is using a little-known law to criminally charge migrants who fail to register presence with the government</title>
      <description>The Justice Department is relying on a federal registration requirement created during World War II to meet the goals of an executive order from President Donald Trump. Some of the charges have been thrown out by judges or withdrawn by prosecutors amid questioning from the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">786d9811-3e41-11f0-8195-000a1ace0264</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 17:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’ve never felt worthy of love or attention. How can I start?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’ve never felt worthy of love or attention. How can I start?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc8563c0-3e3a-11f0-b230-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 16:18:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 science-based ways to reduce your cancer risk, according to an oncologist</title>
      <description>About 40 percent of cancer cases are considered preventable. Try these lifestyle changes to stay healthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5b020d0-3e29-11f0-b5f0-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 14:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56324d40-3e23-11f0-8fbd-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 13:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says tariffs on imported steel will double to 50 percent</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump announced the levies Friday at U.S. Steel in Pittsburgh, where he heralded the recent deal between the American company and its Japanese rival, Nippon Steel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60630420-3da7-11f0-a5f3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 22:42:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tornado watch in effect for D.C. area until midnight</title>
      <description>Severe thunderstorms, capable of producing damaging winds, hail and possibly a tornado or two, are expected to move through the region this evening. Storms may be most numerous between 7 and 10 p.m. Follow the Capital Weather Gang for the latest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ed8a621-3d9e-11f0-80f3-0000a1ace089</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 21:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shakira cancels Saturday's WorldPride concert at Nationals Park, citing complications with previous show</title>
      <description>The pop singer was set to perform in the opening ceremony for WorldPride, the largest LGBTQ+ festival in the world that is taking place in D.C. through June 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9ca0d90-3d9a-11f0-929b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 21:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PBS sues Trump over executive order targeting federal funding, following NPR</title>
      <description>The public broadcaster says the May 1 order violated its First Amendment rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb9f490-3d92-11f0-8be2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 20:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires director of National Portrait Gallery, calling her ‘highly partisan’ and ‘a strong supporter of DEI’</title>
      <description>It is unclear if President Donald Trump has authority to dismiss Smithsonian leaders. The termination marks the president’s first action against an institution he has vowed to purge of “anti-American ideology.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">323228c0-3d88-11f0-b5ac-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contradicting RFK Jr., CDC keeps covid vaccine recommendation for kids</title>
      <description>Coronavirus vaccines are still recommended for healthy children if their doctors approve, according to updated immunization schedules published late Thursday by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The revisions, which also say that the vaccines are no longer advised for pregnant women, add to the confusion surrounding President Donald Trump’s vaccine policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06c5b0a1-3d81-11f0-b750-0000a1ace789</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A key scientist behind the abortion pill dies at 98. Étienne-Émile Baulieu was at the center of battles over reproductive rights.</title>
      <description>Baulieu, a French biochemist, spearheaded the development of the abortion pill drug mifepristone, which became the leading method to end a pregnancy in many countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d3fe150-3d76-11f0-81ad-0000a1ace949</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift buys back the masters to her first six albums, ending years-long ownership fight</title>
      <description>Swift made the announcement in a letter posted to her website.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbd8421-3d74-11f0-afba-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 16:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Trump to revoke legal status for more than 530,000 migrants for now</title>
      <description>A divided Supreme Court cleared the way for the Trump administration to revoke the temporary legal status of migrants from Cuba, Haiti, Nicaragua and Venezuela who under the Biden administration were allowed to live and work in the United States while their immigration cases played out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0f7b3d0-3d63-11f0-85bc-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 14:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76c55440-3d5a-11f0-bd38-0000a1ace591</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff whiplash. Trump vs. Harvard. Gaza talks. Supreme Court. Election denial. Wildfire smoke. Spelling Bee. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">453abb00-3d45-11f0-98cd-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faizan Zaki, 13, of Texas wins the Scripps National Spelling Bee. The runner-up from last year was competing in his fourth bee.</title>
      <description>Nine students competed in Thursday’s final rounds held in Maryland. The national spelling contest celebrated its 100th anniversary this year, and the winner takes home a championship trophy and $50,000 among other prizes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36be29b0-3cfd-11f0-bdb0-0000a1ace900</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbled citations in White House MAHA report bear hallmarks of AI, experts say</title>
      <description>Citations in the initial version of the sweeping health report, which was written in response to an executive order from President Donald Trump, included incorrect authors, and several studies cited do not exist at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53a9810-3cf0-11f0-b0f4-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs can remain in place for now, appeals court says, temporarily pausing a trade court ruling that found them illegal</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had asked the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit to make a ruling. Most of the White House’s “reciprocal” tariffs will remain in effect as litigation proceeds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2191090-3cc6-11f0-a783-0000a1ace336</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge grants Harvard a temporary reprieve from Trump administration’s attempt to bar its enrollment of foreign students</title>
      <description>Judge Allison D. Burroughs ordered that a temporary restraining order she issued last week remain in place until a preliminary injunction is issued. The ruling grants Harvard a reprieve, for the time being, in one of the most high-stakes battles in its ongoing war with the administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4af7a000-3ca8-11f0-afd9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Middle-aged and still getting dismissed as ‘the baby’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Middle-aged and still getting dismissed as ‘the baby’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85ee9ad1-3ca6-11f0-bc27-0000a1ace6bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court narrows scope of federal agencies’ environmental reviews of highways, pipelines and other projects</title>
      <description>The decision centered on a rail line in Utah that would carry billions of gallons of oil and sets new parameters for how far agencies may go in assessing environmental impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65615050-3c97-11f0-bf5b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making duck calls in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c38f111-3c91-11f0-991e-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariffs ruling. Student visas. Elon Musk’s exit. Vaccine confusion. Gaza chaos. Climate warning. Genetic ‘trucks.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">114c7500-3c7c-11f0-9901-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is leaving his role in the Trump administration after a tenure marked by contentious efforts to slash government spending</title>
      <description>The billionaire behind the U.S. DOGE Service wrote on X that his “scheduled time” as a special government employee had come to an end. A day earlier, in a major break with President Donald Trump and Republicans, Musk said he did not approve of the president’s One Big Beautiful Bill, with its massive tax cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d9c1aa0-3c2f-11f0-9f94-0000a1ace01f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Air Force One deal with Qatar is not final, despite the administration's claims</title>
      <description>The Qatari government has asked the United States to clarify that the luxury jetliner's pending transfer was initiated by the Trump administration and that Qatar was not responsible for any future transfers of the plane's ownership, officials told The Washington Post. The delay reflects lingering concerns about legal liabilities stemming from the White House's maneuver to transform what was originally a sale between two countries into a “gift."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">161a2a50-3c27-11f0-9bd1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio says Trump administration will ‘aggressively revoke’ visas for Chinese students</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio has announced that the State Department will collaborate with the Department of Homeland Security to strip the visas of Chinese students with ties to the Chinese Communist Party and those studying in “critical fields.” The plan also includes a revision of all visa criteria for China and Hong Kong, marking the latest escalation in the Trump administration's confrontational relations with Beijing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96ef1c20-3c23-11f0-82ad-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade court blocks Trump's tariffs, saying they are illegal</title>
      <description>The Court of International Trade ruled that President Donald Trump exceeded his authority in imposing tariffs on all imported goods. The president invoked a law that granted him emergency powers over the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d194dbf0-3c1c-11f0-9bd1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to upend one of the nation's largest affirmative action programs to settle lawsuit with White-owned businesses</title>
      <description>The $37 billion Transportation Department initiative, which dates to 1983 and serves an estimated 49,000 businesses, would be prohibited from awarding contracts based on race and sex, effectively ending its founding mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4f8410-3be6-11f0-8820-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend of nine years ‘distant and angry’ when marriage comes up</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend of nine years ‘distant and angry’ when marriage comes up</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ab758c0-3bdd-11f0-9ea2-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would you cut it in the Scripps National Spelling Bee? Try to catch these 24 misspellings.</title>
      <description>Is knowing how to spell still relevant?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8cbbc80-3bdc-11f0-961b-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new land in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f990571-3bc8-11f0-a751-000a1ace9706</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts Putin. Student visas. Elon Musk. Coronavirus shots. Prison escape. Drying river. Flight etiquette. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8203e10-3bb2-11f0-887b-0000a1ace6f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After launching into space, SpaceX loses another Starship in test flight</title>
      <description>A Starship spacecraft came apart midflight Tuesday evening after a successful launch to space. There was no crew aboard the test flight. It was the third loss of a Starship in a row and dealt another setback to Elon Musk’s dreams of using the spacecraft to reach the moon and Mars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb43b80-3b5e-11f0-a6a0-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge tosses Trump executive order punishing law firm WilmerHale</title>
      <description>The ruling is the third time a federal judge has struck down one of President Donald Trump’s orders targeting a prominent law firm. Trump has taken aim at several law firms with ties to his perceived enemies, directing that they be blocked from government contracts and federal buildings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">553aafd1-3b4f-11f0-be86-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 23:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you know these winning words from the national spelling bee? Test your skills.</title>
      <description>Jacques Bailly, a past Scripps National Spelling Bee winner, has served as the competition’s head pronouncer for decades. For our quiz, he picked and pronounced 10 words from 100 years of America’s most famous spelling contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0c96290-3b40-11f0-afd9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is the ‘meaningful’ job worth the physical and mental consequences?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is the ‘meaningful’ job worth the physical and mental consequences?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5f0a5c0-3b15-11f0-b766-0000a1aceff6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. ends covid vaccine recommendation for healthy children and healthy pregnant women</title>
      <description>In a rare move, the health and human services secretary bypassed the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and announced the new policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f165b4f1-3b12-11f0-9318-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beef Wellington mystery in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db7a1280-3afe-11f0-9f79-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s inner circle of advisers is riven by dysfunction and distrust, current and former officials say</title>
      <description>Hegseth purged several top political appointees in April, after internal feuds burst out into the open. But his attempts to portray a new sense of unity among his remaining brain trust are belied by unresolved personality conflicts, inexperience, vacancies in key leadership roles and a steady-state paranoia over what political crisis could emerge next.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c5ca370-3afc-11f0-8a02-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s speech. Republican split. Liverpool car incident. Gaza school. Cancer risk. Hot weather. Mysterious bucket. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc7ac9c0-3ae9-11f0-b3bb-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81 years after he died in World War II, a young aviator was buried in his California hometown</title>
      <description>Second Lt. Thomas V. Kelly Jr. was 21 when he perished with 10 other men on a B-24 bomber shot down near New Guinea on March 11, 1944. Two years ago, his remains and those of three other crew members were recovered from the underwater crash site. Kelly was buried Monday beside family members in Livermore, California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1178a7f1-3a75-11f0-847c-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 21:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you understand your dog’s emotions? Here’s what research tells us.</title>
      <description>Dog owners don’t understand their pet’s emotions as well as they think they do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef605c30-3a5b-11f0-a834-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
