<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 15:03:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rejects limits on White House social media contacts, a win for the Biden administration</title>
      <description>The justices said challengers did not have standing to try to sharply limit what White House officials and other federal employees can say to tech giants about posts on public health, elections, national security and other topics that the government deems problematic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0b0d7b0-33c5-11ef-ac80-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 14:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Yes, chef!’ It's time for today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c835eb0-33c0-11ef-9464-0000a1acebc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 13:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Primary results. Trump allies. Veteran pardons. Evan Gershkovich. Kenya protests. Spending habits. NBA draft. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31610200-33ab-11ef-b5e1-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evan Gershkovich’s espionage trial begins in Russia behind closed doors. The U.S. says the reporter was ‘wrongfully detained.’</title>
      <description>It is the first such trial for an American journalist since the Cold War. Gershkovich was arrested on a reporting trip over a year ago in Russia and faces 20 years in prison if convicted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9345a460-3380-11ef-b233-000a1ace8291</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 05:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Jamaal Bowman (N.Y.) loses Democratic primary to George Latimer in race that highlighted divisions over Israel, AP projects</title>
      <description>The race between Bowman and Latimer, which also included accusations of racism against Latimer, was the most expensive House primary in history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bebdf10-335d-11ef-ba98-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Lauren Boebert wins Republican primary in new Colorado district, AP projects</title>
      <description>Boebert, who has survived several controversies, prevailed in a crowded GOP contest in the state’s 4th Congressional District. She decided to run in the new district after a close general election against a Democrat in the 3rd District in 2022. The new district is more friendly to Republicans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">806c33b0-335b-11ef-86f5-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2024 01:29:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange pleads guilty to U.S. espionage charge, ending years of legal deadlock. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Assange, 52, will head to his native Australia after making a deal with U.S. prosecutors and admitting to publishing military documents about the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. He had spent nearly seven years at the Ecuadorian Embassy in London, evading extradition for a Swedish sex assault investigation over allegations he denied, then for five years fought a bid to send him to the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">205e5980-334c-11ef-afb2-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 23:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Shouldn’t husband come home early, now that his mom is okay?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Shouldn’t husband come home early, now that his mom is okay?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d50fb5b0-330e-11ef-acc9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 16:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Southern’s decision to burn off toxic chemicals in Ohio derailment was unnecessary, NTSB investigators say</title>
      <description>The railway and its contractors disregarded signs that the train’s derailed tank cars posed little risk of exploding, yet went ahead with the venting and burning of toxic vinyl chloride, investigators from the National Transportation Safety Board said. The burn-off sent a towering black cloud of toxic fumes into the air following the accident, spreading contamination over a vast area. In addition, Norfolk Southern failed to communicate adequately with incident commanders, a decision that was unjustified, investigators said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0526dd0-330b-11ef-879e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 15:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An impending ban of these in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14e900a0-32f7-11ef-99e0-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 13:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Criminal Court issues arrest warrants for two top Russian defense officials, alleging war crimes in Ukraine</title>
      <description>According to the indictment, former defense minister Sergei Shoigu and Valery Gerasimov, chief of the staff of the Russian Armed Forces, were responsible for directing attacks at civilian objects and “causing excessive incidental harm to civilians or damage to civilian objects … and the crime against humanity of inhumane acts.” The court, to which Russia is not a signatory, has no powers of enforcement and relies on the 124 nations that are signatories to arrest those indicted for war crimes or crimes against humanity if they visit their territories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2d3f620-32eb-11ef-abd3-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 12:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. surgeon general calls gun violence a public health crisis in landmark declaration</title>
      <description>The advisory from Vivek H. Murthy says the nation must act with urgency to address death and injury caused by firearms, saying inspiration can be drawn from earlier campaigns to combat tobacco use and motor vehicle accidents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a07d610-32e4-11ef-8300-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 11:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Julian Assange. Transgender case. Gun violence. Israel ruling. Student loans. Stanley Cup. Bathroom Picassos. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">064445b0-32e2-11ef-a665-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s Supreme Court rules that ultra-Orthodox must do military service, throwing Netanyahu’s government into turmoil</title>
      <description>The ruling on the controversial issue of the haredim engaging in compulsory military service could lead to the ultra-Orthodox parties quitting the ruling coalition and bringing down Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3af72500-32cb-11ef-ac84-000a1ace0258</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 08:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Panthers win the Stanley Cup for the first time, taking Game 7 of the finals to top Connor McDavid's Edmonton Oilers</title>
      <description>The Panthers jumped out to a 3-0 series lead in the finals but were then sent reeling by the resilient Oilers. They dropped Games 4, 5 and 6 to set up the Game 7 clash in South Florida on Monday night. The Oilers' loss leaves McDavid, Edmonton's dazzling captain, still searching for the Stanley Cup. A Canadian team has not won the Stanley Cup since the Montreal Canadiens in 1993.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98d6a4c0-329e-11ef-8b96-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 02:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two federal court rulings threaten the future of Biden administration’s new student loan repayment plan</title>
      <description>Judges in Kansas and Missouri issued separate injunctions Monday preventing the government from fully implementing and forgiving any more loans through the Save program while they consider lawsuits to end the administration’s plan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14569930-328a-11ef-8b98-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 00:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange expected to plead guilty to a felony, according to court filing</title>
      <description>A court filing indicates the controversial former hacker plans to plead guilty to a single felony count of violating the Espionage Act for his role in obtaining and publishing classified military and diplomatic documents in 2010. The plea deal would end a long-running legal saga and a transatlantic tug-of-war that pitted national security against press freedom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7eb3291-327f-11ef-948f-000a1ace51d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The way your name is spelled is a clue about when you were born. Look up your name to see how trendy it is (or was).</title>
      <description>The Washington Post’s Department of Data dove deep into the trendiest baby names and found one surprising thing almost all of them have in common. We even created a tool to show how any American name fits the trend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e25765d0-326c-11ef-b59e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 21:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They don’t like Biden. They don’t like Trump either. Meet the ‘double haters’ who could decide the election.</title>
      <description>Many voters express resignation, dismay and anger over being asked to choose between Joe Biden and Donald Trump again. These double haters — voters who are dissatisfied with both major-party choices — are likely to prove a critical voting bloc in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34d9def0-3254-11ef-8149-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 18:04:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Best friend is poised to estrange parents over misunderstanding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Best friend is poised to estrange parents over misunderstanding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bd48750-3243-11ef-948f-000a1ace51d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extreme wildfires around the world have doubled in the past 20 years, new study finds</title>
      <description>The analysis, published Monday in the journal Nature Ecology &amp; Evolution, found that climate change is exacerbating fire weather and extreme blazes, which emit high levels of carbon and are often deadly. The six most extreme fire years have occurred since 2017, researchers said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58c1f460-323b-11ef-a3ca-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 15:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vladimir Kara-Murza from a prison colony in Russia: Putin’s definition of a ‘foreign agent’? Anyone who opposes him.</title>
      <description>I am not a foreign agent, the Russian dissident writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5047d650-3237-11ef-a714-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:37:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to review Tenn. law banning gender transition care for minors in justices’ first opportunity to weigh in on treatments</title>
      <description>Transgender young people, their families and medical providers in Tennessee asked the Supreme Court to review an appeals court decision that upheld the laws banning gender transition care for people younger than 18. Twenty-three states have passed such bans since 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55a4da10-3234-11ef-a3ae-0000a1ace9b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 14:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ancient beach reopens in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4ee74c1-322d-11ef-a714-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia attacks. Trump rhetoric. Israeli airstrikes. Global heat. Gen Z struggles. Mail surveillance. Track trials. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcf348b1-3218-11ef-8a15-000a1ace0b7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could a month at an all-inclusive resort in Mexico cost the same as rent in a big U.S. city? This man tried it to find out.</title>
      <description>Expedia contacted TikToker Ben Keenan with an offer to cover the cost of accommodations at a luxury resort on the Yucatán Peninsula. He had nothing to lose, so he flew to Mexico to put his viral question to the test.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c716bee1-31ab-11ef-adc7-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 21:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you think like a key swing-state voter? Answer these 8 questions to find out.</title>
      <description>See what you have in common with this small but influential subset of voters who might decide the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24ae4f70-319b-11ef-8b96-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 19:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Tobacco courts Black and LGBTQ+ activists to help loosen vaping regulations and fight menthol cigarette ban</title>
      <description>The tobacco industry has expanded alliances with activists representing Black, LGBTQ+ and other disenfranchised groups to defend products that public health experts say are harmful.

Anti-tobacco activists say these partnerships help companies gain credibility among regulators and lawmakers, as vaping groups lobby the Food and Drug Administration to approve more e-cigarette products and tobacco firms fight a Biden administration plan to ban menthol cigarettes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a796a72-3188-11ef-99da-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 17:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5a01020-3179-11ef-85e7-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 16:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘You need to know this story’: In 1964, the Klan killed three activists and shocked the nation</title>
      <description>Amid Freedom Summer, a daring effort to register Black Mississippians to vote, three young civil rights workers came to the state’s small town of Philadelphia to check on a church burning. Before the sun rose the next morning, they would all be dead. The town is still grappling with that violent chapter of history on the murders’ 60th anniversary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bae5f90-3170-11ef-9019-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 14:51:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1f738f1-3164-11ef-87a1-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 13:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech firms chase fusion energy and other miracles as AI drains the power grid</title>
      <description>Big Tech companies are going all in on experimental clean-energy projects that have long odds of success anytime soon, even as their race to dominate artificial intelligence boosts demand for fossil fuels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6726ca0-30e2-11ef-8ec3-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 22:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. just reached 100 degrees for the first time in almost eight years</title>
      <description>Today is the first time since Aug. 15, 2016, that Washington's temperature has hit the century mark. It ends the fifth-longest streak on record without hitting 100 degrees and comes as a heat wave now baking the East Coast expands into the Mid-Atlantic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ff656b0-30df-11ef-8516-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 21:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona delegates gathered this month to discuss a secret plan: A far-right effort to throw Trump’s nomination into chaos</title>
      <description>The exact motive behind the plotting remained unclear, but it set off a scramble within the Trump campaign to replace the delegates. One campaign staffer involved in the cleanup described the scheme as an “existential threat” to Trump’s nomination next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7132d150-30be-11ef-8dd6-0000a1ace40b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 17:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My family says I’m ‘selfish’ for not wanting my mom to live with me</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My family says I’m ‘selfish’ for not wanting my mom to live with me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a42992a0-30b0-11ef-97ba-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Black families, the race to preserve civil rights history in the South comes with an unexpected sacrifice</title>
      <description>With the 60th anniversary of the march from Selma to Montgomery approaching next year, Phillip Howard is working to save sites where Martin Luther King Jr. and his followers camped out. But the Black families who still own the land face difficult questions about what they owe to preserving public memory — particularly as civil rights education comes under threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ca63bf0-30a5-11ef-a925-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 14:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb7cd0e1-309b-11ef-b069-0000a1ace78c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of people this week felt the deadly intensity of heat waves fueled by climate change</title>
      <description>A week of scorching heat across five continents shows how human-driven warming has raised the baseline of normal temperatures, scientists say, fueling more frequent extremes. In just the past seven days, a majority of the planet experienced heat waves that were made more likely by climate change, and more than 1,000 temperature records fell around the globe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad93370-3099-11ef-85eb-0000a1acecd2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 13:16:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She spent 23 years asking who killed her mom. Then her phone rang.</title>
      <description>Lauren Preer spent more than two decades waiting for answers in the brutal killing of her mother, Leslie J. Preer, in her Chevy Chase, Md., home. She hoped an arrest would bring closure. Instead, she felt shock — then betrayal and rage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f86d290-3022-11ef-8e3b-0000a1acef42</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 23:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. restrictions on how far Ukraine can fire American weapons into Russia leave key bases out of range, Ukrainian officials say</title>
      <description>The two officials say that the Biden administration’s lifting of a ban on targets in Russia has helped their military reduce some incoming attacks, but that air bases used by planes that drop highly destructive glide bombs are beyond a range set by Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2111e790-3016-11ef-867a-0000a1ace43b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 21:35:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nevada judge dismisses case against Trump electors, ruling prosecutors chose the wrong jurisdiction to file the case</title>
      <description>The decision marks a setback for efforts to prosecute those who submitted certificates falsely declaring Donald Trump the winner of the 2020 election. The Nevada attorney general’s office said it would appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dff6b880-3006-11ef-9400-0000a1ace6d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 19:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It could feel like 105 degrees in D.C. on Saturday. Officials have issued a heat advisory for the region.</title>
      <description>Temperatures could be the highest in the region since August 2016. Sunday’s heat is expected to be similarly intense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74458940-2ff2-11ef-8857-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfb780e1-2feb-11ef-945e-0000a1ace489</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 16:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds gun ban for people subject to domestic-violence restraining orders in rare victory for firearms restrictions</title>
      <description>A federal law that strips guns from those deemed dangerous was among a number of firearms restrictions imperiled after the Supreme Court’s conservative majority bolstered gun rights in its 2022 decision, known as New York State Rifle &amp; Pistol Association v. Bruen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c2ee9c1-2fda-11ef-a975-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 14:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fcbbcc0-2fd2-11ef-a975-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Winnett will not join The Post as editor</title>
      <description>Winnett, deputy editor of London’s Telegraph Media Group, who was to lead The Washington Post newsroom, faced questions about his work in England, including stories based on illicitly obtained records. Early Friday, the editor of the Telegraph, Chris Evans, told staff Winnett will stay with the paper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f541eaf0-2fc7-11ef-ab4e-0000a1ace8c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 12:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump donation surge. Heat wave. Donald Sutherland. Murder suspect. AI emissions. Chimp medicine. Ancient beach. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5da05dd1-2fbd-11ef-ae8b-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s felony conviction fuels a donation surge that narrows Biden’s advantage</title>
      <description>The Trump campaign and an allied super PAC received a huge influx of cash in the days following his May conviction on 34 felony counts of falsifying business records. The surge in post-conviction donations — captured in part in May reports filed to the Federal Election Commission on Thursday — is giving Trump a significant boost as he tries to narrow the Biden campaign’s once-enormous cash advantage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30610b00-2f75-11ef-ae59-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayer is pushing Congress for legislation — and helped shape a provision — that could help fight lawsuits tying Roundup to cancer</title>
      <description>The company has paid billions of dollars in settlements, even as it maintains its weedkiller is safe and denies wrongdoing. A Bayer-backed provision in the House’s sweeping agricultural bill could halt some lawsuits, according to documents viewed by The Washington Post and seven people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd9bfe50-2f51-11ef-919c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Prince George’s County councilman Mel Franklin charged with embezzling campaign funds for personal expenses</title>
      <description>At least $130,000 of his campaign funds were used to pay for personal expenses, including his rent, loans and cosmetic procedures for him and a close friend, prosecutors allege. Franklin abruptly resigned Friday from his seat after serving on the council for nearly 14 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54bd39a0-2f49-11ef-86fa-0000a1ace675</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
