<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 09:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S.’s only native caffeinated plant may soon get a huge boost from tariffs on coffee and tea</title>
      <description>Yaupon, a holly, may be little known outside Indigenous groups, but a tight-knit group of farmers, producers and wild harvesters are ready and waiting for a potential resurgence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">907b37e0-65ac-11f0-9fbc-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 21:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottie Scheffler wins the British Open, capturing his second major championship of the year and the fourth of his career</title>
      <description>The No. 1 player in the world expertly navigated Royal Portrush in Northern Ireland, running away from the rest of the field over the final two rounds. Scheffler, 29, also won the PGA Championship in May after winning the Masters in 2022 and 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1837d1a0-6591-11f0-a953-0000a1ace0dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 17:43:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb75930-6582-11f0-b8d5-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Mexican Coke really better than the U.S. version? We put it to the test.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Coca-Cola will switch to “real cane sugar” instead of high-fructose corn syrup in the United States. Could we taste the difference?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2607d840-6576-11f0-8c4e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">019bc8c0-656e-11f0-b90a-0000a1acec83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 13:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another senior aide to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth is leaving the Pentagon, officials say</title>
      <description>Justin Fulcher was at the center of two strange controversies, including one first reported by The Washington Post on Tuesday in which he stormed out of a meeting with another Pentagon official. He and Hegseth's team both said Saturday that his departure was “amicable.” It's at least the fifth departure of a top adviser in Hegseth’s first six months in office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb761e70-64f4-11f0-b16f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 23:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In an attempt to help lower-income residents, Kansas City poured millions into a grocery store. It’s on the verge of closure.</title>
      <description>Cities and states across the country are experimenting with publicly supported supermarkets. But the problems encountered in Kansas City show these efforts often don’t account for social issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4a34160-64c1-11f0-87fa-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I keep my boundary-stomping parents from ruining my home?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I keep my boundary-stomping parents from ruining my home?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d163c773-64b9-11f0-a7b9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A family found safety and their dream home in America. Then both began to crack.</title>
      <description>For a Haitian family in Springfield, Ohio, the house on Chestnut Avenue represented their future in this country. With their legal status here now threatened, they’re wondering what can be salvaged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c457f80-64ab-11f0-bd8f-0000a1ace992</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 14:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccade281-64a3-11f0-a3c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 13:25:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA eliminates its scientific research arm, cementing plans to cut nearly a quarter of its entire staff</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency said it would dismantle the Office of Research and Development, which conducts independent research on environmental hazards. Agency officials said the EPA has now cut 23 percent of its overall staff through layoffs, separations and retirements, saving taxpayers more than $748 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e95cb030-6437-11f0-9af5-0000a1ace334</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 00:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department asks a federal court to release Epstein grand jury testimony</title>
      <description>Trump administration officials have asked a federal court to unseal more grand jury testimony in the sex-trafficking case against former financier Jeffrey Epstein. The request comes as political outcry intensifies over the administration’s unfulfilled promise to release more details on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea338d60-6425-11f0-93a3-000a1ace6899</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 22:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What causes obesity? A major new study is upending common wisdom.</title>
      <description>The study found that people living in developed countries expend about the same number of calories most days as hunter-gatherers and anyone living in less-industrialized nations, suggesting that inactivity is not the main cause of obesity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">959ee3a0-641e-11f0-b0d5-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 21:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration swaps more than 250 Venezuelans sent to notorious Salvadoran prison for Americans held by Caracas</title>
      <description>The State Department coordinated the exchange involving Venezuelans who were held at the high-security CECOT “counterterrorism” prison. The Americans are a mix of U.S. citizens and permanent residents who were imprisoned by the government of President Nicolás Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a40aa550-6414-11f0-a4a5-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 20:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s antisemitism task force takes aim at other conservative complaints about colleges</title>
      <description>The administration created the Joint Task Force on Anti-Semitism to counter what it describes as widespread failure by universities to protect Jewish students. In reality, many of its unprecedented demands and punishments have nothing to do with antisemitism and instead relate to a conservative campaign to root out diversity, equity and inclusion initiatives and a liberal worldview on college campuses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cda57d1-6408-11f0-8409-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: A distracted driver only got a slap on the wrist in a crash that killed my husband. I want justice.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: A distracted driver only got a slap on the wrist in a crash that killed my husband. I want justice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce65bf30-63f4-11f0-abac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70e32f50-63db-11f0-abac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The end of Colbert’s ‘Late Show’ follows a troubling pattern with implications beyond late-night TV, our columnist writes</title>
      <description>Stephen Colbert announced at the Thursday evening taping of “The Late Show with Stephen Colbert” that he’d found out, only the night before, that his show would be canceled in May 2026 and that no one would be replacing him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">676746c0-63d9-11f0-ad5e-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 13:16:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $9 billion in spending cuts, sending package to Trump’s desk</title>
      <description>The House slashed funding for foreign aid and the Corporation for Public Broadcasting, which funds PBS and NPR. The Senate earlier this week passed the cuts, known as rescissions, meaning the bill will soon become law. The House vote was significantly delayed because of the political pressure facing Republicans around the release of government files related to convicted sex-offender Jeffrey Epstein.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ffffc990-638c-11f0-9b6c-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS cancels Stephen Colbert’s ‘Late Show’ in what the network says was a financial decision</title>
      <description>The late-night talk show will end in May 2026. The announcement came days after Colbert spoke out against the $16 million paid by Paramount, the parent company of CBS News, to settle a lawsuit filed by Donald Trump during last year’s presidential campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80406970-636f-11f0-94bc-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Texas flooding was the deadliest tragedy for children in decades. Here’s who was lost.</title>
      <description>They adored animals and sports. They loved to draw and read. Their giggles were contagious, their hugs spontaneous. Amid the grief, relatives have sought to celebrate what made the children special — and hinted at the young adults they might have one day become.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb09a9e1-635a-11f0-bcb1-0000a1ace6ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 22:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil’s former president Jair Bolsonaro is charged with leading a coup. His son is pushing Trump to sanction a judge in his trial.</title>
      <description>Spurred on by Eduardo Bolsonaro, the White House is considering sanctions against Supreme Federal Court Justice Alexandre de Moraes, according to four people familiar with the situation, which could escalate a growing diplomatic feud between the United States and Brazil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddbb9960-6353-11f0-a312-0000a1ace99d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration adds level of approval to wind and solar projects, threatening to slow them down as tax credit deadline looms</title>
      <description>The Interior Department announced a new level of “enhanced oversight” for renewable energy projects, which will now require approval by the secretary’s office. The move introduces a hurdle to projects that were racing to begin construction before a July 2026 deadline to qualify for tax credits, which were gutted by President Donald Trump’s One Big Beautiful Bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d57c0b0-634f-11f0-a700-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world is choking on screens. Just as this book foretold.</title>
      <description>The world is choking on screens. Just as this book foretold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac7577a0-6348-11f0-8871-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 20:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Visiting mom with memory loss and depression gets harder every time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Visiting mom with memory loss and depression gets harder every time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f79b2e0-6327-11f0-bbf5-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s best sandwiches, according to the experts: You</title>
      <description>We challenged readers to name the tastiest specimens around. Looking for an exemplary Reuben, Philly cheesesteak or Italian hoagie? Right this way.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">871d75c1-6325-11f0-94e5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 15:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. seeks one-day sentence for officer involved in raid that killed Breonna Taylor. He faces up to life in prison.</title>
      <description>In an unusual sentencing memo, the federal government suggested to a judge that the Biden administration should not have prosecuted Louisville officer Brett Hankison on civil rights charges. A federal jury found Hankison guilty in November on charges connected to the March 2020 raid in which Taylor was fatally shot.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54a7341-6313-11f0-89bc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celestial bodies in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70074090-6312-11f0-875e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connie Francis dies at 87. The popular 1950s and ’60s singer sold over 100 million records and was an unlikely TikTok sensation.</title>
      <description>Francis was known for such hits as “Who’s Sorry Now,” “Stupid Cupid” and “Where the Boys Are.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0073ae0-6302-11f0-993c-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA rift. ‘Alligator Alcatraz.’ Crypto stakes. Israeli strikes. Flood risks. AI cheats. Mars rock. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3246e400-62fd-11f0-a6a7-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate narrowly passes bill to slash $9 billion from foreign aid and public broadcasting</title>
      <description>Its passage is a victory for President Donald Trump, weeks after his triumph on tax and immigration legislation, and may signal the start of a more aggressive effort by his administration to claw back funding appropriated by Congress. The legislation now heads to the House, where the Republican leadership is confident about its passage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc5ddb00-62d9-11f0-9650-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 06:48:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department fires Diddy and Epstein prosecutor Maurene Comey, daughter of former FBI director Trump has feuded with</title>
      <description>Comey is a career prosecutor in the Southern District of New York who worked on the criminal cases of Jeffrey Epstein and Sean "Diddy" Combs. The reason for her firing was unclear, according to a person familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">400a0940-62a9-11f0-9bda-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:59:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials halt ‘dangerous’ research despite recommendations of NIH career scientists</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s action has raised concerns among outside scientists, who argue the move could block experiments that are safe and that could lead to new treatments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">261e0f10-62a7-11f0-9849-0000a1aced20</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 00:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rich are preselecting their children based on their genes — and calling it the future of baby-making</title>
      <description>A start-up funded by Silicon Valley investors scores embryos for their genetic potential to develop disorders. Is it a path toward creating perfect babies or false hopes?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29c57f20-629a-11f0-b797-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 23:11:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How one patient’s personal and political worlds collided at the doctor’s office</title>
      <description>My health and my politics walk into a doctor’s office …</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">373bbe10-6260-11f0-8bd3-000a1acec913</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Soon-to-be grandma crowds pregnant daughter with her entitlement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50fde5f0-625e-11f0-bea0-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘delicate subject’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8214f220-624d-11f0-b1ea-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. hits states with requests for voter rolls and election data, sparking concerns of interference ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>Election clerks in both parties, already facing harassment and lawsuits over President Donald Trump’s false 2020 election claims, worry about efforts to examine voting machines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4ef490-6245-11f0-ad01-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 13:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Voter data. Extreme rainfall. Confession letter. Obesity study. Emmy nominations. Sycamore Gap tree. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f954e70-6234-11f0-9e35-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 11:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adelita Grijalva wins Democratic nomination for U.S. House in Arizona special election</title>
      <description>Grijalva won a contested primary in a safely Democratic district, defeating Gen Z content creator Deja Foxx and others. The contest underlined intraparty tensions over age, experience and dynastic politics. Grijalva will be a heavy favorite in the special election to succeed her father, liberal stalwart Raúl Grijalva, who represented the district until his death in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a2bcda0-61f4-11f0-bf2b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 03:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expelled D.C. Council member Trayon White Sr. (D) projected to win special election for his former Ward 8 seat</title>
      <description>White, who was expelled in February after his arrest and indictment on a federal bribery charge, will return to the council for a term that ends in January 2029. He has pleaded not guilty to the charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02736f50-61e5-11f0-b547-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 01:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth lashed out at a top DOGE official in tense Pentagon confrontation</title>
      <description>The episode in April, which has not been reported previously, was sparked by claims that a team leader with Elon Musk’s cost-cutting organization had summoned law enforcement to remove a subordinate from the Pentagon installation, people familiar with the matter said. Hegseth, these people said, deemed it an unacceptable overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcc2f90-61d7-11f0-bfba-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 00:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants to automate the work of federal employees. Here are 6 agencies to watch.</title>
      <description>The Pentagon, IRS and other federal agencies are rapidly adopting AI tools to improve efficiency, an idea championed by Elon Musk that could replace some government workers with technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e7cf30-61d3-11f0-aa71-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 23:27:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>William H. McRaven writes in an op-ed: Cuts to the State Department and USAID will put every American at risk</title>
      <description>Soft power for a tough world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">012a44f0-61ce-11f0-a925-000a1ace3781</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 22:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speaker Mike Johnson and other Republicans break with Trump administration on Epstein files as Democrats call for documents' release</title>
      <description>Johnson (R-Louisiana) called for the Justice Department to release any files related to convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein just days after the Trump administration effectively declared the matter closed. Johnson's interview was released moments after House GOP leaders barely defeated a Democratic effort to force a House vote to release the files.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86db6c60-61b4-11f0-ab7a-0000a1aced00</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:47:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unnerved by wife’s pointed silence during talk about sexual assault</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3222240-6197-11f0-949b-000a1ace7963</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 16:21:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Severance,’ ‘The Penguin,’ ‘The White Lotus’ and ‘The Studio’ lead the Emmy nominations. See the list here.</title>
      <description>The annual awards show honoring the best in TV is set to take place Sept. 14.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90b43a71-6194-11f0-8f80-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 15:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 244 people Trump proposed for his $40 million hero garden, including a few surprises</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump first proposed the “National Garden of American Heroes” during the racial justice protests of 2020, when many Confederate monuments were being toppled. Now it has the funds to become a reality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35291eb0-6184-11f0-bc47-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An interactive performance in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">118f0860-6180-11f0-ab82-0000a1aceb40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 13:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation heated up in June, as Trump’s tariffs began to pressure more sectors in the economy</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed that inflation picked up momentum in June, after months of progress bringing prices under control, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdbdcb20-6177-11f0-8aa0-0000a1ace936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 12:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
