<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 11:03:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israel weapons. Trump meeting. House speaker. Tornadoes. Brain worms. Pandemic risk. ‘The Office.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f6f040-0df3-11ef-96fb-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Truth Social is relatively small. But Trump’s posts find enormous audiences anyway, thanks to an army of amplifiers and surrogates.</title>
      <description>Those concerned about the impact of Donald Trump’s incendiary and often inaccurate messages have long sought ways to limit his reach. A Washington Post analysis shows how those efforts have failed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdae0a60-0d98-11ef-9ec1-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 00:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Denver Nuggets center Nikola Jokic wins NBA MVP award, becoming ninth player to receive the honor at least three times</title>
      <description>Jokic, 29, beat out fellow finalists Shai Gilgeous-Alexander of the Oklahoma City Thunder and Luka Doncic of the Dallas Mavericks to follow up his previous MVPs in 2021 and 2022. He finished second behind Philadelphia 76ers center Joel Embiid in 2023. The other players who have been named MVP at least three times are Kareem Abdul-Jabbar (six times), Bill Russell (five), Michael Jordan (five), Wilt Chamberlain (four), LeBron James (four), Moses Malone (three), Larry Bird (three) and Magic Johnson (three).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c56e0490-0d93-11ef-9a2b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 23:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden says he will stop weapons shipments if Israel invades Rafah, the most direct threat he’s made since war started</title>
      <description>Biden said in an interview with CNN scheduled to air Wednesday that civilians in Gaza have been killed by U.S. weapons as Israel has gone after "population centers." Biden continued: "If they go into Rafah, I’m not supplying the weapons that have been used historically ... to deal with the cities." His acknowledgement that U.S. weapons have been used to kill civilians in Gaza and conditioning of support to the American ally is a notable change from his previous public comments on Israel's military operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e83b1270-0d8d-11ef-937e-0000a1ace8b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House overwhelmingly votes against ousting Speaker Mike Johnson, a blow to Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s efforts to remove him</title>
      <description>Democrats voted with most Republicans in support of a procedural motion that effectively ends the attempt of Greene (R-Ga.) to topple Johnson (R-La.). That means the House will not consider a “motion to vacate,” which would have been a direct vote on Johnson’s leadership. The speaker will keep his job for now, but future ouster attempts are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b90a6b0-0d87-11ef-a3bc-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 22:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do you get an air fryer to make food that’s actually crispy? We answered your cooking questions.</title>
      <description>How do you get an air fryer to make food that’s actually crispy? We answered your cooking questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9183af0-0d5e-11ef-bad6-0000a1ace97f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 17:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family pushes siblings to ‘make amends’ after their mother’s death</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family pushes siblings to ‘make amends’ after their mother’s death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbe3e9a0-0d54-11ef-90a9-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 16:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To please Putin, Russian universities purge liberals and embrace patriotism</title>
      <description>In a transformation of Russia’s education system, pro-Kremlin university administrators have ousted students and professors who oppose the war in Ukraine, slashed humanities programs with ties to the West, and rewritten curriculums to emphasize nationalism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">972a1960-0d53-11ef-99fb-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Human disruptions to the planet have made it easier for diseases to spread — raising the risk of a new pandemic, study finds</title>
      <description>As humans degrade Earth’s environment, we have created a world in which diseases may be increasingly apt to fester and multiply. Climate change and biodiversity losses encourage disease to spread, according to research published Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5d19cd0-0d4f-11ef-94cb-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 15:28:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brittney Griner landed in Russia and wound up in prison. She details what happened in a new excerpt.</title>
      <description>This column — adapted from her memoir, “Coming Home” — is the story of how Griner’s ordeal began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e9ae6e0-0d41-11ef-8022-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reelection bid in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8c1d240-0d3e-11ef-874f-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 13:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels. Israel bombs. Zelensky plot. TikTok lawsuit. Michigan tornadoes. Olive oil. Whale speech. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207c2892-0d2a-11ef-a78d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police begin clearing, making arrests at George Washington University protest encampment</title>
      <description>The move on the pro-Palestinian encampment comes hours before the District’s mayor and police chief are set to testify on Capitol Hill about why they had for nearly two weeks declined requests from the university to clear it from the school’s grounds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9a1ca00-0d21-11ef-9e11-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 10:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. paused shipments of thousands of bombs to Israel amid a rift over its battle plans for Rafah</title>
      <description>In an unprecedented move, the Biden administration paused a shipment of 2,000-pound bombs and other munitions bound for Israel last week as a result of mounting concern about the country’s plan to expand a military operation in southern Gaza that could dramatically increase the conflict’s death toll, senior administration officials said. It is the first known instance of a pause in U.S. arms transfers since the Oct. 7 Hamas-led attack. One U.S. official described the move as a “shot across the bow” intended to underscore the seriousness of Washington’s concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1274980-0ceb-11ef-b37b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 03:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 50 people are trapped inside a FedEx facility after a tornado hit Portage, Mich., county authorities say</title>
      <description>First responders were trying to get the people out but were waiting for the power company to clear downed wires blocking the way, Taylor Koopman, Kalamazoo County spokeswoman, said Tuesday evening. A nearby mobile home park was also hit hard, she said. No deaths had been reported in the city as of about 8 p.m., Portage Mayor Patricia Randall said, though crews were still assessing the damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a04401b0-0cda-11ef-b6a9-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2024 01:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final body found in Baltimore Key Bridge collapse, officials say</title>
      <description>Salvage crews have located the remains of the sixth and apparently final construction worker killed when the Francis Scott Key Bridge in Baltimore was struck by a ship and collapsed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c6edbd1-0cc9-11ef-b23c-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York judge was alarmed by Trump’s response to Stormy Daniels testimony, early trial transcripts show</title>
      <description>New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan called Trump lawyer Todd Blanche to a sidebar during a midday break to say the former president was “cursing audibly” and shaking his head, possibly intimidating adult-film actress Stormy Daniels as she testified in Trump's falsifying records criminal trial. “I am speaking to you here at the bench because I don’t want to embarrass him," Merchan said, according to transcripts. "You need to speak to him. I won’t tolerate that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72a12291-0cc8-11ef-b98c-0000a1ace4b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 23:20:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar and Drake’s rap feud has gotten ugly. Here’s a breakdown, track by track.</title>
      <description>Since Friday, Drake and Lamar have released songs with some serious allegations against each other, igniting pro-sports levels of spectating. Full of easter eggs (and probably misinformation), it’s a classic hip-hop feud with a very modern flavor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c703890-0cc1-11ef-918f-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 22:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump's classified documents trial in Florida delayed indefinitely, judge says</title>
      <description>Judge Aileen M. Cannon canceled the May 20 start of Donald Trump's trial for allegedly withholding classified documents after leaving the White House and obstructing government efforts to get them back, saying she could not set a new date until myriad pre-trial issues are resolved. The decision increases the chances that Trump, who’s on trial in New York for allegedly falsifying business records connected to a hush money payment, will not face another criminal trial before the November presidential election in which he is the likely Republican nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a53f9ca0-0cb8-11ef-8879-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Stormy Daniels’s account of sex with Trump may be problematic, and other takeaways from today’s hush money trial testimony</title>
      <description>The first trial of a former U.S. president took an especially surreal turn, as adult-film actress Stormy Daniels told jurors about an alleged sexual encounter with Donald Trump that she did not want, prompting a call from defense lawyers for a mistrial. Read our takeaways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f335c30-0cb2-11ef-a60c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 20:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok files court challenge to law that could lead to its ban, setting up what could be an existential fight for the popular app</title>
      <description>The filing raises a variety of legal issues arguing that the law, signed by President Biden last month and which calls for TikTok’s sale within 270 days, was an unconstitutional overreach. It called for the court to block the law’s enforcement until it reaches a decision on the substance of the filing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8dd40c0-0c8d-11ef-8ef0-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband admits to one-night stand, wants spouse to ‘let it go’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband admits to one-night stand, wants spouse to ‘let it go’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e69f3b70-0c8a-11ef-b7ab-0000a1ace835</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stormy Daniels, testifying now, recounts how she came to meet Trump in a hotel room — and the pajamas she said he was wearing</title>
      <description>Daniels, who alleged that she had a sexual encounter with Donald Trump years before he sought the presidency, is testifying this morning in his criminal trial. Trump faces 34 counts of falsifying business records related to his reimbursement of his then-lawyer Michael Cohen for a hush money payment made to the adult-film actress shortly before the 2016 election, which was meant to keep her from publicly sharing her story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3530d3e0-0c89-11ef-9de2-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 15:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 1,000 people, including 91 admirals, swept up in ‘Fat Leonard’ scandal, new book reveals. Yet only one admiral went to prison.</title>
      <description>Aides accused Rear Adm. Robert Gilbeau, known as “Crazy Bob,” of faking a mental breakdown in Afghanistan to avoid prosecution. He became the only admiral in history to be found guilty of committing a federal crime while on active duty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08351091-0c7f-11ef-aee0-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 14:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A photo finish in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb54cb80-0c75-11ef-9bed-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adult-film actress Stormy Daniels is expected to testify today in Trump’s hush money trial in N.Y. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Donald Trump faces 34 counts of falsifying business records related to his reimbursement of his former lawyer Michael Cohen for a hush money payment before the 2016 election to Daniels, who alleged that she had a sexual encounter with Trump years earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dde8e80-0c73-11ef-9a38-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 13:13:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel captures Rafah border crossing, imperiling aid efforts to Gaza</title>
      <description>The Israel Defense Forces said it has taken “operational control” of the Gazan side of the Rafah crossing. Egypt has condemned the move, calling it a dangerous escalation. A Gaza border official said the flow of aid into the Strip “stopped completely” as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e10ae20-0c64-11ef-b2b2-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:25:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cease-fire talks. Trump warning. Tornadoes. Putin’s inauguration. Social Security. Highway 1. Met Gala. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f516f190-0c60-11ef-be7a-0000a1ace201</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vladimir Putin sworn in for a fifth term as president, positioning him as Russia’s leader-for-life</title>
      <description>Putin, who has circumvented term limits repeatedly to remain Russia’s supreme political leader for a quarter-century, was inaugurated for a new six-year term that will run through 2030. Putin has vowed to persist with his war in Ukraine and is presiding over a sweeping transformation of Russia into a regressive militarized state in conflict with America and the West.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee584b0-0c54-11ef-84a4-0000a1ace3b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See the best looks from the Met Gala</title>
      <description>“The Garden of Time” dress code promised florals, decadence and the ephemeral beauty of nature. See The Post’s favorite looks from the Met Gala, including Ayo Edebiri, Nicole Kidman and Bad Bunny.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043b93e0-0c13-11ef-85b8-0000a1ace228</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 01:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel to press attack on Rafah as it negotiates possible Gaza cease-fire agreement</title>
      <description>Israel’s war cabinet said late Monday its mediators would return to the negotiating table after Hamas announced it had agreed to a Qatari-Egyptian proposal to pause fighting and release hostages. But the Israeli government also vowed to maintain military pressure on Rafah, where airstrikes and a mass evacuation order stirred panic among the more than a million displaced Palestinians sheltering there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c469e7b0-0bf6-11ef-8357-0000a1aceb43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stars arrive for the 2024 Met Gala, themed ‘Sleeping Beauties: Reawakening Fashion.’ Follow our live red-carpet coverage.</title>
      <description>We’ll have updates from the scene and analysis of the looks, so follow along for all things Met.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">197e85f0-0bf5-11ef-8235-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 22:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. soldier has been detained in Russia on criminal charges, Army says</title>
      <description>An Army spokeswoman said Russia’s government notified the State Department earlier this month of the soldier’s detention in Vladivostok. The soldier’s identity was not disclosed, and neither were the circumstances surrounding the criminal charges or why the solider was in Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d974a300-0be9-11ef-be92-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:47:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security and Medicare will run out of money in just over a decade if Congress doesn’t act, report warns</title>
      <description>A hot job market has delayed the expected fiscal crash, but an aging population and rising federal debt still will put pressure on lawmakers to address the budget, the trustees for Social Security and Medicare said Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fd9b670-0be4-11ef-81f6-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 20:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Post wins Pulitzer Prizes for national reporting, editorial writing and commentary</title>
      <description>The awards recognize The Post’s series on the political power and cultural impact of the AR-15 rifle, as well as editorials by veteran staffer David E. Hoffman on the troubling rise of autocracy around the world and commentary by Vladimir Kara-Murza, a contributing columnist who has been imprisoned in Russia since April 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d62997b0-0bde-11ef-8357-0000a1aceb43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sisters were close — then one accused the other’s husband of abuse</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sisters were close — then one accused the other’s husband of abuse</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6c84b50-0bc1-11ef-86e0-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 16:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin is forging a new Russia: Ultraconservative, militarized and anti-West</title>
      <description>The Russian leader is harnessing his invasion of Ukraine to transform his country into a regressive, militarized state and to fulfill his vision of a restored superpower set on upending the U.S.-led global order.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f098b1-0bb5-11ef-835b-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 14:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Columbia University cancels school-wide commencement, moves ceremonies off main campus amid protests</title>
      <description>Columbia will instead hold “smaller-scale, school-based celebrations.” The university has drawn national attention for an encampment of pro-Palestinian protesters, who occupied a campus building last week before being removed by police.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b6c450-0baf-11ef-b33c-0000a1acedb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:53:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changes to the brain during what? Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d34fcf20-0baf-11ef-8a7e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial finds him in contempt on more gag order violations, warns former president of jail time</title>
      <description>“I find you in criminal contempt for the tenth time,” said New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan, who said he is concerned Donald Trump has not apparently taken heed from his prior findings. “Going forward, this court will have to consider a jail sentence. The last thing I want to do is put you in jail.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7a4bfd0-0bad-11ef-80c6-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel orders 100,000 civilians to evacuate Rafah, says it will operate with ‘extreme force’</title>
      <description>The southern Gazan city is home to more than a million displaced Palestinians and, according to Israel, the last Hamas battalions. Aid agencies have said there is nowhere for civilians to go and U.S. officials have warned a major operation in Rafah would be a “disaster.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">159b6381-0ba1-11ef-8eca-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 12:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s warning. Trump trial. Missing surfers. Henry Cuellar. Gas stoves. Kentucky Derby. Starliner launch. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbd89230-0b97-11ef-8da2-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Loomer’s far-right rhetoric has repelled many would-be MAGA allies, with one notable exception: Trump himself</title>
      <description>People around the former president apparently see Loomer — an anti-Islam, anti-immigration activist — as a liability at a time when Donald Trump’s campaign (if not the candidate himself) is making a conscious effort to make their man appear less extreme, according to several sources close to the campaign’s inner circle. Still, Loomer is dead set on landing a role in a second Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1ded171-0b23-11ef-92e9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 21:08:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12ad0c80-0af9-11ef-a431-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 16:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chris Pratt’s demolition of a historic home to build a modern farmhouse is part of a disturbing trend</title>
      <description>Few people realized the Zimmerman House in Los Angeles was in any danger before it was unceremoniously razed by the actor and his wife, author Katherine Schwarzenegger, who bought the mid-century home and its nearly one-acre plot last year for $12.5 million. Increasingly, preservationists say, these demos are not driven by changing tastes but rather by Americans’ ravenous appetites for larger and larger homes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a10021-0af1-11ef-a431-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 15:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11ca0c11-0ae4-11ef-a0c8-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 13:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 protesters at University of Virginia arrested after violent clash with police</title>
      <description>The university said 25 pro-Palestinian demonstrators at the University of Virginia were arrested, after law enforcement officers in riot gear surrounded a student encampment that the administration said was prohibited</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85dddf60-0a70-11ef-a376-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mystik Dan finishes first in a photo finish in the 150th running of the Kentucky Derby</title>
      <description>The Derby field at Churchill Downs on Saturday also included Dornoch, who is co-owned by former MLB star Jayson Werth, and Fierceness, a colt trained by Todd Pletcher. The Triple Crown continues with the Preakness Stakes on May 18 and the Belmont Stakes on June 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfabc750-0a6b-11ef-bc46-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 23:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Stella, celebrated artist of minimalist power, dies at 87</title>
      <description>Stella achieved early fame with a series of monochromatic paintings that helped establish minimalism as an alternative to abstract expressionism in the late 1950s. He then spent the next several decades creating colorful works that seemed to repudiate his youthful principles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c51f5a50-0a5c-11ef-a82f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 21:25:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Abnormal and unprecedented’: Surge in sea level rise is imperiling the American South</title>
      <description>Americans from Texas to North Carolina are grappling with one of the most rapid sea level surges on Earth, one that is choking septic systems, swallowing roads and drowning wetlands. Search The Post’s data to see how sea levels have changed across the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6cc81d0-0a46-11ef-a6b4-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 18:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
