<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:03:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e4b2671-d96a-11ee-a008-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sweeps GOP primary contests in Michigan, Idaho and Missouri, AP projects, bringing him closer to clinching nomination</title>
      <description>Donald Trump won all three nominating contests Saturday, the Associated Press projected, putting him in a stronger position for March 5, the day 15 states and a third of delegates are awarded as part of Super Tuesday. Nikki Haley, Trump’s main rival for the GOP nod, has vowed to press on until then, despite losing every primary and caucus so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29407740-d8f2-11ee-9d52-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a CVS drugstore in D.C. became a symbol of America's shoplifting panic</title>
      <description>It became a horror story of Late Capitalism. Tales were told on social media, and in the comments sections of local news stories, and they were full of spooky scenes (harsh fluorescent lights shining on bare shelves!) and jump scares (hordes of teenagers reportedly ransacking the stores!).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60767470-d8da-11ee-a050-000a1ace86f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An examination of Robert F. Kennedy’s early years as a lawyer reveals a controversy long before he trained his sights on vaccines</title>
      <description>As a young attorney at Riverkeeper, Kennedy Jr. opened a schism by hiring a new staff scientist just released from federal prison. His crime: running an international wildlife smuggling ring that prosecutors said had damaged rare bird populations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1b5c60-d8c8-11ee-832a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Maryland halts all fraternity, sorority events amid hazing concerns</title>
      <description>The University of Maryland has suspended all “new member” fraternity and sorority events and any events with alcohol while officials look into hazing allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f137eba0-d8b8-11ee-9432-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After a scary ‘incident,’ spouse wants husband out for good</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After a scary ‘incident,’ spouse wants husband out for good</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad1a770-d8b7-11ee-8ca3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘greenest’ car in America might surprise you. Hint: It’s not an EV.</title>
      <description>A new analysis finds that the greenest car in America this year isn’t an electric vehicle — it’s the Toyota Prius Prime, a plug-in hybrid that can go 44 miles on all-electric power. The result shows that size and efficiency, not just drivetrain, matter when buying a new car.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0115171-d8af-11ee-b802-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military airdrops aid into Gaza as relief agencies warn of mass starvation</title>
      <description>Three U.S. officials confirmed Saturday that the airdrops were carried out by C-130 cargo plane. The operation followed similar moves from countries including Egypt, France, Jordan and the United Arab Emirates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">422cf4b1-d8a5-11ee-a9b5-0000a1acecd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 14:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84155970-d8a1-11ee-8137-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 14:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iris Apfel has died at 102. The designer, known for her oversized, owlish spectacles, became a ‘geriatric starlet’ in her 80s.</title>
      <description>Apfel, who died at her home in Palm Beach, Fla., appeared regularly in the style pages of the New York Times and starred in advertising campaigns for Kate Spade and Coach handbags. Stu Loeser, a spokesman for her estate, confirmed her death in a statement but did not provide a specific cause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">560b0030-d832-11ee-8d4a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to launch airdrop campaign over Gaza, Biden says, as humanitarian crisis worsens</title>
      <description>The announcement comes with Gaza on the brink of famine, humanitarian groups say. Aid convoys have struggled to make deliveries amid Israel’s bombardment of the Palestinian enclave and disruptions at border crossings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa7dc480-d801-11ee-b514-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final arguments are underway on whether Fani Willis should be disqualified from case against Trump. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Defense attorneys and prosecutors in the election interference case against former president Donald Trump and his allies are scheduled to make their final arguments this afternoon on whether Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis (D) and her office should be disqualified from the case. Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee has suggested that he does not plan to rule from the bench today, and he has not provided a timeline for his decision. The misconduct allegations threaten to derail the criminal case against Trump, one of four he faces as he again runs for president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c503f10-d7f7-11ee-9302-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 100 convicted Jan. 6 rioters could be resentenced after appeals court ruling</title>
      <description>The U.S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit overturned the use of a sentencing enhancement applied to a Jan. 6 defendant who stormed the U.S. Capitol and was convicted of felony obstruction. The court, however, upheld the use of the obstruction charge that is being challenged by Capitol attack defendants and is also being lodged against former president Donald Trump and will soon be debated by the Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">184003d0-d7f2-11ee-aea3-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 17:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Walgreens, CVS will soon dispense abortion pill in states where it is legal, expanding access ahead of expected Supreme Court case</title>
      <description>The move by two of the nation’s largest pharmacy networks promises to increase the availability of mifepristone as soon as next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d01b2e40-d7ec-11ee-afb0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 16:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28033270-d7d8-11ee-9c46-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 14:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Biden. Gaza deaths. Navalny funeral. IVF bill. Discord leaks. Ultra-processed food. Life’s origin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3abf6381-d7c3-11ee-8145-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes short-term extension to avert partial government shutdown, sending it to Biden to sign before weekend deadline</title>
      <description>The new shutdown deadlines will be March 8 and March 22. The House had passed the bill Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bbf5db0-d769-11ee-8185-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 01:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The palace says Catherine, Princess of Wales, is recovering from a surgery. So why the absurd conspiracy theories?</title>
      <description>Catherine had a planned abdominal surgery in January, and Kensington Palace said from the outset that she wouldn’t be resuming public appearances until after Easter. But perhaps partly because she has so often been the picture of health and fitness, her absence has stirred speculation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2ac06a0-d75b-11ee-ac2d-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Feb 2024 23:40:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
