<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 14:01:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 11 best looks from the Met Gala</title>
      <description>Menswear, for once, didn’t steal the show — it was the show. See our favorite looks from an evening of dignified, grown-up glamour at this year’s fete celebrating the museum’s exhibit “Superfine: Tailoring Black Style.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19f9d7f0-2a80-11f0-a583-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:43:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A facility that’s been closed since 1963 is in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5252cf50-2a7e-11f0-b34e-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-deportation. Hollywood tariff. Gaza occupation. Mike Pence. Texas colleges. Meta AI. Met Gala. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">416bc580-2a69-11f0-86dc-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Service ends air-quality monitoring at all national parks</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has ordered the end to the air-quality monitoring program at national parks across the country, according to two people familiar with the matter and an internal email obtained by The Post. The program collects data on the levels of air pollutants at the 63 national parks in the United States. Federal officials consult this data when deciding whether to grant a permit to a nearby industrial facility, such as a power plant or an oil refinery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a10fa1-2a05-11f0-8dc3-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 23:04:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The stars are arriving on the Met Gala red carpet. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Who best captured this year's Black dandy theme? Watch along with Washington Post reporters as we discuss all the eye-catching looks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2621dce0-2a02-11f0-a4bc-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:41:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. region until midnight</title>
      <description>Storms, some containing torrential rain, hail and strong winds, will sweep through the D.C. area from south to north. Follow Capital Weather Gang's live updates for the latest on the storms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d400a51-2a00-11f0-a97c-0000a1ace97d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 22:29:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Post wins Pulitzers for breaking news and political cartoons; ProPublica wins journalism’s top award in public service category</title>
      <description>The Washington Post was recognized with two Pulitzer Prizes on Monday, including a win in the breaking news reporting category for coverage of the attempted assassination of Donald Trump in July. Ann Telnaes, until recently a political cartoonist for The Post’s Opinions page, was awarded her second win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a72e29d0-29e7-11f0-ae09-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 19:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT maker OpenAI scraps plan to restructure into a for-profit company after pressure from Elon Musk</title>
      <description>OpenAI aimed to separate from its nonprofit board but reversed course after former employees and a lawsuit from Musk alleged it would loosen oversight of its powerful artificial intelligence technology.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55c640e0-29de-11f0-8796-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders owner joins Bowser and Trump to announce 2027 NFL draft on the National Mall, envisioning 1 million fans in D.C.</title>
      <description>Washington Commanders owner Josh Harris, NFL Commissioner Roger Goodell and Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) joined President Donald Trump in the Oval Office for Monday afternoon’s formal announcement about the 2027 NFL draft. Harris told The Washington Post on Monday he hopes to draw 1 million visitors to the District for the annual event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7887aea1-29db-11f0-b927-0000a1ace41d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Choosing that baecation over meeting first grandbaby, explained</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Choosing that baecation over meeting first grandbaby, explained</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c7a9d1-29ca-11f0-b616-0000a1ace652</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 16:01:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The velocity of unladen swallows in today’s On The Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3967e6f1-29b7-11f0-9f19-0000a1ace563</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump interview. Reopening Alcatraz. Australia election. Gaza war. Viral fundraiser. Downpours. Cosmic gold. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19445460-29a0-11f0-8c71-0000a1ace45f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeons attempt a medical first: Removing a spinal tumor through the patient’s eye</title>
      <description>Karla Flores had a tumor strangling her spinal cord near the base of her skull. Her doctors decided to try a risky procedure that had never been performed on a living patient.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bfaa170-292f-11f0-838f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 21:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s 48-hour scramble to fly migrants to a Salvadoran megaprison</title>
      <description>The administration rounded up some Venezuelans two days before the flights to El Salvador took off, pressing forward even as Venezuela agreed to accept deportation flights. A Washington Post investigation found that at least two men who had flown to the United States as vetted refugees were among those believed to have been sent to the prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">982baca0-2910-11f0-9f7d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 17:52:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90a44970-2900-11f0-9a73-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 35 definitive rules of train travel</title>
      <description>Whether you’re hopping up the Northeast corridor or just taking in-town public transit, you should treat your fellow passengers with the courtesy they deserve. Share this guide with the seat sprawlers and cafe car squatters in your life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d952d450-28f8-11f0-bd23-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 15:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05a5f300-28ec-11f0-bb79-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says ‘I don’t know’ when asked whether he is required to uphold the Constitution in NBC interview</title>
      <description>In a wide-ranging interview, President Donald Trump also did not rule out the use of military force to take Greenland but said it’s “highly unlikely” he’d do so with Canada. He downplayed fears of a recession and spoke of both Vice President JD Vance and Secretary of State Marco Rubio as his potential successors, saying that running for a third term “is not something I’m looking to do.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9378b310-28e8-11f0-baf9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 13:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sovereignty wins the 151st Kentucky Derby, the first leg of horse racing’s Triple Crown</title>
      <description>Sovereignty won the Run for the Roses on Saturday at Churchill Downs in Louisville.
The next leg of the Triple Crown is the Preakness Stakes, to be held May 17 in Baltimore, followed by the Belmont Stakes on June 7 in Saratoga Springs, New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3aea8f0-2873-11f0-81d9-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, brown rice is healthier than white rice — except in some limited cases</title>
      <description>Recent concerns over the health risks of eating brown rice are mostly overblown, studies show. Experts contend that the nutritional benefits outweigh any concerns about arsenic in a varied diet. A caveat is that some groups, such as infants and toddlers, may be more vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43423a0-2861-11f0-8d45-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett to step down as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway by year’s end after leading the conglomerate for decades</title>
      <description>Buffett, 94, announced his retirement intention at Berkshire Hathaway’s annual meeting in Omaha. He said he would recommend Greg Abel, whom Buffett has previously said would succeed him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ddedf20-284f-11f0-b290-0000a1ace80d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">165261b0-2839-11f0-81de-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At a Kentucky farm, star racehorses help people fight a monster: Addiction</title>
      <description>The Stable Recovery program at Taylor Made Farm changes lives with the remarkable healing power of animals. Men in the program live on the farm and learn how to care for the elite racehorses, giving them a sense of structure and purpose many of them had struggled to find.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">475fa5b0-282f-11f0-993b-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 14:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd25c8d0-2822-11f0-b3ae-0000a1aceb64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted national security adviser Michael Waltz had angered Trump by coordinating privately with Israel over plans to attack Iran</title>
      <description>Waltz appeared to have engaged in intense coordination with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu about military options against Iran ahead of an Oval Office meeting last month between the Israeli leader and President Donald Trump, two people with knowledge of the episode said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b62b4940-2820-11f0-98d4-0000a1ace003</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia’s center-left party is projected to win reelection in dramatic turnaround fueled by Trump tariffs</title>
      <description>Despite trailing in polls two months ago, Prime Minister Anthony Albanese appears to be on course for a second term, although it is not clear whether his Labor Party would be able to govern outright or would need to partner with a smaller party or independents. Albanese’s comeback would be the second by a center-left leader in less than a week, with Canada’s Mark Carney managing a similar feat on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be499fa0-280c-11f0-9f23-0000a1aceb0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 10:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our best mint julep recipes, plus Hot Browns, pimento cheese and more Kentucky Derby snacks</title>
      <description>Our best mint julep recipes, plus Hot Browns, pimento cheese and more Kentucky Derby snacks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed1b82f0-279c-11f0-b22c-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA plans to cut 1,200 positions as Trump administration eyes downsizing of thousands across U.S. intelligence community</title>
      <description>The White House recently informed lawmakers that it intends to trim the workforce at the CIA and other major U.S. spy units, downsizing the government’s most sensitive national security agencies, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f45755a0-2795-11f0-87e5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of slain Capitol rioter Ashli Babbitt has reached settlement in principle of wrongful-death lawsuit</title>
      <description>Lawyers for the Justice Department and Judicial Watch said they'd reached a settlement in principle with the family of Babbitt, whose fatal shooting became a defining moment of the Jan. 6, 2021, Capitol riot. Babbitt's husband filed the lawsuit last year, seeking $30 million. The case was set to go to trial until President Donald Trump took office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec2fe1e1-2785-11f0-a294-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Daughter wishes I was a ‘normal mom’ who's excited for her wedding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Daughter wishes I was a ‘normal mom’ who's excited for her wedding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f21c510-2774-11f0-94ea-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregg Popovich will no longer coach the Spurs after he suffered a stroke in November</title>
      <description>Popovich, 76, is the NBA’s all-time winningest coach and led San Antonio to five championships since taking over during the 1996-97 season.
He was replaced on an interim basis this season after suffering what the team called a “mild stroke” before a game Nov. 2. The team announced that Popovich will transition to a role as president of basketball operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164f2a40-2771-11f0-9dea-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump budget would cut nondefense programs by 23 percent and increase defense spending by 13 percent next year</title>
      <description>The White House released a partial budget proposal that underscores how much the administration aims to reduce federal spending. There were no details on taxes or on programs such as Social Security and Medicare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68400200-2769-11f0-b21a-000a1ace09b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance writes in an op-ed: What Trump achieved in his first 100 days</title>
      <description>JD Vance: What President Trump achieved in his first 100 days</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7c9420-2765-11f0-842d-0000a1ace054</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Buzzi, famed as dowdy purse slinger on ‘Laugh-In,’ dies at 88</title>
      <description>Buzzi was a comedic actress with a high-beam smile who often played sidekicks both wisecracking and wise. She scowled her way to pop culture fame on the comedy-variety show “Rowan &amp; Martin’s Laugh-In” playing a matron who wields her purse like a cudgel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b77f4e0-2764-11f0-917d-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc7a750-2759-11f0-ba5f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The labor market slowed in April, as employers added 177,000 jobs, a solid showing amid tariff uncertainty</title>
      <description>The unemployment rate remained steady at 4.2 percent, according to the latest jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, as the labor market largely weathered the turmoil of tariff policy in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca1b7b0-2751-11f0-840b-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waltz ouster. Trump setbacks. Elon Musk. Rising prices. Missing journalist. Bird decline. Cookbook drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4555300-2744-11f0-8d89-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration calls for defunding NPR and PBS in executive order</title>
      <description>The order instructs the Corporation for Public Broadcasting to cease direct funding to the services and to end grants that local stations can spend on NPR and PBS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13d15cd1-2720-11f0-a049-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rising Hegseth aide first appointed under Biden has drawn scrutiny inside the Pentagon — and the White House</title>
      <description>Some Republicans loyal to the president have sought to block the elevation of Ricky Buria, whom officials say Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has openly considered for his next chief of staff. The “purity” questions surrounding Buria illustrate the increasingly politicized climate enveloping the Pentagon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09fb7030-26d8-11f0-9da4-0000a1ace337</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taps Michael Waltz for U.N. ambassador, says Secretary of State Rubio will replace him as interim national security adviser</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s announcement on social media followed reports that Waltz, who has lost favor in the White House and among other Trump loyalists, was going to be replaced as national security adviser. Marco Rubio will continue as secretary of state until a permanent replacement for Waltz is found, Trump said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54cc7270-26bb-11f0-915a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says Trump cannot use Alien Enemies Act to deport Venezuelans, in first major ruling on the legality of using the act</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Fernando Rodriguez, Jr. said President Donald Trump exceeded his authority when he invoked the wartime provision to declare, without providing evidence, that the United States was being invaded by a Venezuelan gang and had the authority to deport alleged gang members without a hearing to El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10134600-26b5-11f0-916d-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess who’s actually winning the trade war? Matt Bai spent the past month untangling the case.</title>
      <description>Are countries being pressured to help the world’s richest man? Or are they just making smart deals?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98113810-26a5-11f0-a284-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to replace embattled national security adviser Michael Waltz, current and former officials say</title>
      <description>Waltz’s exit would mark the first major upheaval on President Donald Trump’s top national security staff. His critics have deemed Waltz out of step with Trump’s “America First” foreign policy agenda, and he has steadily lost favor after revelations that he relied on unclassified online communications for highly sensitive government business.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39b17780-26a0-11f0-b6f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to block California’s ban on sales of gas-powered cars by 2035. It’s unclear whether the Senate will follow suit.</title>
      <description>Eleven other states have pledged to adopt California’s ban. The House Republicans’ vote ignores legal opinions from the Senate parliamentarian and the Government Accountability Office that Congress lacks the legal authority to prevent states from enforcing such climate rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c893e50-269b-11f0-a497-000a1ace4569</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal daily information requirements into today's On The Record</title>
      <description>Federal daily information requirements into today's On The Record</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae9a0180-2690-11f0-836c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Clooney, Sarah Snook and Audra McDonald are among the 2025 Tony nominees</title>
      <description>The Tony Awards ceremony honoring the best of the Broadway season will be held June 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69fde810-268c-11f0-ba7c-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine deal. Kamala Harris. Vaccine change. Supreme Court. Gaza map. Pacific Northwest quake. Axolotl hope. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a794250-267b-11f0-a9a1-0000a1ace973</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris condemns Trump’s policies and ‘unconstitutional demands’ in her first major speech since leaving the White House</title>
      <description>The 2024 Democratic presidential nominee urged her supporters to summon the courage to fight what she called President Donald Trump’s efforts to stoke fear and “punish truth tellers.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0223a80-263b-11f0-b737-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitals beat Canadiens in Game 5 to advance to the second round of the Stanley Cup playoffs for the first time since 2018</title>
      <description>Washington, the No. 1 seed in the Eastern Conference, topped scrappy Montreal on home ice Wednesday to take the best-of-seven series. The Capitals, who will meet the Carolina Hurricanes in the second round, had not clinched a playoff series at home since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba3d5c62-262e-11f0-9616-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. will require shift in how new vaccines are tested, HHS says</title>
      <description>The potential change outlined in a statement says all new vaccines will be required to undergo placebo testing, a procedure in which some people receive the vaccine and others receive an inert substance — such as a saline shot — before the results are compared. The Department of Health and Human Services says the move will increase transparency but medical experts fear it could limit access to vaccines and undermine the public’s trust in immunization depending on how it is implemented. HHS did not fully clarify how the change would work and for which vaccines the testing would apply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f91d7c71-2625-11f0-8806-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
