<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 16:03:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>New rules aimed at protecting transgender students are blocked in four states by a federal court</title>
      <description>The regulations, issued by the Education Department in April, represent its interpretation of Title IX, a half-century-old law that bars discrimination in schools based on sex. The preliminary injunction against the rules applies in Louisiana, Mississippi, Montana and Idaho, though similar challenges are pending in other states. The rules are set to take effect on Aug. 1 and affect every K-12 school, college and university in the country that accepts any type of federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">213cbea0-2a64-11ef-bc70-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $895 billion defense policy bill that targets abortion access and diversity protections, advances other GOP priorities</title>
      <description>The bill, initially hailed by lawmakers who drafted it as a feat of bipartisanship, is certain to set up a clash — and prolonged negotiation — with the Democratic-controlled Senate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c715080-2a62-11ef-82ec-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down Trump-era federal ban on bump stock devices that allow rifles to fire hundreds of bullets per minute</title>
      <description>The case turned on whether bump stocks meet the definition of a machine gun. Federal appeals courts were sharply divided over that question in earlier decisions on the ban’s legality, before the Supreme Court took up the lawsuit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a814bc0-2a59-11ef-8ee4-0000a1ace894</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 14:22:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Catholic bishops apologize for church’s role at Indian boarding schools, citing ‘trauma’ for generations of children</title>
      <description>The extraordinary vote represents the most direct expression of regret to date by senior officials in the Catholic Church for its participation in a U.S. government program to systematically strip Native American children of their identities and forcibly assimilate them into White society. It comes weeks after a Washington Post investigation documenting pervasive sexual abuse by Catholic priests at the schools.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73651030-2a53-11ef-a3c2-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:38:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5de79e40-2a52-11ef-921b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abortion pills. IVF vote. Evan Gershkovich. Florida flooding. Racism study. NBA Finals. Taylor Swift. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">349a16e0-2a3d-11ef-bf2d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customers love the Call Your Mother bagel shop in Georgetown. Some neighbors want it closed.</title>
      <description>If the crowds outside got to make the call, the self-described “Jew-ish” deli in a bright pink D.C. rowhome would have no trouble winning officials’ blessing to keep selling its bagels. But owners of neighboring million-dollar rowhouses, citing decades-old zoning laws and a D.C. Court of Appeals ruling, want the shop to stop serving prepared food.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c250d70-29e1-11ef-8472-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This ‘Bridgerton’ duo’s long-simmering, friends-to-lovers romance is bringing the heat to Season 3</title>
      <description>Nicola Coughlan and Luke Newton are heating up the Netflix juggernaut, but their path to Shondaland had plenty of bumps. In interviews with The Washington Post, they discuss their journey from out-of-work artists to the diamonds of the season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6584c0b0-29d0-11ef-a391-0000a1ace4f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 22:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With extreme heat set to roar in, we declare spring over. Here’s how hot it could get next week.</title>
      <description>Starting Monday, every day will probably see highs of at least 90, with the possibility of temperatures approaching 100 during the week’s second half. It could rank among the hottest weeks in several years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9bd09b0-29c3-11ef-94f2-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 20:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans block consideration of bill to protect access to in vitro fertilization. See how every lawmaker voted.</title>
      <description>The measure needed 60 votes to advance and received 48. It was the latest Democratic effort to put Republicans on the defensive amid a broader election-year debate over reproductive health care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09370a81-29bb-11ef-9f1d-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 19:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: The Post’s AI summit, featuring Reid Hoffman, Gen. Mark A. Milley, Maria Ressa, Jen Easterly and more</title>
      <description>Artificial intelligence could herald a massive technology shift that transforms the way we work, live and interact with the world around us. Join The Washington Post for robust discussions about the future of the rapidly evolving technology dominating daily headlines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ed3ec80-29af-11ef-9fc9-0000a1ace245</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 18:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phoenix Police Department routinely uses excessive force and discriminates based on race, Justice Department probe finds</title>
      <description>A federal civil rights investigation into the Phoenix police found that officers there use unnecessarily dangerous force, fail to provide proper oversight and enforce the law based on race, according to a Justice Department report released Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcb8ffe0-29a8-11ef-aeb6-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 17:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. John Fetterman had a history of speeding tickets and distracted driving before his recent car crash, records show</title>
      <description>Fetterman (D-Pa.) was speeding and at fault for a Sunday morning auto accident in western Maryland, where he rear-ended another driver, a 62-year-old woman who was taken to the hospital in an ambulance, according to a Maryland State Police report. The crash was the latest example of unsafe driving by Fetterman, according to public records and people with knowledge of the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d9bcd90-29a2-11ef-a175-0000a1acefc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She’s worried her boyfriend sees her as a sex maid</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She’s worried her boyfriend sees her as a sex maid</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56e03300-299e-11ef-ab52-0000a1ace494</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 16:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court retains access to key abortion medication with procedural ruling, a win for abortion rights after Roe was overturned</title>
      <description>A group of antiabortion doctors challenged the FDA’s regulation of mifepristone, used in more than 60 percent of U.S. abortions. Since the high court overturned Roe v. Wade in 2022, abortion medications have grown increasingly important but have faced court challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91cba801-298f-11ef-b63a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American journalist Evan Gershkovich of the Wall Street Journal to stand trial in Russia on charges of spying for the CIA</title>
      <description>Gershkovich has been detained in Russia for more than a year on spying charges that he, the Journal and the State Department vehemently deny and for which Russian authorities have provided no evidence. Officials previously confirmed that a potential exchange had been in discussion involving Alexei Navalny, the Russian opposition leader, who died in prison, and Vadim Krasikov, a Russian security agent convicted and jailed in Germany on murder charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1ff4250-298e-11ef-8b5c-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 14:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hot dog legend in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08d2b620-2989-11ef-a386-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>G-7 meeting. Trump visit. Interest rates. Southern Baptists. Police abuse. Heat wave. Spicy noodles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0996d600-2974-11ef-b96d-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla shareholders re-approve Elon Musk’s 2018 pay package, Musk says</title>
      <description>The Tesla CEO shared the news Wednesday night on X, his social media platform. Though the full results will not be revealed until Thursday’s shareholder meeting, the current tallies appear to resolve a dispute that has loomed over Musk’s future with the company.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cdb6200-2940-11ef-9217-0000a1ace2c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 04:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heat wave in the eastern U.S. could produce dangerously high temperatures for much of next week. See maps of the region at risk.</title>
      <description>A punishing combination of heat and humidity will remain lodged over the East, potentially for an extended period. It’s already been one of the warmest years on record in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">068c5060-290c-11ef-ac38-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 22:35:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-run House votes to hold Garland in contempt after he refused to turn over Biden interview tapes in classified documents probe</title>
      <description>The vote targeting Attorney General Merrick Garland was a show of Republicans’ displeasure that the Biden administration refuses to turn over audiotapes of President Biden’s interview with federal investigators about classified documents found in his home and former office. The Justice Department has already turned over the transcripts but says handing over the recordings would set a bad precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0de3640-28fd-11ef-8561-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 20:52:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Southern Baptists approve measure asking government to ‘restrain’ IVF, hours after narrowly rejecting a total ban on female pastors</title>
      <description>The 14 million-member convention, the country’s second-largest faith group, has been shifting to the right since a conservative insurgency in the 1980s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0646c211-28ef-11ef-a80d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 19:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fed leaves interest rates unchanged and signals a scaled-back plan to cut rates once this year</title>
      <description>The announcement came just a few hours after an encouraging inflation report beat economists' expectations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a40faf1-28e6-11ef-b715-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard Fineman dies at 75. The veteran political correspondent brought an analytical approach to coverage at Newsweek and on TV.</title>
      <description>Fineman spent 30 years at Newsweek beginning in 1980, serving as chief political correspondent and deputy Washington bureau chief during the era when the magazine, then owned by The Washington Post, was one of the most widely read newsweeklies in the United States. He was also an analyst for NBC and MSNBC for years and became familiar to television viewers through his appearances on shows including “Hardball With Chris Matthews,” PBS’s “Washington Week in Review” and CNN’s “Capital Gang Sunday.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c409830-28e3-11ef-b013-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 17:44:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to curb a ‘growing dislike’ of nephew’s new wife?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to curb a ‘growing dislike’ of nephew’s new wife?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fce81260-28d4-11ef-a122-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How should a restaurant respond to a missing dish? Our food critic is answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How should a restaurant respond to a missing dish? Our food critic is answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">563e8af0-28d1-11ef-bd8d-0000a1ace774</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 15:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of police officers have sexually abused children, The Post found. Many exploited their authority to coerce their victims.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found at least 1,800 state and local law enforcement officers were charged with crimes involving child sexual abuse from 2005 through 2022. Predatory cops often used the power of their badges to find and silence their victims, while officials at every level of the criminal justice system failed to protect children and punish abusers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92eec820-28c7-11ef-94f2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 14:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jerry West dies at 86. He was a Basketball Hall of Famer as a player and executive, and his silhouette inspired the NBA’s logo.</title>
      <description>West died Wednesday morning, the Los Angeles Clippers announced in a statement without specifying the cause.

The 14-time all-star spent his entire playing career with the Los Angeles Lakers from 1960 to 1974, winning the 1972 NBA championship, then won several more titles as an executive with multiple franchises in the ensuing decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f76219f2-28c3-11ef-9717-000a1ace3782</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 13:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap elections in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edcc52b0-28bf-11ef-bcf0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased slightly in the year ending in May, but it’s still above normal</title>
      <description>The latest snapshot from the Bureau of Labor Statistics comes as Federal Reserve officials wrap up their two-day meeting and try to understand where the economy is headed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07f73b0-28b7-11ef-b5d8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 12:32:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden. Primary results. Transgender law. Medical debt. Climate damage. Spaceflight risks. Hot dogs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df994550-28aa-11ef-9217-0000a1ace2c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>27 little travel luxuries to make any trip feel first class this summer</title>
      <description>These self-gifts don’t have to be elaborate or expensive to provide a dash of comfort. They might even fit into your carry-on bag or coat pocket.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a803cf01-283e-11ef-9418-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 22:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. economy is growing significantly faster than expected, World Bank says</title>
      <description>The global economy is doing better now than the bank had projected in January, thanks to resilience in the United States, a report said. However, high interest rates and trade tensions pose risks to the upbeat forecast.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a21d820-2812-11ef-830d-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 16:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Now that she’s the mother-in-law, she sees no need for boundaries</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Now that she’s the mother-in-law, she sees no need for boundaries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba0907c0-280b-11ef-88c7-0000a1ace047</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden convicted of lying during gun purchase, after trial that focused on his drug addiction</title>
      <description>President Biden’s son Hunter was accused of lying when he claimed on a federal gun-purchasing form that he was not using or addicted to illegal drugs, and of illegally possessing a Colt revolver while on drugs. His attorneys said he completed a stint in rehab shortly before buying the gun in October 2018 and was drug-free for the 11 days it was in his possession.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a921900-2806-11ef-bf54-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 15:23:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The Justice Department is under attack like never before,’ Attorney General Merrick Garland writes. ‘This must stop.’</title>
      <description>Merrick Garland: Unfounded attacks on the Justice Department must end</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96a6a770-2800-11ef-9826-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was a beautiful day in this coastal town. Watch what happened when the water started to rise.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post installed cameras along the main road of one North Carolina town to document the many ways rising seas exacerbate high-tide flooding. Higher oceans are compromising stormwater infrastructure, overtopping shorelines, elevating groundwater and combining with rain to make flooding more persistent and insidious over time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">775ef0c0-27fb-11ef-9567-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 14:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know your game show hosts? Prove it in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce3ce4b0-27f6-11ef-8c89-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza cease-fire plan. Trump interview. Alito recording. Hunter Biden. Coastal floods. Apple AI. Elephant names. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b50e1aa0-27e1-11ef-b3ba-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore shipping channel fully reopens more than two months after Key Bridge collapse that killed six workers</title>
      <description>After a colossal cleanup effort, federal and state authorities announced Monday they had fully reopened the main shipping channel to the Port of Baltimore, restoring it to its 700-foot width. The channel had been slowly reopening since the March 26 collapse of the Key Bridge, and some early estimates suggested full restoration could take up to a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad481680-277e-11ef-addb-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 23:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Gaslit by doctors,’ some patients are turning to a shadow system of at-home tests</title>
      <description>A new world of DIY testing is allowing patients to bypass the doctor’s office and take medical tests on their own. The growth is fueled by a distrust of Big Medicine and confidence in home-testing born from the coronavirus pandemic. But the boom angers some doctors, who argue that circumventing their offices can lead to questionable remedies, misdiagnosis or delayed medical care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bac57d60-2770-11ef-9574-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 21:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Lawson dies at 95. The leading civil rights tactician helped organize sit-ins, marches and Freedom Rides in the 1960s.</title>
      <description>Civil rights chroniclers credit the Rev. Lawson, a Methodist minister, with playing a leading role in the opening of restaurants, movie theaters, city buses, public restrooms and municipal swimming pools in Nashville, one of the first major Southern cities to desegregate public accommodations. He was later one of the first Freedom Riders arrested in Jackson, Miss., as the activists sought to integrate interstate bus and train travel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c5255b0-2761-11ef-aaba-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 19:40:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple announces a deal with OpenAI as it aims to play catchup in a race against Google and Microsoft</title>
      <description>Apple announced a deal to use OpenAI's technology to power its generative artificial intelligence offerings, potentially helping it keep up with competitors. But the deal could raise antitrust concerns, experts say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c75a7a0-2759-11ef-853d-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels blindsided after overhearing husband’s therapy session</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse feels blindsided after overhearing husband’s therapy session</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c5a5970-2743-11ef-8268-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 16:04:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A wild upset in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9faff0-272d-11ef-942f-0000a1ace969</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 13:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Israel’s hostage rescue: Top-secret planning and a deadly ‘wall of fire’</title>
      <description>The military operation on Saturday that freed four Israeli hostages and killed more than 270 Palestinians, according to the Gaza Health Ministry, was one of the most dramatic and deadly episodes of Israel’s war against Hamas. This account is based on more than a dozen interviews with former and current Israeli military officials, family members of hostages and Palestinian eyewitnesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06179750-2724-11ef-9ab4-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 12:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil in Israel. European elections. Tax cuts. Tornadoes. At-home tests. Microplastics. D-Day marriage. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9848a210-2718-11ef-881b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home insurance was once a ‘must.’ Now more homeowners are going without.</title>
      <description>Experts say the trend in forgoing home insurance is driven by the growing impact of climate change — which has forced insurers to make larger and larger payouts — and skyrocketing housing prices. As the cost of insurance rises, more Americans have decided to expose themselves to risk rather than pay for it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85720541-26ab-11ef-953a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 21:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far right projected to make big gains in European Parliament; pending loss prompts France’s Macron to call legislative elections</title>
      <description>Early forecasts in the European Parliament elections show voters punishing ruling centrists and boosting nationalist parties that have made populist economic appeals and taken hard-right positions on immigration. After polls showed the far-right National Rally trouncing French President Emmanuel Macron’s centrist coalition, he dissolved the national parliament and set the first round of elections for June 30.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">371ab8b2-2697-11ef-8ec2-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 19:33:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions in taxpayer dollars are going to religious schools via vouchers as the separation between church and state erodes</title>
      <description>School vouchers can be used at almost any private school, but the vast majority of the money is being directed to religious schools, according to a Washington Post examination. The voucher programs, popular with conservatives, are rapidly growing in GOP-run states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27878bd0-2692-11ef-b4b0-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 18:57:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
