<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 20:02:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Baltimore prosecutor Marilyn Mosby sentenced to 12 months of home detention, 2 years of supervised release for fraud and perjury</title>
      <description>Mosby, who gained national prominence for charging police officers following the death of Freddie Gray, had been convicted in federal court in Maryland for lying to mortgage lenders in the process of buying two Florida vacation homes and falsely claiming financial hardship to access retirement money. Mosby has continued to deny wrongdoing, saying she was the target of a politically motivated prosecution, and has been campaigning for a presidential pardon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60fec1f0-193e-11ef-b0b1-0000a1ace832</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 19:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife of local celebrity chef is tired of ‘foodie groupies’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">750f7cf1-191d-11ef-b252-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:59:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Southern to pay $310 million over last year’s toxic train derailment in Ohio, including cleanup costs and a penalty</title>
      <description>The settlement with the Justice Department resolves a lawsuit over the railroad’s discharge of toxic substances following the fiery train derailment in Ohio on Feb. 3, 2023.

Under the agreement, Norfolk Southern will pay an estimated $235 million to cover the costs of the EPA’s efforts to clean up contaminated air, water and soil in and around where the train derailed and toxic fumes were later vented.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a27fb550-1919-11ef-ac3e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 15:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOAA warns this could be among the worst hurricane seasons in decades</title>
      <description>Record-warm ocean waters, fueled by human-caused climate change, are a key factor in the prediction. Hurricane season officially begins on June 1 and typically peaks in August and September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75564060-1911-11ef-bebc-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows disputed South Carolina voting map that critics say excludes Black voters</title>
      <description>At issue was South Carolina’s congressional district map used in 2022, which was created by the GOP-led state legislature and moved Black voters from one district to another. The justices had to decide whether it was permitted as a way to bolster the Republican majority or was an unconstitutional effort to divvy up voters by race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32814070-190f-11ef-8695-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 14:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Endless shrimp in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5aa1120-1908-11ef-8b7c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 13:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Long before the Key Bridge collapse, mariners sounded alarms that a ‘ship strike’ could be catastrophic</title>
      <description>Over the past two decades, as cargo ships grew ever larger, members of a Baltimore harbor safety committee repeatedly raised the possibility that an out-of-control vessel could imperil the Key Bridge, according to previously unreported records obtained by The Washington Post. The records show no indication that the warnings spurred new physical protections for the bridge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dfe6730-18fe-11ef-8b7c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 12:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian state recognition. Nikki Haley. Stage collapse. Bird flu. Fentanyl. Blackouts. Scarlett Johansson. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c57e420-18f3-11ef-a299-000a1ace3042</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI didn’t copy Scarlett Johansson’s voice for ChatGPT, records show</title>
      <description>On Monday, Johansson cast a pall over the release of improved AI voices for ChatGPT, alleging that OpenAI had copied her voice after she refused a request by CEO Sam Altman to license it. But an actress was hired to create the Sky voice months before Altman contacted Johansson, according to documents, recordings, casting directors and the actress’s agent.
The agent, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to assure the safety of her client, said the actress confirmed that neither Johansson nor the movie “Her” were ever mentioned by OpenAI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c849ec0-1892-11ef-bc67-0000a1acef43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 23:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. will soon take antitrust action against Ticketmaster parent Live Nation, according to people familiar with the matter</title>
      <description>Live Nation also operates concert venues and promotes events. Exactly what the federal government would seek in court isn't yet clear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58ce71a1-188b-11ef-b29e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 22:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After mounting a primary challenge against Donald Trump, Nikki Haley says she’ll vote for him</title>
      <description>In her first public appearance since suspending her campaign in early March, the former U.N. ambassador, when asked about which candidate she would prefer on foreign policy, said, “I will be voting for Trump.”
Haley, who did not endorse Trump when she dropped out of the race, went on to say that it was incumbent upon the former president to earn the support of the people who voted for her in the primaries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c521e511-1883-11ef-b8ed-000a1ace16dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 21:39:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans can't get anything done, so they're bullying D.C., Marc Fisher writes in his first Opinions column.</title>
      <description>Republicans in Congress have new ‘solutions’ for D.C. They’re absurd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76550ed0-1879-11ef-8a86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A severe thunderstorm watch is in effect for the D.C. area until 8 p.m. Damaging winds and hail are possible.</title>
      <description>Scattered storms are possible in the region through this evening, especially west and north of the District. A few could contain damaging winds and hail, in addition to heavy rain and lightning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8aa8caa1-1876-11ef-8a86-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 20:04:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Michigan farm worker tested positive for bird flu, the second human case in 2 months in the U.S. The worker has since recovered.</title>
      <description>The worker suffered mild symptoms from the highly pathogenic H5N1 virus, according to state officials. Human cases of bird flu are rare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8154aad0-1873-11ef-89f4-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 19:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. election is set for July 4, with a high probability of ousting the Conservative Party</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Rishi Sunak’s announcement of a summer date landed as a surprise, as some analysts thought he wouldn’t want to face voters before it was absolutely necessary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b026e630-1859-11ef-9109-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband hasn’t properly atoned for calling his spouse an ‘eight’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband hasn’t properly atoned for calling his spouse an ‘eight’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b7f6b1-1854-11ef-ae0f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:59:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live chat: How should a restaurant handle a ‘loud, rude and obnoxious’ group of diners? Our food critic is answering your questions.</title>
      <description>Live chat: How should a restaurant handle a ‘loud, rude and obnoxious’ group of diners? Our food critic is answering your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33892150-1850-11ef-b362-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s where D.C.’s Democratic council candidates stand on crime, education, the Commanders and more. The primary is on June 4.</title>
      <description>Voters will choose a nominee for D.C. Council Wards 4, 7, 8 and at-large in this deep-blue city, where the primary often determines the winner in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70fa2ec0-184c-11ef-9f48-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 15:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The anniversary of a landmark case in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">732d7560-183f-11ef-8361-0000a1ace165</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington-area residents want the Commanders to return to D.C., Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Schar School poll finds that area residents clearly prefer the Commanders’ next stadium be built in D.C. proper as opposed to Northern Virginia or suburban Maryland, where the stadium currently is. A 51 percent majority says the stadium should be built in D.C., while 17 percent say it belongs in Maryland and 15 percent say Virginia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a0d36a0-183e-11ef-8229-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 13:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fundraising email falsely says Biden was ‘locked &amp; loaded’ to ‘take me out’ in Mar-a-Lago search, misrepresenting FBI policy</title>
      <description>Trump’s baseless accusation — an extraordinary distortion of a standard FBI policy on the use of deadly force during such operations — came as the former president faces 88 criminal charges across four indictments, and added to a long history of false and incendiary claims against his political opponents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24eca090-1837-11ef-977e-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 12:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Primary results. Deadly tornadoes. Abortion pills. Flight turbulence. Matthew Perry. Graceland. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f5f8a01-182a-11ef-977e-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ireland, Spain and Norway recognize Palestinian state, with several other European countries expected to follow</title>
      <description>The symbolic diplomatic moves won’t have any immediate effect on the Israel-Gaza war but they put pressure on Israel to move toward a two-state solution, which its government has rejected. Israel has said recognition for a Palestinian state amounts to support for terrorism that jeopardizes peace.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b20b892-180e-11ef-b590-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 07:39:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kevin McCarthy protege wins special election to fill his California House seat, the AP projects</title>
      <description>California Assemblyman Vincent Fong (R) beat Tulare County Sheriff Mike Boudreaux (R) in the special election for California’s 20th District, the Associated Press reported. Fong was endorsed by both McCarthy and Donald Trump and will serve the remainder of McCarthy’s term. He is also a candidate for the full term in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17dc9460-17eb-11ef-97c4-0000a1acec74</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 03:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fulton County District Attorney Fani Willis, who brought Georgia criminal case against Trump, wins Democratic primary</title>
      <description>Willis has beat a Democratic challenger in the primary for district attorney in the Atlanta area, according to the Associated Press. In the general election, Willis is expected to face Courtney Kramer, a Republican lawyer who interned in the Trump White House and was involved in Trump’s efforts to reverse his 2020 loss in Georgia. It has been two months since an Atlanta-area judge ruled that Willis could continue prosecuting the case despite having a romantic relationship with the outside attorney she appointed to lead the investigation. The accusations have slowed the case down, making it unlikely it will get to trial before the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd700d00-17ca-11ef-a206-0000a1acec86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 23:35:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a place with a history of hate, an unlikely fight against GOP extremism — with a crucial test in tonight’s primary</title>
      <description>North Idaho has beaten the far right before. Now renegade Republicans are seeking to root it out of their own party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ef581-17ad-11ef-a95a-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dark new biopic starring Sebastian Stan as a young Trump is the talk of Cannes</title>
      <description>“The Apprentice” drew spots of laughter from the Cannes Film Festival audience. But by and large, it is a chilling origin story.

Former president Donald Trump’s campaign called the film “pure fiction which sensationalizes lies.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53dfb70-17a0-11ef-9aae-0000a1ace376</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11816c0-178b-11ef-b330-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe is funding the draconian practice of detaining migrants in North Africa and dumping them in the desert, investigation finds</title>
      <description>A year-long joint investigation by The Washington Post, Lighthouse Reports and a consortium of international media outlets shows how the European Union and individual European nations are supporting and financing aggressive operations to push tens of thousands of migrants to remote areas in Morocco, Mauritania and Tunisia each year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1f2640-1784-11ef-877c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will not testify in his N.Y. hush-money trial. The defense has rested, and jury deliberations will take place next week.</title>
      <description>Both sides have finished presenting evidence in Donald Trump’s trial over allegedly falsifying business records related to a payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels before the 2016 election. After the judge and the lawyers discuss jury instructions this afternoon, the trial will take a break until closing arguments, scheduled for next Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21a0da90-177f-11ef-8089-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A long-awaited film meets mixed reviews in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">295d87f1-1776-11ef-a553-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East. Trump’s trial. Campaign cash. Extreme weather. African migrants. Scarlett Johansson. Cockroaches. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47c4ef90-1761-11ef-915c-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson threatens legal action against OpenAI, claiming it copied her voice for ChatGPT</title>
      <description>The actress alleges OpenAI CEO Sam Altman tried to hire her, then copied her voice when she said no. The artificial intelligence start-up said it would pause ChatGPT’s new voice features after drawing criticism that it sounded like Johansson’s character in the 2013 movie “Her.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07d5870-16fe-11ef-9332-000a1ace5824</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy Scouts love this scenic Virginia river. Locals say they’re killing it.</title>
      <description>Three hours southwest of D.C., the Maury River suffers as sediment flows from a dam at a campground owned by a scouting organization based in Bethesda, Md. The situation has created an unusual standoff between local residents and an organization known for honor and stewardship but plagued in recent years by controversy and financial trouble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">884c91a0-16f6-11ef-adda-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDIC Chairman Martin Gruenberg announces he will resign once successor is found after reports claimed he led hostile workplace</title>
      <description>Lawmakers have been calling for the resignation of Gruenberg, chair of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, a banking regulatory agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">402a6940-16f3-11ef-9d42-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecution rests in Trump hush money trial after Michael Cohen’s testimony. The defense will call up to two witnesses.</title>
      <description>The prosecution rested and the defense said it would call no more than two witnesses in former president Donald Trump’s criminal trial for allegedly falsifying documents related to a hush money payment. Because of scheduling issues around Memorial Day weekend, the judge said the jury will begin deliberations next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dadaa380-16dd-11ef-937c-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls International Criminal Court’s arrest warrant request for Netanyahu and other Israeli officials ‘outrageous’</title>
      <description>President Biden suggested the top global court’s prosecutor had implied equivalence between Israel’s leaders, including Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, and Hamas’s leaders, whose arrest is also being sought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df7c720-16cc-11ef-b701-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivan Boesky dies at 87. The 1980s Wall Street titan was at the epicenter of an insider-trading scandal.</title>
      <description>Audacious and extravagant, Boesky helped inspire Hollywood’s fictional financial mogul Gordon Gekko and his greed-is-good mantra.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ba3cc80-16c8-11ef-8005-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it selfish or self-care to cancel plans, ‘etiquette be damned’?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it selfish or self-care to cancel plans, ‘etiquette be damned’?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a70cea3-16c4-11ef-9788-0000a1ace214</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship that destroyed Baltimore bridge is finally floated back to port, but its crew remains on board</title>
      <description>Nearly two months after knocking down the Francis Scott Key Bridge, the container ship Dali is back in port in Baltimore. Here’s what happens next to the ship and its crew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b25b8950-16c0-11ef-8c5a-000a1ace8dc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 15:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A crazy morning in Louisville in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffb7e80-16ad-11ef-846b-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange can appeal his extradition to the U.S., Britain’s high court rules</title>
      <description>The legal victory for Assange means he will not be whisked away by U.S. Marshals to the United States, where he faces charges of espionage for releasing reams of sensitive military and diplomatic files via WikiLeaks back in 2010.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8569d10-16a3-11ef-82e8-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Criminal Court prosecutor applying for arrest warrants for Israeli and Hamas officials, including Benjamin Netanyahu</title>
      <description>The prosecutor is applying to the court for warrants against Yahya Sinwar, a Hamas leader, and Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu, for war crimes and crimes against humanity in the Gaza Strip. A panel of judges will consider the warrants. The court previously issued an arrest warrant for Russian President Vladimir Putin over the invasion of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edbd2ca0-1699-11ef-88c5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 11:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran’s president. Trump trial. Biden speech. Sean Combs. Mosquitoes. PGA Championship. Ancient humans. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17e8d670-1698-11ef-a386-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi dead in helicopter crash, state media says</title>
      <description>Raisi was returning from Azerbaijan with Iran’s foreign minister and other officials Sunday when the helicopter went down in foggy conditions. He was elected in 2021, widely seen as the choice of Iran's supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, after a career in the judiciary. Raisi oversaw the crackdown on anti-government protests that erupted in late 2022 and Iran’s first-ever direct attack on Israel in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7fe02c2-1662-11ef-9e6d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xander Schauffele wins the PGA Championship for his first major title</title>
      <description>Schauffele, 30, entered Sunday's final round tied for the lead with Collin Morikawa. The world's third-ranked player previously had 12 top-10 finishes in majors, including ties for second at the 2019 Masters and the 2018 British Open.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b5eb010-1633-11ef-9f6d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 22:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1920 shootout that may belie the Texas Rangers’ romanticized image</title>
      <description>A century after three Tejano men were shot to death, the story that descendants tell of their killing contradicts official accounts. The families blame the storied Texas Rangers, while history has cast the men as tequila smugglers who shot first. Whose story counts as Texas history?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e135e700-1622-11ef-8e3e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3541f0-15fd-11ef-b7e9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An island in Maryland holds tantalizing clues about when and how humans first made their way into North America</title>
      <description>The story of the first Americans has long stoked public and scientific fascination, sometimes fueled by vicious disagreements. Parsons Island in the Chesapeake Bay could rewrite American prehistory, with artifacts suggesting people may have inhabited the area more than 20,000 years ago, a discovery that could push the timeline of arrival earlier than most experts thought possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdbf1720-15f8-11ef-9771-0000a1ace793</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 15:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue teams trying to reach helicopter carrying Iranian president after ‘hard landing,’ state media said</title>
      <description>The incident occurred as President Ebrahim Raisi was traveling back from Azerbaijan with Foreign Minister Hossein Amir-Abdollahian and other officials, state-run IRNA reported. Rescuers are reportedly struggling to reach the helicopter due to foggy conditions and mountainous terrain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2cb1542-15ef-11ef-9020-0000a1ace7f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 14:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
