<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:01:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Gaza after Netanyahu accuses Hamas of violating truce</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu accused Hamas of returning remains that belonged to Ofir Tzarfati, a hostage whose body Israel partially recovered in November 2023. An Israeli military official also said Hamas militants fired a rocket-propelled grenade and sniper rounds at troops in southern Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a31210-b42e-11f0-b068-0000a1ace097</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Category 5 Hurricane Melissa makes landfall in Jamaica, bringing catastrophic floods, storm surge and winds</title>
      <description>The outlook remains grim. Jamaican Prime Minister Andrew Holness said he had “been on my knees in prayer” and gave a dire prediction of what might come: roofs sheared from homes, roads inundated and infrastructure destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97755e50-b420-11f0-bf38-0000a1acec67</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:07:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic states sue to force SNAP payments during government shutdown</title>
      <description>A group of 23 attorneys general sued the Agriculture Department to force it to make billions of dollars in contingency funds available to help feed the most vulnerable individuals and families. SNAP, the Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program commonly known as food stamps, needs $9.2 billion to pay benefits in November. The Trump administration has said there’s no money for next month because of the shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82745e0-b41d-11f0-b622-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: The big women in their family seem to ‘embarrass’ son’s petite wife</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: The big women in their family seem to ‘embarrass’ son’s petite wife</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d019ab3-b417-11f0-bed4-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military kills 14 people in strikes on four alleged drug boats in eastern Pacific</title>
      <description>Fourteen alleged traffickers were killed in the strikes, Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth said on social media, bringing the total to nearly 60 killed in more than a dozen strikes since early September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f3a0d66-b410-11f0-b55e-0000a1ace28f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which wing in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8b19860-b406-11f0-8215-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas sues Tylenol maker, alleging painkiller can cause autism. The lawsuit echoed Trump’s warnings, despite a lack of evidence.</title>
      <description>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton filed a lawsuit against Tylenol maker Kenvue and its former parent company, Johnson &amp; Johnson, alleging the companies deceptively sold the painkiller. The suit, filed in a Texas state court, comes a month after President Donald Trump repeatedly warned pregnant women not to take Tylenol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3589080-b401-11f0-8858-0000a1ace570</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unforgettable night at the World Series lasted 18 incredible innings</title>
      <description>Monday night’s win for the Los Angeles Dodgers over the Toronto Blue Jays, was the second-longest World Series game ever played by time and tied for the longest by innings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9c16f0-b3fb-11f0-bed4-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:39:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa. Trump’s ballroom. Shutdown impacts. Stillbirth study. DEI battle. Grokipedia. MAGA dating scene. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38d17ec0-b3ed-11f0-b4a6-0000a1ace6b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawyers allege cover-up after federal agent shoots at man during D.C. traffic stop</title>
      <description>A D.C. police officer told a judge he was instructed by a superior not to document the shooting in a court record, the lawyers said, and all charges against the man have been dropped. The man’s attorneys say the case symbolizes the potentially fatal consequences of the local police department’s collaboration with federal agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b790cf40-b3a2-11f0-b7ad-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 02:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A meteorologist flew into Hurricane Melissa’s eye. Here’s what it was like.</title>
      <description>Entering the monster storm was humbling, mesmerizing and surprisingly poignant — equal parts scientifically stunning and horrifying from a humanitarian standpoint, writes Matthew Cappucci.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18ca0ae0-b382-11f0-ac2a-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How special counsel Jack Smith’s strongest case against Donald Trump collapsed</title>
      <description>Seeking to get the classified documents case to a jury before the 2024 election, Smith made a fateful decision that some in his office saw as a misstep. This story is adapted from the forthcoming book “Injustice: How Politics and Fear Vanquished America’s Justice Department,” which will publish Nov. 4.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4612fc40-b36a-11f0-8a55-0000a1ace80b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 19:22:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thousands of stillbirths occur without clear warning signs, even in seemingly healthy pregnancies, a sweeping study found</title>
      <description>A study led by researchers at Harvard and Mass General Brigham shows stark socioeconomic divides and thousands of unexplained losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e32ed4c0-b353-11f0-aa67-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend who offered cold comfort in grief is now grieving herself</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend who offered cold comfort in grief is now grieving herself</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cc45253-b34e-11f0-9650-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cancer rates among young adults are rising faster in the Corn Belt, without a clear explanation</title>
      <description>Leading states for corn production have a cancer rate 5 percent higher for young adults, according to the latest data from 2022. But research doesn’t yet offer a satisfying explanation for why rates have shot up this region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67bfc580-b342-11f0-9500-0000a1ace0c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:37:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A throwback to 1812 in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f3dbbf0-b33c-11f0-92eb-000a1ace0518</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-China trade. Trump resistance. Louvre heist. Hurricane. Cancer mystery. Electricity prices. Animal disguises. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e2d74e0-b324-11f0-9589-0000a1ace4f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Melissa, now a Category 5 storm, threatens Jamaica with worst-case scenario</title>
      <description>Melissa continued strengthening Sunday night into Monday as it approaches Jamaica, where it is set to deliver a devastating blow when it makes landfall late Monday into early Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a132060-b31f-11f0-b5a2-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 10:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The food writer emerged from her brush with cancel culture to build the shop of her dreams. We checked it out.</title>
      <description>First Bloom has homemade broth, a wall of pasta and Haribo gummies. You have to plan a Catskills road trip to get there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93d5ded0-b2bf-11f0-b2e5-000a1ace1fd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 small swaps to live with fewer toxic chemicals</title>
      <description>Avoiding hazardous chemicals can be a challenge. We asked environmental health experts what they do to keep themselves safe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6065bcb0-b2aa-11f0-a691-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 20:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a roadside attraction of colossal proportions broke a small Colorado town</title>
      <description>The Texas chain, known for its jaunty beaver mascot and sparkling bathrooms, wants to erect a 74,000-square-foot travel plaza. The proposal has already led to mudslinging on social media and texts, accusations of vandalism, litigation and the downfall of a mayor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53f946e0-b287-11f0-bdbd-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 16:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese and U.S. officials tentatively agree to avert 100% tariffs, a significant de-escalation of a volatile trade war</title>
      <description>The announcement came ahead of President Donald Trump’s Thursday meeting with Chinese leader Xi Jinping.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af3fcd70-b274-11f0-9556-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 14:04:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a84f5540-b273-11f0-a234-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:57:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louvre heist suspects arrested, and one of them was trying to leave France, Paris prosecutor says</title>
      <description>The arrests come a week after thieves broke into the Louvre museum and stole precious jewels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cac3b20-b257-11f0-a060-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 10:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump raises tariffs on Canada by 10% over Reagan ad</title>
      <description>The president had halted trade talks with Canada over a provincial government’s ad that has since been canceled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d571c60-b1ef-11f0-9f5a-0000a1ace49f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 22:09:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s a reason electricity prices are rising. And it’s not data centers.</title>
      <description>Americans have been looking aghast at rising electricity bills. A new study suggests the increase is more nuanced than simply the proliferation of AI and data centers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19644270-b1ea-11f0-af7c-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 21:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump’s ballroom will dwarf the White House</title>
      <description>Through an analysis of architectural renderings, photos and satellite imagery, The Post reconstructed an estimate of the overall footprint of the new East Wing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c050700-b1ad-11f0-a6a9-0000a1ace084</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:15:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17ce70c0-b1a9-11f0-9a6e-0000a1acec02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:47:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This 6-year research project found a surprisingly simple route to happiness</title>
      <description>A study out of Cornell suggests a practical way to keep ourselves on a meaningful path — a happiness hack for our chaotic times, writes columnist Dana Milbank.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d138420-b127-11f0-9fad-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 22:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon orders aircraft carrier to Latin America as Trump signals his intent to escalate campaign against alleged drug traffickers</title>
      <description>A spokesman said the dramatic increase in combat power aims not only to “disrupt narcotics trafficking” in the region but to “degrade and dismantle” the criminal groups that operate there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd4e9470-b104-11f0-b81c-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Is it possible to be a happy working mom?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Is it possible to be a happy working mom?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fa0fbc1-b0f8-11f0-8a52-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Average Obamacare premiums are set to rise 30 percent, documents show</title>
      <description>The price increases — affecting up to 17 million Americans who buy coverage on the federal marketplace — are by far the largest annual premium increases in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19e9f8a0-b0f7-11f0-967a-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 16:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is America’s best sports city? Nine compete for the crown.</title>
      <description>Grit, glamour and green energy define the nation’s top sports towns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1444f060-b0ef-11f0-a237-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Attorney General Letitia James pleads not guilty in mortgage case pushed by Trump</title>
      <description>Attorneys for James said they will seek to disqualify interim U.S. attorney Lindsey Halligan, the federal prosecutor in Virginia who has charged the president’s perceived foes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be2244e0-b0ed-11f0-855d-000a1acef75d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 15:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e8dd240-b0de-11f0-8323-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:34:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security checks will get a 2.8% COLA increase in 2026</title>
      <description>The annual cost-of-living adjustment is in line with overall inflation, but trails categories like energy and health care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0976a6f0-b0dc-11f0-8c5a-0000a1ace3cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown-delayed report showed hotter inflation in September</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed that inflation rose at a 3 percent pace, hotter than in August.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63c43ba0-b0d6-11f0-bc99-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S.-Canada trade. East Wing. Federal workers. NBA gambling. Storm Melissa. Happiness hack. Dinosaur killer. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9359f7a0-b0c8-11f0-9e45-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he’s canceling trade negotiations with Canada over anti-tariff ad</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Canada “fraudulently used” an ad that featured audio from a 1987 radio address by President Ronald Reagan criticizing tariffs. The president cited a statement from the Ronald Reagan Presidential Foundation and Institute that said the ad — aired last week by the government of Ontario — misrepresented Reagan’s address by using “selective audio and video.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">942cfcb0-b094-11f0-89d6-000a1ace3521</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 04:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you pass the new, more challenging U.S. citizenship test?</title>
      <description>The test changes come after the Trump administration signaled it will increase scrutiny on citizenship applications and threatened to revoke some Americans’ citizenship. The Washington Post set 10 questions to represent the 2025 civics test.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d479cbf0-b066-11f0-afa3-0000a1acef72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 23:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration will allow controversial road through Alaskan refuge</title>
      <description>The deal allows a road to cut through the Izembek National Wildlife Refuge, a pristine stretch of coastal wildlands. Interior Secretary Doug Burgum also announced the reopening of the Arctic National Wildlife Refuge to oil and gas development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d374060-b05e-11f0-a000-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 22:17:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White House annex has been completely demolished to make way for Trump’s $300 million ballroom</title>
      <description>The little that remained just after lunchtime included a small section of the East Colonnade, a corridor that previously connected the East Wing to the main White House. Also visible: dump trucks with sandy-colored debris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc8b4b50-b043-11f0-8359-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks bills to pay federal workers during shutdown as it stretches into a fourth week, with no end in sight</title>
      <description>Lawmakers acted mostly along partisan lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fdba480-b040-11f0-b181-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons founder of crypto exchange Binance, Changpeng Zhao, who pleaded guilty to enabling money laundering in 2023</title>
      <description>Zhao agreed to step down as chief executive of Binance as part of a plea deal. The company also agreed to pay a $4.3 billion fine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f454d5b0-b02e-11f0-b7ed-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He’d be a great dad. Is it wrong to marry him just for that?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He’d be a great dad. Is it wrong to marry him just for that?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0836a01-b029-11f0-9d2e-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support for Virginia Democratic attorney general nominee has tumbled since text message scandal, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Likely voters have not transferred much support to Jay Jones’s opponent — Republican incumbent Jason S. Miyares — and the race is a tie, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll. The scandal has not affected the contest for governor, where Democrat Abigail Spanberger holds a 12-point lead over Republican Winsome Earle-Sears.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eb145c0-b028-11f0-96d8-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA’s Portland Trail Blazers head coach and Miami Heat player arrested in sports gambling probe</title>
      <description>FBI agents reportedly arrested Trail Blazers coach Chauncey Billups, a Hall of Famer who played 17 seasons in the league, and the Heat’s Terry Rozier, a former first-round draft pick. Former NBA player Damon Jones was also taken into custody, according to a person familiar with the situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cf21cb0-b019-11f0-bbfd-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stealing jewels in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef7aa00-b014-11f0-8056-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Anglican Church archbishop accused of sexual misconduct, abuse of power</title>
      <description>An attempted kiss, cash payments and other allegations roil the Anglican Church in North America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89264f80-b010-11f0-a346-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s ballroom. Boat strikes. Shutdown. Nuclear submarines. Citizenship test. mRNA vaccines. Brain surgery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6415d8c0-afff-11f0-9899-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
