<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 05:03:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy's ‘DOGE’ vision broke down over deep philosophical differences</title>
      <description>Putting the new “Department of Government Efficiency” inside a White House digital office could give Musk sweeping insight into government operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c94d9370-d85c-11ef-95eb-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 01:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ichiro Suzuki, CC Sabathia, Billy Wagner headline five-player class of inductees to National Baseball Hall of Fame</title>
      <description>Ichiro, a trailblazing Japanese outfielder, narrowly missed becoming the second player unanimously selected by the Baseball Writers’ Association of America. Sabathia and Wagner will also be honored at the annual induction ceremony in Cooperstown, New York, on July 27. Dick Allen and Dave Parker were previously selected for induction by the Classic Baseball Era Committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ae137a1-d84f-11ef-875b-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and tech CEOs announce up to $500 billion in private investments to build new data centers for AI</title>
      <description>President Trump hosted the CEOs of OpenAI, Oracle and SoftBank at the White House to announce the new private-sector investments. Oracle and SoftBank's leaders said they decided to invest more into AI data centers after Trump's election win.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99712d20-d84c-11ef-96dd-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 23:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Files reveal Tulsi Gabbard staffers’ struggle to contain the fallout from her meetings with Syria’s Assad</title>
      <description>Gabbard’s 2017 trip to Syria, where she met as a member of Congress with authoritarian leader Bashar al-Assad, is expected to be a focus of questions from senators weighing her nomination to be director of national intelligence under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77a11de0-d847-11ef-9de1-0000a1aceb07</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 22:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration removes senior Justice Dept. officials from key positions, a sign the agency will be dramatically reshaped</title>
      <description>At least 15 experienced career staffers across several offices, including the national security and criminal divisions, were reassigned, in many cases to lesser roles, according to people familiar with the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the changes hadn’t been publicly announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53f7fb20-d83d-11ef-84a8-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 21:18:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Civil rights groups and 18 states sue to stop Trump’s executive order to end birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>The coalition of states is filing a lawsuit challenging President Donald Trump’s sweeping effort, which legal experts say runs counter to more than a century of legal precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a61ffc60-d81d-11ef-bd5d-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Daughter’s mixed marriage unlocks her aunt’s ‘offensive views’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Daughter’s mixed marriage unlocks her aunt’s ‘offensive views’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611673c2-d81c-11ef-8bc4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders are one win away from the Super Bowl. What’s on your mind ahead of Sunday’s game? Our reporters take your questions.</title>
      <description>Join Post Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier to discuss the upcoming NFC championship game between upstart Washington and the Philadelphia Eagles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b46b7d21-d819-11ef-8cf7-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How executive orders work — and how Trump’s could be overturned</title>
      <description>Donald Trump signed a flurry of executive orders hours after being sworn in as president on Monday. They include withdrawing the United States from the Paris agreement on climate change, ordering federal workers back to the office and cracking down on illegal immigration. But such orders have limitations and do not always last.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddbf1aa0-d810-11ef-8bc4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s second inaugural is memorable for its staggering inappropriateness, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>Donald Trump’s second inaugural speech will be remembered as worse than 59 others, including his first.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09b7b1b0-d80e-11ef-9c50-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military chief says he will resign over Oct. 7, 2023, attacks, citing ‘terrible failure’ to protect citizens</title>
      <description>Lt. Gen. Herzi Halevi announced Tuesday his plans to resign in March, in the highest-level departure of a military or security official over the Hamas-led attacks in 2023. His resignation coincides with the start of a fragile ceasefire in the Gaza Strip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0e33070-d809-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 15:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration ousts Coast Guard’s top admiral in first move on military leadership</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has removed the Coast Guard’s top admiral, according to a message to the service’s members, a first move in what could be several changes to military leadership under President Donald Trump. Adm. Linda Fagan was relieved of her duties by Benjamine Huffman, the acting secretary of homeland security. He did not provide a reason for the decision.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1504f881-d808-11ef-b7de-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:57:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A director is at the center of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7e6aa21-d805-11ef-a7a3-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 14:42:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Birthright citizenship, Jan. 6 pardons, federal workforce changes: Tracking the executive actions Trump took on Day 1</title>
      <description>Donald Trump has also long vowed to dismantle federal regulations, exact revenge on his political enemies, uproot the federal bureaucracy he has referred to as the “deep state” and eliminate what he sees as government waste.

There are limitations to what a president can legally do via executive action, and many of Trump’s orders are expected to be challenged in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de764cc0-d7fc-11ef-9c50-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 13:37:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hotel fire kills 66 people at popular Turkish ski resort</title>
      <description>The early morning blaze at the upscale Grand Kartal Hotel at the Kartalkaya resort in northern Turkey forced guests to jump from the building or to try to escape using sheets hung from windows, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72c4aa81-d7f7-11ef-b91d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jules Feiffer, cartoonist, playwright and screenwriter, dies at 95</title>
      <description>His Pulitzer-winning weekly strip ran in the Village Voice from 1956 to 2000 and was syndicated to more than 100 newspapers. Later comic strips such as Garry Trudeau’s “Doonesbury” are indebted to Mr. Feiffer’s brand of acerbic wit and literate satire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d028f510-d7f1-11ef-904b-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:18:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s inauguration. Jan. 6 pardons. Biden’s last day. Gaza ceasefire. Winter storm. Ozempic. College football. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f42c230-d7ef-11ef-a666-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio State beats Notre Dame in College Football Playoff national championship game, capping a dominant postseason run</title>
      <description>The Buckeyes, who overcame a baffling loss to rival Michigan in their regular season finale, stormed through the inaugural 12-team playoff to win their first national championship since the 2014 season.
Notre Dame was seeking its first national title since the 1988 season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f37c490-d7ad-11ef-9ff4-0000a1ace286</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 04:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive order to halt TikTok ban for 75 days, risking legal showdown</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump signed the order Monday aimed at halting the ban against TikTok so he can “pursue a resolution” outside of a complete prohibition, a legally dubious maneuver poised to test his power to stave off a measure he once championed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57135710-d79c-11ef-b586-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 02:06:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons virtually all Jan. 6 defendants, including Proud Boys leader Enrique Tarrio</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump pardoned virtually all of those convicted in the Jan. 6 riot and commuted the sentences of the remaining 14, while directing his attorney general to drop ongoing cases. That means that all those prosecuted by the Justice Department, from the plotters imprisoned for seditious conspiracy to trespassers to felons convicted of assaulting police officers, will soon be released from incarceration, if they are still in federal custody.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1f93060-d798-11ef-b91d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 01:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive actions, including ordering federal workers back to office and leaving climate pact. Follow live coverage.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump signed actions to revoke unspecified Biden policies, freeze federal regulations and hiring, return the federal workforce to full-time in-person work, direct agencies to address the cost of living, withdraw from the Paris climate treaty and order agencies to preserve records from prosecutions in the last administration that he claimed were political. He said the Jan. 6 pardons would come when he returned to the Oval Office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e70de0-d78f-11ef-a003-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Rubio is confirmed by Senate as Trump's secretary of State, becoming first Cabinet member to be seated</title>
      <description>Rubio, a long-serving Republican senator from Florida, is among Trump’s least controversial Cabinet picks and weathered little pushback from Democrats during his confirmation hearing last week. He inherits a host of diplomatic challenges and has pledged to advance the new administration's “America First” foreign policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f09e4a0-d78a-11ef-9d87-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 23:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth, Trump's nominee for defense secretary, clears key hurdle to Senate confirmation</title>
      <description>The nomination of Hegseth, a former Fox News personality whose selection to lead the Pentagon has been tainted by allegations of personal misconduct, was narrowly advanced by the Senate Armed Services Committee on Monday. Approval by the full Senate looks probable, though some Republicans have not said publicly how they intend to vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae243950-d780-11ef-a95e-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 22:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A subdued Trump painted another dark portrait of America, and 5 other takeaways from his inaugural address</title>
      <description>Donald Trump was inaugurated as president Monday for the second time in eight years. And again, we were all glued to his speech for clues about what lies ahead. Here’s what we learned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9eb2de90-d776-11ef-b586-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 21:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is poised to pardon nonviolent Jan. 6 defendants and commute sentences of others, people briefed say</title>
      <description>Declining a case-by-case review sought by some top advisers, the newly sworn-in president would grant some form of clemency to virtually everyone prosecuted by the Justice Department, according to multiple people familiar with the plan. While Donald Trump could change his mind before the orders are issued, such a blanket action would include cutting short the sentences for plotters imprisoned for seditious conspiracy and felons convicted of assaulting police officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ce1c80-d76a-11ef-9ff4-0000a1ace286</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 20:13:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrants waiting to cross the U.S. border with Mexico through CBP One are learning their appointments have been canceled</title>
      <description>Migrants who arrived at official border crossings Monday learned their CBP One appointments had been canceled moments after President Donald Trump was sworn into office. Many had waited months and immediately began to cry. The CBP One website posted a notice saying the program was no longer available. It was among the first and most visible ramifications of Trump’s new border policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb232a30-d75f-11ef-9639-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 18:54:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Graciousness is not in the cards’: Follow 10 columnists as they react live to Trump’s inauguration</title>
      <description>‘Graciousness is not in the cards’: 10 columnists on Trump’s inauguration</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07e8f951-d757-11ef-a53e-0000a1ace90b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is sworn in as the 47th president. He is now about to deliver his inaugural address. Watch live.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump was sworn in by Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr., officially becoming the 47th president of the United States. Trump is promising a flurry of actions on Day 1 on immigration, energy production, crime and other issues. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f232b660-d750-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Couple fights over father-in-law’s awkward behavior at parties</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Couple fights over father-in-law’s awkward behavior at parties</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23362040-d750-11ef-91b3-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 17:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cecile Richards dies of cancer at 67. The women’s rights activist was the former president of Planned Parenthood.</title>
      <description>In January, Richards shared publicly that she had been diagnosed with glioblastoma, an aggressive form of brain cancer. Richards, the daughter of former Texas governor Ann Richards (D), was a longtime advocate for women’s rights and served as president of Planned Parenthood from 2006 to 2018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef5f1310-d747-11ef-8170-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 16:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will attempt to end birthright citizenship with an executive order. Scholars say the action would be unconstitutional.</title>
      <description>The U.S. government will no longer recognize the citizenship of children born in the United States to immigrants who lack legal status, one of 10 immigration-related executive orders President-elect Donald Trump plans to sign Monday, an incoming administration official told reporters. The official did not provide details on how the administration planned to implement a change that scholars say would be patently illegal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddf2f590-d744-11ef-a539-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:40:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A famous statue is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>A famous statue is the topic of today’s On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">588075e0-d73f-11ef-a95e-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump will be sworn in for his second term, promising a flurry of action on Day 1. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The president-elect is set to be inaugurated in a ceremony moved inside the Capitol because of extreme cold. Before his swearing-in, he is attending a church service and plans to have tea with President Joe Biden at the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">947dc480-d73a-11ef-b586-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden issues preemptive pardons for Anthony Fauci, Jan. 6 committee members, retired general Mark Milley, others</title>
      <description>Hours before leaving office, President Joe Biden announced preemptive pardons for people he said had done nothing wrong but have been threatened with criminal prosecutions during the upcoming Trump administration. They include Fauci, the former top infectious-disease official; Milley, the former chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff; members and staff of the House select committee that investigated the Jan. 6, 2021 Capitol riot; and police officers who testified before the committee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2264f7f1-d72c-11ef-a764-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s inauguration. Executive orders. Gaza ceasefire. TikTok ban. Brutal cold. NFL playoffs. Ancient skull. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23bbe420-d726-11ef-a042-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 12:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump’s request, scores of career diplomats resign from State Department ahead of inauguration</title>
      <description>The forced departures, the prerogative of an incoming administration, indicate a desire to quickly shift the makeup of the department as President-elect Donald Trump seeks to upend the global diplomatic chessboard after four years of President Joe Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e2a6820-d6c8-11ef-b91d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:48:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s first executive orders could include border, oil drilling, DEI and federal worker policies, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Congressional Republican leaders were briefed on the broad contours of what Donald Trump is expected to sign shortly after he is sworn in as president, including sweeping changes related to the southern border, energy and the federal government workforce, two people familiar with the call said. Many of the executive orders are expected to be challenged in court. Follow our Inauguration Day coverage Monday for live updates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab268360-d6b4-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 22:28:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Burst of snow moving through D.C. area and roads will freeze tonight, ahead of Inauguration Day</title>
      <description>The snow will end by 6 or 7 p.m. in most areas, but falling temperatures mean wet and slushy roads will turn icy tonight. Bitter cold is expected Monday with wind chills in the single digits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25cd4d80-d6ae-11ef-ae05-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 21:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jill Biden reflects on Nancy Pelosi, Donald Trump and other relationships</title>
      <description>The first lady, after a half-century in public life, gives The Washington Post an exclusive exit interview — and looks to the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a9f05c0-d6a0-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok says it’s coming back online after Trump vowed to halt ban</title>
      <description>The social media platform thanked the president-elect for giving companies enough “clarity and assurance” to restore services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4de32061-d690-11ef-bf71-0000a1ace0dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 18:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31bf3bc0-d687-11ef-aede-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 17:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First Israeli hostages released from Gaza under ceasefire deal. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Three Israeli women kidnapped by Hamas-led fighters on Oct. 7, 2023, were transferred by the International Committee of the Red Cross to the Israeli military Sunday. Prior to their release, Hamas named them as Romi Gonen, 24, Emily Damari, 28, and Doron Steinbrecher, 31.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76f5efe0-d67d-11ef-b6d5-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump promises to delay TikTok ban in U.S. with Monday executive order</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump says the order on the first day of his term will delay enforcement of the ban so “we can make a deal to protect our national security” with partial U.S. ownership of the platform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70b9faa0-d67c-11ef-b6d5-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders won again? Who are these guys, columnist Barry Svrluga wonders. What is happening here?</title>
      <description>Washington made clear there is no team it can’t beat, no game it can’t win. This completely new football reality has become the talk of the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f25f0db1-d678-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 15:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c91cefa1-d671-11ef-bf71-0000a1ace0dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 14:29:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fighting halts in Gaza as ceasefire takes effect after nearly three-hour delay</title>
      <description>The ceasefire in Gaza has come into effect, Israel said, after Hamas provided the names of three hostages set to be released later Sunday. The halt in fighting was delayed after Hamas failed to provide the list of names on time, during which Israeli strikes killed at least 19 people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08fbd650-d64e-11ef-af2a-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 10:13:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Deadly Israeli strikes continue in Gaza as ceasefire is held up over hostage names</title>
      <description>An earlier alert to this story incorrectly stated that a ceasefire between Israel and Hamas took effect in Gaza. The ceasefire has been held up over Hamas’s list of hostage names.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7516a21-d63f-11ef-abea-0000a1acebd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadly Israeli strikes continue in Gaza as ceasefire is held up over hostage names</title>
      <description>The ceasefire was set to take effect at 8:30 a.m. local time. Hamas said it was late on delivering a list of hostages’ names for “technical reasons.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318d4b60-d63c-11ef-9db7-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ceasefire between Israel and Hamas takes effect in the Gaza Strip, pausing 15 months of war</title>
      <description>The truce began at 8:30 a.m. local time ahead of the first exchange of Israeli hostages for Palestinian prisoners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eb10680-d63b-11ef-a7ec-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders upset Lions to advance to the NFC championship</title>
      <description>Washington won a shocker, 45-31, on Saturday night in Detroit and will play next weekend with a Super Bowl berth on the line. This is the deepest Washington has progressed since 1992, when the franchise won its third Super Bowl. The turnaround led by rookie quarterback Jayden Daniels and first-year coach Dan Quinn is one of the biggest surprises in recent NFL history. In the NFC championship game, the Commanders will meet either the Philadelphia Eagles or Los Angeles Rams, who play Sunday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8707b680-d61d-11ef-a8a8-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 04:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
