<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How a hacker uncovered the data behind Tesla’s $243 million wrongful death verdict</title>
      <description>The carmaker long said it didn’t have an electric vehicle’s stored digital account of its fatal 2019 crash involving Autopilot. The way that data finally was discovered is believed to have played into a Florida jury’s recent landmark finding that Tesla was partially liable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3015680-84e0-11f0-8d73-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8519af91-84dc-11f0-98f2-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump revokes Kamala Harris’s Secret Service detail, which had been extended by Biden</title>
      <description>The president’s decision comes as his 2024 Democratic opponent prepares to travel nationwide for a book tour. Federal law gives vice presidents six months of Secret Service protection after they leave office, though President Joe Biden had lengthened her detail into 2026 before he left the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a772fa0-84d9-11f0-823d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC revolt. Minneapolis victims. Newsom vs. Trump. Tesla. Ultra-processed foods. Weekend forecast. Holiday ranking. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4eaf6040-84c7-11f0-9414-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. has an ‘impostor nurse’ problem, and it’s grown since the pandemic</title>
      <description>Authorities in numerous states have reported people falsely claiming to be licensed nurses or working in positions that require a nursing license without valid credentials. Staffing shortages, underfunding and a lack of oversight have exacerbated the problem, one expert said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50411150-845a-11f0-9a06-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House picks top RFK Jr. deputy to be acting CDC director</title>
      <description>The selection of Jim O'Neill reflects Robert F. Kennedy Jr.'s influence as he seeks to remake federal vaccine policy. It comes a day after the White House fired Susan Monarez, the Senate-confirmed director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, which prompted a series of resignations of other top CDC officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a8c5c60-8451-11f0-823d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-case killer gets 22 years in prison for 2001 murder of his ex-girlfriend’s mother in Chevy Chase, Maryland</title>
      <description>Eugene Gligor admitted he murdered Leslie Preer but claimed he doesn’t remember how it happened. And another element remains unknown to authorities: his motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75e0e8e0-8441-11f0-9b40-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil at CDC as three agency leaders condemn RFK Jr., resign over director’s ouster; GOP senator urges vaccine meeting delay</title>
      <description>As the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reeled from the ousting of its director, three senior leaders who resigned in protest told The Washington Post they were asked to participate in an unscientific vaccine recommendation process that they believe could harm the health of Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece90ba0-843e-11f0-bd4a-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Kari Lake from firing the director of Voice of America</title>
      <description>Judge Royce Lamberth ruled that only a majority vote from the Senate-confirmed board of the broadcaster can fire its director, Michael Abramowitz, dealing a blow to the Trump administration’s effort to dismantle the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cee3be0-843d-11f0-8494-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Conversational calisthenics with mother-in-law who is never direct</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Conversational calisthenics with mother-in-law who is never direct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b543ce0-8428-11f0-ba0c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed governor Lisa Cook sues Trump to block effort to remove her, in a case that could decide central bank independence</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has accused Cook of making false statements on mortgage applications. Cook has yet to respond substantively to the allegations, which have yet to be proved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8a60760-8415-11f0-8a59-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Sticking our necks out’ for these birds in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c32f3a70-8414-11f0-8a28-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jim Irsay, owner of NFL’s Colts, suffered multiple overdoses before he died in May, as a doctor provided opioids and ketamine</title>
      <description>Irsay spent the last two years of his life in the throes of a relapse that he and Indianapolis Colts executives repeatedly hid from the public, a Washington Post investigation found. This relapse, and his death, came as he was under the care of a “luxury” recovery doctor prescribing Irsay opioids and ketamine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64b7e620-8402-11f0-80e8-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis shooting. Fired CDC director. Loyalty purge. ICE plans. Meta AI. College football. Life’s origins. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24940e60-83fe-11f0-91ba-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian strikes pummel Kyiv, killing at least 12 and damaging E.U. building in fiercest attack since Trump-Putin summit</title>
      <description>The Russian weaponry included drones and ballistic and cruise missiles and were the fiercest attack on Ukraine’s capital since President Donald Trump and President Vladimir Putin’s summit in Alaska failed to produce a ceasefire. Trump has threatened “economic war” on Russia if it doesn’t move toward a negotiated end to the conflict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2efc6380-83e4-11f0-a8f8-0000a1ace68b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:54:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC director refuses to resign, as her lawyers accuse RFK Jr. of ‘putting millions of American lives at risk’</title>
      <description>Hours after the Department of Health and Human Services said Susan Monarez is no longer the CDC director, her lawyers said she did not resign and had not been fired. In a fiery statement, the lawyers accused HHS Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and his department of “weaponizing public health for political gain.” Tumult at the public health agency grew as three senior leaders announced their resignations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78c01770-83a6-11f0-9477-0000a1ace9ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration wants to use military base near Chicago as launchpad for potential ICE operations, officials say</title>
      <description>Officials at Naval Station Great Lakes acknowledged having received a request from the Department of Homeland Security that seeks “limited support” for Immigration and Customs Enforcement. The discussion comes as the White House contemplates deploying thousands of U.S. troops to Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1a99dc2-839e-11f0-a313-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Gabbard revoked security clearance of top CIA Russia expert days after Alaska summit with Putin</title>
      <description>The CIA officer was due to take up a prestigious assignment in Europe approved by CIA Director John Ratcliffe. Instead, she was accused of betraying her oath to the Constitution and abusing public trust in a broad, public purge of 37 current and former officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e664dc50-8399-11f0-8e14-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 23:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC Director Susan Monarez is being ousted weeks after confirmation to lead health agency, multiple officials say</title>
      <description>The federal scientist was President Donald Trump’s second choice to lead the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention after he pulled the nomination of former congressman Dave Weldon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">474da270-8383-11f0-96a9-0000a1acef38</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI identifies Minneapolis Catholic school shooter, says it is investigating attack as a hate crime and domestic terrorism</title>
      <description>Two children were killed and more than a dozen people were injured when the shooter opened fire through the windows of a church while children from the adjacent Annunciation Catholic School were attending Mass to mark their first week of school.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">821bb550-837d-11f0-892d-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA limits approval for new coronavirus vaccines to those considered high risk</title>
      <description>Trump administration officials have criticized the previous public health approach to broadly recommend annual coronavirus vaccines. The new approach limits approvals to those ages 65 and older or those with a medical condition that elevates their risk of severe disease. It's unclear if others will be able to access shots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb8fb771-836c-11f0-8dd5-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to bar states and nonprofits, such as Red Cross, from helping undocumented immigrants after disasters</title>
      <description>The new Homeland Security requirements for receiving federal funds have sparked concern among organizations that provide relief in the aftermath of disasters. The rules also say that states and volunteer organizations must comply with immigration officials and enforcement operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57c5fad0-836a-11f0-a3ab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis gunman fired on students at worship service, killing 2 children, injuring 17 people before shooting self, officials say</title>
      <description>The shooter, a man in his early 20s with three weapons, is dead from an apparent self-inflicted gunshot wound, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7158cef0-8360-11f0-886f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple children injured in shooting at Minneapolis Catholic school, hospital says; police say shooter is no longer a threat</title>
      <description>Family members of students at Annunciation Catholic School rushed to the scene, which police had cordoned off with vehicles and yellow tape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bbfd491-8359-11f0-8c8c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury declines to indict D.C. man arrested for throwing a sandwich at federal law enforcement</title>
      <description>The failure by federal prosecutors to secure an indictment Tuesday is the latest example of President Donald Trump’s surge of policing on the streets of D.C. meeting resistance in the city’s federal courthouse. This month, Sean Charles Dunn, a Justice Department employee, was charged with “assaulting, resisting, or impeding certain officers and employees of the United States.” Prosecutors could try again to secure a grand jury indictment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">316bbb70-8358-11f0-a121-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A draw at the Kennedy Center in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6690960-8349-11f0-a774-0000a1ace413</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. judges and grand jurors push back on Trump policing surge</title>
      <description>A federal magistrate judge said one arrest in D.C. was preceded by the “most illegal search I’ve seen in my life.” In another case, a grand jury refused three times to issue an indictment against a woman accused of assaulting a federal officer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adf9a800-8344-11f0-b629-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Transportation Department plans to take over D.C.’s Union Station</title>
      <description>It’s not clear how dramatic the change will be for the transit hub, which connects regional trains and buses to the Metro system. But it is another example of the White House exerting power over the District as National Guard soldiers and federal law enforcement officers continue to patrol the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d60060-833b-11f0-b55e-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death penalty. FEMA letter. Federal Reserve. School ‘swattings.’ AI test. Cracker Barrel. Taylor Swift’s ring. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7151c0-8334-11f0-bc98-0000a1ace758</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration places several FEMA employees on leave after they signed a letter criticizing the agency’s leadership</title>
      <description>Federal Emergency Management Agency officials informed some staffers that they were no longer on active duty after about 180 current and former employees sent a letter Monday arguing current leaders’ inexperience and approach could result in a disaster on the level of Hurricane Katrina, according to documents reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe84b630-82e4-11f0-8d5c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s latest attempt to erode the Fed’s independence is dangerous, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>Frustration with the central bank is understandable, but trying to fire Lisa Cook is not the answer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d60577f0-82a6-11f0-804a-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce announce their engagement on Instagram</title>
      <description>The pop star and Kansas City Chiefs tight end have dated since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce072b80-82a0-11f0-9baa-0000a1ace4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Nieces prefer getting cash gifts and not sending thank-you notes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Nieces prefer getting cash gifts and not sending thank-you notes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ba99810-8296-11f0-ad75-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge dismisses Justice Department lawsuit against all 15 of Maryland’s judges over handling of deportations</title>
      <description>Judge Thomas T. Cullen ruled that the Maryland bench was within its rights to pause deportations for two business days in cases where a habeas corpus petition was filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1003c770-8290-11f0-a759-0000a1acef4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A controversial redesign in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeed4fc0-8280-11f0-9775-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The six factions of Trumpworld: The president melds a contentious coalition</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s coalition is built for internal conflict — held together by fealty to him but riven by differences on immigration, tariffs, abortion and other policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b78c70d0-827e-11f0-804a-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve. Flag burning. Epstein files. Israeli attack. Screwworm. World map. Teacherless school. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8dfff40-826b-11f0-b551-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia accuses Iran of directing antisemitic attacks, expels its ambassador</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said Australia’s security agency determined Tehran was behind at least two attacks on Jewish institutions in Sydney and Melbourne.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8451de71-8239-11f0-8b53-0000a1ace575</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to fire Fed governor Lisa Cook over allegations of mortgage fraud, saying there’s ‘sufficient cause’ for removal</title>
      <description>The president cited his authority to fire governors for cause in a letter posted to Truth Social. The move could lead to a major test of the Federal Reserve’s independence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ae4e260-8216-11f0-af9e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Lloyd Wright’s iconic Fallingwater is leaking. See inside the $7 million effort to save it.</title>
      <description>For the past two years, staff at Wright’s terraced masterpiece in the Pennsylvania woods have found themselves in the middle of a home improvement project on steroids. And they’re doing it all while hewing to strict historic preservation standards and managing the expectations of visitors from around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9fd7c70-81fe-11f0-addc-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House committee subpoenas Epstein estate, requesting ‘birthday book’ allegedly prepared by Maxwell and any ‘client list’</title>
      <description>House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer (R-Kentucky) demanded documents from Jeffrey Epstein’s estate that might shed light on the federal sex-trafficking investigation into the financier. The subpoena, which demands documents by Sept. 8, asks for any book gifted by Ghislaine Maxwell to Epstein for his 50th birthday and anything that could be construed as a “client list” and Epstein’s “Black Book” of contacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8ac61d0-81f2-11f0-a46c-000a1acecc1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diamond baron Maurice Tempelsman dies at 95. He became a major Democratic donor and drew attention as Jackie Onassis’s companion.</title>
      <description>Urbane and intensely private, Tempelsman was as comfortable in the palaces of African autocrats as he was visiting the White House or working back channels with U.S. diplomats. He rose to became the largest player in the U.S. diamond market and gained additional notice for his strolls in Central Park with former first lady Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis, his partner from the early 1980s until her death in 1994.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32d804b1-81ef-11f0-9dc3-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s xAI sues Apple and OpenAI, alleging they colluded to favor ChatGPT in the App Store over his chatbot Grok</title>
      <description>The suit takes aim at a deal Apple struck to use OpenAI’s artificial intelligence software on iPhones and other devices after struggling to compete with its own AI features. Musk’s company seeks billions of dollars in damages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e51f9b0-81e9-11f0-a64b-000a1ace3d25</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily bars Kilmar Abrego García’s deportation to Uganda</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Paula Xinis issued the order from the bench Monday, hours after Homeland Security officials detained Abrego during a required check-in at the U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement field office in Baltimore. Xinis said she wants to hear evidence to ensure that the Trump administration will give him an opportunity to contest his deportation to Uganda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbe0ebd0-81e5-11f0-9a35-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family wonders how to ask childless uncle whether he has a will</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family wonders how to ask childless uncle whether he has a will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ffa111-81d5-11f0-b9db-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star wide receiver Terry McLaurin and Commanders agree on three-year contract extension</title>
      <description>McLaurin’s extension will pay him $96 million with the chance to escalate, a person familiar with the deal said. The 29-year-old has not practiced all summer as he sought a new deal in line with the league's top receivers. This puts him as the sixth-highest paid receiver in the NFL by average annual salary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29337690-81ce-11f0-9f51-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-led House committee is investigating allegations that D.C. police faked lower crime rate data, echoing Justice Department probe</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee is investigating whether D.C. police manipulated data at the direction of department leadership, according to records reviewed by The Washington Post. The inquiry comes on the heels of a Justice Department probe into similar matters and as D.C. officials continue to cite local crime statistics to protest President Donald Trump’s takeover of city law enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a1ed2e0-81cc-11f0-bf9f-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive orders cracking down on cashless bail and flag burning</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump seeks to force Washington, D.C., to abandon its no-cash-bail law and pressure states with similar policies. Another order aims to overturn a Supreme Court decision that said the First Amendment protects flag burning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c40a38b0-81c5-11f0-9d4c-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big launch for this network in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30d9efc0-81b8-11f0-abc4-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In public letter, FEMA staff warn Trump officials’ actions risk Katrina-level disaster</title>
      <description>About 150 Federal Emergency Management Agency employees sent a letter Monday to members of Congress and other officials, arguing that the agency’s direction and current leaders’ inexperience harm the agency’s mission and could result in a disaster on the level of Hurricane Katrina. The letter, on which more than two dozen FEMA staff signed their full names, is the latest example of federal employees speaking out against the Trump administration’s actions and policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c350b1e0-81b3-11f0-bd6e-0000a1ace117</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
