<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Six presumed dead after Baltimore bridge collapse, Coast Guard officials say</title>
      <description>Officials are shifting from a rescue operation to a recovery effort, the Coast Guard said in a news conference. At least eight people from a construction crew had fallen into the water while working on the bridge, officials said earlier Tuesday, after a ship struck the bridge. Two of those people had been rescued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cbe1550-ebc9-11ee-ba58-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 23:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBC reverses its decision to hire former RNC chair Ronna McDaniel as a contributor, after on-air backlash from network stars</title>
      <description>Political analyst Chuck Todd and MSNBC hosts Rachel Maddow and Joe Scarborough were among those who lambasted the hiring of the former Republican National Committee chair, citing her promotion of Donald Trump’s false election-fraud claims and media-bashing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">301171e0-ebbd-11ee-9083-0000a1aceb81</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 22:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qatari royal invested about $50 million in conservative network Newsmax amid Middle East tensions during the Trump administration</title>
      <description>A member of the Qatari royal family made a substantial investment in the pro-Trump media outlet in 2019 and 2020, according to documents and representatives for Newsmax and the royal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81c7100-ebb3-11ee-b379-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 21:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. picks tech lawyer Nicole Shanahan as his running mate for his longshot independent White House bid</title>
      <description>Kennedy announced Shanahan as his vice-presidential pick on Tuesday, a move that aims to provide more ballot access to his campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">304729e0-eba7-11ee-ba58-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 19:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump placed under gag order that bars him from commenting on witnesses, prosecutors and jurors in N.Y. hush money case</title>
      <description>The judge overseeing Donald Trump’s April 15 trial in Manhattan issued a limited gag order barring the former president from discussing witnesses, prosecutors, jurors or prospective jurors, or members of the judge’s staff and their families.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d3dc540-eba5-11ee-aa2b-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 19:17:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife wants to cut off contact with ‘negative’ sister-in-law</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife wants to cut off contact with ‘negative’ sister-in-law</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c9ef2d0-eb8e-11ee-bf00-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 16:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems unlikely to restrict access to the widely used abortion pill mifepristone</title>
      <description>Less than two years after the Supreme Court overturned the right to an abortion guaranteed by Roe v. Wade, a majority of justices seemed skeptical that the antiabortion doctors challenging access to the medication used in more than 60 percent of U.S. abortions had standing to sue. The court will rule by late June or early July on whether to continue to allow mifepristone to be sent by mail, prescribed without an in-person medical visit and used up to 10 weeks into pregnancy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9df88b0-eb89-11ee-b7f5-0000a1ace0d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Attorney General Ken Paxton reaches deal to avoid trial on state felony securities fraud charges</title>
      <description>Paxton was charged nearly a decade ago for allegedly defrauding investors at a Dallas-area tech company by not disclosing that he was paid by the company to recruit them. Under the agreement reached in Harris County district court, Paxton will avoid jail time but is required to make restitution and complete community service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05f32cd1-eb83-11ee-9a67-000a1ace912b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 15:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freighter lost power just before it struck Baltimore’s Key Bridge, and 6 workers fixing pot holes are still missing, officials say</title>
      <description>The bridge collapse sent at least eight people into the water, all of whom were part of the construction crew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c30f7c53-eb7f-11ee-94ad-0000a1ace913</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:47:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court is hearing arguments in an abortion pill case that could limit access for millions. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Less than two years after the Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade, the issue of reproductive rights is returning to the high court today. The Biden administration and the manufacturer of mifepristone are seeking to reverse a lower-court ruling that would make it more difficult to obtain the medication. Join Washington Post reporters for live coverage and analysis of the oral arguments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e2d4070-eb7a-11ee-a61c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Two layers of schmear’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff38f2c2-eb74-11ee-942c-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore bridge collapse. Trump rulings. Abortion rights. U.S.-Israel rift. Sean Combs. Shohei Ohtani. Air taxis. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">035c4330-eb60-11ee-9d02-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London court asks for new U.S. assurances that Julian Assange’s rights will be protected before deciding on his final appeal bid</title>
      <description>The High Court of Justice stated that if the satisfactory assurances aren’t received in three weeks, Assange can move forward with an appeal in U.K. courts. Among the assurances the court asked for is that he receive the same First Amendment protections as a U.S. citizen and there will be no death penalty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c8c1990-eb5f-11ee-92aa-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 10:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire officials say they are searching for up to 20 people in the water after Baltimore’s Francis Scott Key Bridge collapsed</title>
      <description>Strong winds and frigid temperatures at the scene make conditions difficult for rescuers, the Baltimore fire department’s director of communications told The Post. The bridge collapsed after a Singapore-flagged vessel, the 948-foot Dali, crashed into the bridge, a Coast Guard spokesman said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ee37450-eb56-11ee-9dd7-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 09:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore’s Francis Scott Key Bridge collapses into the river after being struck by cargo ship</title>
      <description>It was not clear how many people were on the bridge when it fell into the water. A Singapore-flagged vessel, the 948-foot Dali, crashed into the bridge, said Petty Officer 1st Class Matthew West, a Coast Guard spokesman, in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baf08620-eb45-11ee-95d2-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 07:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs’s homes raided by Homeland Security as he faces several lawsuits over allegations of abuse, sex trafficking</title>
      <description>R&amp;B singer Cassie, Combs’s former girlfriend, filed a blockbuster lawsuit against Combs in November. The lawsuit alleged that Cassie suffered a “cycle of abuse, violence, and sex trafficking” at the hands of the famed producer. The lawsuit was soon followed by others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb24dca0-eaf6-11ee-85eb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:27:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani addresses sports betting scandal involving former interpreter, saying he’s ‘saddened and shocked’</title>
      <description>The Los Angeles Dodgers star spoke publicly about the sports betting scandal involving his former interpreter for the first time. The Dodgers fired Ippei Mizuhara, Ohtani’s longtime friend and interpreter, last week amid allegations that Mizuhara stole millions from Ohtani to cover gambling debts.

A previous alert pointed to live coverage of his press conference. The stream experienced technical difficulties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6efdca30-eaf4-11ee-85c1-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 22:10:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dodgers star Shohei Ohtani makes his first comments on a sports betting scandal involving his former interpreter. Watch live.</title>
      <description>Ohtani, the Los Angeles Dodgers superstar whose interpreter was fired last week amid allegations of gambling and theft, is expected to address the matter in a prepared statement. Ohtani didn’t personally comment on the scandal as it unfolded last week, though his representatives claimed he had been the victim of a “massive theft.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">039505e0-eaf1-11ee-adbb-0000a1ace452</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 21:45:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In post-Roe America, the number of ‘self-managed’ abortions rose sharply, report finds</title>
      <description>Researchers attribute the spike, in part, to volunteer-led networks distributing abortion pills in states with bans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2967d350-eae3-11ee-b534-0000a1ace18f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 20:06:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marc Thiessen passed up the chance to see one of the greatest voices of the 20th century. He won't make that mistake again.</title>
      <description>See your music heroes before it’s too late</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a3e42e0-eacc-11ee-a1d6-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 17:21:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial to start April 15, judge says, rejecting defense motion to sanction prosecutors</title>
      <description>Lawyers for former president Donald Trump had asked to delay his New York criminal trial at least until June and to sanction prosecutors over the last-minute revelation of potential evidence about Michael Cohen, Trump's former lawyer and fixer and a key witness. Trump is accused of falsifying business records to cover up his reimbursement to Cohen of a hush money payment during the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5d14201-eac2-11ee-bf62-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dad encourages their young son’s sore-winner behavior</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dad encourages their young son’s sore-winner behavior</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5590160-eac0-11ee-bad0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli government cancels planned diplomatic visit to U.S. as tensions flare over U.N. vote demanding Gaza cease-fire</title>
      <description>The Israeli delegation had been set to include Minister of Strategic Affairs Ron Dermer and National Security Adviser Tzachi Hanegbi. The cancellation comes after the United States abstained from voting on a U.N. Security Council resolution calling for a Gaza cease-fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ba7ed40-eabf-11ee-9aa3-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:51:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wins request to reduce $464 million bond for massive civil fraud judgment. He now has 10 days to post $175 million.</title>
      <description>A panel of New York appellate judges came to Donald Trump’s aid Monday, ruling that he must post a $175 million bond within 10 days to stop Attorney General Letitia James from beginning to take his assets while he appeals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b917f40-eabd-11ee-a9a1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 15:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N. Security Council passes its first resolution calling for a Gaza cease-fire after four failed attempts. The U.S. abstained.</title>
      <description>The resolution, backed by 14 nations including Russia and China, demands an immediate cease-fire during the month of Ramadan and the release of all hostages. Four previous cease-fire resolutions had failed, including one proposed by the United States on Friday. The American abstention is likely to further strain U.S. relations with Israel amid sharp disagreements over Israel’s planned military offensive in Rafah.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b0dff20-eab6-11ee-9b8f-000a1aced9dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 14:45:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Jamie Raskin (D-Md.) endorses Prince George’s County Executive Angela Alsobrooks in state’s Democratic primary for U.S. Senate</title>
      <description>Raskin, the ranking Democrat on the House Oversight Committee, said he would help any Democrat who wins the primary and faces the likely GOP nominee — former governor Larry Hogan — in a closely watched Senate race that could determine which party controls the chamber.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55ec25e0-eaaf-11ee-9793-0000a1ace31c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A milestone transplant in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efb72b10-eaab-11ee-8eef-000a1acec616</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 13:31:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing’s CEO and two other top executives to leave the aerospace giant amid safety scandal</title>
      <description>Chief executive Dave Calhoun will depart at the end of 2024, according to an announcement from the company. The aerospace giant’s chairman and the head of its commercial airlines division are also leaving as the company faces heightened scrutiny over a host quality control issues that came to light after a piece of an Alaska Airlines jet fell off midflight in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c560e870-eaa5-11ee-90f6-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 12:46:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moscow attack. Trump deadline. Averted shutdown. Princess Catherine. Measles. March Madness. Adultery law. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6270720-ea96-11ee-9b30-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asked if Americans were better off during his last year in office. In many ways, the answer is no.</title>
      <description>A look back at the third week of March 2020 reveals a nation that was plunging into a pandemic and a leader exhibiting the erratic characteristics that his supporters love and his detractors revile. But some have warmed in their views of Donald Trump’s presidency overall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e73fa250-ea29-11ee-b2ac-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 22:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies are vying to bring back supersonic air travel. Here’s what to know about their efforts — and the likelihood of success.</title>
      <description>There hasn’t been a commercial supersonic passenger jet since the Concorde stopped flying in 2003. Since then, supersonic jets have been used primarily by the military. Now NASA and a growing number of private companies are promising to bring back a form of modern supersonic travel that will be quieter, greener and more affordable than in the past. But there are questions about whether they can make good on their claims, given the economics of air travel and growing concerns about the impact of commercial aviation on the environment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">575c8ef0-ea24-11ee-a343-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 21:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tammy Murphy, wife of New Jersey governor, drops out of state’s Democratic race for U.S. Senate</title>
      <description>Murphy’s move leaves surging Rep. Andy Kim (D-N.J.) as the overwhelming favorite in the Democratic primary to replace Sen. Bob Menendez (D-N.J.), upending the state’s party machine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5bd9390-ea1f-11ee-9739-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 20:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘Hail Mary’ plan sought to pair the Wizards and Caps arena with a Fairfax casino. Youngkin and Leonsis rejected it.</title>
      <description>Three Virginia political and business figures have pitched the plan as backers of the original deal mount an 11th-hour effort to rescue the project, which has faced serious setbacks in the General Assembly. But Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) and the teams’ owner, Ted Leonsis, have flatly rejected the idea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6d68070-ea00-11ee-ae0e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 17:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe2c4760-e9f8-11ee-a9bc-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 16:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One cherry tree’s rush to bloom, day by day, as climate change propels earlier peaks</title>
      <description>Watch a cherry tree’s buds unfold over 10 days, and find out how climate change is pushing D.C.’s famous trees to hit peak earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7985590-e9f4-11ee-a8a9-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 15:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Figure skating wants ice princesses. Amber Glenn said, ‘Screw it.’</title>
      <description>Glenn, the current U.S. female figure skating champion, felt trapped in a life of unspoken expectations, seeking the approval of coaches and judges. So she stopped attempting to make herself the idealized version of a figure skater and started telling people about her depression, eating disorder and ADHD. She also came out as bisexual and pansexual.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e015b750-e9eb-11ee-9feb-0000a1acefdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 14:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dac86170-e9e2-11ee-be5f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 13:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We pitted dairy and plant milk against each other in the ultimate test. This is how they stack up.</title>
      <description>Dairy milk is popular, but more people are embracing plant-based milks. Which one is best for you? Pick your team and see how the competition plays out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd49af90-e95c-11ee-9f8a-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Angelos dies at 94. The Baltimore lawyer was best known as the combative owner of MLB's Orioles.</title>
      <description>Peter G. Angelos won hundreds of millions of dollars for workers injured by exposure to asbestos, then became wider known to the public as the chief owner of the Baltimore Orioles for three decades. The Orioles said Angelos had been “ill for several years” in a statement announcing his death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62274f70-e946-11ee-93c3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a bankrupt bettor became the bookie at the center of the scandal surrounding Dodgers star Shohei Ohtani</title>
      <description>The Post used interviews and previously unreported law enforcement and court records to fill out the backstory of Mathew Bowyer, a gambler turned bookie who became intertwined with baseball’s biggest star, rocking the sports world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25ab23f0-e937-11ee-abe5-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They obsessed over Catherine, Princess of Wales. Now they’re hit with a sobering truth.</title>
      <description>People who mocked and speculated about Catherine during her public absence have deep regrets after learning she has cancer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ecb9600-e926-11ee-87cd-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 15:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38c28370-e919-11ee-ad07-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll from Moscow concert attack rises to at least 115 as more bodies are found, Russian authorities say</title>
      <description>Russian officials say they expect the death toll to rise further, given the number of seriously injured. The militant group ISIS has claimed responsibility for the raid, which followed U.S. government warnings this month about a “planned terrorist attack” in the Russian capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d31a08a0-e8fe-11ee-83ce-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:19:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes $1.2 trillion spending bill slightly past deadline, averting shutdown despite brief expiration of funding</title>
      <description>The House passed the legislation Friday morning. The Senate stalled over disagreements about GOP amendments before finally reaching a late-night breakthrough. The White House said President Biden would sign it into law on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65782ac0-e8db-11ee-8537-0000a1ace299</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB launches formal investigation into betting scandal involving Los Angeles Dodgers superstar Shohei Ohtani</title>
      <description>Major League Baseball said in a statement that its Department of Investigations “began their formal process investigating the matter” Friday, adding that it "has been gathering information" since learning about the allegations of theft made against Ippei Mizuhara, who had served as Ohtani's interpreter. The Dodgers fired Mizuhara earlier this week amid allegations he stole millions from Ohtani to cover gambling debts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d97988e0-e8a6-11ee-b8d4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 23:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISIS claims responsibility for Moscow concert attack that has killed at least 40</title>
      <description>A news agency for the terrorist group, which opposes Russia as an enemy of Muslims, said it was behind the deadliest attack in the country in over a decade. A U.S. official, speaking on the condition of anonymity, said the United States had “no reason to doubt” the claim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1648f160-e89e-11ee-befc-0000a1aced61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Women allege sexual misconduct, harassment by polo champion</title>
      <description>A half-dozen young women interviewed by The Washington Post alleged that John Gobin, a polo champion who runs a school for the sport in Virginia, engaged in a pattern of sexual harassment.

The allegations — some made in a newly filed lawsuit — include inappropriate touching and demeaning comments. At the time, some of the women were teenage workers at the school. Through an attorney, Gobin said all the claims by the women are false. He has not been charged with a crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fee34b0-e897-11ee-b323-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:57:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Mike Gallagher’s departure will leave GOP with just one-vote margin in House</title>
      <description>Under Wisconsin law, Gallagher’s seat is expected to remain vacant until January, with the November general election to determine who wins. After Gallagher leaves on April 19, House Speaker Mike Johnson (La.) will only be able to spare one vote to pass any conservative legislation through the chamber on party lines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3574abb0-e88f-11ee-8cac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gunmen in camouflage attacked a popular Moscow concert venue. Dozens were wounded or killed, state media reported.</title>
      <description>Several gunmen opened fire Friday night at Crocus City Hall, a popular concert venue on the outskirts of the Russian capital, and there were reports of an explosion. The region’s governor said he was going to the scene.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba343c0-e879-11ee-9212-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine, Princess of Wales, has cancer, she says in a recorded address</title>
      <description>The announcement follows months of speculation about the health of the 42-year-old princess, who has not made an official appearance since Christmas and underwent abdominal surgery in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24dc3e70-e877-11ee-a78a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:08:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
