<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 17:02:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar will headline the 2025 Super Bowl halftime show in New Orleans</title>
      <description>The rapper revealed the plan Sunday in a video posted to YouTube. This will be Lamar’s second Super Bowl performance, after his 2022 set with Dr. Dre.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37a4d760-6e00-11ef-89ed-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 16:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">922127c0-6dfb-11ef-8aa5-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors thought her constantly running nose was due to allergies or a virus. It signaled something more serious.</title>
      <description>Treatments prescribed to Shemika Rodriguez hadn’t helped. After three months, her episodic drip turned into a constant flow that made her feel like she was drowning when she lay down. But she came to suspect she knew the cause. Eight years earlier, one of her relatives had been diagnosed with a similar problem that had an unfortunate ending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1f92dd0-6df6-11ef-b534-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 15:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Commanders begin their season today. This is your ultimate game-day guide.</title>
      <description>As the Commanders open their season on the road, we've got everything you need to watch from home: the key matchup, stats to know, trivia and even food recs. Here’s a helpful guide for the 4:25 p.m. Eastern game between the Commanders and Tampa Bay Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22d28cd0-6def-11ef-bffc-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing reaches tentative deal with machinists union in effort to avoid costly strike</title>
      <description>The agreement increases pay by 25 percent over four years and commits Boeing to build its next new aircraft in Washington state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">478782a1-6deb-11ef-a32d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 14:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95784e91-6de6-11ef-ab4d-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aryna Sabalenka of Belarus wins the U.S. Open, defeating American Jessica Pegula for her third Grand Slam singles title</title>
      <description>Sabalenka, 26, made up for her loss to American Coco Gauff in last year's U.S. Open final with Saturday's victory over the No. 6 seed Pegula. The second-seeded Sabalenka captured her second Grand Slam title of the year after winning the Australian Open in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95dac1b0-6d69-11ef-b60d-0000a1ace278</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 22:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother of Georgia suspect is said to have called school minutes before shooting, warning of ‘extreme emergency’ involving her son</title>
      <description>Text messages and a phone log reviewed by The Washington Post, along with exclusive interviews with a relative of the suspect, provide the strongest indications yet that school officials were alerted to concerns about him on the morning of the shooting and may have been looking for him in the minutes before he allegedly killed four people and injured nine with an AR-15-style rifle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c693f571-6d63-11ef-a214-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 21:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An au pair, a husband’s affair and a double homicide</title>
      <description>Juliana Peres Magalhães, an au pair from Brazil, is charged with second-degree murder in a killing that took place in the main bedroom of Christine and Brendan Banfield’s Virginia home, where Magalhães took care of their young daughter. After the fatal shooting, she moved into that bedroom with Brendan, as the two were in a romantic relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c62fdd0-6d4c-11ef-9fec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Jayden Daniels the one who will finally stop Washington’s woes at quarterback?</title>
      <description>The Commanders are set for the NFL season and have something rare behind center: hope. Jayden Daniels, the reigning Heisman trophy winner and No. 2 pick out of LSU, has earned glowing reviews during the preseason and appears to be the answer at a position the franchise has been unable to solve for decades. A look at his upbringing in San Bernardino, Calif., and his emergence in Baton Rouge shows what might make him different than the QBs who have failed here before him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a0197e0-6d30-11ef-bd61-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The plan was to move migrants to a small town. Then came anger, fear and a fight over the meaning of shelter.</title>
      <description>As dozens of migrant families slept on the floor of Boston’s airport, the state decided to open a shelter in a town of 11,000 people. Inside one small corner of the nation’s immigration crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6fb260-6d23-11ef-9808-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea9f320-6d1c-11ef-9808-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Fritz advances to U.S. Open final, will be first American man in Grand Slam singles final in 15 years</title>
      <description>The No. 12-ranked Fritz defeated fellow American Frances Tiafoe, ranked 20th, in the first all-American semifinal in a men’s Grand Slam event since 2005. The last time an American man made a Grand Slam final was 2009, when Andy Roddick lost at Wimbledon to Roger Federer. Fritz will face top-ranked Jannik Sinner, who ousted Britain’s Jack Draper in three sets, in Sunday’s final.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24adf780-6cc6-11ef-a3b5-0000a1ace015</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 03:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Cheney, Republican former vice president, says he will vote for Kamala Harris to ‘put country above partisanship’</title>
      <description>Cheney, who served as George W. Bush’s No. 2 and in other Republican administrations, said in a statement he will cast a ballot for the Democratic nominee, confirming remarks his daughter had made hours earlier.
“In our nation’s 248-year history, there has never been an individual who is a greater threat to our republic than Donald Trump,” Cheney said. “He tried to steal the last election using lies and violence to keep himself in power after the voters had rejected him. He can never be trusted with power again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dbb0ac0-6c9e-11ef-a4fa-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 22:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with plotting an attack on a N.Y. Jewish center on the Oct. 7 anniversary of the Hamas attacks in southern Israel</title>
      <description>U.S. officials have charged a Canadian resident with plotting to travel to New York to try to carry out a mass shooting attack against Jewish people on the one-year anniversary of the attacks, authorities announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a86e641-6c94-11ef-b75e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York judge delays Trump sentencing in hush money case until after presidential election</title>
      <description>The decision to push sentencing from Sept. 18 to Nov. 26 means voters will cast ballots in the presidential election without knowing whether Donald Trump, the Republican nominee, could face jail time for his conviction on 34 counts of falsifying business records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58524440-6c73-11ef-b078-0000a1ace191</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 17:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My 17-year-old son is dating a 14-year-old. Her parents don't approve.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My 17-year-old son is dating a 14-year-old. Her parents don't approve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67753940-6c6f-11ef-8b1d-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 16:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. woman fatally shot at West Bank protest; witnesses say Israeli forces shot her</title>
      <description>The State Department said it was “urgently gathering more information about the circumstances of her death.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f7ac4c0-6c66-11ef-92b6-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia teen suspect and his father appear in court on charges in shooting that left four dead at high school</title>
      <description>The suspect, 14, faces four counts of felony murder in connection with the shooting. He was brought into Barrow County Superior Court shortly after 8:30 a.m. through a side door, dressed in a green shirt, his long blond hair shaggy, and shackled at his wrists and feet. His father appeared in court shortly after his son. The father is being held on four counts of involuntary manslaughter, two counts of second-degree murder and eight counts of cruelty to children in connection with the deadly shooting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8680bb00-6c58-11ef-ae25-0000a1aceff4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 14:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48d2ec50-6c54-11ef-98ce-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Economy adds 142,000 jobs in August, as the labor market continues to slow under weight of high interest rates</title>
      <description>The labor market notched another month of sluggish growth in August, according to data released Friday from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, giving the Federal Reserve reason to cut interest rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35d01b80-6c4c-11ef-9c91-0000a1ace423</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 12:33:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia shooting charges. JD Vance. Hunter Biden. Hot summer. Parkinson’s clue. NFL. See-through mice. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2787ded0-6c3f-11ef-8f1b-0000a1ace990</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth just sweltered through the hottest summer in recorded history</title>
      <description>The world’s average temperature this summer just edged out the record set last summer, according to Europe’s top climate agency. The new findings, coupled with data from the first half of the year, indicate that 2024 will be the hottest year known to science.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">638f9080-6bf4-11ef-9301-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new NFL season begins tonight as the Super Bowl champion Kansas City Chiefs meet the Baltimore Ravens. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The NFL is going big with its season opener, a star-studded matchup featuring past MVP winners Patrick Mahomes and Lamar Jackson, plus Taylor Swift's favorite tight end. The game will also mark the regular season debut of the league's new kickoff format, a major change designed to reduce injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ccc8e60-6be8-11ef-8873-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Father of Ga. high school shooting suspect was arrested on charges of involuntary manslaughter, second-degree murder</title>
      <description>Colin Gray was arrested Thursday night by the Georgia Bureau of Investigation, the agency said. Gray was charged with four counts of involuntary manslaughter, two counts of second-degree murder and eight counts of cruelty to children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0aca4b80-6be4-11ef-8713-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parkinson’s may begin in the gut, study says, adding to growing body of evidence</title>
      <description>The study, published in JAMA Network Open, found that people with upper gastrointestinal conditions — in particular, ulcers or other types of damage to the lining of the esophagus, stomach or upper part of the small intestine — were far more likely to develop Parkinson’s disease later in life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28bed370-6bd7-11ef-8873-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 22:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden pleads guilty to federal tax charges, could face hefty fine and prison sentence</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden’s son entered a last-minute guilty plea on the day jury selection was supposed to begin in his federal trial. He could face up to 17 years in prison and fines of up to $1.3 million, a judge in Los Angeles said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff447940-6bcd-11ef-8dd8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 21:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How does divorced parent adjust to having less time with son?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How does divorced parent adjust to having less time with son?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">151054f1-6bb1-11ef-a495-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 18:02:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Times publisher A.G. Sulzberger writes in an op-ed: The quiet war against press freedom could come to America. Here’s how.</title>
      <description>Some foreign leaders have ruthlessly curtailed journalism. American politicians could draw from their playbook, Sulzberger writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">224aecd0-6bab-11ef-9cc0-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 17:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Biden offers plea in tax case, in effort to avoid second criminal trial</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden’s son Hunter tried to resolve his federal tax case Thursday morning as jury selection was about to begin, offering an Alford plea in which he maintains he is innocent but acknowledges that the prosecution’s evidence would likely result in a guilty verdict.

The judge adjourned the court proceedings until 11 a.m. Pacific time so prosecutors could consider the plea offer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4c1370-6ba0-11ef-ab71-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 16:02:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fictional train in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">197bbaa0-6b8b-11ef-8c12-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ugandan Olympic runner Rebecca Cheptegei dies after she was set on fire by her ex-boyfriend</title>
      <description>Cheptegei is the third high-profile athlete to be killed in a domestic violence incident in Kenya, where she was based.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ac69bf0-6b8a-11ef-8dd8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia school shooting. Liz Cheney. Trump hearing. U.S. Steel. Toxic plastic. Space spectacle. ‘Game of Thrones.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff2f72a0-6b75-11ef-8453-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The FBI learned of Ga. high school shooting suspect a year ago and sheriffs had questioned the teen and his father, agency says</title>
      <description>FBI agents received anonymous tips over a year ago about online threats allegedly made by the suspect now accused of killing four and injuring nine others at Apalachee High School. Jackson County Sheriff's officers interviewed the teen suspect and his father, who said hunting guns were kept in the house but his son did not have unsupervised access to them. Local schools were alerted about the tips, the FBI said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86862070-6b1f-11ef-bb0f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 00:41:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liz Cheney, in a break with the Republican Party, says she will vote for Democratic nominee Kamala Harris</title>
      <description>Cheney, the former congresswoman who served as vice chair of the House committee that investigated the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, made the announcement in North Carolina, which is considered to be one of the battleground states that could help decide the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1802e0-6b10-11ef-b589-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 22:54:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia school shooting suspect in custody is a 14-year-old student; two students and two teachers were killed, officials say</title>
      <description>Police identified a teenager as the suspect in a shooting at Georgia’s Apalachee High School that killed four people Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379cea91-6aff-11ef-ace2-0000a1ace897</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 20:49:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is preparing to block Nippon Steel’s purchase of U.S. Steel in stunning move, people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>The move would formally block Nippon Steel’s proposed $14.9 billion acquisition of U.S. Steel, according to three people with knowledge of the matter, who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The proposed deal has been under investigation by the Committee on Foreign Investment in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e57c0520-6ae5-11ef-b32c-0000a1ace78b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:48:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least two killed and several wounded in Georgia high school shooting, according to a law enforcement official</title>
      <description>Several others were wounded in the shooting at Apalachee High School, about 35 miles northeast of Atlanta. A suspect is in custody, the Georgia Bureau of Investigation said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a707a030-6ae3-11ef-b014-0000a1aceddf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the asteroids that scare scientists. Are we prepared for them?</title>
      <description>These are the asteroids that scare scientists. Are we prepared for them?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afb52e81-6ae0-11ef-a8f5-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89f20890-6ada-11ef-a089-0000a1aceb59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6820140-6ad6-11ef-a0b7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta’s oversight body says ‘from the river to the sea’ isn’t necessarily hate speech, a decision likely to fuel Israel-Gaza debates</title>
      <description>The company-funded oversight body ruled the social media giant shouldn’t automatically take down posts using the phrase, a decades-old rallying cry for Palestinian nationalism that has reignited debate about the boundaries of acceptable speech. The clash has forced the company to closely examine its content rules amid scrutiny from Jewish groups that have accused it of allowing antisemitism to surge and criticism from pro-Palestinian groups, which argue Meta has stifled political critique amid a deadly war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">201ec341-6ad5-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was pitched as ‘an extraordinary opportunity’ to protect the planet and people. The Post found deep failures.</title>
      <description>C-Quest Capital said its stoves could improve people’s lives and reduce carbon emissions. But an investigation by The Washington Post in Mozambique reveals that the company promised more than it could deliver — a further hit to a troubled offsets market used by BP, Shell and other major corporations to meet their climate goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc82a752-6ac7-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unsettling new milestone for this city in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb86c81-6ac1-11ef-a59a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian strike. Trump vs. Harris. Gaza talks. School cop. Landslides. Cellphone study. Titanic. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca02062-6aac-11ef-882a-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Foreign Minister Dmytro Kuleba resigns amid government shake-up</title>
      <description>Kuleba’s exit follows those of other high-ranking officials in Ukraine this week. Kuleba, who has been in the role since 2020, has been a key voice in Ukraine’s drive to receive foreign weapons and to push allies to loosen restrictions on how they are used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413b7d20-6a8f-11ef-8149-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A louder voice in fighting abortion bans: Men in red states</title>
      <description>Two years after the Supreme Court overturned federal protections for abortion, growing numbers of men in deeply conservative states are speaking out in defense of reproductive rights because of the harrowing experiences they’ve seen wives or partners go through when pregnancies went tragically awry.

They have an integral role in the debate, a legal expert says: “Men telling their own stories … is going to be a big way to change hearts and minds.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a68d420-6a42-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. charges Hamas leaders with terrorism, citing Oct. 7 attack, and is investigating killing of Hersh Goldberg-Polin</title>
      <description>Attorney General Merrick Garland stressed that Hamas was responsible for the Oct. 7 deaths in southern Israel and said the United States will investigate the killing of Goldberg-Polin, 23, whose body was found in Gaza last week, as an act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5e906f1-6a3e-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A school resource officer admitted to sexually abusing two students. A South Carolina judge just sentenced him to probation.</title>
      <description>Richland County Sheriff's Deputy Jamel Bradley kept his job for years despite multiple complaints of sexual misconduct with teen girls, a Washington Post investigation found. The judge ordered Bradley to register as a sex offender, against the recommendation of prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">783b3240-6a2e-11ef-8990-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab9fcb30-6a0d-11ef-8557-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
