<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 01:25:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>All new cars must have automatic emergency braking systems by 2029 under new federal safety rule</title>
      <description>The standards require cars to apply brakes automatically to avoid hitting pedestrians and other vehicles, even at higher speeds. Industry groups say the rule is impractical and that no currently produced vehicles can achieve the new standard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33968de0-0680-11ef-8793-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:28:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 officers fatally shot, 5 injured while serving warrant in Charlotte, N.C.</title>
      <description>Members of a U.S. Marshals fugitive task force were met with gunfire while trying to serve a warrant. The shooter was also killed, police said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7de832b0-067e-11ef-8774-0000a1ace886</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 23:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real Rick Steves is so much more complex than the travel host you see on TV</title>
      <description>At 68, America's favorite travel expert is still working hard and speaking out on ways to make the country a little more like his beloved Europe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a73f5e30-066b-11ef-b350-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 21:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump on trial: Personal anguish, political defiance and a loss of control</title>
      <description>Two weeks in, the first criminal trial of a former president has been personally taxing for Donald Trump and disruptive to his campaign for a return to the White House. The indictments that once helped Trump lock down the GOP nomination by firing up his base have become a serious constraint in the general election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05815f90-065b-11ef-b45d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 19:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appellate court rules state health-care plans must pay for gender-affirming surgeries, a major win for transgender rights</title>
      <description>The decision came from a set of cases out of North Carolina and West Virginia, where state officials argued that their policies were based on cost concerns rather than bias. The U.S. Court of Appeals for the 4th Circuit rejected that argument, saying the plans were discriminating against trans people in need of treatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5aacf0f0-0648-11ef-9054-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:48:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is checking his phone the best way to prove he isn’t lying anymore?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is checking his phone the best way to prove he isn’t lying anymore?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f4e2280-0643-11ef-b401-0000a1acecd0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 16:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All about open seating in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b93ec100-062c-11ef-bc15-0000a1ace8c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 13:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian intelligence officer directed plot to kill Modi critic on U.S. soil, stunning Western officials, Post investigation finds</title>
      <description>The Post has identified an officer in India’s intelligence service who directed a murder-for-hire scheme to kill a Sikh activist in New York. Higher-ranking officials in the Indian service have also been implicated, according to current and former Western security officials, as part of a sprawling investigation by the CIA, FBI and other agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">331d8030-0626-11ef-95f1-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 12:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>College protests. World Central Kitchen. Tornadoes. Tesla lawsuits. Sea level rise. Low birthrates. Vegan cheese. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7e45bf1-0617-11ef-af74-0000a1acef61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2024 11:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My mom won’t vent her frustrations to my dad. So she dumps them on me.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My mom won’t vent her frustrations to my dad. So she dumps them on me.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0feeae40-05b3-11ef-ac34-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A homeless woman got an apartment in an upscale D.C. building. Conflicts with neighbors and eviction notices ensued.</title>
      <description>In 2021, Staci Jameson had been living in a tent when she received a housing voucher for a one-bedroom apartment downtown. Soon after, she began clashing with neighbors and building management. Her case illustrates the myriad challenges that come after unhoused people are given a place to live, as well as the mental health and other support that is often needed to help them succeed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da02f610-05a3-11ef-b1a8-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 21:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New details from lawsuits test Tesla’s claim that drivers are solely responsible for Autopilot crashes</title>
      <description>The Washington Post obtained dash-cam footage of Tesla crashes that offers sometimes-shocking details of vehicles allegedly on Autopilot. At least eight new lawsuits and a federal investigation contend that Tesla’s technology invites drivers to overly trust the automation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c26982f0-0597-11ef-94ba-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 19:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump met privately with his former rival DeSantis, who agreed to help with campaign fundraising, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump and Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis met privately Sunday morning in Miami, breaking a years-long chill between the presumptive Republican nominee and his onetime chief primary rival. The meeting was friendly, according to a person with direct knowledge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee564610-0587-11ef-98c6-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 17:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aefff880-0578-11ef-9902-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 16:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden roasted Trump at the White House correspondents’ dinner — but made it clear it was no joke</title>
      <description>Washington’s annual mashup of political humor and earnest paeans to the free press is typically a good-natured collection of one-liners and affectionate jabs at friends and enemies alike. But it was the leading 2024 presidential contenders who loomed largest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be407380-0567-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 14:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b8a1bc0-0563-11ef-b467-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 13:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They bought homes for under $1 million. Here’s what they learned.</title>
      <description>Last year, just over 4 million existing homes sold in the United States — the lowest number in nearly three decades, according to the National Association of Realtors. Nine households that bought real estate in the past year share how they navigated the buying process during these tumultuous times.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9881be00-04eb-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 23:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Among the 18 Trump allies indicted in Arizona this week: A senior counsel to the RNC’s election integrity team</title>
      <description>When conservative lawyer and media personality Christina Bobb became the latest member of Donald Trump’s inner circle to be charged for her alleged role in the effort to reverse the 2020 presidential election results, it became immediately clear she would not have to give up her day job with the Republican National Committee. Bobb’s indictment solidifies her identity as a dedicated Trump loyalist and potentially elevates her role within the RNC.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb4b0850-04cb-11ef-8e47-0000a1acec20</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 19:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A vegan cheese beat dairy in a big competition. Then the plot curdled.</title>
      <description>When Climax Foods’ plant-based blue cheese was named as a finalist in the Good Food awards, traditionalists were shaken. Its status was revoked as controversy fomented.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036318c0-04c1-11ef-b672-0000a1ace1b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 18:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for something to watch? These are the best new TV shows and series in 2024 so far.</title>
      <description>“Ripley,” “The Sympathizer,” “Shogun,” “Fallout,” “Elsbeth,” “Constellation” and “The Girls on the Bus” all make our critics’ evolving list of the year’s best TV shows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2fc4c20-04b7-11ef-af7a-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 17:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Elaine: After a traumatic birth, new mom can’t let go of debilitating fears</title>
      <description>Ask Elaine: After a traumatic birth, new mom can’t let go of debilitating fears</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e395adc0-04af-11ef-8376-0000a1acec1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 16:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened to a man who threatened Marjorie Taylor Greene (R-Ga.): ‘You spread hatred, and you’re gonna pay for it’</title>
      <description>In a time of rising political anger, one man going through a mental health crisis threatened the congresswoman after seeing one of her political ads. Then came the consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1245b2c0-04a4-11ef-be41-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 14:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">433cd6b0-049a-11ef-a79b-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Restoring sight is now possible with gene therapy</title>
      <description>Several companies are experimenting with optogenetics to create a “bionic eye” that can restore sight in visually impaired people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53bbfa60-0414-11ef-bfdb-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 21:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asia’s next war could be triggered by a rusting warship on a disputed reef</title>
      <description>In the South China Sea, tensions over competing claims by China and countries in Southeast Asia have grown more intense than at any time in recent years. The risk of armed confrontation increasingly hinges on China’s efforts to block the Philippines from resupplying the crew aboard a dilapidated navy ship intentionally grounded on a contested reef to establish it as a military outpost.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7888a7a1-03f4-11ef-a7ba-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 17:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret meetings, social chatter: How the Columbia protest started a nationwide student revolt</title>
      <description>The day after dozens of pro-Palestinian protesters were arrested at Columbia, hundreds of students nationwide joined a Zoom to learn how they could start their own encampments. The coordination has led to what historians now call one of the most consequential student uprisings in recent times. Here’s how it unfolded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">501f8140-03e9-11ef-a36b-0000a1ace835</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most lopsided first round in NFL draft history made it clear: Offense rules, our analyst says</title>
      <description>When the NFL draft began Thursday night, the first 14 picks were offensive players. The 23 offensive players chosen in the first round shattered the previous mark of 19. The draft’s biggest takeaway: Even after a season in which scoring dropped, the NFL is doubling down on this era’s skew toward offense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd3880b1-03de-11ef-b2da-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 15:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safety regulators launch new review of whether Tesla did enough to fix Autopilot</title>
      <description>Tesla recalled 2 million cars with Autopilot in December to add warnings. Federal regulators are now questioning whether the remedy goes far enough. Autopilot can still be activated on roads with cross traffic or no center median, where The Post found at least eight serious or fatal crashes have occurred.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4612ea0-03d9-11ef-8ce6-0000a1ace289</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 14:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8e37510-03d0-11ef-930f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump immunity. Student protests. Harvey Weinstein. Kenya flooding. NFL draft. Disinfectant. Loud cicadas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2229bb71-03bc-11ef-8033-0000a1ace586</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL draft: Chicago Bears select QB Caleb Williams first overall; Washington Commanders take QB Jayden Daniels. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The first two players chosen were both former Heisman Trophy-winning quarterbacks — Williams at USC and Daniels at LSU — and more quarterbacks are expected to follow. Follow our live coverage of the first round.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">011f34d0-0364-11ef-9135-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2024 00:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Southern California cancels main commencement ceremony, citing new safety measure amid protests over Israel-Gaza war</title>
      <description>The university has also faced criticism after announcing earlier this month that it would not include a speech by its valedictorian, who is Muslim and pro-Palestinian, at the ceremony because of safety concerns. This week, more than 90 protesters were arrested after officers struggled to break up a demonstration on campus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40d58810-0344-11ef-9b78-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 20:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FCC restores net neutrality regulations that were repealed during the Trump administration</title>
      <description>The Federal Communications Commission voted 3-2 to reimpose rules first adopted in 2015 during the Obama administration. But the internet is different now, and some telecom executives are arguing that the advent of 5G requires additional exemptions, while others call such exemptions a loophole.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9292df0-032a-11ef-80b9-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:40:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems poised to reject Trump’s immunity claim in 2020 election case, in a way that further delays his D.C. trial</title>
      <description>During nearly three hours of oral argument, a majority of Supreme Court justices seemed to be looking for a way to provide narrow protections for a president’s core constitutional duties. But all seemed to agree a president is not shielded from prosecution for private conduct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80889511-0326-11ef-87c3-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 17:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why not get rid of email at work? Daniel Pink is answering your questions live.</title>
      <description>Daniel Pink is fielding your ‘Why Not?’ ideas and answering your questions</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c154440-031f-11ef-bb2e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Can one spouse tell another to stop traveling so much for work?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Can one spouse tell another to stop traveling so much for work?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4794a0-031d-11ef-8fb8-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 16:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haitian Prime Minister Ariel Henry resigns, a crucial step for new elections and U.N.-approved police deployment amid gang violence</title>
      <description>A transitional presidential council was sworn in on Thursday, and a government decree said Michel Patrick Boisvert would serve as interim prime minister. Boisvert has been leading the government since Henry left the country on a diplomatic trip in February.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">037301c0-0315-11ef-a94b-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>N.Y. court overturns Harvey Weinstein’s 2020 rape conviction and orders new trial — a shocking twist in a pivotal #MeToo case</title>
      <description>The New York Court of Appeals ruled the judge in Weinstein’s trial improperly allowed testimony about allegations that weren’t part of the case, according to the Associated Press. The former movie mogul will remain in prison on his 2022 California rape conviction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4a7c90-0309-11ef-a8ac-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:43:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court weighs if Trump is immune from prosecution on charges of trying to subvert the 2020 election. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The oral argument in Washington comes as Donald Trump is on trial in New York in the hush money case. The justices’ ruling on immunity will have a major impact in shaping presidential power and accountability for future occupants of the White House — and whether Trump will be tried on federal charges in D.C. before this year's election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14eaab40-0308-11ef-98c4-0000a1ace4c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Sucks to be you’ if you’re not on the train they're building in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">950589f0-0306-11ef-a0af-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 100 pro-Palestinian protesters arrested near Emerson College in Boston; campus protests in Texas, California also broken up</title>
      <description>Protests spread at colleges across the country, with dozens of arrests at the University of Southern California and the University of Texas at Austin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e10d321-0305-11ef-9a82-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 13:11:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy grew at a 1.6% annualized rate in the first quarter, as consumer spending slowed</title>
      <description>New data from the U.S. Bureau of Economic Analysis shows gross domestic product remained solid, although consumer spending slowed as higher prices weighed on the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1da1ac41-0301-11ef-8a05-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New federal rules will slash air, water and climate pollution from U.S. power plants. Red states are certain to sue.</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency finalized an ambitious set of rules that will cut air pollution, water pollution and planet-warming emissions spewing from power plants across the country. The rules will crack down on releases of mercury, greenhouse emissions and other pollutants from power plants' smokestacks, waste dumps and wastewater discharges. Republican attorneys general are likely to challenge some or all of the regulations in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2bdb6f30-02fc-11ef-8f1d-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2020 election charges. Abortion case. College arrests. Bird flu. Plastic polluters. NFL draft. Flight refunds. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f65b3b50-02f2-11ef-8b17-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Meadows, Rudy Giuliani, pro-Trump electors and other allies charged in Arizona 2020 election interference probe</title>
      <description>The indictments cap a year-long investigation by Arizona Attorney General Kris Mayes (D) into the unsuccessful attempt to keep Donald Trump in the White House after he lost the 2020 presidential election by trying to award Arizona’s electoral votes to Trump instead of Joe Biden, who won the state. Arizona is the fourth state, following Michigan, Georgia and Nevada, to seek charges against those who formed an alternate slate of presidential electors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ebc4380-0291-11ef-b16f-0000a1ace203</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 23:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Cohen, preparing to take the stand against his ex-boss, says he’s reformed. Will America buy it?</title>
      <description>After years as Donald Trump’s bruising personal attorney, Cohen is a man on a quest for redemption. But as he prepares to serve as a linchpin in the Manhattan district attorney’s criminal case against the former president, America’s most famous ex-fixer remains a divisive figure — even among partisans on the Trump-loathing left.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db0f1450-0281-11ef-a142-0000a1ace818</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 21:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-controlled Arizona House votes to repeal Civil War-era abortion ban. The measure now heads to the state Senate.</title>
      <description>Soon after Roe v. Wade was overturned, the 1864 law briefly took effect in the state, only to be blocked by the courts. Earlier this month, the Arizona Supreme Court revived it, inciting a national uproar and political panic among Republicans as 2024 elections loom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d38b20-0270-11ef-8445-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 19:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court conservatives seem skeptical that federal law can require hospitals to perform emergency abortions in states with bans</title>
      <description>The Biden administration has invoked the Emergency Medical Treatment and Labor Act to argue that the federal government can penalize hospitals that fail to provide emergency abortions in states with strict abortion bans. But conservative justices appeared skeptical the 40-year-old federal law — which requires hospitals that receive federal funds to stabilize or transfer all emergency patients regardless of their ability to pay — could be used to require abortions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd683fa1-0258-11ef-a199-0000a1acefff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:37:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Why do cooked chicken thighs sometimes look bloody, and are they safe to eat? Chat with our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd2a21c0-0257-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: ‘Close’ friend kept daughter’s wedding a secret for almost a year</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc16e20-0253-11ef-8cd8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
