<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 05:02:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Las Vegas Aces complete WNBA Finals sweep to cement dynasty status</title>
      <description>Behind superstar A’ja Wilson, the Aces beat the Phoenix Mercury four straight times and won their third championship in four seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">790c10f0-a64a-11f0-86a8-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 02:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces new 100 percent tariffs on China</title>
      <description>The president said he might cancel a meeting with Chinese leader Xi Jinping in retaliation for Beijing’s “hostile” move to limit access to rare minerals used in manufacturing. Stocks sank on his earlier threats to increase tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63835b92-a621-11f0-a89f-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration begins laying off federal workers amid shutdown, fulfilling president’s threat</title>
      <description>White House budget director Russell Vought said reductions-in-force were underway.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e42a09e0-a5fb-11f0-801d-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens tariffs on China, says he may cancel upcoming meeting with President Xi Jinping</title>
      <description>The president wrote on TruthSocial that he is unhappy about China’s “hostile” move to limit access to rare minerals used in manufacturing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe7be0e0-a5f4-11f0-a88f-0000a1ace307</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:20:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MIT rejects Trump administration deal for priority federal funding, the first university to publicly turn down the offer</title>
      <description>Last week, the Trump administration offered nine universities a “Compact for Academic Excellence in Higher Education,” presented as an opportunity to receive competitive advantages from the federal government. It was the latest attempt by the administration to force colleges into compliance with President Donald Trump’s ideological priorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fe24f61-a5ed-11f0-b45d-0000a1ace9c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside billionaire Peter Thiel’s private lectures: Warnings of ‘the Antichrist’ and U.S. destruction</title>
      <description>The tech investor said critics of technology are “legionnaires of the Antichrist” in recent private lectures on Christianity in San Francisco that connected government oversight of Silicon Valley to an apocalyptic future, according to recordings reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e790711-a5e2-11f0-b420-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 14:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eaf90870-a5dd-11f0-982d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James. Trump and Gaza. Shutdown deadlock. Peter Thiel. Polar bears. Weekend storm. Bad Bunny. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ce6471-a5c8-11f0-a82f-000a1aced47b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Peace Prize awarded to María Corina Machado, a Venezuelan democracy crusader</title>
      <description>The Venezuelan opposition leader has become a symbol of democratic resistance against an increasingly authoritarian regime, even as she has been forced into hiding and barred from holding public office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56f5e120-a5ba-11f0-ac92-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s cabinet approves Gaza ceasefire deal, triggering countdown for Hamas to release remaining hostages</title>
      <description>Cabinet approval sets in motion a sequence expected to bring about the release of some 48 Israeli hostages, living and dead, in exchange for hundreds of Palestinians held in Israeli prisons as well as a halt to Israel’s bombardment of the Gaza Strip.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9afa6b0-a568-11f0-a182-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump from deploying troops in Illinois for now</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Chicago on Thursday temporarily halted the administration’s push to dispatch the National Guard in and around the country’s third-largest city. The administration is almost certain to appeal the decision, which is the second time in a week that a judge has rejected President Donald Trump’s efforts to place troops in a major city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01d4a3e0-a568-11f0-925c-000a1ace827b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:30:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sports wager with terrible odds that bettors can’t stop making</title>
      <description>Parlays offer long odds and big potential payouts by combining individual bets into one with multiple “legs.” As betting booms, they are accounting for an increasing share of the money wagered on sports, according to a Washington Post analysis of state data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cf7a9a0-a565-11f0-94ad-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 23:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department indicts N.Y. Attorney General Letitia James in mortgage fraud case</title>
      <description>She becomes the latest of President Donald Trump’s foes charged in a case that career prosecutors had turned down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac004170-a550-11f0-9dbc-0000a1ace491</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 20:43:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Spouse can’t drive anymore and expects to be driven on demand</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Spouse can’t drive anymore and expects to be driven on demand</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78bbabe0-a52a-11f0-8304-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/10/09/carolyn-hax-spouse-demand-personal-driver/</title>
      <description>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/10/09/carolyn-hax-spouse-demand-personal-driver/</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1572df0-a529-11f0-80f8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nobel Prize in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c255feb0-a514-11f0-8eed-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unorthodox deal-making helped reach a Gaza peace deal that might actually hold, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>"If the deal holds, Trump can legitimately bolster his claim to be a peacemaker."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1764ff00-a510-11f0-855c-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She left the medical mainstream and rose to be RFK Jr.’s surgeon general pick</title>
      <description>Casey Means has criticized the medical establishment. She could be put in a position to change it if confirmed, as expected, to one of the nation’s most recognizable and trusted medical posts. Several medical and scientific experts expressed concern that she could amplify policy recommendations that are not grounded in evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d07200-a50c-11f0-8eed-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel Prize in literature awarded to Hungarian author László Krasznahorkai, renowned for his ‘apocalyptic’ epics</title>
      <description>The Swedish Academy honored the writer, whom critic Susan Sontag once called the “master of the apocalypse” for “his compelling and visionary oeuvre.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9402b0c1-a501-11f0-a3f3-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 11:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza breakthrough. Troops in Chicago. Charlie Kirk. Data scramble. Wildfire arrest. Prime Day. Dolly Parton. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134155b0-a4ff-11f0-824b-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bipartisan measure to block Trump’s lethal strikes against alleged Venezuelan drug smugglers fails in Senate</title>
      <description>Democrats called the administration’s strikes unconstitutional but were unable to persuade enough Republicans to vote for a restraining measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbe9b440-a4a9-11f0-bb6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:49:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hamas agree to peace deal to begin ending war in Gaza, Trump says</title>
      <description>The president’s announcement says the agreement includes the release of hostages by Hamas and the withdrawal of Israeli troops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87895330-a49d-11f0-8d85-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 23:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40 best restaurants in and around D.C.</title>
      <description>Washington Post food critic Tom Sietsema celebrates, one last time, some of the many places that make D.C. one of the best food cities in the country — starting with a Top 5 list. His restaurant of the year: Albi, the Levantine jewel that just keeps getting better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a610ff0-a492-11f0-9099-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 22:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s sprawling hunt for Charlie Kirk critics spans nearly 300 investigations</title>
      <description>The inquiry, resulting in a smattering of disciplinary action so far, follows an extraordinary Pentagon directive aimed at silencing criticism of the slain activist and Trump supporter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d4f02f0-a47d-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A quarter of FBI agents have been assigned to immigration enforcement, internal data shows</title>
      <description>The intense focus on immigration has raised alarm among current and former FBI agents who say morale is low across the bureau as agents have less time to dedicate to national security, white-collar crime and complex cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">409d6b40-a476-11f0-8e3e-0000a1ace64f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 18:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man arrested for allegedly starting L.A.-area Palisades Fire that killed 12 people in January, officials say</title>
      <description>Jonathan Rinderknecht, a 29-year-old from Florida, was charged with destruction of property by means of fire, authorities said at a news conference. The fire burned more than 23,000 acres in the area before being contained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f71bac0-a462-11f0-afb2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings buffeted by mom’s cruelty take one last hit with her will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00ffb8a0-a460-11f0-b1d0-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</title>
      <description>Dining chat: The worst meals Tom Sietsema had in his 25 years as a dining critic</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">774763d2-a458-11f0-b9fa-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI director James Comey makes first court appearance and pleads not guilty in case roiling Justice Department</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has opened several criminal investigations into President Donald Trump’s perceived foes in what legal experts and retired judges have described as an unprecedented attack on the rule of law. Comey is the first former senior government official to be charged as part of Trump’s efforts, but the case against him has been fraught for years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd71e9e1-a452-11f0-81ef-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:27:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pynchonian elements in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22c31c80-a44b-11f0-875f-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They say they can’t walk or see. Meet the veterans defrauding the government.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found that the Department of Veterans Affairs’s $193 billion disability program has turned into a rich target for fraudsters. Some of them fake blindness or paralysis to get as much as $1 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e4f88b0-a43e-11f0-a0f2-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:01:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flight delays. Supreme Court. Troop deployments. Gaza rescue. Storm tracker. AI pessimism. Bob Ross. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ee0cc0-a435-11f0-995f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel in chemistry awarded to trio researching metal-organic frameworks, a kind of molecular scaffolding with wide implications</title>
      <description>The Nobel Prize winners were Susumu Kitagawa of Kyoto University in Japan, Richard Robson of the University of Melbourne in Australia and Omar Yaghi of the University of California at Berkeley.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a01bb040-a430-11f0-98d8-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 10:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TikTok keeps its users scrolling for hours a day</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters analyzed data from more than 800 TikTok users to learn how the app turns people into power users, some of whom spend hours per day scrolling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cccc9c0-a3d7-11f0-a65b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 23:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six surgeons general write in an op-ed: It’s our duty to warn the nation about RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>We took an oath to declare dangers when we found them. We’re doing that again today.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a8e3321-a3aa-11f0-a949-000a1ace22b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:19:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears deeply skeptical of Colorado law that bans conversion therapy for gay and transgender minors</title>
      <description>A majority of justices appeared sympathetic to an evangelical therapist whose attorney argued that the state ban infringes on the therapist’s free-speech rights to counsel religious teens dealing with their sexual orientation and gender dysphoria in ways she said are consistent with biblical teachings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c44cbf0-a39f-11f0-bd46-000a1ace63c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal workers are not entitled to back pay after shutdown, White House budget office argues in memo</title>
      <description>The top lawyer at the Office of Management and Budget argued in a draft memo obtained by The Washington Post that a law Congress passed and President Donald Trump signed in 2019 does not guarantee back pay to furloughed workers, ratcheting up tensions in Washington over the week-long shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7512af1-a399-11f0-84ea-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:22:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Twin teens don’t want to meet their widowed parent’s new love</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Twin teens don’t want to meet their widowed parent’s new love</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05d8cd0-a396-11f0-8ca3-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE has kept most offices open during the government shutdown — but not the one inspecting conditions at detention centers</title>
      <description>Immigration and Customs Enforcement’s entire Office of Detention Oversight has been placed on furlough, despite surging numbers of detainees. The contrast between the office’s temporary closure and the ongoing immigration crackdown highlights how the Trump administration’s priorities have steered ICE’s operations during the funding impasse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9294dc20-a391-11f0-95db-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portland is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70441a0-a386-11f0-b403-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 14:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tom Sietsema says goodbye after 25 years. And we finally reveal what our food critic looks like.</title>
      <description>He’s written hundreds of restaurant reviews and thousands of reader Q&amp;As and somehow never had his face appear online before now. Far from retiring, Tom plans to cook more and stay connected with fellow food enthusiasts -- and has some suggestions for getting more out of your restaurant experience.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9cc6af1-a375-11f0-afec-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:05:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Oct. 7 anniversary. Pam Bondi. Covid shots. Everest rescue. TikTok addiction. Food critic reveal. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bef247f0-a36c-11f0-847c-000a1ace3410</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nobel in physics awarded to scientists showing quantum mechanics on a macro scale</title>
      <description>John Clarke, Michel Devoret and John Martinis shared the prize for demonstrating quantum mechanics on a new scale, used in today’s phones, computer, cameras and fiber optic cables.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7422e470-a36a-11f0-973d-0000a1ace551</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 10:43:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump slashed university funding. Here are six key drugs that relied on it.</title>
      <description>The Post examined six major drugs tied to federally funded research, which is now under threat at universities nationwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b040c10-a2f7-11f0-9a11-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 21:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These photos show what it looks like in the world’s data center capital</title>
      <description>These photos show what it looks like in the world’s data center capital</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6de5740-a2cf-11f0-b0bf-0000a1ace16b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:15:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s arguments can end only when boyfriend decides he’s done</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s arguments can end only when boyfriend decides he’s done</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d321abc0-a2cd-11f0-b6e9-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court won’t hear Ghislaine Maxwell’s appeal</title>
      <description>Maxwell, an associate of deceased financier Jeffrey Epstein, was convicted of sex trafficking in 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a23b560-a2bc-11f0-a250-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nothing is real on this new app in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9708bda0-a2b8-11f0-a250-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA spends billions on dubious, even fraudulent disabilities benefits</title>
      <description>Military veterans are swamping the U.S. government with dubious disability claims — including cases of brazen fraud totaling tens of millions of dollars — that are exploiting the country’s sacred commitment to compensate those harmed in the line of duty, according to a Washington Post investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98d70b71-a2ac-11f0-944b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Gaza talks. Unusual shutdown. Supreme Court. Disability benefits. Ozempic at Costco. SNL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6ff4e0-a2a3-11f0-a0f6-0000a1ace1d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
