<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 22:02:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>How far can Jayden Daniels take these Commanders? Our sportswriters are answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>For the first time in years, Washington's NFL team is generating real optimism. Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier are answering readers' questions about the team, which will try to win its third straight game Sunday at Arizona.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21cd1c70-7c21-11ef-b76c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:05:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Lack of focus at work sends new parent into spiral of self-hate</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Lack of focus at work sends new parent into spiral of self-hate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8452a0a0-7c20-11ef-9415-000a1ace6279</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 16:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York Mayor Eric Adams charged with bribery, wire fraud and seeking campaign funds from a foreign national, indictment says</title>
      <description>The indictment reveals a lengthy list of accusations that grew out of what prosecutors called “corrupt relationships" with rich foreigners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72ee64a0-7c18-11ef-8e76-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 15:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans can order free rapid coronavirus tests by mail starting today, ahead of an expected winter covid wave</title>
      <description>The Biden administration will begin shipping four free at-home tests per household on Monday. People can order the tests through covidtests.gov.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f04ebb60-7c0f-11ef-b57f-0000a1aceccd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 14:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A torch goes out in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65d02900-7c0b-11ef-a350-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hoda Kotb says she’ll leave ‘Today’ show early next year</title>
      <description>“I realized that it was time for me to turn the page at 60, and to try something new,” Kotb said on air.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60963a70-7c0a-11ef-9415-000a1ace6279</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Helene, now Category 2, likely to intensify before pummeling Florida and the Southeast. See forecasts and live updates.</title>
      <description>As the massive storm moves toward Florida’s Gulf Coast, its sheer size means dangerous tropical storm-force winds will reach hundreds of miles from the storm's center. The Big Bend area, where the state’s peninsula meets the Panhandle, could see rising water up to 20 feet. And some areas of the United States, including places well beyond Florida, could see over a foot of rain and threats of life-threatening flash-flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c6c7540-7c08-11ef-90e2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 13:08:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Angela Alsobrooks pulls ahead of Larry Hogan in Maryland’s must-win Senate race, poll finds</title>
      <description>Alsobrooks, the Democratic Prince George’s County executive, has pulled clearly ahead in Maryland’s unusually competitive U.S. Senate race with a double-digit lead among likely voters, according to a Washington Post-University of Maryland poll, in a contest critical to deciding control of the chamber next year.

Alsobrooks leads Hogan — a Republican former governor elected twice in the deep-blue state — by 11 percentage points among likely voters, even though the poll shows Hogan has won over a sizable portion of Democrats and remains about as popular with voters as his rival.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cac17381-7bfe-11ef-a6e5-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s meetings. Hurricane Helene. Eric Adams. Lebanon. Shutdown bill. AI Judi Dench. Constitution copy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cc066d0-7bf6-11ef-9410-0000a1aceb4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York City Mayor Eric Adams indicted amid an apparently wide-ranging corruption probe, a person familiar with the investigation said</title>
      <description>The person spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss an ongoing investigation. The indictment was not public Wednesday, and the specific charges Adams faces could not be learned. But the mayor issued a statement saying he expected to face federal charges, “based on lies.” Another person, also speaking on the condition of anonymity, said they had been told by the mayor’s team that an indictment against him</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe88480-7bb1-11ef-9a39-0000a1ace7c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 02:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes bill to avert government shutdown, sending it to Biden and setting up another spending fight in December</title>
      <description>The bill funds the federal government through Dec. 20. The measure also includes $230 million to beef up the Secret Service budget to protect candidates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">838b3bc0-7b8d-11ef-9a39-0000a1ace7c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 22:28:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane Helene is now predicted to hit Florida’s Gulf Coast late Thursday as a dangerous Category 4 storm and could intensify</title>
      <description>Potentially catastrophic storm surge along Florida’s Big Bend could reach a maximum of 20 feet, a level of inundation that may be "unsurvivable" in some locations, the National Weather Service warns. Dangers are expected to extend well beyond Florida, with heavy rainfall, strong winds and flooding forecast northward into parts of Georgia and the Carolinas, and in mountainous areas of southern Appalachia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e89f0b3-7b8a-11ef-82cf-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 22:04:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top OpenAI executive Mira Murati leaves the company, adding to a recent exodus of senior leaders from the company behind ChatGPT</title>
      <description>Murati was chief technology officer and was briefly interim CEO last year when the board tried unsuccessfully to oust chief executive Sam Altman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a792f00-7b7f-11ef-8f8a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:48:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill to avert government shutdown and beef up Secret Service budget</title>
      <description>The measure moves to the Senate, where a vote is expected later Wednesday. The new deadline would be Dec. 20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99c2bea1-7b7d-11ef-9984-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 20:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says it’s willing to use nuclear weapons against any nation that attacks with the support of a nuclear power</title>
      <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin said the country’s nuclear policy needed to be updated in light of “new sources of military threats.” An attack by a nonnuclear power with the support of a nuclear one would be seen as a joint attack on Russia, he said in a speech to his security council.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f13af30-7b66-11ef-b62c-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta’s answer to ChatGPT is AI that sounds like John Cena or Judi Dench</title>
      <description>Meta is revamping its chatbot by equipping it with an array of celebrity voices, including Awkwafina, Keegan-Michael Key and Kristen Bell, the social media giant announced at its annual developers conference. The move is part of a bet that the star power will draw users to the company’s artificial intelligence tools for entertainment, part of a menu of options that will allows users to personalize Meta’s AI.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">443dedb0-7b64-11ef-80dd-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 17:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hillary Clinton reflects on extremism, hate and what can unite America in an excerpt from her new book</title>
      <description>Hillary Clinton: To err is human, to empathize is superhuman</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54f43111-7b59-11ef-a03a-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:15:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend makes it clear his mom will always be No. 1</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend makes it clear his mom will always be No. 1</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95bda660-7b57-11ef-b0fe-000a1ace8069</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 16:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel is preparing soldiers for a possible ground maneuver in Lebanon, IDF chief tells troops</title>
      <description>Lt. Gen. Herzi Halevi, chief of staff of the Israel Defense Forces, told soldiers to prepare for a possible entry to Lebanon, where they would “go in, destroy the enemy there and decisively destroy” Hezbollah’s infrastructure. Israel has called up two reservist brigades, it announced Wednesday, as it continued to strike targets it said were linked to Hezbollah, and the Lebanese group launched its own aerial attacks on Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f140d11-7b55-11ef-9499-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: My takeout orders are made so fast, the food is never hot. Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: My takeout orders are made so fast, the food is never hot. Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">898a6d61-7b52-11ef-886c-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helene is now a hurricane and will continue to strengthen on its collision course with the Florida coast</title>
      <description>The massive storm could bring serious impacts to not just Florida but also a swath of the southeastern United States. In addition to a “life-threatening” storm surge that could reach up to 15 feet in the Big Bend area and up to 8 feet in Tampa, the National Hurricane Center is warning that several major cities — including Tampa, Orlando, Ocala and Jacksonville — could experience tropical-storm-force winds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b36add60-7b50-11ef-8e76-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 15:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A resurgence for this restaurant in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">661cb4b1-7b42-11ef-9984-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL stadiums will soon double as shelters during hurricanes and other disasters</title>
      <description>The Federal Emergency Management Agency told The Washington Post on Wednesday that football stadiums nationwide will be designated as emergency shelters, temporary hospitals and other venues needed during catastrophic events. Four stadiums in the New York City area, Pittsburgh, Seattle and Tampa have signed on so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">322ecb80-7b37-11ef-8a12-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 12:10:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon crisis. Harris speech. Trump suspect. Missouri execution. Tropical storm. Plane near-miss. Ghost-hunting. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f624600-7b2d-11ef-8e4e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2024 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri executes Marcellus Williams despite prosecutors’ attempts to pull him off death row</title>
      <description>Williams denied killing former St. Louis Post-Dispatch reporter Felicia “Licia” Gayle in 1998, a murder for which he was convicted. Prosecutors and then-Gov. Eric Greitens (R) worked to stop his execution in the past decade, but Gov. Mike Parson (R) insisted that Williams, 55, be put to death.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">545e42d0-7ace-11ef-b389-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 23:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alleged Trump golf course gunman charged with attempted assassination of a political candidate</title>
      <description>Ryan Routh, who was initially charged with two gun violations, now faces a total of five counts and a potential sentence of life in prison. He was arrested Sept. 15 after a U.S. Secret Service agent saw a rifle poking through the bushes near where former president and 2024 Republican nominee Donald Trump was playing golf. On Monday, prosecutors said Routh allegedly left a note with a friend months ago admitting to an attempted assassination of Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdd16f20-7ac5-11ef-b33a-0000a1aced86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 22:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ocean is eating away at this island in Texas. People are planning new condos.</title>
      <description>Since 2010, Galveston has experienced a burst of sea level rise, which has added a staggering 8 inches to the ocean’s height there, according to federal data analyzed by The Post. But development plans are continuing along the coast, where many residents hope a massive federal project might one day fortify the shrinking shoreline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc8c6d40-7ab7-11ef-9658-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 21:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Ellison, key figure in trial of crypto mogul Sam Bankman-Fried, sentenced to prison despite cooperating with prosecutors</title>
      <description>Ellison, the star witness in the trial of FTX co-founder Bankman-Fried, was sentenced Tuesday in federal court. She confessed to playing a central role in one of the largest financial frauds in history, but her testimony helped prosecutors convict her former boss and ex-boyfriend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2654dab0-7ab1-11ef-bfb5-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 20:11:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s the cheapest day to fly for the holidays? Airfare expert Scott Keyes is taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>What’s the cheapest day to fly for the holidays? Airfare expert Scott Keyes is taking your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65e07471-7a91-11ef-bb4a-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The main character of this piece isn’t a person:’ Behind the number that has shaped political debate and the fate of presidents</title>
      <description>John Lanchester on the Bureau of Labor Statistics</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40ff90d1-7a8e-11ef-921d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 16:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: He had an affair while his spouse recovered from surgery</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: He had an affair while his spouse recovered from surgery</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4ffee10-7a8d-11ef-9d28-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grocery chains are bigger than ever. See who runs the stores near you.</title>
      <description>The traditional supermarket industry has shrunk as big-name grocers acquired their smaller local and regional rivals — and the biggest grocery merger yet is awaiting approval.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5618121-7a89-11ef-8c83-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 15:29:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metro set to bring back self-driving trains. The system was shut off after a deadly 2009 crash that was later blamed on other issues.</title>
      <description>With approval from safety regulators, Metro will bring back automated operations on the Red Line by the end of this year, and on the rest of the system by summer. Trains will still have operators riding on them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7e3d580-7a7e-11ef-b33a-0000a1aced86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 14:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A clash over crypto in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79f53801-7a79-11ef-8a65-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington’s Jayden Daniels announced himself to the NFL with a ‘holy cow’ night, columnist Barry Svrluga writes</title>
      <description>Whatever happens Sunday in Arizona or the following week against Cleveland or all the weeks that remain in Daniels’s rookie season and the rest of his career, remember Monday night. Monday night is when we discovered for sure he can do this — “this” being quarterbacking an NFL team with a combination of explosiveness and calm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c8bbe51-7a74-11ef-8ace-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 12:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes. Harris vs. Trump. Missile test. Missouri execution. Looming hurricane. Recycling. Dementia hope. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eb225c0-7a64-11ef-a7e3-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 11:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon's Health Ministry says more than 550 killed since Israeli strikes began Monday, as world leaders try to avoid a wider war</title>
      <description>Israel’s air force struck positions in southern and eastern Lebanon, killing at least 558 people, including 50 children, according to the Health Ministry. At least 1,835 were wounded. Hezbollah fired more rockets Tuesday as world leaders scrambled to cool tensions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01454590-7a64-11ef-90e2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2024 10:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-backed effort to change how Nebraska allocates electoral votes hits roadblock after a GOP state lawmaker’s comments</title>
      <description>Republican state Sen. Mike McDonnell said Monday he does not support changing how the state awards its electoral votes before the November election, imperiling a last-ditch push by former president Donald Trump and his GOP allies.
Nebraska is one of two states that partly awards its electoral votes by congressional district. That allowed Joe Biden to pick up an electoral vote in the solidly red state in 2020 by carrying the vote in a competitive House district in the Omaha area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b1144b0-79dc-11ef-8477-0000a1acedd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 18:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: John Kerry. Kristalina Georgieva. Innovative CEOs. Powerful storytellers. Watch The Post’s climate summit.</title>
      <description>Explore the course of climate change across all seven continents. We spotlight environmental challenges from melting Antarctic glaciers to deforestation of the Amazon, along with the lessons learned for humanity and the bold solutions for new pathways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2eb455a1-79d5-11ef-a4ab-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 17:56:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mapping 8 paths to victory for Harris and Trump in the 2024 presidential election</title>
      <description>We mapped five likely scenarios based on Kamala Harris and Donald Trump’s current standing in the polls, plus three less likely scenarios, including a tie in the electoral college.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1362a30-79c9-11ef-998a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:35:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Burned-out sibling dreads becoming caregiver again by default</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Burned-out sibling dreads becoming caregiver again by default</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fd7f310-79c5-11ef-b7c9-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 16:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California sues ExxonMobil, accusing it of lying about plastics being recyclable ‘in a decades-long campaign of deception’</title>
      <description>The lawsuit, filed Monday in San Francisco County Superior Court, alleges that Exxon falsely promoted all plastics as recyclable. Only about 5 to 6 percent of plastic gets recycled in the United States, according to recent estimates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01838eb0-79c2-11ef-b0f8-0000a1aceb98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 15:39:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘ridiculous’ achievement in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af2dbcf0-79b0-11ef-80fa-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 13:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected Trump golf-course gunman left note saying, ‘This was an assassination attempt,’ according to court filing by prosecutors</title>
      <description>The man arrested with a rifle near where Donald Trump was playing golf this month left a note to a friend saying, “This was an assassination attempt,” according to a new court filing on Monday, shortly before Ryan Routh is expected to appear for a hearing. Routh has been held on gun charges after the Sept. 15 incident, in which authorities say he was spotted and fired upon by a Secret Service agent before he could see Trump or fire a shot. The note offers specific evidence suggesting that Routh’s intention was to kill the former president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e63d7d60-79ac-11ef-b5c4-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 13:08:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lebanon says at least 100 killed, 400 wounded as Israel launches ‘extensive’ strikes on Hezbollah</title>
      <description>Israel said it struck 300 targets in Lebanon on Monday as a military spokesman warned of “extensive, precise” strikes against Hezbollah and called for civilians to evacuate or move away from areas in which the militant group operates.

Lebanon’s Health Ministry said at least 100 people were killed and more than 400 wounded, making Monday the deadliest day in Lebanon since Israel and Hezbollah started trading strikes last October. Its count did not distinguish between civilians and combatants, but it said that children, women and paramedics were among those wounded or killed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cd4b340-79a0-11ef-b240-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East. Campaign chaos. Trump suspect. Shutdown deal. Photo hack. WNBA. Travel benefits. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1f451e0-799a-11ef-9a99-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benny Golson dies at 95. The jazz saxophonist was known for his grace, warmth and technical virtuosity.</title>
      <description>Golson was the composer of such elegant jazz standards as “I Remember Clifford,” “Along Came Betty” and “Whisper Not.” He died Sept. 21 at his home in Manhattan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9aeab123-793e-11ef-9ecb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 23:58:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the Taliban starts restricting men, too, some regret not speaking up sooner</title>
      <description>Besides imposing severe rules on women, new laws require men to grow fist-length beards and bar them from imitating non-Muslims in appearance or behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d6b9120-792e-11ef-b635-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 22:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not ready for a knee replacement? You might be able to fix your cartilage instead.</title>
      <description>New techniques include a pellet made of coral and hydrogels that can help alleviate pain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df69c1f0-791c-11ef-98d0-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 19:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s how much water ChatGPT uses to help you write an email</title>
      <description>AI needs a lot of electricity and water to stay cool in data centers. We break down the toll, prompt by prompt, to show the scale of AI’s environmental needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b494910-790f-11ef-9fac-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Sep 2024 18:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
