<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 20:03:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-assistant principal indicted in high-profile shooting of teacher by 6-year-old student at Virginia’s Richneck Elementary School</title>
      <description>The former assistant principal, Ebony Parker, had been accused in the past of failing to do anything after being warned the boy had a gun. A special grand jury empaneled to investigate the matter is expected to release a report Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a3763c0-f69a-11ee-82cd-0000a1ace1c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Arizona Supreme Court clears way for near-total abortion ban, invoking 1864 law that forbids procedure except to save mother’s life</title>
      <description>The ruling said the law will not be enforced for 14 days. It superceded the previous law, which mandated the right to end a pregnancy by the 15-week mark, resetting policy to the pre-Roe v. Wade era.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c72c710-f695-11ee-ab09-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 17:19:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents of Oxford, Mich., school shooter sentenced to 10 to 15 years each for involuntary manslaughter</title>
      <description>James and Jennifer Crumbley were convicted in the school shooting committed by their son Ethan Crumbley after a landmark approach by prosecutors. They were accused of failing to secure a gun in their home and ignoring his pleas for help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac1bca50-f690-11ee-870a-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:46:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife is constantly looking for evidence of spouse’s infidelity</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife is constantly looking for evidence of spouse’s infidelity</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f148a51-f68a-11ee-a8c8-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 16:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which of Trump’s lies stick? Republicans believe some falsehoods more than they did six years ago, our poll finds.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Schar School Fact Checker poll finds that most Americans, including Republicans, do not believe many of Donald Trump’s most repeated claims. But he has made significant inroads in convincing Republicans that his lies are the truth. That applies to election integrity especially — the basis of Trump’s “big lie.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">334abb50-f67b-11ee-b14e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 14:12:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An undefeated season in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56aba4c0-f675-11ee-a8c8-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar eclipse. Student debt. Abortion politics. Tesla settlement. Jonathan Majors. Pregnancy effects. March Madness. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b244120-f660-11ee-ba56-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 11:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut beats Purdue to win NCAA men’s basketball championship for second consecutive year</title>
      <description>The Huskies completed a dominant NCAA tournament run Monday night in Glendale, Ariz., to become the first back-to-back men’s champion since Florida in 2006 and 2007. The Boilermakers were seeking their first national championship, a year after they lost to a No. 16 seed in the round of 64.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e22ce210-f621-11ee-9353-000a1ace5bbd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 03:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have eclipse FOMO? Want to relive it? Here are the most stunning highlights.</title>
      <description>There were scientific experiments, tourist events and religious ceremonies as Americans took in the awe-inspiring view of the last coast-to-coast total solar eclipse until 2045.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f999650-f609-11ee-a5e8-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 00:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla settles case over fatal 2018 crash of an Apple engineer</title>
      <description>The case involves a fatal crash in March 2018, when a Tesla in Autopilot careened into a highway barrier near Mountain View, Calif., after getting confused by what the company’s lawyers described in court documents as a “faded and nearly obliterated” lane line. Details of the settlement were not disclosed, according to court documents released Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99201a20-f5f3-11ee-aa03-0000a1ace134</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 22:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The leaders of Egypt, France and Jordan call for a cease-fire in Gaza. A two-state solution would bring peace, they write.</title>
      <description>The war in Gaza and the catastrophic humanitarian suffering it is causing must end now. Violence, terror and war cannot bring peace to the Middle East. The two-state solution will.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4789c071-f5e5-11ee-b1d3-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 20:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Follow along as the moon plunges a swath of North America into darkness in a rare celestial phenomenon</title>
      <description>Not since 2017 has the United States experienced a total solar eclipse, and we won’t see another sweep across the nation until 2045. Washington Post staff members are scattered across the map today, some in the path of totality, to capture what the expected millions of astral enthusiasts will experience as the moon passes between the sun and Earth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cdcd060-f5cd-11ee-b48c-0000a1aced16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 17:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Cancer patient hopes to limit texts and calls after surgery</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Cancer patient hopes to limit texts and calls after surgery</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e1ce430-f5c3-11ee-9fe7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 16:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trolls directed by Russia stoke anti-Ukraine sentiment in the U.S., leaked Kremlin documents show</title>
      <description>In an ongoing campaign, Russian political strategists and trolls have written thousands of fabricated articles and social media posts that promote American isolationism, according to a trove of Kremlin documents obtained by a European intelligence agency and reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">efc07431-f5bf-11ee-be91-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 15:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Jonathan Majors avoids jail time in his sentencing for assault and harassment of ex-girlfriend Grace Jabbari</title>
      <description>Majors’s conviction last year cost him high-profile roles with Marvel and Disney. He was sentenced to counseling programs and time served on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9d2dfb0-f5b5-11ee-b1fd-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out the cloud forecast for your area as the solar eclipse sweeps across the U.S.</title>
      <description>New England remains the sunniest spot for today’s eclipse, while the cloud forecast has somewhat improved for the Dallas area. Find out where it will be sunniest, cloudiest or somewhere in between.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5962a3f0-f5b0-11ee-97d3-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 14:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A classic goes electric in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dec1960-f5ac-11ee-a12c-0000a1ace3c8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 13:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says abortion should be left to states after months of mixed signals</title>
      <description>In a video posted on social media, Trump took credit for the overturn of Roe v. Wade and said that it's "now up to the states to do the right thing." For months, the former president has wavered between highlighting and downplaying his role in curtailing abortion rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2e05ff0-f599-11ee-829b-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar eclipse. Trump gag order. Gaza war. Online privacy. Covid cases. March Madness. Trash thief. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">265b2b80-f597-11ee-8046-000a1acedf48</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What not to do to when watching the solar eclipse tomorrow</title>
      <description>Can I make eclipse glasses at home? Can I view the eclipse through a camera? The best practices for observing a solar eclipse are really not that complicated, but these events are so rare for most people that it is easy to forget the basics. Our solar safety tips can help.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a6b0d90-f52b-11ee-9c9f-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 22:10:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina beats Iowa to win NCAA women’s basketball championship and complete an undefeated season</title>
      <description>The Gamecocks (38-0) defeated record-setting guard Caitlin Clark and the Hawkeyes in Cleveland on Sunday to win their third national championship and become the 10th undefeated national champion in the sport’s history.
Clark’s college career ends with a loss in the national final for the second consecutive year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8379c480-f523-11ee-8da1-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 21:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lawmakers unveil sprawling proposal to expand U.S. privacy protections. Here’s what’s in it.</title>
      <description>Unveiled by two top lawmakers, the bipartisan bill would force companies to limit how much personal information they collect from consumers, a major breakthrough in the decades-long fight to pass online privacy protections. The measure, reviewed by The Washington Post, would set a national baseline for how a broad swath of companies can collect, use and transfer data on the internet. It also would give users the right to opt out of certain data practices, including targeted advertising. Despite Sunday’s announcement, the proposal faces uncertain prospects as no comprehensive privacy bill has ever cleared a chamber of Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dad2ce20-f519-11ee-a2e3-0000a1ace875</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 20:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Couldn’t make it to the path of totality? Here’s how to watch tomorrow’s partial eclipse locally.</title>
      <description>The D.C. area will experience a partial solar eclipse Monday from 2:04 to 4:32 p.m., peaking at 3:20 p.m. Here’s information on what will happen, the weather forecast and recommended viewing places.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b35b0da0-f503-11ee-aa41-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 17:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a6bdca0-f4f8-11ee-9cfd-0000a1ace001</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 16:04:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s latest doctor vouching for his health: A member of his Bedminster golf club</title>
      <description>As former president Donald Trump assails President Biden’s condition, his only medical disclosure is a brief letter from a doctor with little national profile. Bruce Aronwald, a New Jersey osteopathic physician, is also an active member of Trump’s nearby Bedminster golf club. Aronwald’s assessment doesn’t include key details, such as Trump’s blood pressure, medications or weight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a0f970-f4f1-11ee-b365-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 15:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">377fa5d0-f4e3-11ee-8752-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 13:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut will face Purdue for NCAA men’s basketball championship after top seeds hold serve in Final Four</title>
      <description>Defending national champion U-Conn. beat Alabama on Saturday night in Glendale, Ariz., after Purdue defeated North Carolina State.
On Monday, the Huskies will seek to become the first back-to-back men’s champion since Florida in 2006 and 2007, while Purdue will play for its first national title after losing in the round of 64 to No. 16 seed Fairleigh Dickinson last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65bd5612-f48c-11ee-bcff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 03:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals pitcher Stephen Strasburg, MVP of the 2019 World Series, has retired, according to MLB</title>
      <description>Strasburg, whose retirement was long expected, did not announce his decision to step away from the game, nor did the Nationals. Instead, it was posted on MLB’s transactions log Saturday. The No. 1 overall pick in the 2009 draft, Strasburg began his career with tremendous hype but was ultimately derailed by injury.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6dd2c0-f473-11ee-af4f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 00:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No eclipse glasses? Here are old school ways to watch Monday’s eclipse.</title>
      <description>Special eclipse glasses are the best way to safely watch Monday’s solar eclipse across the contiguous United States. But if you don’t have glasses, here are several low-tech ways to see and enjoy the eclipse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dd2b380-f44a-11ee-8338-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 19:16:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Montana GOP Senate candidate says he lied to park ranger about gunshot wound in 2015</title>
      <description>Tim Sheehy was cited for illegally discharging a weapon in a national park but says he made up the gunshot to cover up a bullet wound he received as a Navy SEAL in Afghanistan that he never reported to superiors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e06d960-f43d-11ee-910b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 17:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My son’s 5-month relationship ended 3 years ago. He’s still reeling.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My son’s 5-month relationship ended 3 years ago. He’s still reeling.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">000bc410-f431-11ee-8900-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 16:16:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As the war in Ukraine worsens and Russia advances on battlefield, Zelensky faces terrible options</title>
      <description>Short of soldiers, weapons and ammunition, Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky has no way out of a worsening war — unable to advance militarily and unwilling to surrender occupied territory to Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">078725e0-f42c-11ee-b8e0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 15:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She failed to terminate her unwanted pregnancy. It changed another woman’s life.</title>
      <description>Evelyn desperately tried to terminate her pregnancy in three states before ultimately choosing adoption. Would a long-planned reunion with her 1-year-old offer the healing she needed?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aecbe770-f425-11ee-ac84-000a1acef853</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 14:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb559bc0-f419-11ee-a052-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa beats Connecticut in women’s Final Four, will face South Carolina for national championship</title>
      <description>The Hawkeyes, led by record-setting guard Caitlin Clark, reached the national final for the second consecutive year after beating the Huskies on Friday night in Cleveland.
Earlier in the evening, South Carolina remained undefeated and secured its spot in Sunday’s final with a victory over North Carolina State.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d537c460-f3c6-11ee-9ee8-0000a1ace78d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 03:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House and Senate leaders are nearing agreement on a landmark bill aimed at protecting Americans’ privacy online</title>
      <description>The expected deal would vault Congress closer to a historic agreement lawmakers have sought for decades. It would create a mechanism to allow individuals to sue companies that violate their privacy, among other provisions, according to a person familiar with the negotiations who spoke on the condition of anonymity. Further details are expected to be announced next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26fd28b0-f3a6-11ee-81bf-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 23:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See what the solar eclipse will look like in your city</title>
      <description>Whether you see a total or partial eclipse all depends on where you are. The difference is enormous.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7365880-f38f-11ee-ba2d-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 21:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The nation’s largest assisted-living chain uses a staffing algorithm; some managers say it left facilities dangerously short-handed</title>
      <description>Brookdale Senior Living, the leading operator of senior homes with 652 facilities, acquired the algorithm-based system and used it to set staffing at its properties across the nation. But as Brookdale’s empire grew, employees complained the system, known as “Service Alignment,” failed to capture the nuances of caring for vulnerable seniors, documents and interviews show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baa2f290-f36d-11ee-a1d1-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: How do I ask my wife for an open marriage?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: How do I ask my wife for an open marriage?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c239f80-f369-11ee-9242-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 16:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4.7-magnitude earthquake hits New York City area, according to USGS</title>
      <description>The small quake was centered in suburban Lebanon, N.J., according to the United States Geological Survey. Social media users reported feeling it from New England to Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4586710-f35b-11ee-aefd-0000a1ace909</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5350c70-f350-11ee-b016-0000a1ace334</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 13:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy added 303,000 jobs in March, reflecting a surprisingly booming labor market that continues to beat predictions</title>
      <description>The labor market continues to churn out jobs at a healthy pace, thanks in part to the leisure and hospitality sector, even as interest rates remain high, according to the latest data from the Bureau of Labor Statistics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfaf2160-f348-11ee-b807-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump case. Gaza aid. Airport security. ALS drug. Snowstorm. Final Four. Salmon crash. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a69b7510-f33b-11ee-a736-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli investigation finds the strike that killed seven World Central Kitchen aid workers was in ‘serious violation’ of procedures</title>
      <description>The Israeli Defense Forces said the decision to strike the vehicles was made in error and came after the IDF misidentified vehicles in the aid convoy as carrying Hamas operatives. It also found the IDF drone operators were not made aware of the aid convoy’s coordination plan, and the aid group’s logo was not visible to the cameras tracking the vehicles at night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91216911-f33b-11ee-8418-000a1ace137f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel announces new Gaza aid routes after Biden demands more humanitarian relief in call with Netanyahu</title>
      <description>Israel’s war cabinet announced new measures to allow more aid into Gaza, including the opening of the Erez border crossing, after a call between President Biden and Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu on Thursday morning. Biden warned that U.S. policy toward Israel could change if Israel did not take steps to protect noncombatants and boost aid to Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1429aa0-f2f0-11ee-96c3-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 02:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What starvation is doing to Gaza’s children</title>
      <description>Hundreds of thousands of children in Gaza are going hungry. Even if more aid arrives, experts say the damage will be lasting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd302970-f2d2-11ee-b755-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 22:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where, when and how to watch the solar eclipse — and what it will look like: Your ultimate guide</title>
      <description>On Monday, a total solar eclipse will sweep across North America, blocking out the sun momentarily for millions of viewers along a path stretching from northern Mexico to Maine. We won’t see another until 2044. Here’s everything you need to know to prepare for this rare celestial phenomenon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a24069b0-f2ca-11ee-85d9-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 21:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Cannon rejects Trump’s bid to dismiss classified documents case based on Presidential Records Act</title>
      <description>The ruling could avert a looming standoff between special counsel Jack Smith and Judge Aileen M. Cannon. It comes two days after Smith said the judge was pursuing a legal premise that was “wrong,” and urged her to rule quickly so that he would have the option of appealing before trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fcb36911-f2b6-11ee-b984-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Centrist group No Labels says it will not field a ticket in the 2024 presidential election</title>
      <description>The group said in a statement that it had not identified candidates “with a credible path to winning the White House” and that the “responsible course of action is for us to stand down.” Allies of President Biden sought to discourage the group from moving forward with a ticket they feared could help Donald Trump at the polls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d3511b1-f2b5-11ee-aec1-0000a1ace470</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. policy toward Israel will change unless it heeds Biden on Gaza aid and civilian protections, Blinken suggests</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken spoke to reporters following President Biden’s call with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu. The warning lacked specifics and came as the Biden administration continued to approve the transfer of thousands of bombs to Israel despite calls to condition aid in the aftermath of the Israeli airstrike that killed seven aid workers with the World Central Kitchen charity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">baccef30-f2b1-11ee-898b-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
