<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:02:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Senate passes Trump-backed election map</title>
      <description>In a quick, party-line 18-11 vote that took Democrats by surprise early Saturday, the Republican-controlled chamber approved the map, which aims to help the GOP hold its narrow U.S. House majority in the midterms by creating five new districts in areas Trump won by double digits in 2024. The plan now heads to Gov. Greg Abbott (R), who is expected to swiftly sign it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03e5a540-7fe7-11f0-96e1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyle Menendez, who killed his parents in their Beverly Hills home, is denied parole alongside his brother</title>
      <description>The denials are a setback in the campaign to release the brothers, who are serving life sentences for murdering their parents in 1989. The Menendez family has largely supported the siblings, who maintain that they carried out the slayings  in self-defense after suffering alleged physical and sexual abuse at the hands of their father.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98746c90-7fcf-11f0-96e1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilmar Abrego García is released in Tennessee, lawyer confirms, despite Trump administration’s insistence he should ‘never go free’</title>
      <description>The Maryland man illegally deported to El Salvador was released Friday as he awaits trial on human smuggling charges. Federal officials obeyed a pair of court orders to release Abrego García and allow him to return to Maryland. Immigration officials may seek to quickly deport him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932c0fa0-7f8d-11f0-a1ef-0000a1ace205</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ releases full transcript, audio from interview with Jeffrey Epstein associate Ghislaine Maxwell</title>
      <description>Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche conducted two days of interviews with Maxwell in Florida in July amid growing pressure on the Trump administration to release more information about Epstein, the wealthy sex offender. On Friday, Blanche said he was releasing the interview with Maxwell, who is serving a 20-year sentence for sex trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e38b1fa0-7f8c-11f0-8281-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel’s CEO has agreed to give the U.S. government $10 billion, Trump says</title>
      <description>The president equated the payment to 10% of the American chipmaker’s value, saying he told CEO Lip-Bu Tan that “it would be good having the United States as your partner” and that “they've agreed to do it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13534730-7f88-11f0-a1af-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center to host the 2026 World Cup draw in December, Trump announces</title>
      <description>The 2026 World Cup, set to begin in June, will be staged in the United States, Canada and Mexico. Washington will not host matches, but a draw at the Kennedy Center allows the District to join the festivities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cc8f11-7f80-11f0-9aca-0000a1ace061</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration purge of national security agencies widens with firing of DIA chief Lt. Gen. Jeffrey Kruse</title>
      <description>Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth’s sacking of Kruse, the director of the Defense Intelligence Agency, marks the latest removal of a senior military or intelligence officer in a wider purge of national security agencies’ top ranks, according to two people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae41fe21-7f7f-11f0-af09-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth authorizes National Guard to carry weapons in D.C. deployment</title>
      <description>The 2,000 National Guard members participating in the military deployment President Donald Trump has ordered in Washington, D.C., will “soon be on mission with their service-issued weapons,” the Pentagon said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">332274d0-7f76-11f0-92ae-0000a1ace614</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:36:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican National Committee elects Trump-backed Joe Gruters as chair</title>
      <description>The election of Gruters, a state senator in Florida, ensures that another loyalist of President Donald Trump remains at the helm of the RNC heading into the midterms. 

Gruters succeeds Michael Whatley, who stepped down to run for a U.S. Senate seat in North Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68edc0a0-7f6d-11f0-8310-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump seeks $2 billion to beautify D.C. in latest effort to control city affairs</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump, a longtime real estate developer, has falsely claimed he has solved the city’s crime problems. Now he seeks to transform Washington into a place reminiscent of his private golf clubs. 

It is unclear how likely Congress is to grant the funds or whether city leaders will support the effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2907df70-7f6d-11f0-bd1e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department finds George Mason University improperly used race in hiring, seeks apology from president</title>
      <description>The department also has asked the Virginia university to conduct trainings and revise policy. The university did not immediately respond to the finding, which comes as the Trump administration has scrutinized universities across the country over diversity, equity and inclusion policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4a330e0-7f67-11f0-8310-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Howard University president to exit after two years; institution’s former leader to return as interim</title>
      <description>The departure of Ben Vinson III, who has led Howard since 2023, comes days into the start of the new academic year at the historically Black university in the nation’s capital. His final day will be Aug. 31. The interim leader will be former president Wayne A.I. Frederick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">664640f1-7f65-11f0-ac6a-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:36:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed’s Powell says changing economic factors ‘may warrant’ interest rate cuts, but doesn’t signal when</title>
      <description>The central bank chief said a softening labor market combined with continued inflation risks from tariffs and immigration policy made for a challenging environment. President Donald Trump has been pressuring the Fed to lower rates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6abdd71-7f60-11f0-92b1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c489f660-7f5c-11f0-a567-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI searches former Trump national security adviser John Bolton’s suburban Washington home</title>
      <description>A person familiar with the matter didn’t say what brought investigators to Bolton’s residence in Maryland. Bolton has emerged as a staunch critic of Donald Trump. Earlier this year, the president revoked Bolton’s security clearances and canceled his security detail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b79cd580-7f52-11f0-a50b-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visa vetting. Smithsonian exhibits. Trump ruling. Gaza famine. Menendez brothers. Hurricanes. Birdsong at night. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27cb3600-7f47-11f0-8902-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Famine confirmed in Gaza City region and is projected to spread within weeks, global hunger monitor says</title>
      <description>More than half a million people are facing catastrophic conditions “characterized by starvation, destitution and death,” according to the Integrated Food Security Phase Classification report.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">551b8e81-7f3c-11f0-b7b0-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 09:42:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Erik Menendez is not granted parole. He and his brother, who awaits his hearing, were convicted of killing their parents in 1989.</title>
      <description>Menendez had been sentenced to life in prison. A parole hearing for his brother, Lyle, is scheduled for Friday. The Menendez family has long claimed the Beverly Hills murders were in self-defense after abuse at the hands of the boys’ father, but prosecutors argued the shotgun slayings were conducted by the siblings for financial gain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">245f2940-7efc-11f0-b94e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Florida to dismantle Alligator Alcatraz immigrant detention facility in 60 days</title>
      <description>The order from U.S. District Judge Kathleen Williams hands environmentalists a major win after they clashed with Gov. Ron DeSantis and his administration over the impacts the site was having in the federally protected Everglades. It also deals a blow to what had become a marquee symbol of President Donald Trump’s immigration policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c2ba9d0-7efa-11f0-9750-00000a1ace07</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 01:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans ‘continuous vetting’ of all 55 million foreigners with legal U.S. visas</title>
      <description>The State Department says it intends to scour law enforcement, immigration records and social media for tens of millions of current U.S. visa holders, including for “overstays, criminal activity, threats to public safety … or providing support to a terrorist organization.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90d7ce60-7ee8-11f0-ae03-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House targets ‘woke’ Smithsonian content in new list that includes exhibitions on race, slavery, immigration and more</title>
      <description>The list comes two days after the president said he would send his attorneys through the museums, adding that the Smithsonian focused too much on “how bad Slavery was.” Some artists named in the list called it a badge of honor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">183902e0-7ee7-11f0-8239-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 23:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court clears way for nearly $800 million in cuts to grants for the National Institutes of Health</title>
      <description>The justices sided with the Trump administration, which argued that research on diseases in minority, gay and transgender communities was unscientific and went against the president’s efforts to eliminate initiatives related to diversity, equity and inclusion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">343042f0-7ed4-11f0-a048-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 21:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge rules Alina Habba, Trump’s pick for U.S. attorney in New Jersey, is not serving lawfully</title>
      <description>The decision means Habba must be disqualified from participating in ongoing cases. But the judge paused his decision to give the Justice Department a chance to appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a461f770-7ecb-11f0-8925-0000a1ace34d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 20:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California House Democrats push through redistricting plan to counteract Texas GOP ahead of 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>The California Democrats’ measure to create a new ballot question is one of three redistricting bills that are expected to pass in the state Senate and House, then reach Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) for his signature today. State voters must then decide in November on a plan that would create five new Democratic-leaning congressional districts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ac6e050-7ec5-11f0-b3f6-0000a1ace80b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 19:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will patrol D.C. streets tonight alongside law enforcement officials</title>
      <description>“I’m going to be going out tonight with the police and with the military," President Donald Trump said in an interview aired with talk show host Todd Starnes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c02ab900-7eae-11f0-9e52-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Physical 5-year-old roughhouses right through parental warnings</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Physical 5-year-old roughhouses right through parental warnings</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97b28530-7ea8-11f0-965b-0000a1acedc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court voids $500 million fine in N.Y. civil case against Trump but upholds fraud finding</title>
      <description>In February, New York Attorney General Letitia James won a history-making civil case against President Donald Trump, his company, two of his children and two former executives when a state court judge determined that they collectively committed a long-running fraud. On Thursday, the state appeals court called the nearly $500 million fine “excessive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e51c46d0-7ea3-11f0-b4b1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Justice Department employee threw a sub at a federal agent and was fired. Now ‘Sandwich Guy’ is a resistance icon.</title>
      <description>Sandwich Guy’s real name is Sean Charles Dunn, a D.C. resident who was captured on video hurling a footlong at a federal officer and now faces a felony charge. His likeness has popped up around the city in protest art and in online memes. And, yes, you can buy a shirt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c2cb8d0-7ea0-11f0-a8f0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evangelical leader James Dobson dies at 89. He fueled the rise of the religious right through his group Focus on the Family.</title>
      <description>Dobson, a child psychologist, built a national following with his talk radio empire and nonprofit, Focus on the Family. He attracted an estimated 7 million weekly listeners and marshaled support for President Ronald Reagan’s election in 1980.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df68f8a0-7e99-11f0-b058-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:19:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This South American country is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47d6ff10-7e93-11f0-93b9-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S and E.U. release details of trade pact that would keep tariffs high on European vehicles and lower semiconductor tariffs</title>
      <description>A joint statement confirmed that the United States will impose a 15 percent tariff on most European products. The U.S. has now agreed to lower its 25 percent tariff on imported cars to 15 percent for European vehicles once the European Union introduces legislation to eliminate its already-low tariffs on American industrial products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af920600-7e88-11f0-b773-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine-Russia. ICE in D.C. Voting maps. Transgender patients. Beef prices. Reading slump. Windowless window seats. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f943fe80-7e7d-11f0-9922-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. subpoenas sought addresses, doctors’ notes, text messages on care for transgender minors</title>
      <description>The unusual demand for detailed information about patients suggests the Trump administration wants to launch civil or criminal investigations of medical providers in states where gender transition care for minors remains legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b151cd20-7e35-11f0-a1b7-000a1ace433b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 02:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas House approves election map favored by Trump after Democrats return to state, moving it closer to final passage</title>
      <description>The Republican-controlled chamber passed the map, which would create five new congressional districts in areas President Donald Trump won by double digits in 2024 and set off a nationwide partisan fight over redistricting. The state Senate is expected to pass it as soon as this week and send it to Gov. Greg Abbott (R) for his signature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b5fc990-7e1d-11f0-a15d-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 23:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Department drops long-standing guidance that directed schools to accommodate students who are not fluent in English</title>
      <description>The move is an acceleration of President Donald Trump’s executive order declaring English the country’s “official language.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46219940-7e17-11f0-9fae-0000a1ace9c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department fires top press officer for Israeli-Palestinian affairs after internal debates over Middle East policies</title>
      <description>Shahed Ghoreishi recommended expressing condolences for slain journalists in Gaza and opposing the forced displacement of Palestinians, according to documents reviewed by The Washington Post. U.S. officials said the firing sent a chilling message to State Department employees that communication straying from ardent pro-Israel messaging — even if it’s in line with long-standing U.S. policy — will not be tolerated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04d5d8c0-7e12-11f0-8173-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 22:07:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why so few Americans read for pleasure, according to a new study</title>
      <description>Only 16 percent of Americans age 15 and over read for leisure every day in 2023, according to a study published Wednesday in the journal iScience, compared with 28 percent of Americans in 2003. The new findings from researchers at the University of Florida and University College London come as Americans’ attention spans and print book sales are in decline, and artificial intelligence technology is aiming to summarize knowledge as quickly as possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0624bc0-7e08-11f0-8d0a-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 20:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third federal judge rejects DOJ’s request to unseal Epstein grand jury transcripts, saying public interest doesn’t outweigh secrecy</title>
      <description>The Justice Department asked three different federal judges to release transcripts related to the investigation. And U.S. District Judge Richard Berman, who has been overseeing the legal proceedings of the Jeffrey Epstein case in New York, is the third judge to reject the request.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f72a7950-7df9-11f0-a7d4-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:14:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s happening: People are starting to talk like ChatGPT</title>
      <description>It’s happening: People are starting to talk like ChatGPT</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">844d7590-7def-11f0-9340-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Tell busybody sister about diagnosis that could affect her, too?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Tell busybody sister about diagnosis that could affect her, too?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4faaa90-7dde-11f0-af4b-0000a1ace596</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls for resignation of Federal Reserve governor Lisa Cook in his latest effort to bend the U.S. central bank to his will</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump issued the call after Bill Pulte, director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency, accused Cook of mortgage fraud and asked the Justice Department to investigate her. In targeting Cook, Trump appears to be looking to open up more vacancies on the Fed board, accelerating the point at which Trump-aligned governors could hold a majority.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b8fef11-7dd4-11f0-ab79-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These places will be hit by big waves and coastal flooding as Hurricane Erin passes</title>
      <description>A dozen eastern states are under weather alerts as the storm makes its closest approach to the United States starting today. Erin’s massive wind field brings risks of dangerous surf and possible flooding to coastal communities, even as the storm passes hundreds of miles offshore. See whether your region might be impacted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c699f980-7dce-11f0-abed-0000a1acec61</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:05:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new name in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93a36470-7dca-11f0-8e75-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most D.C. residents strongly oppose Trump’s takeover of city police, Post-Schar School poll finds</title>
      <description>Washington, D.C., residents overwhelmingly oppose President Donald Trump’s decision last week to take over the D.C. police and order federal law enforcement and the National Guard onto District streets, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll. And 65 percent don’t think his actions will make the District safer from violent crime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98ea1de0-7dc3-11f0-b73c-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s unusually large personal security requirements are straining the Army agency charged with protecting him</title>
      <description>The Army Criminal Investigation Division, which fields security for top Defense Department officials, has had to pull agents off criminal investigations to staff weeks-long assignments guarding family homes in Minnesota, Tennessee and D.C., according to numerous officials familiar with the operation. The assignments have at times extended to residences belonging to Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s former spouses, the officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a54a7c0-7db9-11f0-a29d-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Pete Hegseth. Jeanine Pirro. Voting maps. English learners. Hurricane Erin. Good life. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d899d1b0-7db4-11f0-89c7-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C’s top prosecutor says her office will no longer pursue gun charges for people carrying rifles, shotguns</title>
      <description>U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro said the new policy was crafted by the Justice Department and its solicitor general. The shift comes as the Trump administration ramps up federal law enforcement to unprecedented levels in D.C. and complicates the White House’s boasts of seizing guns as part of the crackdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18ed9e41-7d65-11f0-9f85-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 01:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jeanine Pirro boasted of working to help Trump and GOP while at Fox News, unredacted documents show</title>
      <description>Court filings from voting technology company Smartmatic in its $2.7 billion defamation suit against Fox News include previously unreported text messages and emails between the network’s employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d2cd2f0-7d5c-11f0-a5bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The city is dead’: As Restaurant Week arrives in D.C., owners see a decline in reservations amid takeover of city’s police force</title>
      <description>Business owners are concerned that the continued surge in law enforcement could affect their revenue during a vital period of the summer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55fd19d0-7d58-11f0-8dc3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. probes whether D.C. police manipulated data to make crime rates appear lower, escalating tensions between Trump, city</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump confirmed the investigation on social media, saying the city is “under serious investigation.” D.C. government officials have questioned the unprecedented federal takeover of local police, repeatedly citing department statistics showing violent crime down 27 percent from a year ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8783870-7d1c-11f0-a07e-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
