<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 07:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>A day before Sonya Massey was killed by a deputy, her mother called 911: ‘I don’t want you guys to hurt her’</title>
      <description>Massey’s mother said her daughter was having a mental breakdown and implored law enforcement officers not to harm her, newly released 911 recordings show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">055a17c0-4fb5-11ef-9f67-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 03:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris responds to Trump’s attacks on her racial identity: ‘The same old show’ of ‘divisiveness and disrespect.’</title>
      <description>“Let me just say: The American people deserve better. The American people deserve better,” Vice President Harris said at a historically Black sorority event.
Former president Donald Trump said earlier Wednesday that he had been aware of Harris’s Indian heritage but didn’t know she was Black “until a number of years ago when she happened to turn Black.” “And now she wants to be known as Black,” Trump added, questioning Harris’s identity during a combative question-and-answer session at the National Association of Black Journalists convention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d42a48b1-4f9f-11ef-8e19-0000a1ace0d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 00:48:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accused 9/11 plotter Khalid Sheikh Mohammed reaches plea deal with U.S. to avoid death penalty</title>
      <description>The agreement with Mohammed and two others charged in the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks on the United States was approved by a senior U.S. defense official overseeing their cases at the U.S. military detention facility in Guantanamo Bay. A panel of military officials eventually will determine the men’s sentences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0825da60-4f93-11ef-8c56-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 23:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 5 highlights from Paris Olympics: Leon Marchand, Pan Zhanle make swimming history and U.S. men’s basketball wins big</title>
      <description>Marchand, the 22-year-old French phenom, became the first swimmer to win both the 200-meter butterfly and the 200 breaststroke at the same Games. China’s Pan shattered his own world record in the 100 freestyle. U.S. star Katie Ledecky continued her dominance in the 1,500 freestyle, setting an Olympic record and winning her first gold in Paris. In men's basketball, LeBron James and Bam Adebayo powered the Americans to a win over South Sudan. The Spanish duo of Rafael Nadal and Carlos Alcaraz saw their doubles run end in the tennis quarterfinals at Roland Garros.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fc55460-4f8c-11ef-911d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 22:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another brutal heat wave is cranking up in the D.C. region, and it could last a week</title>
      <description>The National Weather Service has issued a heat advisory for Thursday afternoon, when it could feel like 107 degrees, factoring in the humidity. This latest heat wave begins amid the District's second hottest summer on record to date.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c90b7d00-4f86-11ef-bb08-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 21:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Katie Ledecky wins 1,500-meter freestyle, tying records for most Olympic medals and gold medals by a female swimmer</title>
      <description>It was Ledecky's first gold medal of the Paris Games. She’ll have a chance to break both records Thursday when the Americans swim the 4x200 freestyle relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd1ecb40-4f73-11ef-939c-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:33:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Harris ‘wants to be known as Black,’ questioning her identity in his remarks at a convention of Black journalists</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump said he had been aware of Vice President Harris’s Indian heritage but didn’t know she was Black “until a number of years ago when she happened to turn Black.”

Trump claimed Harris used to only promote her Indian heritage — even though, as a moderator pointed out, she was part of a historically Black sorority and embraced her Black identity in many ways. “And now she wants to be known as Black,” Trump said during a very combative question-and-answer session at the National Association of Black Journalists convention in Chicago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0c84ee0-4f72-11ef-953a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 19:27:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed leaves interest rates unchanged but inches closer to long-awaited cut</title>
      <description>Central bankers have kept borrowing costs at the highest level in more than 20 years to stifle inflation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d939b1-4f66-11ef-953a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 18:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says ‘crushing blows’ dealt to Hezbollah and Hamas, but stops short of claiming responsibility for Hamas leader’s death</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu said in a televised address that Israel was in a fight against Iranian-backed groups in the region, including Hamas, Hezbollah in Lebanon and the Houthi movement in Yemen. “In the last few days, we have struck crushing blows on each of them,” he said, but without taking responsibility for the killing Wednesday of Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh in Tehran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97357950-4f65-11ef-9af1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norma Padgett dies at 92. Her rape accusation in ‘Groveland Four’ case led to a gross miscarriage of justice in the Jim Crow South.</title>
      <description>The four Black men she accused of rape in Florida in 1949 were exonerated seven decades later. Two had been killed, and two spent years in prison. She refused to publicly recant her story.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ba719c0-4f63-11ef-bdd9-0000a1ace011</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 17:36:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After a scare with their first baby, husband says no to a second</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After a scare with their first baby, husband says no to a second</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d52a810-4f56-11ef-939c-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 16:03:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: A server blocked me from using the inside restroom when I was seated outside</title>
      <description>Dining chat: A server blocked me from using the inside restroom when I was seated outside</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1440e530-4f50-11ef-9395-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 15:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s all coming back to the Eiffel Tower in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea481af0-4f40-11ef-b052-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 13:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas leader. Harris rally. Project 2025. Venezuela protests. Suicide rates. Heat wave. Simone Biles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08ccf5a0-4f2c-11ef-83e1-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas leader Ismail Haniyeh was killed in Tehran, the group says in statement</title>
      <description>Haniyeh, the head of Hamas’s political bureau, was killed in the Iranian capital after participating in the inauguration of Iran’s new president, Hamas said in a statement. It was unclear how Haniyeh was killed. He led Hamas in the Gaza Strip for over a decade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf8b3570-4eec-11ef-92fe-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 03:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 4 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. women’s rugby wins its first medal and tennis star Coco Gauff falls in contentious loss</title>
      <description>The U.S. women's rugby sevens team beat Australia at the buzzer in a dramatic bronze medal game. Earlier, Gauff lost to Croatia’s Donna Vekic in women’s singles tennis after a tearful argument over a questionable call. In other highlights, Simone Biles and the U.S. women's gymnastics team won gold, the U.S. men's soccer team advanced to the Olympic quarterfinals for the first time in 24 years, and Australian swimmer Kaylee McKeown edged American rival Regan Smith for 100-meter backstroke gold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17f0c5b1-4ebf-11ef-a0d3-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 22:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have babies for Russia: Putin presses women to embrace patriotism over feminism</title>
      <description>Facing his country’s demographic decline and a war in Ukraine that is killing and wounding many men, the Russian president is urging women to adopt traditional roles and serve the nation by giving birth young and often, and by raising their children to be patriots. Critics say the policy is rolling back rights and protections, including against domestic violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9de5f900-4ebb-11ef-9132-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 21:35:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 2025 to end policy work, as attacks on the right-wing group spurred backlash from Trump. Its director is also departing.</title>
      <description>The right-wing policy operation that became a rallying cry for Democrats and a nuisance for Republican nominee Donald Trump is winding down its policy operations, and its director, former Trump administration personnel official Paul Dans, is departing. The Heritage Foundation also recently distributed new talking points encouraging participants to emphasize that the project does not speak for Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd1c5060-4ea7-11ef-806c-0000a1ace702</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 19:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women capture Olympic gold in team gymnastics, redeeming Tokyo stumble</title>
      <description>Led by Simone Biles and Sunisa Lee, the women’s team held off Italy (silver) and Brazil (bronze) to win its third gold medal in the past four Olympics after it took silver at the Tokyo Games in 2021. It’s the Americans' ninth straight team medal. Biles and Lee will compete in the all-around competition on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4bbd67e0-4ea1-11ef-9e4d-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 18:26:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets Hezbollah commander near Beirut in response to deadly rocket strike over the weekend, military says</title>
      <description>The strike Tuesday night on the outskirts of the Lebanese capital followed warnings from Israel that it would retaliate for a rocket strike that killed 12 children and teenagers in the Israeli-occupied Golan Heights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16bdd8e0-4e9c-11ef-a227-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes landmark bills to protect kids online, raising pressure on House</title>
      <description>The pair of bills — the Kids Online Safety Act, or KOSA, and the Children and Teens’ Online Privacy Protection Act, referred to as COPPA 2.0 — would force digital platforms to take “reasonable” steps to prevent harms to children such as bullying, drug addiction and sexual exploitation, and would broaden existing federal privacy protections to include kids and teens 16 years old and younger. Proponents of the measures hope Senate passage will amplify calls for the package to be taken up in the House, where the bills have garnered bipartisan support but negotiations publicly unraveled last month amid infighting between House Republican leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">276caff0-4e96-11ef-b3d7-0000a1ace401</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 17:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simone Biles and the U.S. women are vying to reclaim gold in the Olympics team gymnastics final. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Led by Biles and defending all-around champion Sunisa Lee, the Americans are heavy favorites to win gold. The team has said it is seeking redemption for its 2021 stumble in Tokyo, where Biles withdrew from some events because of a disorienting mental block and the Americans took silver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c00e5e0-4e8e-11ef-9a2f-0000a1ace369</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband won’t admit that he prefers sleeping in separate bedrooms</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband won’t admit that he prefers sleeping in separate bedrooms</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f2bc3a0-4e8d-11ef-b6b8-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 16:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Details emerge from Trump rally about local officer’s shot and role it may have played before gunman was killed by Secret Service</title>
      <description>After a local officer fired at him, Thomas Matthew Crooks temporarily recoiled from his rooftop perch and did not shoot again before he was killed by a Secret Service countersniper, according to officials familiar with the investigation along with a Washington Post video analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce992b60-4e8b-11ef-a173-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 15:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landslides in southern India kill at least 99 people, officials say</title>
      <description>Dozens of others were injured or missing after heavy rains struck the state of Kerala during the height of monsoon season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae193c70-4e7e-11ef-913f-0000a1ace305</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 14:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stamp with a clue in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32dea9b0-4e78-11ef-8915-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 13:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris vs. Trump. Rally shooter. Venezuela protests. Gaza aid. Alzheimer’s test. Pommel horse. Northern lights. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da022572-4e62-11ef-b6b8-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convicted war criminal William Calley is dead at 80. He was the face of the My Lai massacre, one of the Army’s darkest chapters.</title>
      <description>Calley was the only person convicted in connection with the 1968 massacre, in which U.S. troops killed hundreds of unarmed South Vietnamese men, women and children. His death in April was not previously reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f1bdc50-4e04-11ef-83f5-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 23:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chinese migrants are illegally entering the U.S. from Mexico in record numbers, testing Biden and Xi</title>
      <description>U.S. authorities have encountered more than 55,000 Chinese migrants crossing illegally from Mexico during the past 18 months — up from 3,813 in 2022. It is the last stage of the journey known in Chinese as zouxian — “walking the line.” Driven in part by the stifling economic and political fallout of China’s extended covid-19 lockdowns, the Chinese arrivals have become a political and national security flash point in Washington.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5caa6ec0-4dfe-11ef-98a3-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 23:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 3 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. women's basketball opens with a rout and Summer McIntosh coasts to swimming gold</title>
      <description>McIntosh, a 17-year-old Canadian star, won the women's 400-meter individual medley in dominant fashion. Elsewhere, the U.S. women’s basketball team opened group play with a blowout of Japan, Novak Djokovic defeated Rafael Nadal in the second round of the men’s tennis singles tournament, and the U.S. men earned their first medal in the gymnastics team event since 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5190b180-4df8-11ef-ae75-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 22:17:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gymnast Stephen Nedoroscik is at the Olympics for one reason: Pommel horse. Today, he became both a medalist and viral star.</title>
      <description>Pommel horse is an apparatus so fickle that one misstep can derail an athlete’s rhythm and send the routine into disarray. And in the waning moments of Monday’s final, Nedoroscik had to deliver for the United States to clinch its first Olympic team medal since 2008. He leaped onto the apparatus and began swinging, floating through each element and maneuvering his hands with precision. His teammates watched with their arms around one another, and as soon as he dismounted, the celebration began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbbf2c0-4de5-11ef-a7fe-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 20:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 2 children dead and 6 in critical condition after mass stabbing in English seaside town</title>
      <description>Police detained a teenage boy with a knife Monday in the attack that killed two and injured another nine children and two adults in Southport in North West England.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">500583d0-4ddb-11ef-ae92-0000a1ace580</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:49:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. men win bronze in the gymnastics team competition. It’s the Americans’ first Olympic medal in the event since 2008.</title>
      <description>Over the past three years, the U.S. gymnasts have aggressively pushed to increase the difficulty of their routines after a disappointing output in Tokyo. Japan earned the gold medal while China took home silver Monday in Paris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">332dbbb0-4dd6-11ef-9b2a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 18:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Type A parent wants to tell chronically late partner to be on time</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Type A parent wants to tell chronically late partner to be on time</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccfd2b81-4dc3-11ef-ae93-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 16:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An enthusiastic phone call in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b07a0650-4dae-11ef-a343-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 13:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro claims victory in Venezuelan election; several countries, including U.S., cast doubt</title>
      <description>President Nicolás Maduro’s electoral council declared him the winner of Sunday's election, though his opponent, Edmundo González, also claimed victory. Multiple world leaders called for transparency over how votes were counted, while Russia, China and Cuba congratulated Maduro.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b899a2f1-4d9f-11ef-84e2-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:43:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In an op-ed, Biden calls for ‘three bold reforms’ to restore trust in the Supreme Court and American democracy</title>
      <description>President Biden pushes for term limits and a code of conduct for the Supreme Court, and a constitutional amendment making clear there is no immunity for crimes a former president committed while in office. Read his op-ed in The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9567570-4d9a-11ef-a8a5-0000a1acec72</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Election countdown. Supreme Court. Israel. Venezuela’s disputed vote. Park Fire. Simone Biles. Chimp language. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4262af0-4d99-11ef-a24f-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Nicolás Maduro’s electoral council declared him the winner of Venezuela’s election</title>
      <description>Maduro’s electoral council claimed the authoritarian socialist won the hard-fought contest Sunday despite independent exit polling that suggested challenger Edmundo González captured twice as many votes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c486ea30-4d60-11ef-9394-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 04:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simone Biles advances to gymnastics all-around final and Torri Huske leads U.S. swimming's medal haul on Day 2 at Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>The Americans cruised into the women's gymnastics team final, with Biles and Sunisa Lee earning spots in the all-around final. Huske edged teammate Gretchen Walsh for a gold-silver finish in the women's 100-meter butterfly, and French star Leon Marchand set an Olympic record in the men's 400 individual medley. Elsewhere, the U.S. men's basketball and women's soccer teams won in group play, and two Americans featured in the women's fencing individual foil final.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4db870-4d2a-11ef-bc08-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 21:45:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kamala Harris took control of the Democratic Party</title>
      <description>In the hours and days after President Biden's departure from the race, party officials and campaign aides raced to flip an entire brand from fading hope to salute emojis. What resulted was a flash-bang midsummer swap at the top of the presidential ticket, an outpouring of volunteer energy, a rebound in the polls and a flood of hundreds of millions of dollars in donations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cf69fc0-4d23-11ef-94ab-0000a1ace713</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 20:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usha Vance once told friends Trump appalled her. Now, with her husband on his ticket, she’s working to elect him.</title>
      <description>Usha Vance rarely expressed her political views while rising through prestigious law schools and clerkships — but she expressed revulsion to her friends about president Donald Trump’s actions amid the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol. Some of those friends watched in disbelief earlier this month as she addressed a Republican National Convention crowd in support of Trump and his running mate: her husband, JD Vance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3729b271-4d1b-11ef-853d-0000a1ace6d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 19:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edna O’Brien dies at 93. The groundbreaking Irish writer of ‘The Country Girls’ captured women’s struggles in a male-dominated world.</title>
      <description>The book, which was banned in Ireland, made O’Brien a literary sensation and propelled her into the Swinging Sixties cultural whir.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37255230-4d06-11ef-8134-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 17:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a532550-4cfa-11ef-9394-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sanctions crushed this brutal regime’s elite. So they built a zombie economy fueled by drugs.</title>
      <description>A stimulant called Captagon has become the fabulously profitable core of Syria’s economy and helped the country’s political and military elite cling to power. The illicit pills, manufactured in Syrian factories and sold across the Middle East, are generating an estimated $10 billion a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">481a1ba0-4cef-11ef-a227-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 14:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c225e30-4ce7-11ef-850e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 13:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caeleb Dressel anchors relay to first U.S. gold and Katie Ledecky takes bronze in 'race of the century' on Day 1 at Paris Olympics</title>
      <description>The Summer Games are underway in Paris. The United States claimed its first gold medal in the men's 4x100-meter freestyle swimming relay, powered by Dressel in the final leg. Ledecky earned her first medal in Paris with bronze in the women's 400 freestyle, and NBA sensation Victor Wembanyama shined in his Olympic debut for host France.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e6451f0-4c64-11ef-9d2b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 22:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who do you think Harris’s VP pick should be? Choose what her ticket needs, and we’ll tell you who fits the bill.</title>
      <description>We have a sense of the contenders for Kamala D. Harris’s running mate, considerations in choosing one of them, and their strengths and weaknesses as candidates. Now, this is where you come in: Take our quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d162b41-4c5d-11ef-bfe6-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 21:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My brother stopped talking to me after a heated political discussion</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My brother stopped talking to me after a heated political discussion</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e2c36a0-4c32-11ef-a191-000a1acef43f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 16:06:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance’s ‘Hillbilly Elegy’ echoes truths about Kentucky. But many locals question his theories about the White working class.</title>
      <description>Vance’s bestseller turned movie recounts the summers he spent with his grandmother in Jackson, Ky., the distressed Appalachian town of his ancestors. Numerous friends and neighbors there who are close to his family said they don’t doubt that his stories are broadly true. What many take issue with, though, are Vance’s conclusions about the root causes of the area’s poverty and violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee1f0a40-4c24-11ef-8ac9-0000a1aceb30</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jul 2024 14:31:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
