<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 13:11:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>ICE ads. East Wing photos. Kennedy Center. Vaccination rates. Tatiana Schlossberg. Women’s health. In and out list. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33253fe0-e640-11f0-852b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT is overrated, our tech columnist writes. Here’s what to use instead.</title>
      <description>Geoffrey A. Fowler has been running a chatbot fight club for a year. Now he shares which AI tools win out — and which to avoid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">124397a0-e5e0-11f0-8410-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 00:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tatiana Schlossberg, environmental journalist and granddaughter of President John F. Kennedy, dies of cancer at 35</title>
      <description>Schlossberg announced her terminal cancer diagnosis in a New Yorker essay that took aim at her cousin, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., whom she called “an embarrassment.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">880d0a90-e5b6-11f0-82b2-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:34:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Russia’s war grinds on, its society is fraying</title>
      <description>The Kremlin presents the country as strong, united and on an inevitable path to victory. But as peace negotiations drag on and dissent is suppressed, fatigue and resentment are festering.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78f7b6b0-e5a5-11f0-b4f0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Her family says don’t marry him — because they think he’s gay</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Her family says don’t marry him — because they think he’s gay</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59d14e31-e5a1-11f0-b4f0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 17:02:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What huge, beautiful things does 2026 have in store? Take David Ignatius’s quiz.</title>
      <description>It’s New Year’s, and another calm, uneventful year surely awaits us all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d643a50-e592-11f0-a31c-0000a1ace772</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 15:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security ends year in turmoil as record backlogs delay services</title>
      <description>Customer service deteriorated by key measures as the agency enacted sweeping cuts in President Donald Trump’s second term, internal data and interviews show.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2151c890-e58e-11f0-82b2-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:45:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much do you remember about 2025? Play today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1defead0-e58c-11f0-8dd8-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security seeks emergency demolition of historic buildings in D.C.</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security is seeking to fast-track the demolition of more than a dozen historic buildings at St. Elizabeths in Southeast Washington, asserting that the conditions of the vacant structures represent an “emergency” and pose potential security risks, according to documents obtained by The Washington Post. Preservationists contend no evidence of an emergency exists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a47d960-e583-11f0-8149-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 13:27:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela strike. Trump and Netanyahu. Kennedy Center. Social Security. Ice storm. Wine risks. AI fight club. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09c7bfc1-e577-11f0-80aa-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duty? Insanity? These former members of Congress want to come back.</title>
      <description>By The Washington Post’s latest tally, at least 18 former members — 11 Democrats and seven Republicans — are asking voters to send them back to D.C. next year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28fb8011-e50a-11f0-b169-000a1ace89f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 23:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who benefits from the new H-1B system? Use this interactive to find out.</title>
      <description>Congress mandates that only 85,000 new skilled worker visas — known as the H-1B visa — can be issued every year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">254425c0-e4fc-11f0-9a61-0000a1ace0f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother is broke, expectant and planning the ‘tackiest’ wedding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother is broke, expectant and planning the ‘tackiest’ wedding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6789d342-e4d8-11f0-af07-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The epidemic of toxic flattery is spreading</title>
      <description>What do AI, Trump’s cabinet and the academy have in common? They aim to please.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d483150-e4d0-11f0-b2db-000a1acef642</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your On the Record year in review starts now!</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa0a4200-e4c3-11f0-96d7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:35:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vance stepped in to broker a reconciliation when Trump and Musk were bickering</title>
      <description>The months-long offensive by JD Vance and other White House officials, the details of which have not been previously reported, worked. But the peace offers a glimpse into the next phase of the singular political partnership — one that carries both risk and reward for all involved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbb19f20-e4be-11f0-a058-0000a1acec53</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine talks. Netanyahu meeting. Trump and Musk. Pipe bomb suspect. Screen time. Cellular aging. Nudge word. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfe13980-e4ad-11f0-aabf-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving a kid a phone before this age can be especially harmful, research suggests</title>
      <description>A wave of new studies is shedding light on the risks of early smartphone access and heavy screen use for adolescent mental health and development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ed03a60-e441-11f0-93c5-0000a1ace1b4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f79be40-e40f-11f0-85fd-0000a1ace480</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ben Sasse is exiting the stage far too soon</title>
      <description>Ben Sasse is exiting the stage far too soon</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a382d901-e40b-11f0-b479-0000a1ace24d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wolves, long feared and reviled, may actually be lifesavers</title>
      <description>A new line of research has found that wolves in the Midwest and Canada not only keep deer populations in check, but they also alter deer behavior in ways that help prevent car crashes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f36bb20-e40a-11f0-b5f1-0000a1ace5fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9209a480-e3fa-11f0-bf2a-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:36:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE shift in tactics leads to soaring number of at-large arrests, data shows</title>
      <description>As the Trump administration presses to increase deportations, the agency has moved away from focusing on arresting migrants at local jails to tracking them down in communities, a Washington Post analysis found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb5b7040-e3f7-11f0-af50-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:16:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brigitte Bardot, French femme fatale and cultural phenomenon, dies at 91</title>
      <description>The actress and singer was a symbol of sexual revolution. She later became an animal-welfare campaigner and incendiary right-wing commenter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa5d6060-e3d9-11f0-8684-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bankruptcies soar as companies grapple with inflation and tariffs</title>
      <description>Businesses in vulnerable sectors find themselves caught between rising costs and beleaguered consumers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df729480-e381-11f0-9e77-0000a1ace39b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two baby giraffes are missing. Alicia Silverstone and others want answers.</title>
      <description>The giraffes would be around eight months old, which would make them about 9-feet tall and 700 pounds. Silverstone, of “Clueless” fame, has joined PETA in offering a $50,000 reward for information leading to their whereabouts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b10e6bc0-e370-11f0-9f38-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 22:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>74 suicide warnings and 243 mentions of hanging: What ChatGPT said to a suicidal teen</title>
      <description>Analysis of high-schooler Adam Raine’s ChatGPT account by attorneys for his parents shows how the chatbot became a confidant as he planned to end his life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">548ac790-e352-11f0-9680-0000a1ace615</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 18:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04a9a7b0-e333-11f0-9d4f-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. sank the alleged narco-terrorists’ boat — and let them go</title>
      <description>In blowing up the vessel, destroying evidence and repatriating the survivors, the U.S. cut short a process that has helped bring down traffickers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eee553a0-e32f-11f0-906d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 14:25:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology just can’t kill this popular Midwestern bar game</title>
      <description>Pull tabs, legal in Minnesota and a few other states, have been a cherished tradition for nearly 50 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c552a00-e2a7-11f0-9f0c-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 22:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds of residents signed up for FEMA buyouts after Hurricane Helene. Not one has been approved.</title>
      <description>Some of the homeowners seeking help are still paying mortgages on homes that are no longer livable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc07c8e0-e289-11f0-9050-0000a1ace903</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:36:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I perform at a piano bar. The most requested song might surprise you.</title>
      <description>So long “Piano Man.” Chappell Roan’s ode to a gay bar now draws the most requests, Jesse Rifkin writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf941260-e287-11f0-8ae1-0000a1ace30d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 18:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus! It’s the holiday edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday weekend points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0e704c0-e272-11f0-825e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 good things that happened in 2025</title>
      <description>25 good things that happened in 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">819cc0f0-e26a-11f0-9576-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:52:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New science points to 4 distinct types of autism</title>
      <description>Scientists are redefining autism as a complex condition with multiple forms, challenging traditional notions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62532390-e267-11f0-9ca0-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. strikes Islamic State in Nigeria after Trump's warnings against Christian killings</title>
      <description>U.S. forces struck Islamic State targets in northwestern Nigeria on Christmas evening, following up on threats to the country over killings of Christians, President Donald Trump announced in a Truth Social post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba58b5c0-e1ed-11f0-babc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 23:59:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 charts that show where the economy is heading</title>
      <description>The U.S. economy experienced steady growth in 2025, despite concerns over inflation and the job market, with artificial intelligence playing a significant role in driving growth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e350eca0-e1bf-11f0-aaec-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 things about living a healthy life we learned from super agers this year</title>
      <description>People in their 80s, 90s and 100s (and the scientists who study them) taught us plenty about aging well.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6418a160-e1a3-11f0-8c87-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas from On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b02dbf1-e1a0-11f0-b7d1-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:44:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a nearly 70-year-old debut novelist published 2025’s breakout hit</title>
      <description>With virtually no marketing or social media presence, Allen Levi’s book became a blockbuster, with a late-breaking plot turn so brutal, anguished readers grill him about it at all public appearances. The author’s own path has taken a few twists.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7ffba90-e116-11f0-8f40-0000a1aced24</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Laissez-faire mom-in-law leaves the stress to me’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘Laissez-faire mom-in-law leaves the stress to me’: Carolyn Hax’s readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a4a91e1-e0ea-11f0-bc6c-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The old-world antisemitism in a Christmas pageant near you</title>
      <description>"I’m certainly not the first immigrant to discover Old World darkness lurking in the U.S."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cc1a270-e0e2-11f0-8c78-0000a1aceb56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE documents reveal plan to hold 80,000 immigrants in warehouses</title>
      <description>Rather than shuttling detainees around the country to wherever detention space is available, as happens now, U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement aims to speed up deportations by establishing a deliberate feeder system, an internal document says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43c03381-e0d9-11f0-8ce0-000a1ace1088</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A holiday diss track in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Christmas Eve points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5702a660-e0d6-11f0-94b9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court. Epstein files. ICE warehouses. News subscriptions. Nursing home. Coffee vs. tea. Deer cam. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c318540-e0c0-11f0-bc00-0000a1aced78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We read thousands of internal ICE messages. They show how officials make raids go viral.</title>
      <description>Internal discussions reveal how the agency has coordinated with the White House to satisfy Trump administration demands for arrest videos.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d8b67b0-e057-11f0-a2e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:31:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court will not allow National Guard deployment in Chicago area for now, handing Trump a major defeat</title>
      <description>“At this preliminary stage, the Government has failed to identify a source of authority that would allow the military to execute the laws in Illinois,” the court wrote in an unsigned ruling. The decision is a significant setback for President Donald Trump’s campaign to push troops into cities across the country over the objections of local and state leaders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a35e5d30-e03e-11f0-85d4-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:33:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her daughter was unraveling, and she didn’t know why — until she found the AI chat logs</title>
      <description>Generative AI has attracted a rising number of users under the age of 18. For children in the midst of critical stages of emotional, mental and social development, the appeal of an artificial companion — designed to create the illusion of intimacy — can be powerful, one expert said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ebc0e60-e029-11f0-a971-000a1aced838</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dad’s new wife assumes grandma role by stepping on toes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dad’s new wife assumes grandma role by stepping on toes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">468db500-e021-11f0-a2e4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former GOP senator Ben Sasse announces he has terminal cancer</title>
      <description>“Last week I was diagnosed with metastasized, stage-four pancreatic cancer, and am gonna die,” Sasse, 53, wrote in a social media post. He was first elected to the Senate in 2014, representing Nebraska, and was one of a handful of Republican senators who regularly spoke out against President Donald Trump. Sasse resigned from his seat partway through his second term to become president of the University of Florida.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41def3a0-e019-11f0-94ae-0000a1acef7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:05:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
