<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 02:23:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration orders Pentagon to make plans for sweeping budget cuts, exempting border security and a select few programs</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has ordered senior leaders at the Pentagon and throughout the U.S. military to develop plans for cutting 8 percent from the defense budget in each of the next five years, according to a memo obtained by The Washington Post and officials familiar with the matter — a striking proposal certain to face internal resistance and strident bipartisan opposition in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef3cab20-eefa-11ef-aa4c-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Transportation Department revokes approval of New York City congestion pricing toll on drivers</title>
      <description>Transportation Secretary Sean P. Duffy said the toll, which went into effect in January in an effort to cut planet-warming emissions and fund improvements to the city's transportation system, was a “slap in the face to working class Americans.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f18c24f1-eef0-11ef-97ea-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74733971-eee3-11ef-88e1-0000a1ace156</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, without evidence, accuses Zelensky of being a ‘Dictator without Elections’ — echoing rhetoric from Russia</title>
      <description>The outburst is President Donald Trump's latest attack on Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and Ukraine, which previously had U.S. support in its fight against Russia's invasion. Many of Trump's recent criticisms of Zelensky have been previously made by Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">301e2930-eee1-11ef-b6e6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059f0c60-eedc-11ef-94d5-0000a1acecbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across the breadth of Africa, Islamist extremism is spiking, military coups are spreading and Russian influence is on the rise</title>
      <description>As these ominous forces converge, the stakes are high for the region, and the reverberations could be felt beyond its borders. Read the stories of a jihadist, a Russian mercenary, a defiant broadcaster and others, both African and outsider, who are shaping this new chapter of African history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4d24c0-eed6-11ef-8807-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A long-time cast member in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fad9970-eece-11ef-9d81-0000a1ace814</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Musk. Free coronavirus tests. Jair Bolsonaro. Delta crash. Hostage releases. A$AP Rocky. Favorite child. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">015060a0-eeb9-11ef-827b-0000a1ace794</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil charges former president Jair Bolsonaro with leading plot to seize power, kill political rivals</title>
      <description>Bolsonaro is accused of leading an extensive plot to overthrow the Brazilian government following his 2022 electoral loss, including an attempt to poison Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the country's current president, and participation in an armed criminal organization. The charges are a historic rebuke of a politician whose brash and aggressive form of politics dominated the country for years and left it deeply polarized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea4d3250-ee65-11ef-8bdf-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 02:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A$AP Rocky found not guilty of two counts of felony assault with a semiautomatic firearm</title>
      <description>Rocky, whose legal name is Rakim Mayers, was accused of shooting at his former childhood friend A$AP Relli (Terell Ephron) twice outside a Hollywood hotel in November 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">869a19b0-ee5d-11ef-9ef8-000a1ace5d0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 01:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA is losing hundreds of employees. That could slow disaster response.</title>
      <description>The job cuts at the Federal Emergency Management Agency, which come in addition to the firing of more than 200 employees last week, targeted probationary and contract workers, and could affect people across the country who are struggling to prepare for disasters or rebuild. The FEMA firings were part of a wave of terminations of federal workers that took place over the holiday weekend and Tuesday, according to agency officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">450502e0-ee52-11ef-9d24-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Trump administration’s error-plagued firing spree, which dismissed thousands for ‘performance’ reasons without evidence</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke to more than 275 federal workers and reviewed dozens of government records to compile an account of the chaotic process, which swept up some long-serving employees, military veterans and people with disabilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ded7760-ee4e-11ef-aa0e-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 23:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs of probationary Defense Department employees are expected soon as team from Musk’s DOGE arrives at Pentagon, officials say</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has directed defense agencies to turn over a list of such employees by the end of Tuesday, with the expectation that many could be laid off as soon as this week, people familiar with the matter say. The directive coincides with the arrival at the Pentagon of personnel from Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service, which has overseen the firing of thousands of probationary employees in other federal agencies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">479a9c80-ee3f-11ef-8200-0000a1ace34f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pope Francis has pneumonia in both lungs, Vatican says, as concerns grow over ‘complex’ infection</title>
      <description>Francis, who had part of one lung removed in his youth, was admitted to the hospital Friday. He has suffered from declining health and mobility for years, and his current hospitalization is his fourth since ascending to the papacy in 2013.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b635b20-ee2f-11ef-9d24-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 19:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did all 80 people survive after a plane flipped on the Toronto runway? What to know about ‘crashworthiness.’</title>
      <description>Aviation experts say aircraft design and a fast response from the cabin crew helped everyone aboard the regional jet escape after it flipped upside down in the snow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d0cca31-ee21-11ef-b286-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:53:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend talks about marriage, but where’s the engagement?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend talks about marriage, but where’s the engagement?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9bdc361-ee19-11ef-97b0-0000a1acec50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 17:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. federal prosecutor resigns after declining to take part in Trump administration plan to freeze EPA grant funding</title>
      <description>Denise Cheung, head of the criminal division in the U.S. attorney’s office in D.C., resigned in protest Tuesday morning after she refused to aid in freezing assets of a multibillion-dollar Biden administration environmental grant initiative, according to two people who spoke on the condition of anonymity because they weren’t authorized to discuss it publicly.

Cheung’s departure comes on the heels of prosecutor resignations after orders to dismiss corruption charges against New York Mayor Eric Adams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50ddbe70-ee18-11ef-a0a9-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 16:49:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing a dance in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67ff6fb0-ee07-11ef-b87d-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 14:48:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta crash. Elon Musk. Ukraine talks. Pope Francis. ‘Gulf of America.’ Snow forecast. Lincoln Memorial. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81f95d1-edef-11ef-b4b7-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sorrow, hope and longing of Japan’s ‘Missing Post Office’</title>
      <description>The old post office is a repository for 60,000-plus pieces of mail: letters, birthday cards and New Year’s greetings sent from all over Japan to those with no forwarding address: Lost friends and pets; past and future selves; and, most frequently, the dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036b84b0-ed96-11ef-88ca-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 01:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Social Security official exits after clash with Musk’s DOGE over attempts to access sensitive data, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Billionaire Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service has pushed for sensitive records at the Social Security Administration, leading to the departure of its acting commissioner. The agency is responsible for managing pension payments for more than 70 million American seniors and manages significant troves of personal data, including those related to Americans’ work history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d2df432-ed8d-11ef-be6f-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All 80 people on Delta flight that crashed and turned upside down at Toronto airport have been evacuated from the plane, FAA says</title>
      <description>The regional jet departed Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport on Monday morning. What caused the aircraft to flip upside down on the tarmac remains unknown, but weather conditions at the time were harsh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf634bd0-ed81-11ef-bd40-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50b667c1-ed51-11ef-beb3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was a Jan. 6 juror. What she learned surprised her.</title>
      <description>When the jury summons for federal criminal court arrived in my mailbox in November 2023, Lauren Ober knew she had to answer it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3a3c91-ed4d-11ef-af96-0000a1ace410</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 16:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Presidents’ Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c435100-ed3c-11ef-9440-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 highlights from ‘Saturday Night Live’s’ sprawling and unexpectedly poignant 50th anniversary special</title>
      <description>The three-hour-plus broadcast was packed with A-list stars including Eddie Murphy, Tina Fey, Paul McCartney, Adam Sandler and many more, who paid tribute to its five-decade run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2d78aa0-ed37-11ef-a842-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Trump’s firings. Ukraine talks. Freed hostage. Deadly storm. Healthy drinks. SNL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae77c641-ed26-11ef-ab97-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Saturday Night Live’ 50th anniversary special starts soon. Join our reporters and critics for live insights, analysis and more.</title>
      <description>Luminaries including Adam Sandler, Eddie Murphy and Tina Fey will be on hand as the NBC staple celebrates a half-century of comedy. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db03900-ecc9-11ef-83ac-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s DOGE seeks access to personal taxpayer data, raising alarm at IRS</title>
      <description>The unusual request would put sensitive data about millions of American taxpayers in the hands of Trump political appointees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b479dd0-ecc5-11ef-a5f5-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relatives and records cast doubt on Guantánamo migrants being ‘worst of the worst’</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke with family members of six Venezuelan men being held in Guantánamo. Despite the impression given by Homeland Security officials, the migrants were taken into custody after crossing the border — not during a targeted immigration operation in a U.S. city or at a jail or prison while serving a sentence. The relatives firmly deny they are members of the Tren de Aragua gang.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4123b6b0-ecb5-11ef-8d6b-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mountain by any other name should still be Denali, Alaskans say</title>
      <description>Denali means “the great one,” and those living in the snow-shrouded midst of North America's tallest peak question why one of President Donald Trump's first actions was to rename it for a 19th-century predecessor who never set foot in Alaska.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5176beb0-ec9a-11ef-9366-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9fc3e90-ec89-11ef-8bbd-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was the deadliest workplace in America. So why didn’t safety regulators shut it down?</title>
      <description>Inspectors issued more than 100 safety violations and millions in fines. Yet deaths and injuries continued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9def47b1-ec83-11ef-b0ff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f48b790-ec73-11ef-ae3f-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful, potentially damaging winds possible in D.C. area this afternoon</title>
      <description>After downpours exit midday, very strong winds are expected in the afternoon, potentially gusting to 50 to 60 mph. The National Weather Service has issued a high wind warning until 10 p.m. and cautions that power outages are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">525dd1e0-ec6f-11ef-96d1-0000a1ace502</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stunning pattern of suicide blights one of the Marines’ most iconic jobs</title>
      <description>Marine Corps drill instructors are a national symbol of discipline. But for some, their imposing persona belies a dark reality, a joint investigation by The Washington Post and Military.com found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b61b10-ebf3-11ef-ba5c-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 23:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfdc7130-ebc5-11ef-ac36-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rejects Trump request for half of its rare-mineral wealth in exchange for continued U.S. assistance</title>
      <description>The offer and Ukraine’s consideration of it rippled through European diplomatic circles not only for its audacity but also because the war-ravaged country appeared to be seriously considering how to reach a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92f03a40-ebc0-11ef-ab97-0000a1ace20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A portrait of a mystery woman was found hidden beneath a century-old Picasso</title>
      <description>With the help of advanced imaging technology, conservators at the Courtauld Institute of Art in Britain discovered the figure under the moody blues of the “Portrait of Mateu Fernández de Soto,” painted by Pablo Picasso in 1901. The woman’s fashionable chignon hairstyle, shoulders and fingers are visible in the infrared image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71fe9230-ebbd-11ef-97d7-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal documents show how DOGE wrote the playbook for Trump’s DEI purge — and whom they plan to fire next</title>
      <description>A team of staffers at the U.S. DOGE Service mapped out President Donald Trump’s campaign to eliminate diversity, equity and inclusion programs from the government, documents show. DOGE’s three-phase plan lays out how the team next intends to fire hundreds of workers in non-diversity roles, as well as employees who work in offices that exist by law to protect equal rights, according to documents obtained by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ff11b40-ebab-11ef-9e0a-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">916f3700-eba9-11ef-819e-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American hostage Sagui Dekel-Chen released by Hamas after 16 months in captivity, following tense week during Gaza ceasefire deal</title>
      <description>Dekel-Chen, an American Israeli dual national, was released alongside Sasha Alexander Troufanov and Iair Horn, as part of an exchange deal that is expected to see 369 Palestinian prisoners and detainees released. His wife was pregnant when he was kidnapped, and the father of three has not yet met his newborn child.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f845b41-eb7a-11ef-8c47-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice officials seek to drop Eric Adams case after 7 veteran prosecutors resign over request to do so</title>
      <description>The Justice Department on Friday filed a motion to drop the charges against Adams, asking a judge to decide the fate of a case that has ignited a dramatic standoff between the Trump administration and veteran prosecutors. In an extraordinary meeting earlier Friday, acting deputy attorney general Emil Bove gathered members of the Justice Department's Public Integrity Section to see who might be willing to sign the motion asking a judge to dismiss the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6ac1e31-eb2d-11ef-b26b-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hawk crew in fatal midair collision may not have received crucial tower instruction, NTSB says</title>
      <description>The microphone was depressed aboard the Black Hawk hurtling toward the American Airlines passenger jet on Jan. 29, so the crew may not have heard an instruction from Air Traffic Control to pass behind the jet 17 seconds before impact, the National Transportation Safety Board said Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df3efac0-eb12-11ef-9b91-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vice President JD Vance on Friday met with far-right German leader Alice Weidel, the highest-ranking U.S. official ever to do so</title>
      <description>Vance also met with leaders of Germany’s two other major parties, which are locked in competition ahead of Feb. 23 elections, in which Weidel’s Alternative for Germany party might break through a taboo and join a ruling coalition for the first time since World War II.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e85a29e0-eb0d-11ef-aa30-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband punched the floor out of anger and broke his hand</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband punched the floor out of anger and broke his hand</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b467900-eb02-11ef-89fc-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lead Eric Adams prosecutor also quits over demand to drop charges, saying only a ‘fool’ or ‘coward’ would do so</title>
      <description>Hagan Scotten, who led New York Mayor Eric Adams’s federal corruption case, has quit over the Trump administration’s demand that the case be dismissed, calling any lawyer who would move in court to toss the charges a “fool” or “coward,” according to a copy of a letter obtained Friday. This week, the acting U.S. attorney in New York and five Justice Department officials in Washington resigned over the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b42fbed0-eb00-11ef-b5e1-0000a1ace887</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D analysis of the view from the helicopter’s cockpit shows how pilots could have mixed up jets in fatal DCA crash</title>
      <description>The Post’s examination — based on a 3D model using flight data and air traffic control transmissions, and interviews with former Black Hawk pilots — shows how the American Airlines jet and a second plane, though separated by miles, would have appeared close to one another near the horizon before the deadly collision on Jan. 29.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bf359a0-eae8-11ef-b7c3-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f712f60-eae0-11ef-b60d-0000a1ace2cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal firings. Kennedy confirmation. Ukraine. Crash reconstruction. Bird flu. Winter storm. Roman ruins. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39f3bbb0-eacb-11ef-9713-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
