<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 02:22:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Countries are preparing for the worst after Trump's comments on Gaza, David Ignatius reports</title>
      <description>To a region still recovering from the trauma of war, Trump’s proposed takeover of Gaza was incendiary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac74e060-e41d-11ef-9738-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:02:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our personal finance columnist reviewed the ‘deferred resignation’ contract with a law professor. Her verdict: Don’t sign.</title>
      <description>Our personal finance columnist reviewed the ‘deferred resignation’ contract with a law professor. Her verdict: Don’t sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e69b691-e419-11ef-b3a4-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 23:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive order that aims to ban trans student-athletes from competing on girls’ and women’s teams</title>
      <description>The new order threatens to deny federal funds for schools that allow transgender athletes to compete in K-12 and college sports. It’s the latest salvo in President Donald Trump’s attack on transgender rights, another that will ricochet through schools across the country, as the president delivers on another contentious culture war promise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9920c3a1-e407-11ef-b1fb-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 21:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will not send funds to Gaza and hasn’t committed to sending troops, White House says, after his proposal to displace Gazans</title>
      <description>White House Press Secretary Karoline Leavitt told reporters Wednesday that the United States “is not going to pay for the rebuilding of Gaza.” She also said President Donald Trump “has not committed” to putting boots on the ground there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24d435e0-e3f3-11ef-85ee-0000a1ace36f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:58:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China considers pulling the plug on TikTok in the U.S. as it waits for a ‘grand deal’ on trade with Trump</title>
      <description>TikTok’s Chinese owner appears to be slow-rolling negotiations for a sale while waiting for a green light from the Chinese government, even as corporate allies of President Donald Trump race to broker a deal to sell the app to an American bidder, according to three people familiar with the talks, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss private business transactions.

But Beijing is increasingly likely to take a hard-line approach, letting TikTok’s U.S. operations die rather than approving a sale as it holds out for a “grand deal” with the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">824e24f1-e3e5-11ef-b464-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 17:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge indefinitely blocks Trump’s order to end birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>Maryland U.S. District Judge Deborah L. Boardman issued the preliminary injunction on Wednesday in response to a lawsuit brought by civil rights groups. The injunction applies nationally and will remain in place as the case is adjudicated. The Trump administration is expected to appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3a9151-e3dc-11ef-a046-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 16:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NWSL must create $5 million fund to compensate women’s soccer players abused by coaches and officials, new settlement states</title>
      <description>The deal involves the attorneys general from Washington, D.C., Illinois and New York, and the NWSL Players Association. It was reached more than three years after allegations of harassment, emotional abuse and sexual misconduct sparked a crisis that rocked the league and sport, led to investigations and prompted a series of changes by the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1e1e950-e3d0-11ef-aba1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:51:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ‘everlasting’ musical instrument in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abf7da10-e3ce-11ef-bf97-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS resumes accepting packages from China and Hong Kong hours after blocking them in effort to comply with Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Rather than refusing packages from China and Hong Kong entirely, the U.S. Postal Service says it will work with Customs and Border Protection on a way to collect new tariffs imposed by President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7298a501-e3ca-11ef-9bb5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 14:06:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Gaza proposal. Elon Musk. Tariff impacts. Sweden shooting. Abortion pills. Winter storms. Expensive violin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8ca7ba2-e3b8-11ef-b59e-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most USAID workers to be put on leave as all overseas staff are recalled, Trump administration says</title>
      <description>The move is the latest action in a jarring broadside against America’s foreign aid architecture that has followed President Donald Trump’s return to the White House. In the weeks since his inauguration, the new administration has announced a broad freeze on foreign aid programs — unleashing upheaval across the aid sector and financial crises for groups reliant on USAID funding — and fired, furloughed or put on leave the bulk of AID employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec82e010-e37a-11ef-b770-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 04:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>USPS suspends package service from China as Trump’s tariffs kick in</title>
      <description>The U.S. Postal Service’s decision may block, at least temporarily, parcels from retailers including Shein and Temu from entering the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f1194d0-e367-11ef-af1a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 02:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says U.S. would ‘take over’ Gaza Strip, says Palestinians should leave in news conference with Netanyahu</title>
      <description>In a news conference with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, Trump suggested Gazans should leave the war-torn area and that the U.S. would step in and “develop it,” possibly on a long-term basis and with U.S. military involvement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">815e8fe0-e358-11ef-8a4d-0000a1aceb31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities say they’ve recovered the remains of all 67 people killed in last week’s midair crash. Here are many of their stories.</title>
      <description>Among those killed were young figure skaters, soldiers, attorneys and a group that had been on a hunting trip, according to their families and friends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e949040-e353-11ef-b540-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:54:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New year, new pregnancy: This pronatalist couple wants to make America procreate again</title>
      <description>Simone and Malcolm Collins, along with their soon-to-be five children, are avatars for a new pronatalist movement. With Trump 2.0, they’re more optimistic than ever.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4fa4731-e34b-11ef-a1fe-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 23:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes permanent displacement of Gazans as he welcomes Netanyahu to White House</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump framed the vision as a practical and humane response to the physical destruction of Gaza after 16 months of intense bombardment from Israel. His comments threatened to inflame the Arab world as Trump prepared to welcome Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to the White House on Tuesday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65971990-e343-11ef-a7c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google drops its pledge not to develop AI for weapons, surveillance or in ways ‘likely to cause overall harm’</title>
      <description>Executives said in a blog post that companies should create AI that “supports national security.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c04541a0-e339-11ef-ad23-0000a1ace199</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freezing rain could produce icy glaze in D.C. area Wednesday night into early Thursday morning</title>
      <description>Untreated roads and walkways could become slick, causing school delays and closings. The National Weather Service has issued winter weather advisories for the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c734b40-e336-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 20:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard, Trump’s controversial nominee for director of national intelligence, clears Senate committee vote</title>
      <description>After Gabbard’s narrow approval by the Senate Intelligence Committee, she will face a full Senate vote next week. Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman from Hawaii, faced bipartisan skepticism about her suitability for overseeing the full roster of U.S. intelligence agencies during a tense confirmation hearing last week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21b4f490-e32f-11ef-b770-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Families and LGBTQ advocacy groups sue to halt Trump order aiming to restrict care for transgender youth</title>
      <description>The lawsuit comes as hospitals across the country have paused some gender transition care for people younger than 19 in response to President Donald Trump's executive order seeking to block federal support for such treatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5877bb91-e32d-11ef-abb4-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council expels Trayon White Sr. (D-Ward 8) over ethics rules, the first time the body has taken such a step in its history</title>
      <description>The punishment results from a federal charge that White took $35,000 in bribes from an associate seeking to extend government contracts. White has pleaded not guilty to the charge. He is still eligible to run for his seat again in a special election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d169a691-e322-11ef-a9a7-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 18:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI agents sue to keep officials from compiling a list that could be used to fire thousands involved in Trump and Jan. 6 cases</title>
      <description>Attorneys for the agents, who filed suit anonymously in U.S. District Court for the District of Columbia, said any effort to use that information as a basis to fire FBI employees would be unlawful, retaliatory and a violation of civil service protections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a584d7e0-e320-11ef-a53a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Layoffs across the federal government are ‘likely’ if not enough workers take the deferred resignation offer, internal email warns</title>
      <description>The assistant commissioner of a division of the General Services Administration told staff to prepare for deep cuts. Federal workers have until Thursday to accept an offer to resign now and be paid through September.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c80bec1-e31b-11ef-a4fd-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom won’t stop rehashing every painful detail of Dad’s final days</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom won’t stop rehashing every painful detail of Dad’s final days</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95592670-e319-11ef-b2c6-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr., Trump’s nominee to serve as the top U.S. health official, clears key hurdle for Senate confirmation</title>
      <description>Kennedy, who faced tough questioning in recent hearings over his positions on vaccines, abortion and other major health-care issues, was advanced by the Senate Finance Committee. He still needs approval by the full Senate to be confirmed as secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02af2f10-e30d-11ef-ae7a-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 15:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Power grab. Immigration crackdown. Netanyahu visit. Fire insurance. Microplastics. Cannabis drinks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ef42200-e2ef-11ef-80d9-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China institutes a 15% levy on U.S. coal and gas in retaliation after Trump’s tariffs take effect</title>
      <description>Beijing also imposed additional tariffs on farm machinery and other products from the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac713300-e2c1-11ef-8b15-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 06:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fed-up sheriff jailed children who made school shooting threats: ‘I’m going to perp walk your kid’</title>
      <description>Thousands of students made threats after the deadly Apalachee High School shooting in Georgia, a Washington Post analysis finds — leading frustrated police to arrest nearly 500. Nowhere was the crackdown more harsh than in one Florida county.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae8d5ae0-e282-11ef-b6b9-000a1ace097f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 23:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump preps order to dismantle Education Department as DOGE works to raze it from within, officials say</title>
      <description>Closing the agency would require congressional approval, so the new administration hopes to diminish it. Already, the White House has tried to reduce the agency’s workforce by putting scores of employees on administrative leave, pressuring staff to voluntarily quit and sending DOGE officials in to probe books, people familiar with the matter say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b220771-e27e-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trudeau, after call with Trump, says U.S. will pause tariffs on Canada for 30 days</title>
      <description>In a tweet, Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said he had a good call with President Donald Trump, will appoint a fentanyl czar and will implement the $900 million border plan his government announced in December.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">582741f0-e27a-11ef-b2ac-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 22:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The 2025 Grammys performances, ranked from best to worst</title>
      <description>On Beyoncé and Kendrick’s big night, a new generation of pop stars wowed onstage. Here’s what impressed us — and what was forgettable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">557ed5b0-e263-11ef-91dc-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:16:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I haven’t filed tax returns in 5 years. Can I correct this without going to jail? Our personal finance columnist takes your questions.</title>
      <description>I haven’t filed tax returns in 5 years. Can I correct this without going to jail? Our personal finance columnist takes your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd7bf880-e261-11ef-bf28-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:06:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consumer Financial Protection Bureau halts all work after Trump appoints Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent as its acting director</title>
      <description>The CFPB is actively engaged in litigation with banks, tech firms and others it oversees. Elon Musk has previously called to “delete” the agency, and President Donald Trump fired its director over the weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0369391-e259-11ef-a202-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 18:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Closeness of friendship with ex-wife makes girlfriend uncomfortable</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Closeness of friendship with ex-wife makes girlfriend uncomfortable</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b11e0391-e250-11ef-acbf-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 17:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists discover microplastics are building up in our brains — with potentially dangerous effects for human health</title>
      <description>New research published Monday in Nature Medicine shows that microplastics are breaking the blood-brain barrier — and building up in the human body. Brains from people who died in 2024 had 50 percent more plastic fragments in them than samples from 2016, indicating that the particles are accumulating as plastics production has boomed worldwide. The scientists also found that the brains of patients with dementia had significantly more microplastics than healthy ones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7642a3e0-e24e-11ef-9afd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should you take the Trump administration’s buyout offer? A risk expert explains how to make a good decision.</title>
      <description>A handful of prompts can help you decide how to decide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcc1eb50-e249-11ef-ad89-0000a1ace760</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 16:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will delay tariffs against Mexico for one month, Mexican president says</title>
      <description>Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum tweeted that she had a “good conversation” with President Donald Trump and pledged to deploy 10,000 members of the Mexican national guard to the border to combat drug trafficking, particularly of fentanyl. The tariffs had been set to take effect early Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7fd17d1-e244-11ef-b556-0000a1ace6c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 15:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new chatbot in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a77d9650-e23e-11ef-b766-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow slumps 500 points as Trump tariffs, fears of trade war rattle global markets</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 and tech-heavy Nasdaq also fell sharply Monday after the Trump administration imposed sweeping levies on goods from Canada, Mexico and China, which all promised retaliatory measures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4e65ba0-e23b-11ef-8785-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 14:34:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Elon Musk. Plane wreckage. Hostage release. School threats. Grammy winners. Near-Earth asteroid. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64e6d9e0-e226-11ef-a237-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary of State Marco Rubio backtracks on Trump’s near-total foreign aid freeze, issues waiver for ‘life-saving’ assistance</title>
      <description>The State Department on Friday issued a blanket "stop-work" order, immediately pausing almost all U.S. foreign assistance. On Tuesday, amid global confusion and concern, the State Dept. abruptly and quietly sent a notice that seemed to indicate broad swaths of this funding could continue. Humanitarian groups around the world are still unsure what it means for them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71d51681-ddee-11ef-8bdc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 03:09:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth to take actions against Trump foe Mark Milley, the former Joint Chiefs chairman, official says</title>
      <description>Hegseth has decided to revoke Milley’s security detail and order an inspector general inquiry into his behavior as the Pentagon’s top officer, a senior defense official said, taking extraordinary action against a frequent target of President Donald Trump. The official said there was motivation within the administration to “take a star” from Milley, meaning officials also want to see Milley demoted in retirement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80806a80-ddea-11ef-90c1-000a1ace014d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 02:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. disparaged vaccines dozens of times in recent years and made baseless claims on race</title>
      <description>A Washington Post review found that Kennedy, whose Senate confirmation hearings for health secretary start Wednesday, criticized vaccines in at least 114 podcast appearances, interviews and public speeches since 2020. In at least 36 of those cases, Kennedy, who did not respond to requests for comment, falsely linked autism to vaccines. He also has said that White and Black people should have separate vaccination schedules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6269b30-dddf-11ef-8895-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 01:25:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House tells federal workers they can quit now and be paid through Sept. 30</title>
      <description>The White House’s Office of Personnel Management sent a message outlining a way workers could resign by Feb. 6, then go on paid leave for several months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a29aac81-ddcb-11ef-a803-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 23:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge delays White House spending freeze until Feb. 3 in emergency order</title>
      <description>Nonprofit groups had challenged the Office of Management and Budget order in court, calling it unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8705f640-ddc7-11ef-86f9-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:30:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to fire members of two independent agencies tasked with protecting workers, breaking with decades of precedent</title>
      <description>The dismissals represent a dramatic break from Supreme Court precedent decided in 1935, which holds that the president cannot fire members of independent agencies except in cases of malfeasance or neglect of duty.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de1cad1-ddc3-11ef-82ff-0000a1ace118</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 22:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian will close its diversity office after Trump’s DEI order</title>
      <description>The institution’s secretary also told staff on Tuesday that the Smithsonian would comply with President Donald Trump’s return-to-office mandate and freeze on new federal hires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08400190-ddbb-11ef-bae2-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 21:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration clarifies spending freeze was meant to be limited, but order has spurred chaos, including Medicaid outages</title>
      <description>White House officials say a pause on grants applies only to programs involving foreign aid, immigration and DEI. But the initial impact of the Monday order appears to have gone far beyond that; on Tuesday, Medicaid and Head Start reported funding problems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e1f7f70-ddb6-11ef-bae2-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 20:29:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caroline Kennedy calls her cousin RFK Jr. a ‘predator’ in searing letter, warning senators not to confirm him as HHS secretary</title>
      <description>In a detailed letter to lawmakers and a video, the former U.S. ambassador to Australia questioned the ethics of President Donald Trump’s nominee, as well as his views on vaccines. Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s confirmation hearing is set to begin Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e2a9aa0-dd9d-11ef-80ab-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sister rips into her for not being charming enough on trips</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sister rips into her for not being charming enough on trips</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a253f240-dd99-11ef-b6fc-000a1ace9bc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
