<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 07:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Chiefs will face Eagles in Super Bowl LIX, with Kansas City vying to become the first team to win three straight Super Bowls</title>
      <description>The Chiefs topped the Buffalo Bills in the AFC championship game to advance to their fifth Super Bowl in six seasons. Earlier today, the Philadelphia Eagles blew out the upstart Washington Commanders in the NFC championship game. The Chiefs beat the Eagles in Super Bowl LVII two years ago. This year's game is Feb. 9 in New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">140f5050-dc5a-11ef-bfb7-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 02:54:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders lose to Eagles in NFC championship game, ending magical season fueled by rookie QB Jayden Daniels</title>
      <description>Washington fell, 55-23, on Sunday in Philadelphia to end a breakout season for the team, which won 14 games and advanced further than it had in more than three decades. The Eagles will meet either the Kansas City Chiefs or Buffalo Bills in the Super Bowl on Feb. 9 in New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49f65190-dc3d-11ef-a3fb-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 23:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cancer patient turned a grim prognosis into the gamble of her life</title>
      <description>Katie Doble received a prognosis of 16 months to live. She didn’t know whether she should plan her wedding or her funeral. But she had one advantage many other cancer patients don’t: Her father was a doctor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e51b0970-dc30-11ef-8580-0000a1acec48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Commanders visit the Eagles in the NFC championship game with a trip to the Super Bowl on the line. Follow for updates.</title>
      <description>After a stunning upset of the Detroit Lions last weekend, rookie quarterback Jayden Daniels and the Commanders are one win away from the franchise’s first Super Bowl appearance since 1992. To get there, they’ll have to beat the Eagles, who have already earned playoff victories over the Packers and Rams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd2a9620-dc1e-11ef-880b-000a1acefc16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 19:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces tariffs and other sanctions after Colombia refuses U.S. planes with deported migrants</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump retaliated Sunday with immediate 25 percent tariffs and visa restrictions after the Colombian president said his country would not accept deportation flights unless the Trump administration ensures that repatriated Colombian migrants are treated with the “dignity that a human being deserves.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9f0b680-dc1a-11ef-880b-000a1acefc16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 19:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials set quotas for ICE to aggressively ramp up arrests of immigrants, increasing odds that noncriminals are detained</title>
      <description>U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials have been directed to increase the number of people they arrest from a few hundred per day to at least 1,200 to 1,500 because President Donald Trump has been disappointed with the results of his mass deportation campaign so far, according to four people briefed on the instructions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c42a4dc0-dc17-11ef-8aa5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 19:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘A roster change for the ages’: 8 writers on the Commanders’ comeback</title>
      <description>‘A roster change for the ages’: 8 writers on the Washington Commanders</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">facb8730-dc0e-11ef-8ad1-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 17:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34b7fe91-dc07-11ef-8580-0000a1acec48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 17:01:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After Daniel Snyder’s exit from the Commanders, the NFL at last has a relevant D.C. team again</title>
      <description>The Commanders’ spot in the NFC championship game represents a relieved satisfaction for the NFL. Washington is on the verge of a Super Bowl berth after Josh Harris’s ownership group endured a chaotic process that included last-minute decisions before finalizing its purchase of the team from Snyder. The result: There’s a flagship franchise in Washington again.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d79f4120-dbfa-11ef-8a44-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 15:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35b7eef0-dbf2-11ef-bcfa-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean president indicted on insurrection charges after martial law attempt</title>
      <description>President Yoon Suk Yeol, who briefly imposed martial law on the country last month, is the first sitting South Korean president to be indicted and criminally investigated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7edb0500-dbd3-11ef-bb3e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 10:51:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends late-night purge that ousted at least 15 independent inspectors general</title>
      <description>“I don’t know them,” the president said Saturday night, even though many of those he fired were appointed during his first term. The dismissals appeared to violate federal law, which requires Congress to receive 30 days’ notice of any intent to fire a Senate-confirmed inspector general.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7aa8ef80-db90-11ef-a4e6-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 02:51:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s first-week strategy: ‘Flood the zone.’ Repeat.</title>
      <description>It was all part of a plan to begin with a bang and follow a detailed policy blueprint, although key administrative posts remained stuck in a hiring bottleneck and many of his directives lacked immediate effect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">540bb5b0-db68-11ef-a16f-0000a1ace113</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 22:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loretta Ford dies at 104. Her groundbreaking work in nursing transformed the way millions received health care.</title>
      <description>Dr. Ford co-founded the nurse practitioner profession amid resistance within the medical community.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21c81ef0-db4e-11ef-bebe-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 18:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate easily confirms Kristi Noem to lead the Department of Homeland Security</title>
      <description>The department is key to President Donald Trump’s plans to deport millions of undocumented immigrants and impose a crackdown at the U.S.-Mexico border. It also oversees vital agencies like the Secret Service and Federal Emergency Management Agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa3fcd80-db41-11ef-8580-0000a1acec48</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 17:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 science-based ways to reduce your risk of dementia</title>
      <description>A disturbing new study predicts that new cases of dementia will double by 2060, estimating that 1 million U.S. adults will develop the memory-destroying brain disease. From diet and exercise to protecting against hearing loss and maintaining social connections, there are ways to reduce the risk, experts say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78515340-db35-11ef-b570-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d09b1af0-db2a-11ef-b435-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four female hostages are back in Israel and reunited with their families, while 200 Palestinian prisoners have been released, Israel says</title>
      <description>The four female soldiers were released earlier than expected on Saturday, in the second week of a protracted ceasefire and hostage release deal that has halted 15 months of fighting. However, Israel said Hamas had violated the agreement to release all living civilian women first, and that it would delay withdrawing its troops from north Gaza as a result.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b353080-db21-11ef-bfa3-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:35:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump fires at least 12 independent inspectors general in late-night purge</title>
      <description>The White House is firing many inspectors general — the independent watchdogs at major Cabinet departments charged with identifying fraud and abuse. It is a purge that could lead to the president installing loyalists to the crucial roles overseeing major agencies like Energy and Transportation. Most of those dismissed were Trump appointees from his first term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca212861-dad3-11ef-be8f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 04:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth confirmed as Trump’s defense secretary, an appointment expected to bring a dramatic shift in national security policy</title>
      <description>The former Fox News personality, whose nomination was overshadowed by a raft of misconduct allegations, overcame withering opposition from lawmakers who deemed him unfit to run the Pentagon and oversee the nation’s military.

Three Republicans, Sens. Mitch McConnell (Kentucky), Lisa Murkowski (Alaska) and Susan Collins (Maine), joined the chamber’s Democrats in opposing his nomination. Vice President JD Vance cast the tiebreaking vote.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">693e1c80-dac7-11ef-a55d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 02:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. skipped an official meeting meant to prepare the White House for a possible pandemic</title>
      <description>Kennedy, who’s been nominated to serve as the United States’ top health official, was instead on Capitol Hill to lobby senators for their votes. National security and health experts said they were troubled by Kennedy’s absence from the session, given the possibility of a serious health crisis like avian flu on the Trump administration’s watch.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">282718b1-daa3-11ef-afac-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 22:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court to decide whether states can allow religious public schools</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court agreed Friday to consider whether the state of Oklahoma may fund a proposed Catholic charter school, a blockbuster case that could redraw the line between church and state by allowing religious public schools for the first time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab4c26f0-da9d-11ef-a1d8-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. to sharply curtail prosecutions of antiabortion protesters who disrupt access to clinics</title>
      <description>A day after President Donald Trump pardoned 23 people convicted under the 1994 FACE Act, the Justice Department said it would drop three pending cases and would prosecute future cases only under "extraordinary circumstances," including if protesters cause “death, serious bodily harm, or serious property damage.” Trump and his allies have accused the Biden administration of bringing cases against "peaceful pro-life protestors."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68069cd0-da99-11ef-afac-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 21:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified to announce my pregnancy. How do I handle this?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified to announce my pregnancy. How do I handle this?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cccc7a40-da7b-11ef-a037-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration raids are alarming communities, but ICE has arrested fewer people this week than when Trump took office in 2017</title>
      <description>The Trump administration circulated photos Friday showing U.S. troops loading shackled detainees onto a military cargo plane, as the White House declared a start to the mass deportation campaign the president promised along the campaign trail. But ICE arrest numbers suggest the show of force has so far outpaced the government’s capacity to quickly increase deportations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14dbd032-da7a-11ef-af69-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:38:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">922b3c30-da5f-11ef-af69-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:29:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s executive orders. Elon Musk. Explicit texts. Wildfires. Oscar snubs. NFL playoffs. Pandas debut. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc923bf0-da4a-11ef-9528-0000a1ace97c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside TikTok's frantic scramble to halt the ban in the U.S.</title>
      <description>The China-based company said it would "go dark" unless the outgoing administration assured the app's service providers they would not be punished under the ban-or-sale law. The White House demurred, calling it a "stunt,"  and the app went offline for 14 hours — until Donald Trump said he would act fast to give it a reprieve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c690300-d9f1-11ef-97b5-0000a1ace537</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 01:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to close down Pentagon office focused on the prevention of civilian deaths resulting from U.S. military activity</title>
      <description>The Civilian Protection Center of Excellence, a small directorate established by Congress to help the military limit unintended civilian harm in conflict zones, is under scrutiny from the new administration. The Department of the Army, where the center is housed, is drafting a proposal to defund and potentially “disestablish” the office, according to people familiar with the matter and an internal document reviewed by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20faa901-d9de-11ef-9188-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 23:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman indicted in crash that killed NFL rookie Khyree Jackson, two others</title>
      <description>Minnesota Vikings rookie Khyree Jackson, 24, and former high school teammates Anthony Lytton Jr., 24, and Isaiah Hazel, 23, were killed in a car crash last summer. Cori Clingman, the driver of the vehicle that hit them, was allegedly speeding, impaired by alcohol. She faces up to 30 years in prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdd60d30-d9da-11ef-a328-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 22:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth’s nomination for defense secretary clears a key procedural step in the Senate, moving him closer to confirmation</title>
      <description>Republicans have appeared largely unmoved by the allegations of personal misconduct clouding Hegseth’s nomination, though two indicated Thursday they plan to vote against his confirmation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c654110-d9c5-11ef-a5b2-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 20:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnson aide advised against subpoena of Jan. 6 witness Cassidy Hutchinson to prevent release of ‘sexual texts’ lawmakers sent her</title>
      <description>An aide to House Speaker Mike Johnson advised Republican colleagues against subpoenaing Hutchinson, a former White House aide, as part of their investigation into the Jan. 6, 2021, attack to prevent the release of sexually explicit texts that lawmakers told the office they sent her, according to written correspondence reviewed by The Washington Post and a person familiar with the effort.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c9b2620-d9bb-11ef-ac59-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:55:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge issues temporary restraining order blocking Trump policy banning birthright citizenship</title>
      <description>U.S. District Court John C. Coughenour granted the request to a coalition of states that had sued. President Trump signed an executive order Monday to end birthright citizenship for the children of undocumented immigrants and foreign visitors. The order is facing a bevy of legal challenges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f4ea2d1-d9ba-11ef-b9e2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 18:48:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Angry at a lifelong friend for a recent, shocking arrest</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Angry at a lifelong friend for a recent, shocking arrest</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">befa6291-d9ab-11ef-b0ce-0000a1ace6d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 17:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An artist photographed abortion clinics. What caught her eye hung on the walls.</title>
      <description>Artist Carmen Winant’s photos are inspired by the fraught timetable of abortion rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25382940-d9aa-11ef-be4c-0000a1ace464</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 16:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising prices again in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece9c5c0-d996-11ef-aea4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Emilia Pérez,' 'Wicked' and 'The Brutalist' led the Oscar nominations, followed by 'A Complete Unknown' and 'Conclave'</title>
      <description>There was no Barbenheimer, but 2024 was an especially dynamic year at the movies. "Anora" and "The Substance" also had numerous Academy Awards nods.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c0df6f0-d991-11ef-8a9e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 13:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump interview. Border plans. Laken Riley Act. New wildfire. College enrollment. Coffee benefits. Statue discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9444f350-d981-11ef-a55d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This was cruel’: These migrants waited months for a chance to legally cross the border. Under Trump, they’re stuck in Mexico.</title>
      <description>The migrants at El Buen Samaritano shelter had applied through the U.S. government’s CBP One app to be granted parole and enter immigration proceedings. Then, within hours of his swearing-in, President Donald Trump argued in an executive order that the program violated federal law, resulting in appointment cancellations, frustration and fear.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eb25f00-d921-11ef-99bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pardons two D.C. officers convicted of misconduct. Their fatal pursuit of a young Black man sparked civil unrest in 2020.</title>
      <description>In granting clemency, President Donald Trump waded into a case that stoked racial tensions and resulted in the first murder conviction of a D.C. police officer for on-duty actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">650530e1-d91e-11ef-99bb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:10:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department freezes all civil rights cases, including police investigations</title>
      <description>The Justice Department ordered its civil rights division to halt any litigation left over from the Biden administration and not pursue any new cases or settlements. The decision seems likely to jeopardize multiple police reform agreements finalized in recent months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e25473d0-d919-11ef-beab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 23:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes Laken Riley Act, first bill of Trump’s new term and sign of immigration crackdown to come</title>
      <description>The bill would allow Immigration and Customs Enforcement agents to detain undocumented immigrants accused of theft-related crimes, raising questions about due process. The act was named in memory of a nursing student killed in February by an undocumented immigrant in Georgia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c21720-d90d-11ef-9726-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 22:08:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to order at least 1,000 additional U.S. troops to Mexico border in what may be first of several deployments, officials say</title>
      <description>The Defense Department is expected to order the additional military personnel to bolster security at the southern border under President Donald Trump, according to two U.S. officials familiar with the plans. The officials said the personnel will augment the roughly 2,500 service members already deployed to the border under the Biden administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e009800-d8f6-11ef-a92b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 19:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Pushy mom won’t take ‘busy’ for an answer on playdates</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Pushy mom won’t take ‘busy’ for an answer on playdates</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6de075d1-d8e2-11ef-86d8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 17:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: I think a driver ate my food delivery</title>
      <description>Dining chat: I think a driver ate my food delivery</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b0d6020-d8de-11ef-9df9-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 16:29:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Columbia law professor criticized Israeli students. An investigation put her job at risk.</title>
      <description>Columbia Law School professor Katherine Franke alleged Israeli students bullied Palestinian peers, spurring colleagues’ complaints and a school investigation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbe2531-d8d8-11ef-9281-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A huge navy boater in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f40f30b0-d8d3-11ef-a838-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 15:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. threatens to prosecute local officials who do not comply with Trump’s plans for immigration enforcement</title>
      <description>In a memo, acting deputy attorney general Emil Bove said state and local officials must "comply with the Executive Branch’s immigration enforcement initiatives,” including mass deportation efforts. The directive is likely to face blowback from legal advocacy groups and local officials who say deporting otherwise lawful undocumented immigrants destabilizes their communities and makes immigrants afraid to report crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88250ec1-d8cd-11ef-9df9-0000a1ace356</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pardons. Elon Musk. West Bank. Prince Harry. Winter storm. Ichiro Suzuki. Drug-addicted rats. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66bc8e30-d8b8-11ef-8d27-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prince Harry settles lawsuit with Rupert Murdoch’s newspapers for a ‘substantial’ sum and an apology</title>
      <description>The trial over claims of illegal information gathering and high-level cover-up ended practically before it began as Murdoch’s group paid the prince and former Labour Party deputy leader Tom Watson an undisclosed sum. The newspaper group apologized for “serious intrusion” into their private lives. Over the years, 1,300 others had agreed to settle with the media conglomerate over similar issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cfcd4b1-d8b0-11ef-b6c1-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 11:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
