<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 22:03:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rooftop solar panels are flooding California’s grid. That’s a problem.</title>
      <description>California, which leads the nation in solar power, and its grid operator are grappling with a strange reality: so much solar that some of it has to be thrown away. The glut is raising electricity prices and could undercut future renewable energy investment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86740971-00ef-11ef-8aaa-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 21:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Test your ‘dream economy’ against reality and see which one is better</title>
      <description>We’ll tell you how your vision tracks with the real world — and what other readers thought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbfbe441-00df-11ef-8fcc-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 19:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court justices hearing case on homeless ban appear divided between protecting rights and controlling a worsening problem</title>
      <description>In arguments on a Grants Pass, Ore., statute outlawing sleeping in public places, attorneys for unhoused people argued that criminalizing homelessness when there were no other living options was cruel and unusual punishment — and thus unconstitutional. The city insisted it needed flexibility to protect public health and public spaces. The court’s decision, likely to be announced in late June, could be the most significant ruling on the rights of the unhoused in decades.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d23b5f2-00cd-11ef-a43a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 17:24:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel has not provided evidence that large numbers of U.N. Palestinian refugee agency workers have militant ties, report finds</title>
      <description>The Colonna report found that the U.N. Relief and Works Agency is in need of reforms to ensure it remains neutral, but said Israel has yet to offer evidence supporting its claims that significant numbers of UNRWA employees are members of Hamas or Palestinian Islamic Jihad. The Israeli allegations in January spurred the United States and other donor countries to suspend funding for UNRWA amid a humanitarian crisis in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d437aab0-00c5-11ef-b6b1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to revive a friendship killed by a hostile text?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to revive a friendship killed by a hostile text?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3863ff0-00c2-11ef-a021-0000a1acef1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 16:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening statements are set to begin in Trump’s hush money trial in New York. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Prosecutors and defense lawyers are expected to start laying out their cases in Donald Trump’s trial for allegedly falsifying business records to hide a hush money payment during the 2016 presidential election campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6b67dd0-00ad-11ef-b321-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:39:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A double album in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0901a91-00ac-11ef-8b22-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 13:33:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid. Trump trial. Supreme Court. Israeli general. Solar power. Meta AI. Cicadas. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">780a7e30-0097-11ef-8ca0-0000a1ace070</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military intelligence chief resigns over Oct. 7 Hamas attack</title>
      <description>Maj. Gen. Aharon Haliva is the first general of the Israel Defense Forces staff to offer to leave his position due to the failures that led to the attack and the war in Gaza. He serves as commander of the IDF’s Operations Directorate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">067d2590-0085-11ef-9364-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nelly Korda wins the Chevron Championship for her fifth consecutive LPGA Tour victory and second career major title</title>
      <description>Korda, 25, matched the LPGA Tour record for consecutive victories held by Nancy Lopez and Annika Sorenstam. The world’s No. 1 player claimed her other major title at the 2021 Women’s PGA Championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a89306a0-0031-11ef-9379-000a1ace39dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 22:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At Trump’s N.Y. trial, the jury pool spoke, and he had to listen</title>
      <description>The jury selection process for Donald Trump’s hush money trial created something akin to a national focus group — albeit with a New York accent — giving ordinary Americans a chance to offer their opinions and reflections on the former president’s nearly five decades in the public spotlight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a8b2e80-0022-11ef-bf6a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 21:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My boyfriend’s parents treat me like an outsider</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My boyfriend’s parents treat me like an outsider</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b82e840-0011-11ef-b71f-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 19:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c3714b0-fff8-11ee-9379-000a1ace39dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her love of backcountry skiing drew her to boarding school in the Swiss Alps. Then the mountain crumbled underneath her.</title>
      <description>Emily Franciose adored backcountry treks so much that she left her Colorado home to attend Ecole d’Humanité, a small boarding school in Hasliberg, Switzerland. But an accident caused the Wellhorn mountain to fall apart beneath her skis — and left her parents wanting answers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">200f34a1-fff2-11ee-b8a7-00000a1ace5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 15:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Oregon city outlawed homeless people from sleeping in public. The Supreme Court will decide whether the ban is cruel and unusual.</title>
      <description>Grants Pass, Ore., banned sleeping in public spaces, even though the city has no homeless shelters. The court decision, expected in late June, could be the most consequential ruling on the rights of the unhoused in decades, and could either uphold or derail increasingly punitive efforts across the country that seek to deal with homelessness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fec8cf20-ffe9-11ee-82b9-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 14:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c714ae1-ffe6-11ee-a4b7-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2024 13:53:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A real Prince of Denmark tries to live a normal life in Washington</title>
      <description>Prince Joachim and his family arrived last summer for his diplomatic post, leaving behind royal drama to raise a family in D.C. with hardly anyone noticing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d758420-ff61-11ee-b96f-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 21:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes $95 billion foreign aid package, with funds for Ukraine and Israel, with bipartisan support</title>
      <description>Republicans joined with Democrats to push the measures, which also include money for Taiwan and to regulate TikTok, in a package assembled by House Speaker Mike Johnson (R-La.). Johnson defied far-right members to put Ukraine aid on the floor and may face a motion to oust him from the speakerhip because of it. The Senate is expected to take up the foreign aid package early next week and President Biden has signaled he will sign it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e878e151-ff40-11ee-9bde-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 18:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl LPs now outsell CDs. See how records get made in 2024.</title>
      <description>Artists like Taylor Swift and Beyoncé are releasing vinyl albums with exclusive tracks, cover art and more. On this Record Store Day, see how they are made— from lacquer to label.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">246d96b0-ff37-11ee-b599-0000a1ace9c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the 10 financial documents you need to keep forever, our personal finance columnist says. Scan and shred the rest.</title>
      <description>These are the 10 financial documents you need to keep forever, our personal finance columnist says. Scan and shred the rest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c71d7c0-ff30-11ee-9fca-000a1ace1f21</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 16:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riding the baddest bulls made him a legend — and plenty of money. Until one broke his neck.</title>
      <description>J.B. Mauney is arguably the greatest rodeo bull rider ever. But since suffering a career-ending injury last September, he has been forced to grapple with the aftermath of a career built on the edge of primal danger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">742644a0-ff22-11ee-9729-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37a35e31-ff1a-11ee-b304-0000a1aceb16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 13:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress extends controversial warrantless surveillance law for two years</title>
      <description>Laboring into the early hours of Saturday morning, Congress squeaked through the renewal of a surveillance program that U.S. spy agencies regard as one of their most valuable tools, and that critics on the left and the right say intrudes on Americans’ privacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c047500-fed1-11ee-b144-0000a1acec5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 04:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Volkswagen workers in Tennessee pass historic vote to unionize in a victory for the UAW</title>
      <description>In Chattanooga, Tenn., autoworkers became the first at a Southern auto factory to approve a union with an election since the 1940s. They join a handful of unionized auto factories in the South, where local laws make it harder for unions to organize. The UAW has endorsed President Biden.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1c210d0-febd-11ee-8441-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 02:29:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to withdraw troops from Niger after Washington and junta fail to agree on continued military presence, U.S. officials say</title>
      <description>Kurt Campbell, the State Department’s No. 2 official, met with Niger’s prime minister Friday and accepted his demand that American forces leave the West African country, a move the Biden administration had resisted and one that is certain to transform the United States’ counterterrorism posture in that part of the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a7e3ed0-feb2-11ee-b4e6-0000a1aceb66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 01:06:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Northern Virginia serves as the world’s internet hub. Its neighbors are paying a price.</title>
      <description>Football-field-size buildings that hold computers processing nearly 70 percent of the world’s internet traffic are gobbling up electricity at a rate that’s unsustainable. Coal will be the key.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9e46e90-fe98-11ee-9a8c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 22:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration issues new Title IX rules protecting transgender students, sexual assault victims</title>
      <description>The Title IX regulations bar schools from discriminating against transgender students, feeding a culture clash with conservative states and school boards that have limited transgender rights in schools. The new rules also mandate changes for how schools handle claims of sexual assault and harassment on campus.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b1b7490-fe83-11ee-841c-000a1ace4d53</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 19:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full jury seated for Trump’s N.Y. trial; opening statements expected next week</title>
      <description>A full 12-member jury and six alternates have been chosen for Donald Trump’s trial in New York on criminal charges, which began Monday, setting the stage for opening statements next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93b6db80-fe74-11ee-b6a7-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 17:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My cousin is telling people I’m excluding her ‘out of revenge’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My cousin is telling people I’m excluding her ‘out of revenge’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da8bc460-fe6c-11ee-b71f-0000a1ace9fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to know about Taylor Swift’s surprise double album drop overnight</title>
      <description>Swift released “The Tortured Poets Department” at midnight on Friday. She had something else in store a couple of hours later. Here are the main things to know about the album.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad94fb61-fe68-11ee-a56f-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 16:20:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rare bipartisan House coalition advances $95 billion foreign aid bill to likely passage, which could cost Johnson his speakership</title>
      <description>The legislation, crafted by House Speaker Mike Johnson (R-La.), contains funding for Ukraine and Israel in their wartime conflicts, as well as money for Indo-Pacific allies. More Democrats than Republicans supported the procedural motion known as a rule. The House is slated to vote on passage midday Saturday. But that vote could trigger a move to oust Johnson from his right flank, many of whom oppose Ukraine aid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a66e2b0-fe64-11ee-bd03-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 15:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s retaliatory strike on Iran appears to have been designed to avoid escalating tensions, officials and analysts say</title>
      <description>Israeli officials said the strike was meant to send Iran a message after Tehran launched hundreds of drones and missiles at Israel last weekend — the vast majority of which were shot down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4453b680-fe5b-11ee-9b6e-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 14:44:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ef904e0-fe52-11ee-95bf-0000a1ace0d2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For the first time, polluters may have to pay to clean up PFAS, commonly known as ‘forever chemicals,’ under new EPA rule</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency designated two of the most pervasive forms of PFAS as hazardous substances under the nation’s Superfund law. The rule could help hundreds of communities affected by contamination and could mean billions of dollars of liabilities for major chemical manufacturers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f00d9ec0-fe4f-11ee-801e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 13:22:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump jury. Title IX. Land rules. Rising temperatures. Women’s sleep. Taylor Swift’s surprise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f86f66c0-fe3b-11ee-b42d-00000a1ace68</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel carries out airstrike on Iran in retaliation for Tehran’s drone and missile attack, Israeli official says</title>
      <description>The official, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discus sensitive military matters, said it was intended as a message to Iran that Israel had the ability to strike inside the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd27a6c0-fe0a-11ee-a296-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 05:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death Valley is alive this year. A super bloom is the latest sign.</title>
      <description>Just weeks after the resurrection of a long-dead lake, the area’s native wildflowers are bursting into bloom. These fleeting phenomena can be traced to the unusual and record-setting precipitation that has inundated California in recent months. Scientists estimate that tens of thousands of acres have bloomed simultaneously, sparking delight from new arrivals and those who have carefully tended Death Valley — more often one of the world’s most extreme places.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8fba2d0-fddb-11ee-90d2-0000a1ace1cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 23:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. vetoes U.N. resolution that would grant full member status to Palestinian state</title>
      <description>The United States voted against a U.N. Security Council resolution that aimed to extend full member status to a Palestinian state. Robert Wood, the alternate American representative to the United Nations, said afterward that Washington “continues to strongly support a two-state solution.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">284270f1-fdcd-11ee-b057-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 21:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve jurors have been selected in Trump’s N.Y. hush money trial after two were dismissed earlier in the day</title>
      <description>A dozen jurors have been selected to hear former president Donald Trump’s hush money trial in Manhattan, rapidly pushing the proceedings closer toward opening statements. Jury selection is expected to continue Friday as alternates are sought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2b18ce0-fdc5-11ee-873f-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 20:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can blood tests detect cancer? Some patients are using them already.</title>
      <description>New tests can detect cancer by measuring “signals” in your blood. Many experts say these tests represent a remarkable new chapter in cancer detection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88e465e0-fdbd-11ee-bcee-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 19:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. just changed how it manages a tenth of its land, putting conservation on equal footing with mining, grazing and drilling</title>
      <description>The Interior Department’s rule represents a seismic shift in the management of roughly 245 million acres of public property.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">963d3c80-fda9-11ee-87cb-000a1acedd72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which U.S. congressional districts benefit from Ukraine aid? Marc Thiessen has the details.</title>
      <description>We mapped the U.S. congressional districts producing weapons for Ukraine. Many are represented by members who have been vocal opponents of Ukraine aid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a74174a0-fda5-11ee-9bc6-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 17:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dickey Betts dies at 80. The singer and guitarist co-founded the Allman Brothers Band and wrote hits including ‘Ramblin’ Man.’</title>
      <description>Betts wrote several of the band’s most enduring compositions, including the instrumentals “In Memory of Elizabeth Reed” and “Jessica,” and the pastoral love song “Blue Sky.” He remained best known for the 1973 song “Ramblin’ Man,” which became the band’s only top-10 hit on the Billboard Hot 100. The lyrics, set against a bouncy, upbeat melody, expressed the resigned and unrepentant wanderlust of a man “born in the back seat of a Greyhound bus / Rollin’ down Highway 41.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de2b1a00-fda2-11ee-881e-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: What will this parent do after the kids graduate and move out?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: What will this parent do after the kids graduate and move out?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7d05280-fd9d-11ee-902c-0000a1ace171</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 16:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico city enduring toxic arsenic levels in water offers a reminder: Safe water is not available to all Americans</title>
      <description>State and federal records show that in each of the past 16 years, drinking water samples tested in majority-Latino Sunland Park, N.M., have contained illegally high levels of arsenic. Now, residents fear the health consequences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80d44550-fd9a-11ee-9a21-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 15:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump trial juror was dismissed, and potential issues arose with a second juror. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>One of the seven jurors who had been sworn in was excused after telling New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan that news reports described her profession and other personal details that led her to be identified as a juror. Jurors’ names are not being released publicly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4cb8a25-fd8d-11ee-beee-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 14:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. imposes new sanctions after Iran’s attack on Israel. The economic penalties target Iranian drone production.</title>
      <description>U.S. Treasury Secretary Janet L. Yellen said the Biden administration’s actions would “degrade and disrupt” Iran’s drone program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5566aad0-fd8a-11ee-b711-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why did this animal cross the road? Play today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee2e0630-fd87-11ee-8be6-0000a1ace9b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s hush money trial further splinters his relationship with his beloved New York</title>
      <description>He was a publicity hound and a tabloid star — a Queens boy made good who burst onto the Manhattan scene through sheer force of personality. But now, in a trial that began Monday, the former president’s long-running and turbulent love affair with the city seems to have finally run into irreconcilable differences.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c1f2020-fd84-11ee-bd1e-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 13:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine strike. Trump trial. Impeachment vote. Arizona abortion. Toxic water. Volcanic eruption. Escaped elephant. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfbfb2d0-fd72-11ee-9a60-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
