<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 07:02:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: It was a remarkably civil affair, and other takeaways from the vice-presidential debate</title>
      <description>Gov. Tim Walz ended strong over Jan. 6 but struggled early, while Sen. J.D. Vance appeared confident and tried to blunt the GOP position on abortion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62813aa0-8075-11ef-85cc-0000a1ace421</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 04:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More policy, fewer zingers: Vance, Walz spar on Middle East, border and more in debate. Follow our coverage for the second half.</title>
      <description>Republican JD Vance and Democrat Tim Walz introduce themselves on the national stage in the early-goings of the vice-presidential debate, while also having more in-depth discussions on Israel's war in Gaza and with Iran, climate change, immigration at the U.S. southern border, taxes and the economy than voters saw during presidential debates between Donald Trump and Joe Biden and Kamala Harris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47a95f00-8061-11ef-a2ae-0000a1ace495</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:54:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'That is pure demagoguery': Follow along as 11 columnists discuss the VP debate</title>
      <description>'That is pure demagoguery': Follow along as 11 columnists discuss the VP debate</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76e82af0-805f-11ef-8627-0000a1aceb7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 01:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance and Tim Walz to face off tonight in the only planned vice-presidential debate. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters provide news and analysis as Donald Trump and Kamala Harris’s running mates take the stage in New York for what could be the final big event ahead of November’s presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47087a31-8058-11ef-99ad-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 00:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding help to get sober is hard. In deep-red Kentucky, it’s even harder as a mom.</title>
      <description>The state is rocked by the opioid crisis and has imposed a near-total ban on abortion, meaning residents who become pregnant while grappling with addiction have few options.

With substance use factoring into half of the state’s maternal deaths, help extends only so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09d570e0-8040-11ef-8d0f-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 21:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Amos dies at 84. The ‘Good Times’ and ‘Roots’ actor risked his career to protest demeaning portrayals of Black characters.</title>
      <description>Amos, a running back turned actor, appeared in scores of TV shows, including as Gordy the weatherman on “The Mary Tyler Moore Show” and the adult Kunta Kinte on “Roots,” the landmark ABC miniseries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd092e31-8024-11ef-b41e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:43:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>120 additional sexual assault lawsuits to be filed against Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs</title>
      <description>A team of lawyers announced Tuesday that they would be filing 120 sexual assault lawsuits against Sean Combs — a massive legal action that appears to have few, if any, precedents in the #MeToo era. The lawsuits would exponentially increase the number of sexual abuse accusations against the music producer. Combs is being held at a Brooklyn jail on federal charges of racketeering and sexual trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe3500d0-8020-11ef-8bf2-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 18:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband blabs to a friend about spouse’s health issues</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband blabs to a friend about spouse’s health issues</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02c31141-801d-11ef-99cf-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>'Scourge of terrorists and child pornographers’: Geraldine Brooks takes readers inside the IRS’s small, pivotal cybercrime unit</title>
      <description>Geraldine Brooks on Jarod Koopman of the Internal Revenue Service</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379c42a1-8019-11ef-bc6b-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:18:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran fires missiles at Israel, Israeli military says, as sirens sound across the country. Follow our live updates.</title>
      <description>The attack comes days after Israel killed Hezbollah leader Hasan Nasrallah, a key Tehran ally, and as Israeli ground forces enter Lebanon, sparking fear of an even wider war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7cf80f0-8014-11ef-b41e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 MacArthur ‘genius grant’ winners include a TV creator, an acclaimed author and a biologist who studies lizards</title>
      <description>A violinist, a poet, a disability activist and a cabaret performer are also among the recipients of the $800,000 fellowship. See the full list.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">860cd4a0-800e-11ef-97f7-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 16:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran is preparing an imminent ballistic missile attack against Israel, White House official says</title>
      <description>The United States is “actively supporting” Israel’s “defensive preparations,” the official said, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive matter. “A direct military attack from Iran against Israel will carry severe consequences for Iran.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd3a1e80-7ffe-11ef-bc6b-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 14:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sunflowers and soup in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58ea9e90-7ff9-11ef-98aa-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris and Trump in close North Carolina race, Post poll finds, a state that hasn’t voted for a Democrat for president since 2008</title>
      <description>North Carolina voters are closely divided in the choice between Donald Trump and Vice President Kamala Harris, according to a Washington Post poll, with no sign that Lt. Gov. Mark Robinson’s scandal-plagued campaign for governor has diminished Republican enthusiasm for the former president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef31ea50-7fec-11ef-8dcd-0000a1ace08d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 12:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vance vs. Walz. Helene’s floods. Israeli incursion. Abortion ban. Pete Rose. Vanishing fireflies. Jimmy Carter. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59c3cd10-7fe4-11ef-8692-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 11:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Port strike freezes shipping from New England to Texas, posing a threat to the U.S. economy five weeks before Election Day</title>
      <description>A strike by the longshoremen’s union representing 47,000 dockworkers has caused East Coast and Gulf of Mexico container ports to shut down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46bac613-7fad-11ef-8fcd-0000a1aceb73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 04:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Helene’s floods caught North Carolina off guard</title>
      <description>Before this scenic, rustic Great Smoky Mountain refuge turned into a trap many didn't see coming, there were signs of Hurricane Helene’s unthinkable potential. Many said the torrential rains and flash floods — which have claimed an untold number of lives — caught them unprepared. Now Helene, one Haywood County official said, could “change how we think about storms in the mountains.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59d1daa0-7f93-11ef-930e-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 01:20:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Rose dies at 83. The Cincinnati Reds star awed fans but was banished from baseball after gambling on his team as manager.</title>
      <description>Known as “Charlie Hustle” for his aggressive style of play, Rose won two World Series titles with his hometown team on his path to breaking the all-time hits record.
In 1989, reports surfaced that he was deep in debt from gambling. Major League Baseball’s commissioner’s office released a report that year with testimony from Rose’s bookies that he bet on baseball — including the Reds, while he was managing the team — during the 1985, ’86 and ’87 seasons. He was banished from the game and excluded from the Hall of Fame.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">043fccd0-7f86-11ef-a9eb-0000a1acebc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 23:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel launches ground operation in southern Lebanon, Israeli military says</title>
      <description>The invasion, described by the Israel Defense Forces as “limited, localized, and targeted ground raids,” is aimed at destroying Hezbollah infrastructure and pushing their fighters away from the Israeli border after 11 months of drone and rocket strikes on northern Israel. A U.S. official told The Post on Monday that Israel has said the operation will be limited in scope and smaller than its last ground invasion of Lebanon in 2006.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48976760-7f83-11ef-8c0c-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 23:25:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This photo of a lavish breakfast on the National Mall captivated the country. The real story was a mystery — until now.</title>
      <description>In 1974, a dozen friends wore morning coats and floor-length dresses, dined on oysters, drank champagne and danced together as a string quartet played in the shadow of the Lincoln Memorial. The extravagant scene drew in a Washington Post photographer, who captured the moment in a mysterious image that would ricochet around the country in newspaper reprints.
A year ago, the daughter of that photographer met one of the participants and began to put the pieces together.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">698e3d60-7f77-11ef-b497-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 22:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA staff got into Vance’s and Walz’s medical files, sparking a Justice Department investigation</title>
      <description>Department of Veterans Affairs officials this summer discovered that at least a dozen employees at the agency’s massive health-care arm, the Veterans Health Administration, improperly accessed medical files for vice-presidential nominees JD Vance and Tim Walz, who are both veterans. It’s not clear yet whether the records were shared with anyone outside VA.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42ef4520-7f6b-11ef-9b96-000a1aced27b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 20:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In an exclusive interview, Marc Thiessen spoke to Donald Trump about Project 2025, deterrence and Trump’s own immigrant story</title>
      <description>Trump wants to make deterrence and (really) legal immigration great again</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413e9ad0-7f5e-11ef-b7ba-0000a1acebc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 19:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inspectors raised safety and sanitation issues at Boar’s Head plant in Virginia long before listeria outbreak that killed 10 people</title>
      <description>A Washington Post examination revealed that filthy conditions, aging equipment and haphazard cleaning at the plant may have made some of its products microbial time bombs waiting to explode.

The hunt for the deadly agent unfurled across a month and a half — an effort The Post reconstructed through more than two dozen interviews with former Boar’s Head employees; victims, their families and lawyers; and public health officials and food safety experts as well as a review of more than 150 pages of documents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1922c9c0-7f56-11ef-a3e1-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 18:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Second-grader feels ‘neglected’ during Mom’s time with teen sisters</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Second-grader feels ‘neglected’ during Mom’s time with teen sisters</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f5b1721-7f45-11ef-a9da-0000a1ace549</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 16:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Completely and entirely erased’: How Helene swallowed one mountain town</title>
      <description>Scenes of destruction and suffering lay almost everywhere in Swannanoa, N.C. — cars in tree limbs, mangled homes, mud-choked roads, and people desperate for water and food after Helene devastated western North Carolina.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb3474a0-7f41-11ef-bdb9-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:37:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dikembe Mutombo dies at 58. The basketball Hall of Famer dominated on defense at Georgetown and in the NBA.</title>
      <description>The all-star center for the Denver Nuggets, Atlanta Hawks and Philadelphia 76ers — who also played for three other teams during an 18-year NBA career — built an off-court legacy through his humanitarian work in central Africa.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44962d40-7f3d-11ef-a59c-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 15:04:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel has told U.S. it is planning a limited ground operation in Lebanon that could start imminently, U.S. official says</title>
      <description>The American official said Israel’s planned campaign would be smaller than its last war against Hezbollah in 2006 and would focus on clearing out militant infrastructure along the border to remove the threat to Israeli border communities. On Monday, Israeli forces carried out limited raids in Lebanon, according to an Israeli familiar with the operation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c641e1f1-7f37-11ef-81e4-000a1acebfc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 14:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A legend of the stage and screen in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53e180e0-7f30-11ef-bdb9-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 13:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helene’s damage. Vance vs. Walz. Hezbollah leader. Port strike. Kris Kristofferson. AI veto. Earth’s atmosphere. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2519d830-7f1b-11ef-917c-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how Helene left a trail of devastation from Florida to the Carolinas, killing at least 87 in its path</title>
      <description>Videos show the massive swath of destruction from the storm, with its devastating combination of water and wind that hit hundreds of miles from Florida to the Southern Appalachians. Entire communities were flooded; some were cut off with no way in or out. Homes and vehicles have been swept away, and hundreds of roads have been washed out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ddec1f60-7ebe-11ef-b7ba-0000a1acebc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 23:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kris Kristofferson dies at 88. The singer-songwriter was a rugged but tender-hearted star of song and screen.</title>
      <description>His trove of country-pop hits such as “Me and Bobby McGee” and “Help Me Make It Through the Night” pushed him to the forefront of American popular composers. His sophisticated compositions juxtaposed freedom and loneliness, romance and loss, tenderness, and a degree of carnality.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af99b30-7eb6-11ef-a1d4-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 22:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Under a Texas sun, agrivoltaics offer farmers a new way to make money</title>
      <description>Solar grazing helps farmers feed their flocks while the expanding solar industry provides more clean energy to the grid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81173070-7eac-11ef-99e1-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 21:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Austria’s Freedom Party on track to win the national parliamentary election, an unprecedented far-right victory in the post-war era</title>
      <description>If election projections hold up, the win would be the first national victory for the country’s far right since World War II. But the anti-immigration Freedom Party may not be able to find coalition partners to form a government under provocative leader Herbert Kickl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">930b32b0-7e9b-11ef-a3a4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 19:46:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mark Robinson’s campaign for North Carolina governor came crashing down and induced GOP panic</title>
      <description>Top Republicans, including Donald Trump, long championed or enabled Robinson. Then came a CNN report tying Robinson to an old account on an obscure online porn forum. This was not a failure to vet their candidate, critics said — it was a conscious decision to look away.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d611e80-7e8c-11ef-b7ba-0000a1acebc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 17:56:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">220608c1-7e7c-11ef-987d-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 16:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flooded North Carolina towns continue to struggle with communication problems as relatives search for loved ones after Helene</title>
      <description>The true extent of the storm’s toll remains unknown in western North Carolina, where cell phone and internet signals have been spotty. Buncombe County has received more than 1,000 reports of people looking for loved ones, the county manager said Sunday. But the number is expected to decrease as signals are restored.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b13926b0-7e79-11ef-97db-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 15:44:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1372da00-7e67-11ef-a3bb-0000a1ace568</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 13:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a phone call, Arizona’s top three Democrats debated how to handle 98,000 voters with no record of providing citizenship proof</title>
      <description>Their predicament was “an urgent, a dire situation,” Gov. Katie Hobbs said, according to audio of the call obtained by The Washington Post. Secretary of State Adrian Fontes said critics would “beat us up no matter what the hell we do.” Attorney General Kris Mayes worried they would be accused of rigging the 2024 election in a crucial state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4aea5501-7df7-11ef-a13e-0000a1acec60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Sep 2024 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why millions of Americans give up control of their thermostats</title>
      <description>Power companies are tapping into customers’ smart thermostats, EV chargers and home batteries to prevent blackouts when the grid is strained.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11685e10-7de5-11ef-bb33-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 22:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Biblical devastation’ in North Carolina towns flooded by Helene</title>
      <description>The death toll from Helene climbed as emergency responders rushed to rescue residents in small mountain towns that have been cut off from communication. Rescuers said they were struggling to respond to the high number of calls reporting emergencies. Anxious relatives took to Facebook to search for loved ones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fab11b51-7ddd-11ef-8213-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 21:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private messages sent in 2020 show JD Vance harshly criticizing Trump’s record</title>
      <description>In messages sent near the end of President Donald Trump’s time in office, Vance wrote that Trump had “thoroughly failed to deliver on his economic populism.” The timing contrasts with Vance’s explanation for how he transformed from an anti-Trump critic in 2016 to a supporter in 2020, saying that he was converted by Trump’s success as president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7891b00-7dc9-11ef-a657-000a1ace0d80</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 18:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My daughter is a harsh parent. I’m worried for my granddaughter.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My daughter is a harsh parent. I’m worried for my granddaughter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32bd5211-7db7-11ef-95e4-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 16:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half the U.S. has banned trans girls from girls sports. A mom may be among the first to face a penalty.</title>
      <description>When Jessica Norton let her trans daughter play volleyball, the school district accused her of breaking Florida law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ba72d80-7db0-11ef-a525-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 15:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4dcd900-7d9d-11ef-8cc6-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 13:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah chief Nasrallah’s power spanned the Middle East. His death is a blow to Iran and could plunge Lebanon into crisis.</title>
      <description>Hasan Nasrallah, a Shiite cleric, was born in a shantytown in Beirut and rose through Hezbollah’s ranks in the 1980s. He strengthened ties with Tehran and transformed the group into a sprawling political, military and social movement, with considerable power both inside Lebanon and in countries such as Syria and Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17d71f90-7d98-11ef-8cc6-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 12:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military says Hezbollah leader Hasan Nasrallah is dead; militant group has not confirmed</title>
      <description>The Shiite cleric was one of Israel’s archfoes for decades and led one of the most powerful militant groups in the region with backing from Iran. His death could sharply escalate the risks of a wider Middle East war nearly a year after Hamas’s deadly raid from Gaza touched off Israeli attacks that have claimed tens of thousands of lives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ba86f01-7d74-11ef-848d-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 08:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chicago White Sox set modern MLB record for futility with their 121st loss</title>
      <description>The White Sox lost to the host Detroit Tigers on Friday night to fall to 39-121 with two games to play. They eclipsed the 1962 New York Mets, who went 40-120-1 in their first season as a major league franchise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">642faf01-7d35-11ef-a941-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2024 01:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hezbollah’s leader was target of Israeli strike, says person familiar with information shared by Israel. His condition is unknown.</title>
      <description>Hasan Nasrallah, the head of Hezbollah, was the target of an Israeli strike in Beirut on Friday, according to a person familiar with information provided by Israel to the United States after the attack, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss sensitive matters. Residents of Lebanon’s capital reported large blasts and pillars of smoke billowing over neighborhoods in the city’s south.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8642f7b0-7d0c-11ef-9673-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 20:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 20 killed in three states as Helene’s devastating flooding continues. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>More than 4 million are without electricity in a swath of the country as Helene continues its northward path, leaving a deadly and destructive trail from Florida through Georgia and into the Carolinas. As severe floodwaters swept through one North Carolina town, knocking out communication, the mayor there described the scene as “simply apocalyptic.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df9adc60-7cf3-11ef-a660-00000a1ace0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 17:13:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department charges three men in alleged Iranian plot to hack into email accounts of Donald Trump's campaign staff</title>
      <description>Masoud Jalili, Seyyed Ali Aghamiri and Yasar Balaghi “prepared for and engaged in a wide-ranging hacking campaign” targeting current and former U.S. officials, political campaigns, members of the media, and others, the indictment charges. The plot allegedly included an effort to try to share campaign documents with news organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be95efe0-7cef-11ef-933c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 16:44:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
