<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 01:26:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military launches investigation after reports of World Central Kitchen aid workers killed in Gaza strike</title>
      <description>The food aid nonprofit’s founder, celebrity chef José Andrés, said that several employees had been killed in an Israeli strike. The Israel Defense Forces said it was aware of the allegations and would conduct “a thorough review” after photos appearing to show the killed aid workers circulated on social media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae5d5e0-f08a-11ee-a653-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump posts $175 million bond to keep N.Y. authorities from seizing his property after civil fraud judgment</title>
      <description>The former president’s posting of the bond was necessary to keep New York Attorney General Letitia James from initiating legal steps to take over his properties, including Trump Tower. An appeals court panel recently ruled to reduce the bond from $464 million in the massive civil fraud judgment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6fcc340-f087-11ee-8dc5-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rematch of 2023 title game, Caitlin Clark and Iowa face Angel Reese and LSU for spot in Final Four. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>After their epic, taunt-filled matchup in last year’s national championship game, Clark’s Hawkeyes are about to take on Reese’s Tigers in the NCAA women’s basketball tournament’s Albany Region 2 final.
Follow our coverage for live updates, highlights and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b5cd4e1-f07b-11ee-a5d0-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our reporters went into Gaza’s largest hospital for the first time in months. Mass destruction and the smell of death awaited them.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters were among a handful of foreign journalists taken inside al-Shifa hospital in Gaza City by the Israeli military on Sunday after two weeks of heavy fighting with militants. The hospital, once Gaza’s premier medical facility, has been destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ce8d21-f06f-11ee-90a5-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Supreme Court allows strict state abortion ban to take effect, but greenlights putting the issue on the November ballot</title>
      <description>Florida’s conservative high court ruled that the state’s constitution does not protect abortion rights. But in a separate decision it also ruled that voters can decide in November whether an amendment enshrining the right to an abortion should be approved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d289dbf0-f064-11ee-b815-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Republicans texted and emailed their way into a money problem</title>
      <description>Small-dollar donations to Donald Trump and the GOP are way down since 2019 and 2020. But the former president’s team says they see a turnaround coming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64e33690-f056-11ee-bc7a-0000a1acec87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 18:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says an Israeli strike killed a senior Iranian commander in Syria</title>
      <description>A strike near Iran’s embassy in Damascus killed Mohammad Reza Zahedi, a senior commander in Iran’s Revolutionary Guard Corps, according to Iranian state media. Syrian state media reported that at least five people were killed in the strike.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bfaadf0-f04d-11ee-9090-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bird flu detected in person who had contact with infected Texas cattle, the second case of a human sickened by this strain in U.S.</title>
      <description>A highly virulent bird flu detected in dairy cows in five states has now been confirmed in a human patient in Texas. The case raises growing concern about mammal-to-mammal transmission of the virus and questions about whether this pathogen is now more easily transmitted among mammals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34adc180-f04b-11ee-bc9e-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: It’s tough to split kid duty with someone who runs 15 hours a week</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: It’s tough to split kid duty with someone who runs 15 hours a week</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04a22620-f041-11ee-82a2-0000a1acef87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgraced ex-lawyer Alex Murdaugh sentenced to 40 years for laundering millions, AP reports. He is already serving 2 life sentences.</title>
      <description>Murdaugh, who is also serving life sentences for the murder of his wife and son, admitted to 22 financial crimes, including stealing settlements meant for a quadriplegic man’s family.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43289b30-f03d-11ee-b651-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America suddenly has a record number of bees. What happened to colony collapse?</title>
      <description>The new Census of Agriculture shows that America’s honeybee population has rocketed to an all-time high. But the census has limitations, so The Post’s Department of Data dug deep into the numbers and found two big forces behind the boom, one surprising and one quite familiar. What we didn’t find was good news for native pollinators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a0eb10-f031-11ee-a08b-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A much-debated movie prop is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e37113d0-f02c-11ee-8942-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 13:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel protests. Baltimore cleanup. Trump attacks. Major storm. AT&amp;T breach. March Madness. Skin-bound book. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9c3a780-f016-11ee-af5e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The men’s Final Four is set: North Carolina State, Purdue, Connecticut and Alabama will compete for a national championship</title>
      <description>Top overall seed Connecticut will continue its championship defense against sharpshooting Alabama on Saturday in Glendale, Ariz., and fellow No. 1 seed Purdue will take on No. 11 seed N.C. State.
The semifinal winners will play for the national title April 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d46dff0-efb7-11ee-a5d8-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls his globe-trotting ex-diplomat ‘my envoy.’ Neither is in office.</title>
      <description>Richard Grenell is meeting with far-right foreign leaders, attacking President Biden and offering a glimpse at what U.S. foreign policy could be like in a second Trump term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0509bf0-efa1-11ee-8ff3-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">598f2d50-ef7d-11ee-a062-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar eclipse towns have two big concerns as they welcome a tourism boom: Traffic and port-a-potties</title>
      <description>Small towns in the path of totality are pulling off logistical feats to welcome visitors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f339480-ef6c-11ee-9ae3-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cf80ef0-ef63-11ee-9f0c-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Marines are testing out new, more nimble and lethal regiments designed to gain the advantage if there’s a war with China</title>
      <description>Across an island-hopping battlefield in Asia, the Marines are embedding new forces that would partner with allies to sink ships and down fighter planes if Beijing moves to take Taiwan or challenge for supremacy in the South China Sea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40e0ee10-eedd-11ee-8eaa-000a1acedd61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 21:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Steven Mnuchin’s plan to buy TikTok, but not its algorithm, has some insiders bewildered</title>
      <description>The former treasury secretary is telling investors he aims to buy TikTok without its export-blocked code, according to two people familiar with the pitch who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The plan would require Mnuchin to rebuild a service built on billions of lines of code — including the popular video app’s coveted recommendation algorithm — an idea observers said suggests a lack of familiarity with how tech companies actually work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98434ee0-eec5-11ee-9ea1-0000a1ace22d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: He told me he saw a future with me. Now he has a new girlfriend.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: He told me he saw a future with me. Now he has a new girlfriend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd7f93d0-eeb2-11ee-b99b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is pushing EVs. Who actually wants them? Listen to the latest episode of ‘Impromptu,’ our new podcast.</title>
      <description>The Biden administration wants America to transition to electric cars. But who’s actually opting in? Post Opinions columnists talk about how to navigate the speed bumps and what needs to happen to rev up this revolution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">703c8a40-eeae-11ee-bee0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 15:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSU’s Kim Mulkey holds grudges, battles everyone and keeps winning</title>
      <description>As the women’s game finally takes center stage, Mulkey is viewed by some as college basketball’s cartoonishly ornery supervillain and an essential part of the show. But some former players say that while her coaching approach gets results, including four national titles, it also takes a toll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5f0a80-eea3-11ee-9fce-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 14:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f502cd0-ee99-11ee-a19e-0000a1ace946</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We are trying to find some way not to retreat,’ Ukrainian President Zelensky tells David Ignatius</title>
      <description>President Volodymyr Zelensky delivered a stark message to Congress in an interview on Thursday as Russian missiles were pounding southern Ukraine: Give us the weapons to stop the Russian attacks, or Ukraine will escalate its counterattacks on Russia’s airfields, energy facilities and other strategic targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1267300-ee01-11ee-a285-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration greenlights more bombs and warplanes for Israel despite widening rift with Netanyahu</title>
      <description>The State Department in recent days quietly approved the transfer to Israel of billions of dollars in bombs and fighter jets despite Washington’s concerns about an anticipated military offensive in southern Gaza that could threaten the lives of hundreds of thousands of Palestinians. The arms packages include more than 1,800 MK84 2,000-pound bombs, which have been linked to previous mass-casualty events.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ece4480-edfc-11ee-b486-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My fiancé and I are minimalists. My dad keeps sending us junk.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My fiancé and I are minimalists. My dad keeps sending us junk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">968462e0-edeb-11ee-ab2e-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials guarded Baltimore’s Key Bridge from terrorism and decay for decades. They didn’t foresee a ship collision.</title>
      <description>After the Sept. 11 attacks and the 2007 Minneapolis bridge collapse, Maryland officials scrambled to ensure the bridge was safe from similar events. Then, this week, a 95,000-gross-ton container ship hit it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e788964-ede1-11ee-bc10-000a1ace0f0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 15:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a8cbb61-eddc-11ee-aa1d-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Gossett Jr. dies at 87. He was the first Black man to win the best supporting actor Oscar.</title>
      <description>In a career spanning nearly seven decades, Gossett became one of the most recognizable actors of his generation. He worked on Broadway and other stages starting in the 1950s, appearing in dramas such as Lorraine Hansberry’s landmark “A Raisin in the Sun.” The boundary-breaking actor later won an Emmy for “Roots” (1977) and an Academy Award for “An Officer and a Gentleman” (1982).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db365470-edd2-11ee-959b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks to accelerate the nation’s transition to electric trucks and buses, a follow-up to tougher rules on cars</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency finalized a rule requiring manufacturers to reduce emissions from new trucks, delivery vans and buses.

The rule — aimed at reducing climate impacts — could also cut harmful air pollution in disadvantaged communities. Some truck makers had lobbied to weaken it and might challenge it in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80afcbe0-edcc-11ee-8976-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyoncé’s new record, ‘Cowboy Carter,’ dropped at midnight — and it's a lot of album. Here are our takeaways.</title>
      <description>The record was hyped as the R&amp;B and pop star’s first “country” full-length. It ain’t, she would later clarify. So what kind of album is it? It’s a journey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2149ad0-edc5-11ee-b70b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore bridge cleanup. Biden fundraiser. Sam Bankman-Fried. Deadly bus crash. Census update. AI clones. Beyoncé. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e92a0f0-edbb-11ee-8976-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s ‘America First’ views date back to the 1930s, Robert Kagan writes. Americans rejected it then. Will we now?</title>
      <description>Trump’s anti-Ukraine view dates to the 1930s. America rejected it then. Will we now?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">181cb5e0-ed52-11ee-ac34-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 22:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden promised to install thousands of EV charging stations. Only 7 have been built.</title>
      <description>President Biden has long vowed to build 500,000 stations. But more than two years after Congress allocated $7.5 billion toward the effort, only seven stations have been built in four states: Hawaii, Ohio, New York and Pennsylvania.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a53be20-ed4d-11ee-bdeb-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) vetoes bills that would have created a legal market for recreational cannabis in Virginia</title>
      <description>Passed on largely party-line votes by the Democratic-controlled General Assembly, the identical House of Delegates and Senate bills would have set commercial standards and licensing requirements for large and small retailers to sell cannabis products. Virginia legalized the possession of small amounts of recreational marijuana three years ago but never settled on a mechanism to allow legal sales.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16be5800-ed4a-11ee-b5d9-0000a1ace8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 21:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dodgers took a risk when they committed so much to Shohei Ohtani. They decided it was worth it.</title>
      <description>The Los Angeles Dodgers did not commit to the two-time MVP from Japan solely because of the value he can provide on the field. Adding Ohtani to the most star-studded roster in the sport felt to them as though it would create off-field value of an entirely different scale. But for the first time in his career, the eyes that follow Ohtani, his team and the league that made him its poster child are staring for less flattering reasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd733d40-ed3d-11ee-8cdf-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 20:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina will proceed with voting map judges previously said ‘exiled’ Black voters rather than wait for Supreme Court decision</title>
      <description>A federal court ruled Thursday that time had run out to draw a new congressional district in South Carolina and said the state could use its existing map this year even though it had earlier determined that map was unconstitutional. The panel of three judges last year concluded that South Carolina’s Republican-led legislature “exiled” 30,000 Black voters from the district to make it safer for a White GOP incumbent, Rep. Nancy Mace. The Supreme Court heard arguments on the case in October but has yet to rule on it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">802603b0-ed22-11ee-8ea2-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 16:44:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sam Bankman-Fried sentenced to 25 years in prison for convictions related to his cryptocurrency trading platform, FTX</title>
      <description>The FTX co-founder was also ordered to repay over $11 billion. Bankman-Fried was convicted in November of fraud, conspiracy and money laundering after FTX’s victims suffered billions in losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6ccbec1-ed1b-11ee-b6f2-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 15:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New red-eyes will take to the skies in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8c3b950-ed06-11ee-bb32-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 13:25:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Bridge collapse. Joe Lieberman. Disney vs. DeSantis. Methane rule. Opening Day. Leap second. ‘Titanic.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f20a600-ecf2-11ee-8b42-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remains of two people recovered in Patapsco River near Baltimore Key Bridge wreckage, according to people with knowledge of search</title>
      <description>Divers have been searching for at least six people missing since the bridge collapsed early Tuesday when it was struck by a container ship leaving the port in Baltimore. The two people whose remains were recovered from the water have not been publicly identified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">800cd6a0-ec83-11ee-8819-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:46:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Joe Lieberman has died at 82. The doggedly independent four-term U.S. senator was also a vice-presidential candidate.</title>
      <description>As Al Gore's running mate in 2000, he was the first Jewish candidate on the national ticket of a major party. Eight years later, he supported Republican presidential candidate John McCain over Barack Obama.

Lieberman viewed himself as a centrist Democrat, solidly in his party’s mainstream with his support of abortion rights, environmental protection, gay rights and gun control. But he was also unafraid to stray from Democratic orthodoxy, most notably in his consistently hawkish stands on foreign policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94df4d70-ec82-11ee-9fa2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can’t get thrown out for thinking, so take a swing at George Will’s baseball quiz</title>
      <description>Worse than a Mets doubleheader would be striking out on these questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c284e321-ec7d-11ee-abe2-0000a1ace82b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 21:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitals and Wizards are set to stay at Capital One Arena until 2050 after teams’ owner Ted Leonsis and D.C. reach a deal</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) reached an agreement with Leonsis, the CEO of Monumental Sports &amp; Entertainment, to keep the teams playing at the downtown D.C. arena. The news comes after the city of Alexandria announced it was ending negotiations to bring the teams to a new arena in Potomac Yard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8d962b0-ec7a-11ee-9673-0000a1aced89</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alexandria says it has stopped negotiating to bring Wizards and Capitals to the city, so arena project won’t go ahead</title>
      <description>The teams currently play at Capital One Arena in downtown D.C., where they have a lease that runs until 2047.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76849300-ec76-11ee-ba58-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 20:13:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change is altering Earth’s rotation enough to mess up clocks and impact the need for a ‘negative leap second,’ study finds</title>
      <description>The melting of polar ice is affecting Earth’s rotation and could have an impact on precision timekeeping, according to a paper published Wednesday in the journal Nature. The new calculations suggest that in 2029 it may be necessary to insert a “negative leap second” into the calendar to get the planet’s rotation in sync with Coordinated Universal Time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3137d2c0-ec68-11ee-baff-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLB team owners approve Baltimore Orioles sale. The deal shifts control of the team to David Rubenstein just before Opening Day.</title>
      <description>Rubenstein, one of the founders of the Carlyle Group private equity firm, and a cohort of investors reached an agreement with the Angelos family in January; their pact makes the Baltimore native the team’s “control person,” the term Major League Baseball uses to designate the lead decision-maker for a franchise. The Orioles are set to face the Los Angeles Angels on Thursday in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d857cf40-ec56-11ee-b994-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Over-attentive couple give new meaning to ‘neighborhood haunt’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Over-attentive couple give new meaning to ‘neighborhood haunt’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">957493f0-ec53-11ee-a2a0-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeSantis allies agree to settlement with Disney, ending legal feud that erupted after company’s opposition to ‘don’t say gay’ law</title>
      <description>The board appointed by Florida Gov. Ron DeSantis (R) to oversee Disney’s former special taxing district voted Wednesday in favor of settling a lawsuit with the entertainment giant. The governor and Disney have been in a protracted legal battle for the last two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e8c55c1-ec50-11ee-9025-0000a1ace352</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:42:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
