<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 05:01:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The sorrow, hope and longing of Japan’s ‘Missing Post Office’</title>
      <description>The old post office is a repository for 60,000-plus pieces of mail: letters, birthday cards and New Year’s greetings sent from all over Japan to those with no forwarding address: Lost friends and pets; past and future selves; and, most frequently, the dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036b84b0-ed96-11ef-88ca-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 01:16:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Social Security official exits after clash with Musk’s DOGE over attempts to access sensitive data, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Billionaire Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service has pushed for sensitive records at the Social Security Administration, leading to the departure of its acting commissioner. The agency is responsible for managing pension payments for more than 70 million American seniors and manages significant troves of personal data, including those related to Americans’ work history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d2df432-ed8d-11ef-be6f-00000a1acedb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All 80 people on Delta flight that crashed and turned upside down at Toronto airport have been evacuated from the plane, FAA says</title>
      <description>The regional jet departed Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport on Monday morning. What caused the aircraft to flip upside down on the tarmac remains unknown, but weather conditions at the time were harsh.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf634bd0-ed81-11ef-bd40-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 22:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Estranged sister is back after ideological hairpin turns</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50b667c1-ed51-11ef-beb3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was a Jan. 6 juror. What she learned surprised her.</title>
      <description>When the jury summons for federal criminal court arrived in my mailbox in November 2023, Lauren Ober knew she had to answer it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3a3c91-ed4d-11ef-af96-0000a1ace410</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 16:36:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Presidents’ Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c435100-ed3c-11ef-9440-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 highlights from ‘Saturday Night Live’s’ sprawling and unexpectedly poignant 50th anniversary special</title>
      <description>The three-hour-plus broadcast was packed with A-list stars including Eddie Murphy, Tina Fey, Paul McCartney, Adam Sandler and many more, who paid tribute to its five-decade run.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2d78aa0-ed37-11ef-a842-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 14:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Trump’s firings. Ukraine talks. Freed hostage. Deadly storm. Healthy drinks. SNL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae77c641-ed26-11ef-ab97-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘Saturday Night Live’ 50th anniversary special starts soon. Join our reporters and critics for live insights, analysis and more.</title>
      <description>Luminaries including Adam Sandler, Eddie Murphy and Tina Fey will be on hand as the NBC staple celebrates a half-century of comedy. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db03900-ecc9-11ef-83ac-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:50:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s DOGE seeks access to personal taxpayer data, raising alarm at IRS</title>
      <description>The unusual request would put sensitive data about millions of American taxpayers in the hands of Trump political appointees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b479dd0-ecc5-11ef-a5f5-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relatives and records cast doubt on Guantánamo migrants being ‘worst of the worst’</title>
      <description>The Washington Post spoke with family members of six Venezuelan men being held in Guantánamo. Despite the impression given by Homeland Security officials, the migrants were taken into custody after crossing the border — not during a targeted immigration operation in a U.S. city or at a jail or prison while serving a sentence. The relatives firmly deny they are members of the Tren de Aragua gang.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4123b6b0-ecb5-11ef-8d6b-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 22:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mountain by any other name should still be Denali, Alaskans say</title>
      <description>Denali means “the great one,” and those living in the snow-shrouded midst of North America's tallest peak question why one of President Donald Trump's first actions was to rename it for a 19th-century predecessor who never set foot in Alaska.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5176beb0-ec9a-11ef-9366-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9fc3e90-ec89-11ef-8bbd-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 17:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was the deadliest workplace in America. So why didn’t safety regulators shut it down?</title>
      <description>Inspectors issued more than 100 safety violations and millions in fines. Yet deaths and injuries continued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9def47b1-ec83-11ef-b0ff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 16:32:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f48b790-ec73-11ef-ae3f-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:36:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powerful, potentially damaging winds possible in D.C. area this afternoon</title>
      <description>After downpours exit midday, very strong winds are expected in the afternoon, potentially gusting to 50 to 60 mph. The National Weather Service has issued a high wind warning until 10 p.m. and cautions that power outages are possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">525dd1e0-ec6f-11ef-96d1-0000a1ace502</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2025 14:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A stunning pattern of suicide blights one of the Marines’ most iconic jobs</title>
      <description>Marine Corps drill instructors are a national symbol of discipline. But for some, their imposing persona belies a dark reality, a joint investigation by The Washington Post and Military.com found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07b61b10-ebf3-11ef-ba5c-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 23:17:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my Muslim parents about my Christian boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfdc7130-ebc5-11ef-ac36-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine rejects Trump request for half of its rare-mineral wealth in exchange for continued U.S. assistance</title>
      <description>The offer and Ukraine’s consideration of it rippled through European diplomatic circles not only for its audacity but also because the war-ravaged country appeared to be seriously considering how to reach a deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92f03a40-ebc0-11ef-ab97-0000a1ace20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 17:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A portrait of a mystery woman was found hidden beneath a century-old Picasso</title>
      <description>With the help of advanced imaging technology, conservators at the Courtauld Institute of Art in Britain discovered the figure under the moody blues of the “Portrait of Mateu Fernández de Soto,” painted by Pablo Picasso in 1901. The woman’s fashionable chignon hairstyle, shoulders and fingers are visible in the infrared image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71fe9230-ebbd-11ef-97d7-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 16:53:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal documents show how DOGE wrote the playbook for Trump’s DEI purge — and whom they plan to fire next</title>
      <description>A team of staffers at the U.S. DOGE Service mapped out President Donald Trump’s campaign to eliminate diversity, equity and inclusion programs from the government, documents show. DOGE’s three-phase plan lays out how the team next intends to fire hundreds of workers in non-diversity roles, as well as employees who work in offices that exist by law to protect equal rights, according to documents obtained by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ff11b40-ebab-11ef-9e0a-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">916f3700-eba9-11ef-819e-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 14:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American hostage Sagui Dekel-Chen released by Hamas after 16 months in captivity, following tense week during Gaza ceasefire deal</title>
      <description>Dekel-Chen, an American Israeli dual national, was released alongside Sasha Alexander Troufanov and Iair Horn, as part of an exchange deal that is expected to see 369 Palestinian prisoners and detainees released. His wife was pregnant when he was kidnapped, and the father of three has not yet met his newborn child.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f845b41-eb7a-11ef-8c47-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 08:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice officials seek to drop Eric Adams case after 7 veteran prosecutors resign over request to do so</title>
      <description>The Justice Department on Friday filed a motion to drop the charges against Adams, asking a judge to decide the fate of a case that has ignited a dramatic standoff between the Trump administration and veteran prosecutors. In an extraordinary meeting earlier Friday, acting deputy attorney general Emil Bove gathered members of the Justice Department's Public Integrity Section to see who might be willing to sign the motion asking a judge to dismiss the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6ac1e31-eb2d-11ef-b26b-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 23:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hawk crew in fatal midair collision may not have received crucial tower instruction, NTSB says</title>
      <description>The microphone was depressed aboard the Black Hawk hurtling toward the American Airlines passenger jet on Jan. 29, so the crew may not have heard an instruction from Air Traffic Control to pass behind the jet 17 seconds before impact, the National Transportation Safety Board said Friday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df3efac0-eb12-11ef-9b91-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 20:32:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vice President JD Vance on Friday met with far-right German leader Alice Weidel, the highest-ranking U.S. official ever to do so</title>
      <description>Vance also met with leaders of Germany’s two other major parties, which are locked in competition ahead of Feb. 23 elections, in which Weidel’s Alternative for Germany party might break through a taboo and join a ruling coalition for the first time since World War II.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e85a29e0-eb0d-11ef-aa30-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:57:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband punched the floor out of anger and broke his hand</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband punched the floor out of anger and broke his hand</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b467900-eb02-11ef-89fc-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lead Eric Adams prosecutor also quits over demand to drop charges, saying only a ‘fool’ or ‘coward’ would do so</title>
      <description>Hagan Scotten, who led New York Mayor Eric Adams’s federal corruption case, has quit over the Trump administration’s demand that the case be dismissed, calling any lawyer who would move in court to toss the charges a “fool” or “coward,” according to a copy of a letter obtained Friday. This week, the acting U.S. attorney in New York and five Justice Department officials in Washington resigned over the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b42fbed0-eb00-11ef-b5e1-0000a1ace887</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 18:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D analysis of the view from the helicopter’s cockpit shows how pilots could have mixed up jets in fatal DCA crash</title>
      <description>The Post’s examination — based on a 3D model using flight data and air traffic control transmissions, and interviews with former Black Hawk pilots — shows how the American Airlines jet and a second plane, though separated by miles, would have appeared close to one another near the horizon before the deadly collision on Jan. 29.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bf359a0-eae8-11ef-b7c3-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 15:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f712f60-eae0-11ef-b60d-0000a1ace2cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 14:29:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal firings. Kennedy confirmation. Ukraine. Crash reconstruction. Bird flu. Winter storm. Roman ruins. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39f3bbb0-eacb-11ef-9713-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google and Apple return TikTok to their app stores</title>
      <description>The tech companies are restoring the social media app to their online stores, weeks after removing it under a law that banned TikTok in the United States. President Donald Trump previously ordered a temporary pause on the ban.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78929730-ea79-11ef-8e1e-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 02:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s team invited a far-right activist on his trip to Europe, alarming Pentagon officials fearful of political infringement</title>
      <description>Trump administration officials at the Defense Department invited Jack Posobiec, who is known for peddling conspiracy theories and trolling political opponents online, to participate in Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s first official travel overseas, according to a planning document obtained by The Washington Post and people familiar with the decision. The move has exacerbated concerns among military officials that the nonpolitical institution will be dragged into partisan warfare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c70b4e40-ea68-11ef-9e2b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration tells agency heads to fire probationary staff in effort to shrink federal workforce, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Thousands across the government were laid off Thursday in messages delivered through pre-recorded videos and on group calls, according to people familiar with the matter. There are roughly 200,000 employees hired by the federal government within the past two years to whom the directive might apply, though it was not immediately clear how many would be affected because some, such as those in public safety and law enforcement jobs, were exempted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec20baf0-ea61-11ef-804f-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Justice Department officials resign after Trump administration orders end to prosecution of New York City Mayor Eric Adams</title>
      <description>New York prosecutors so far have not asked the trial judge to dismiss corruption charges against Adams, despite being ordered to do so Monday. Acting U.S. Attorney Danielle Sassoon and two senior officials involved in public corruption investigations in Washington resigned their positions Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac45a270-ea51-11ef-bedc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 21:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Trump’s executive order aiming to restrict health care for transgender youth</title>
      <description>A lawsuit filed by families and LGBTQ advocates challenged an executive order issued by President Donald Trump last month that seeks to block federal support of gender transition care for people under 19, a move that led some hospitals across the country to pause such treatment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f36ba60-ea49-11ef-93b7-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 20:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge grants a one-week extension to the pause on Trump’s attempt to put more than 2,000 USAID workers on leave</title>
      <description>The delay prohibits action by the Trump administration while the judge considers workers’ request for a longer injunction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b596f30-ea41-11ef-bfe8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces new ‘reciprocal’ tariff policy to tax foreign goods at the same rate that other nations apply to American products</title>
      <description>The reciprocal tariffs are in response to what President Donald Trump calls unfair behavior by U.S. trading partners, who in some cases apply higher tariffs to specific American goods than the United States applies to the same products from those countries. They could go into effect in coming weeks or months, according to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7a7e060-ea3c-11ef-9b7c-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Why won’t family help a would-be writer with networking?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Why won’t family help a would-be writer with networking?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11e7a8b0-ea2c-11ef-9e3d-0000a1acec13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 17:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a longtime anti-vaccine activist, is confirmed by the Senate to serve as the nation’s top health official</title>
      <description>The nomination drew opposition from Democrats and medical experts over his controversial views on public health but was bolstered by those who supported his “Make America Healthy Again” campaign focused on childhood obesity and chronic health.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17a5ada0-ea28-11ef-8e81-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uncle Sam’s moment in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a0e4aa0-ea18-11ef-b806-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk’s layoffs. Putin and Trump. Tulsi Gabbard. D.C. helicopters. Homeless camps. Disney warnings. Cosmic messenger. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0b638380-ea02-11ef-99f7-000a1ace6903</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel likely to strike Iran’s nuclear sites in coming months, U.S. intelligence warns</title>
      <description>A preemptive attack would set back Iran’s nuclear program by mere weeks or months but would escalate tensions across the Middle East, according to a U.S. intelligence report. Current and former U.S. officials told The Washington Post those findings derive from an analysis of Israeli planning following the country’s bombing of Iran in late October.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da14aca0-e99d-11ef-a3ce-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s federal worker buyout offer can move forward after judge lifts hold</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Massachusetts declined to further pause the Trump administration’s buyout offer to federal workers, rejecting a call from several labor groups that had sued over the program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e307c1b1-e995-11ef-af4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 23:05:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sedona Prince, women’s basketball star who sparked March Madness reforms, faces abuse claims</title>
      <description>As her profile has grown nationally, Prince, a 6-foot-7 star for Texas Christian University, has faced a string of abuse allegations, according to interviews and records obtained by The Washington Post, including after an altercation on campus last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7aa80e0-e991-11ef-a572-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 22:36:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center board appoints Trump as its chair, and its president confirms she is leaving</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump had already fired board members who were appointed by President Joe Biden, as part of Trump’s plans to control programming at Washington’s premier arts institution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9f4d4290-e979-11ef-9a42-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rural America, more women are saying ‘I don’t’</title>
      <description>In rural America, more women are saying ‘I don’t’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ca9a5c0-e96b-11ef-af4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 18:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he spoke with Putin in their first known call since he took office and they agreed to visit each other’s countries</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has previously demanded that Russian President Vladimir Putin put an end to the war in Ukraine, but Trump has offered few concrete indications of how he would foster a breakthrough.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c68118e0-e966-11ef-9a42-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 17:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tulsi Gabbard is confirmed by the Senate as Trump’s director of national intelligence, overcoming stiff opposition</title>
      <description>The nomination of Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman turned supporter of President Donald Trump, stirred fierce debate. But she managed to assuage the concerns of a handful of Republicans skeptical about her qualifications and past behavior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bdd076f1-e961-11ef-bfbd-000a1ace5295</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:52:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Can I tip less to eat out more? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Can I tip less to eat out more? Our food critic is taking your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b4b2850-e95f-11ef-99f7-000a1ace6903</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 16:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
