<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 06:01:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: One father's search for his daughter, one of the many children missing after Texas floods swept through a summer camp. A previous alert had an incorrect link.</title>
      <description>Between broken tree limbs and muddied cabins, Michael McCown spent Saturday searching the devastated grounds of Camp Mystic for his little girl. She is one of about two dozen girls from the camp who are unaccounted for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0ba8470-5a0b-11f0-840c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 01:52:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One father’s search for his daughter, one of the many children missing after Texas floods swept through a summer camp</title>
      <description>Between broken tree limbs and muddied cabins, Michael McCown spent Saturday searching the devastated grounds of Camp Mystic for his little girl. She is one of about two dozen girls from the camp who are unaccounted for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6469a0-5a09-11f0-b6f4-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 01:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buc-ee’s just opened its first Virginia location. It is truly a behemoth.</title>
      <description>As the supersize Texas-based chain expands toward the Mason-Dixon Line, a new region discovers what the beaver’s all about.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcca8100-59ef-11f0-8def-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 22:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four months of rainfall in four hours: How a deadly downpour caught Texans by surprise</title>
      <description>Meteorologists had cautioned there was potential for flooding across Central Texas. But there was little indication of just how torrential the rain would become, killing more than two dozen people, many of them children at camp.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e33e1e50-59bf-11f0-9279-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best advice about in-laws from therapist Sahaj Kaur Kohli</title>
      <description>Best advice about in-laws from therapist Sahaj Kaur Kohli</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0c4dc0-59ba-11f0-87de-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 16:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A town tried to heal racial divides by removing a statue. It revived Confederate support instead.</title>
      <description>What started as an effort to promote unity in Edenton, North Carolina, by reconsidering its most prominent downtown symbol did the opposite: A chapter of the Sons of Confederate Veterans, long extinct locally, sprang to life.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a6b16b0-59ae-11f0-a1d8-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 14:43:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2dbc3c0-59a3-11f0-a26b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 13:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 24 dead, children still missing after heavy flooding in Central Texas, sheriff says</title>
      <description>Twenty girls were missing from a summer camp on the Guadalupe River after the waterway swelled to historic highs, authorities said earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1985671-594a-11f0-ab17-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 02:51:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs ‘Big Beautiful Bill’ into law, marking his biggest legislative accomplishment</title>
      <description>On a day of patriotic celebration at the White House, President Donald Trump signed his signature piece of legislation — a culmination of a string of successes in recent weeks and a remarkable display of how the president has been able to bend allies and adversaries alike to his agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc869e70-5924-11f0-bf1a-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 22:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 13 dead and 20 children missing in Texas floods as rescue efforts and rain continue</title>
      <description>An all-girls summer camp along the banks of the Guadalupe River in Central Texas was flooded and 20 girls are unaccounted for after heavy rains inundated the region. Gov. Greg Abbott said the state is sending the National Guard and water rescue teams to the area as more rain is expected in coming hours.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54c7ef60-5920-11f0-af74-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 21:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump’s big bill will affect you, from Medicaid cuts to tax credits</title>
      <description>The legislation will affect nearly every American, regardless of their stage in life or income level, with big implications for seniors, families and immigrants. Here’s a breakdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf3d9530-58e3-11f0-b6c1-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 14:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager. It’s your Fourth of July edition of On the Record!</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adbca210-58de-11f0-9bb7-0000a1aceb78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 13:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s bill. Turbocharged deportations. Supreme Court. California fire. Coronavirus. July Fourth. Rare comet. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c0db840-58c6-11f0-adf6-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump ignored GOP warnings and broke a key campaign promise to score a win on the tax bill</title>
      <description>Congressional Republicans on Thursday passed President Donald Trump’s signature $3.4 trillion measure that cuts taxes and spending and sets aside hundreds of billions of dollars for immigration enforcement. But in Trump’s eagerness for a legislative victory, he walked away from his promise not to touch health care — risking the GOP majority in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff0b7540-5859-11f0-a772-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 22:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headed to a cookout? These summer sides are ready in 20 minutes or less.</title>
      <description>Headed to a cookout? These summer sides are ready in 20 minutes or less.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2f53a80-5850-11f0-a667-000a1acecf48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 21:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly 140 EPA staffers who signed ‘dissent’ letter criticizing agency’s direction under Trump administration are put on leave</title>
      <description>Administration officials on Thursday sent emails to 144 employees in connection with a letter that criticized the Environmental Protection Agency’s current direction and policies, and 139 were placed on leave. Officials said the workers are now facing investigations because they signed the letter using their official job titles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5897ec0-5842-11f0-ac59-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 19:21:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes massive tax cut and immigration enforcement package, sending Trump a major legislative win</title>
      <description>The House voted to extend President Donald Trump’s first-term tax cuts and dramatically increase spending on immigration enforcement, while reversing many of the Biden administration’s accomplishments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d1f1861-583c-11f0-8764-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:33:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE is increasingly targeting undocumented migrants with no criminal record</title>
      <description>A dataset analyzed by The Washington Post offers one of the most detailed snapshots yet of whom Immigration and Customs Enforcement is arresting and removing as it attempts to fulfill President Donald Trump’s campaign promise to carry out the largest deportation operation in U.S. history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79c7cd90-582f-11f0-a54d-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 17:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend snatches phone to read her texts with male best friend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend snatches phone to read her texts with male best friend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4536e640-5827-11f0-a197-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 16:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court will take up the legality of bans on transgender athletes in women’s sports</title>
      <description>The cases involve laws in Idaho and West Virginia that ban transgender athletes from participating in women’s and girls’ school sports teams.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21cdddf0-5816-11f0-aac5-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘historic’ replacement in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1cfa32a0-5812-11f0-a54d-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 147,000 jobs in June, a solid showing even as businesses and households grapple with economic uncertainty</title>
      <description>The Labor Department released its latest snapshot of the state of the labor market. Forecasters had predicted 110,000 jobs to be added in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0803790-5809-11f0-913c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 12:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House vote. Sean Combs verdict. Asylum ruling. Jobs report. Del Monte bankruptcy. Ancient DNA. Rare cloud. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e35d6810-57fc-11f0-86b1-0000a1ace371</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s massive tax and immigration bill clears key procedural hurdle in House, setting up final vote</title>
      <description>The Republican-led House narrowly voted Thursday to adopt a rule that allows debate to begin on the package, which President Donald Trump has urged Congress to pass by July 4. The Senate approved the measure Tuesday. House leaders have been scrambling to nail down support from wavering Republicans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca4fbec0-57e0-11f0-ba66-0000a1aceb70</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 07:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge bars Trump administration from expelling asylum seekers</title>
      <description>A U.S. district judge has invalidated a proclamation that President Donald Trump signed on his first day in office that declared an “invasion" on the border and invoked emergency presidential powers to deport migrants without allowing them to apply for asylum. The ruling is a major blow to the administration’s efforts to curtail crossings at the U.S. southern border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">891057c0-5782-11f0-8d93-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 20:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How quickly would a nuclear war be over? 45 minutes.</title>
      <description>How a nuclear attack on the U.S. might unfold, step by step</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db5d60a0-5777-11f0-ba79-0000a1acef1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 19:07:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man pleads guilty to murdering four University of Idaho students in 2022, as part of deal to avoid death penalty</title>
      <description>Bryan Kohberger will face consecutive life sentences. The mysterious killings at an off-campus house disrupted a quiet Idaho college town and drew national attention as authorities searched for weeks for the killer before arresting Kohberger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7d518940-576e-11f0-ae02-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 18:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. grew increasingly frustrated with University of Virginia’s DEI efforts before its president resigned, letters show</title>
      <description>Over two months this spring, Justice Department officials sent seven letters to the University of Virginia, alleging possible racial discrimination in admissions and hiring, inaction to address antisemitism on campus, and a failure to remove diversity, equity and inclusion efforts. Officials warned that a failure to take “immediate corrective action” could lead to punitive steps, including possible termination of federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ce66fe0-5764-11f0-9304-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 16:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents debate making their recent master’s graduate pay rent</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents debate making their recent master’s graduate pay rent</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb7876d0-575d-11f0-8326-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 16:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP tax bill includes a $6,000 ‘senior deduction.’ Here’s who qualifies.</title>
      <description>The provision emerged from President Donald Trump’s campaign pledge to end taxes on Social Security. But experts say many Americans are excluded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a694a270-5759-11f0-9259-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 15:31:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Their server asked, ‘How was everything?' Should they have told the truth?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Their server asked, ‘How was everything?' Should they have told the truth?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29a26d40-5756-11f0-9bb2-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 15:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs was found not guilty of sex-trafficking and racketeering, but was convicted of a lesser charge</title>
      <description>Combs had been charged with one count of racketeering conspiracy; two counts of sex trafficking by force, fraud or coercion; and two counts of transportation to engage in prostitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a0360b0-5750-11f0-83bb-000a1ace71d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 14:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A verdict has been reached in the Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs sex-trafficking trial. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>A jury has decided Combs’s future after a seven-week trial that delivered bombshell testimony detailing brutal violence, sexual predation and “freak-offs.” Follow our coverage as we learn the verdict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0803d5a0-574e-11f0-a71e-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 14:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you for not smoking in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d294bbf0-5748-11f0-a670-0000a1ace058</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tax bill. CBS settlement. Sean Combs trial. Trans athletes. Jimmy Swaggart. AI notetakers. Wimbledon. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b95724d0-5733-11f0-9fd5-000a1acef02b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBS owner Paramount agrees to settle Trump lawsuit over Harris interview for $16 million</title>
      <description>Donald Trump sued the network in October, alleging that it manipulated Harris’s answers “to tip the scales” in her campaign’s favor. CBS said the interview was simply edited for time. The money will go to Trump’s future presidential library, not to him directly, and the network will not apologize as part of the settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fceb3e91-56ff-11f0-8a4a-0000a1acecb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 04:49:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When he’s 72, this former outfielder will still be on the New York Mets’ payroll. Here’s how the deal came about.</title>
      <description>When the Mets wanted to buy out Bobby Bonilla’s contract 26 years ago, a life insurance salesman turned sports agent crafted an unconventional agreement that the team is still paying for.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3e6a712-56c3-11f0-9a83-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 21:38:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jurors reach partial verdict in Sean ‘Diddy’ Combs trial, but undecided on racketeering charge</title>
      <description>A judge is expected to tell the jurors to keep deliberating until they have full agreement. The seven-week trial delivered bombshell testimony detailing brutal violence, sexual predation and “freak-offs.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d62940-56c0-11f0-ad4c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 21:17:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coco Gauff goes down in shocking first-round Wimbledon upset after her French Open victory</title>
      <description>Gauff, the tournament’s No. 2 seed, was ousted in straight sets by Dayana Yastremska. Gauff was coming off her second Grand Slam singles title with a win in the French Open last month. The 25-year-old Yastremska had never made it past the fourth round in three previous appearances at Wimbledon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5185171-56b7-11f0-b55e-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 20:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to move FBI to the D.C. building that housed USAID, thwarting effort to relocate bureau to Maryland</title>
      <description>The timing was not clear for when the FBI would move to the Ronald Reagan Building and International Trade Center, according to three people who had been briefed on the decision. The FBI had been slated to move to Greenbelt, Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f3cf472-56a4-11f0-af93-0000a1ace8c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:53:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flood and severe thunderstorm watches in effect across the region into tonight</title>
      <description>Widespread storms are expected this afternoon and evening capable of producing torrential rain, damaging winds and dangerous lightning. The National Weather Service is particularly concerned about flooding because of “off the charts” moisture levels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeab2320-56a1-11f0-b423-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 17:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes Trump’s sweeping tax and spending legislation, sending it back to the House before final passage</title>
      <description>The measure would extend tax cuts from President Donald Trump’s first term that are set to expire, while adding new tax breaks and spending hundreds of billions on immigration enforcement and defense. It would also cut social safety net programs and add trillions to the national debt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2021fea0-5695-11f0-9471-0000a1acec85</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent looks to defer meeting daughter’s much-older boyfriend</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent looks to defer meeting daughter’s much-older boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b08414c0-5694-11f0-8f67-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Swaggart dies at 90. The televangelist was felled by a sex scandal, etched in public memory by his tear-streaked confession.</title>
      <description>At his peak in the late 1980s, Swaggart reached millions of viewers. His broadcasts generated revenue of $140  million a year with a signature combination of fire and brimstone, music, and the relentless marketing of Swaggart-branded items, including Bible study manuals, T-shirts and copies of Jesus’ crown of thorns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc1a87e1-568d-11f0-87f6-000a1ace0850</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 15:13:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Researchers asked 5 AI models to fact-check Trump. Here’s what they learned.</title>
      <description>Though Trump appears to support AI, that does not mean AI supports him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5ac69d0-568b-11f0-960b-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the attempted assassination of Trump and Biden’s final efforts to save his campaign coincided on one pivotal day: July 13, 2024</title>
      <description>One year later, a new book goes behind the scenes of a pivotal day during the most consequential presidential campaign in U.S. history. The book, “2024: How Trump Retook the White House and the Democrats Lost America,” by three current or former Post reporters, will publish July 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8182ebe0-5687-11f0-b409-0000a1ace43d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 14:27:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fish from a lab in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48b9c730-5681-11f0-a3c0-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 13:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate vote. ‘Alligator Alcatraz.’ Idaho suspect. Sean Combs trial. Hurricane data. Proxy quitters. Cruise rescue. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872b9d70-566a-11f0-82ba-0000a1aceddb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How federal officials cracked the biggest health care fraud scheme in U.S. history</title>
      <description>Hundreds of thousands of Americans complained about receiving mysterious Medicare bills. Now federal officials say it was part of a $10.6 billion scheme.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ca9dd60-55f6-11f0-9e24-0000a1acec11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 21:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE secured the power to view records that could benefit Elon Musk’s businesses for years, a Post examination found</title>
      <description>Musk said the U.S. DOGE Service was scouring government data for federal waste. Now some of that data could be valuable by giving the world’s richest man a competitive advantage in the private sector, experts say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">239fd6a0-55d8-11f0-9dc9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 17:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
