<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 14:02:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Filing for bankruptcy again in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e463ac1-03fd-11f0-8fdd-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 13:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes. Deportations. Federal workers. Midwife arrest. Wildfires. FBI warning. Returning astronauts. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19f94d30-03e8-11f0-9881-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes on Gaza have killed more than 400 people, Gaza’s Health Ministry says, after Israel broke its ceasefire with Hamas</title>
      <description>Israel’s military resumed a large-scale bombing campaign in the Gaza Strip early Tuesday, with health officials saying large numbers of people were trapped under rubble. The White House said Israel had consulted it about the strikes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08b71b50-03e4-11f0-8438-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 10:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel resumes deadly strikes in Gaza, jeopardizing ceasefire with Hamas</title>
      <description>At least 20 Palestinians were killed and 50 injured, the Gaza Health Ministry said, as Israel vowed to increase its “military strength” against Hamas amid stalled negotiations between the two sides.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">794641a1-03a5-11f0-b6db-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 03:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials push back on order barring Alien Enemies Act deportations, escalating their fight with federal courts</title>
      <description>The administration for weeks has questioned the power of judges to constrain the president, harshly attacking judges who issue nationwide injunctions and finding ways to circumvent certain adverse rulings. On Monday, the government cast doubt on a judge's authority to halt deportations of alleged gang members under the Alien Enemies Act.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">946b8fe0-038b-11f0-93d3-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:57:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visiting Kennedy Center, Trump says he envisions remaking annual Honors event and suggests he could host it</title>
      <description>The cultural center's board voted to expand who picks honorees for its marquee event celebrating major figures in culture. The president also said the Kennedy Center would bring in more Broadway hits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1576ace2-0388-11f0-82a8-0000a1ace243</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 23:32:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In a Trump-supporting county, some residents worry Medicaid cuts could throw them back into an opioid spiral</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and other Republicans have said entitlement programs like Medicaid, Medicare and Social Security will remain untouched, even as he pushes for a contraction of federal spending. But Democrats and congressional bookkeepers warn that such cuts are impossible without slashing essential services that benefit low-income Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6b235b0-036a-11f0-a928-000a1ace6bc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 20:02:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 hotel red flags that should make you run in the other direction</title>
      <description>Does that hotel listing look too good to be true? Industry insiders and experts offer tips on what to scrutinize before booking a hotel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12abcbb0-0349-11f0-8686-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 16:01:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The 11 best bets to win the NCAA men’s basketball tournament</title>
      <description>Who is most likely to win it all? Before you fill out your tournament bracket, read our analysis to discover which teams have the best chance at claiming the national championship next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c3ca0b0-033c-11f0-9723-0000a1ace82c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning onto ‘We the Best’ Street in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17a9ebc0-0334-11f0-8686-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 13:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s deportations. Voice of America. Deadly storms. U.S. strikes Houthis. Nightclub fire. March Madness. Volcano. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee06f160-031e-11f0-9ab3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House official says 137 immigrants were deported under Alien Enemies Act and questions judge’s power to block such removals</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio touted video on social media showing shackled immigrants being forced off airplanes in El Salvador, hours after a federal judge barred deportations under the wartime statute.
A White House official who spoke on the condition of anonymity said a single judge should not have the power to usurp the president’s executive authority, adding that the fact that two of the three flights were out of the United States before the judge’s order “strengthens our case.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bece58e2-02d1-11f0-b6db-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:47:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NCAA women’s basketball tournament bracket is set. See the full field of 68 teams here on our interactive page.</title>
      <description>UCLA, South Carolina, USC and Texas earned No. 1 seeds in the annual March Madness event.
Opening-round play begins Wednesday on the road to the Final Four in Tampa next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ab8fa0-02cb-11f0-aaff-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 01:03:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NCAA men’s basketball tournament bracket is set. See the full field of 68 teams here on our interactive page.</title>
      <description>Auburn, Duke, Houston and Florida earned No. 1 seeds in the annual March Madness event.
Opening-round play begins Tuesday on the road to the Final Four in San Antonio next month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">122f8eb1-02b8-11f0-808c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 22:43:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NCAA tournament men’s and women’s brackets will be revealed tonight. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>March Madness is here, and it all starts tonight on Selection Sunday. The men’s tournament selection show starts at 6 p.m. Eastern, followed by the women’s tournament selection show at 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08173150-02b1-11f0-85bb-0000a1ace9df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 21:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to prepare for a recession before it’s too late, according to personal finance columnist Michelle Singletary</title>
      <description>Escalating trade wars, federal worker layoffs and market turmoil make for a gloomy economic future. If a downturn is coming this year, here are some ways to prepare yourself mentally and financially, Singletary writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4875c3c0-0297-11f0-8337-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump tapped Kari Lake to lead Voice of America. Then he dismantled it.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s campaign to break apart the federal bureaucracy and control U.S.-backed news content across the globe has effectively gutted VOA, potentially forcing it to go dark for the first time since World War II.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eec46580-0290-11f0-85bb-0000a1ace9df</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 18:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9daed00-027f-11f0-8549-0000a1ace122</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 16:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fierce storm system that killed at least 34 people in six central states heads to East Coast, bringing a risk of tornadoes</title>
      <description>At least 66 tornadoes have been reported in seven states, leveling homes and leaving trails of debris. Wildfires and dust storms have raged from Kansas to Oklahoma and Texas, dropping visibility and fueling deadly car pileups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">860665f1-0279-11f0-8aca-0000a1aceb11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 15:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49efe4a1-026b-11f0-8565-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Mar 2025 13:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump from deporting Venezuelan migrants under Alien Enemies Act and orders planes in the air to turn around</title>
      <description>The president had invoked the wartime Alien Enemies Act for the first time since World War II, targeting alleged members of Venezuela's Tren de Aragua gang. A federal judge then granted a request from civil rights groups to temporarily stop him from deporting the Venezuelans under the act and said any planes in the air with such migrants must return to the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a71047d0-01f6-11f0-af10-0000a1ace101</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 23:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump invokes centuries-old Alien Enemies Act to speed up deportation of Venezuelan immigrants accused of being gang members</title>
      <description>The president issued the proclamation shortly before a federal judge is expected to hear a challenge to the centuries-old wartime law. The provision allows the administration to arrest and deport migrants affiliated with the Tren de Aragua gang without a court hearing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1bd3881-01e0-11f0-a0ad-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 21:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. launches large-scale military strikes against Yemen’s Houthis as Trump issues sharp warning to Iran</title>
      <description>In a statement on social media announcing the operation, President Donald Trump vowed to use “overwhelming lethal force” against the militant group in response to its “unrelenting campaign of piracy, violence, and terrorism against American, and other, ships, aircraft, and drones.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c3e6f81-01d0-11f0-b68f-0000a1acec37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 19:03:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump guts several congressionally mandated agencies and cancels Biden-era environmental policies</title>
      <description>One of the president’s latest executive orders is aimed at severely curtailing funding to several agencies, including one that oversees the media outlet Voice of America and the Wilson Center, a respected nonpartisan think tank. Another order cancels 19 Biden-era environmental and labor regulations, including one that mandated a $15-an-hour minimum wage for federal contractors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">235ef560-01cb-11f0-b0be-0000a1ace134</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:27:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We analyzed dozens of ultra-processed snacks. These are the healthiest options.</title>
      <description>Your snacking habit could have a significant impact on your health. Nutritious whole foods are the best options, but sometimes the most convenient or satisfying option is a packaged snack. To help you make healthier choices, we created a guide to snacks that are lower in salt, sugar, fat and other additives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c4632c0-01b8-11f0-990a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 16:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 10 killed by storms in Missouri, authorities say, with tornado risks set to peak Saturday across swath of U.S.</title>
      <description>The Missouri State Highway Patrol said the number of deaths became clearer Saturday morning after tornadoes, thunderstorms and hail raked the state overnight. Numerous significant tornadoes are expected by afternoon and evening, with the highest risk across several states in the Deep South.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbf7a5a0-01ad-11f0-8cd1-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 14:57:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01290d50-01a3-11f0-b6d4-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 13:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate passes standalone bill to avert a $1 billion hit to the D.C. budget in GOP's continuing resolution</title>
      <description>The bill — led by Sens. Chris Van Hollen (D-Maryland) and Susan Collins (R-Maine) — must go back to the House for approval, and it is unclear whether Republicans there will support it. If it does not pass the House, the district must still contend with what's expected to be more than $1 billion in budget cuts, which city officials have warned could impact every corner of the D.C. government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5adb61f0-0125-11f0-b991-0000a1acef08</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Government shutdown averted as Senate votes to extend funding, but Democrats remain bitterly divided over strategy</title>
      <description>The move sends a continuing resolution to keep the government funded through Sept. 30 to President Donald Trump to sign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e3454b1-0123-11f0-975d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 22:25:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measure to avert government shutdown advances in Senate with Democratic support. The final vote is expected later today.</title>
      <description>The Republican-authored resolution cleared a procedural hurdle that required 60 votes. A final Senate vote on the measure, which is supported by President Donald Trump, is expected later Friday ahead of a midnight deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be8e8720-0118-11f0-bfe6-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 21:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Will enough Democrats vote to advance a GOP bill to avert a government shutdown? Follow the Senate vote count live.</title>
      <description>Senate Minority Leader Charles E. Schumer said Thursday that he plans to support the Republicans’ funding bill — but he is likely to need seven other Democrats to overcome a filibuster. A government shutdown is set to begin after midnight if Congress does not approve funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab0a7100-0113-11f0-8bdc-000a1ace4b21</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My mother-in-law and sister-in-law are estranged. Is it a big deal?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My mother-in-law and sister-in-law are estranged. Is it a big deal?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55aab110-00f6-11f0-809b-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 17:04:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earth’s oceans rose to highest level in three decades — and faster than expected</title>
      <description>The average global sea level rate last year climbed to 0.23 inches per year — about 35 percent higher than expected, a NASA analysis found. The rise in global levels is concerning because it’s an indicator of what to expect in flood-prone areas, scientists say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7147db80-00e9-11f0-8c33-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Russia has demanded to end its war: All land seized from Ukraine, sanctions relief and more</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is pushing Russia to agree to a Ukraine ceasefire and peace talks. But Russian President Vladimir Putin has maintained inflexible, maximalist conditions for any potential agreement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">509ac540-00e0-11f0-9b22-0000a1acef38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 14:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alan Simpson dies at 93. The three-term Republican senator from Wyoming was a leading deficit hawk with a barbed and feisty wit.</title>
      <description>Simpson was first elected in 1978 and served 10 years as the GOP whip. He had an unrivaled talent for leavening dry policy discussions with evocative aphorisms (“don’t squat with your spurs on” was one favorite) and was known for pushing the 1986 immigration reform bill through a reluctant Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f05a48b0-00d8-11f0-813d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:33:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a862b30-00d8-11f0-b84e-0000a1aceddd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 13:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown deadline. Federal workers. Birthright citizenship. Putin’s demands. Plane fire. Microplastics. Baby wombat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b8398d1-00c3-11f0-a435-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Minority Leader Schumer says he plans to support GOP funding bill, lowering the odds of a government shutdown</title>
      <description>The government is set to shut down at 12:01 a.m. on Saturday unless lawmakers pass a bill to keep it open. The update from Senate Minority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-New York) comes a day after he said there were not enough Democrats to support the bill and as his party faced intense pressure to oppose it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4628e20-0062-11f0-8add-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 23:29:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johns Hopkins University to lay off more than 2,000 workers after $800 million in federal cuts</title>
      <description>The Baltimore-based university, one of the country's top research institutions, has been hit hard by the Trump administration's cuts to the U.S. Agency for International Development. The cuts affect programs that fight disease, provide clean drinking water and care for children around the globe, among other initiatives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0605d00-0059-11f0-ad0d-0000a1ace509</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 22:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An FDA official helped save a 6-year-old from a brain-eating amoeba. That really wasn’t the end of the story.</title>
      <description>Michael Lewis on Heather Stone of the Food and Drug Administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad289621-004f-11f0-85fc-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 21:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 enters correction territory as tariffs and inflation weigh on Wall Street traders</title>
      <description>The benchmark stock index has shed more than 10 percent since its record close last month as the Trump administration’s escalating trade war raises the possibility of a recession.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49eaf110-0046-11f0-be53-0000a1ace620</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 20:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Supreme Court to allow partial plan to end birthright citizenship while litigation continues</title>
      <description>Judges have halted President Donald Trump's effort to ban citizenship for babies born in the United States to parents who are undocumented immigrants or in the country on temporary visas, with several issuing orders that apply nationwide. The Trump administration asked the Supreme Court to limit those orders to the individuals or states involved in the litigation while the cases make their way through the court system, or to at least allow the relevant agencies to begin developing plans and issuing public guidance for banning birthright citizenship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d551f660-0044-11f0-8a49-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: John Feinstein dies at 69. The sports commentator and author had a long affiliation with The Post. A previous alert misstated his age.</title>
      <description>Feinstein wrote dozens of sports books, including “A Season on the Brink” about the volatile Indiana University men’s basketball coach Bob Knight.

A previous alert misstated his age. This has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7395bc1-003d-11f0-b50d-00000a1ace12</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 19:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Feinstein dies at 68. The sports commentator and best-selling author had a long affiliation with The Post.</title>
      <description>Feinstein wrote dozens of sports books, including “A Season on the Brink” about the volatile Indiana University men’s basketball coach Bob Knight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67a48850-0038-11f0-851a-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:24:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to immediately offer jobs back to some fired probationary workers</title>
      <description>Judge William Alsup in California directed Trump officials to offer jobs back to some workers who were fired in a sweeping round of cuts last month, the scale of which has not been disclosed by the administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">173d5870-002d-11f0-90e9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 17:03:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin does not immediately dismiss idea of a 30-day ceasefire with Ukraine but cautions that many details must be ironed out</title>
      <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin said that he supports a ceasefire in principle but that the implementation raises many questions, particularly regarding verification across a long frontline. He added that these issues would need to be discussed with the United States, “perhaps” in a phone call with President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d06a0e0-0029-11f0-9bc5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Teens call out dad as abusive, leave other parent reeling</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Teens call out dad as abusive, leave other parent reeling</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e636400-0024-11f0-aa87-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top IRS lawyer is removed from his role as Musk’s DOGE clashes with career staff over access to taxpayer records, officials say</title>
      <description>William Paul, acting chief counsel of the Internal Revenue Service, was removed from his position as billionaire Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service seeks access to sensitive records, according to five people familiar with the matter. Paul, a career official named to the position in January, will be replaced by Andrew De Mello.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5052b540-001b-11f0-ad35-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 14:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House withdraws Dave Weldon’s nomination to lead Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, officials say</title>
      <description>The decision to pull the former Florida congressman from consideration to lead the top public health agency comes after scrutiny of his longtime promotion of false claims that vaccines may cause autism. It marks a rare setback for a Trump administration nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0bf1020-0010-11f0-b42b-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A partnership with a bad aftertaste in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d88dda90-000f-11f0-9d1d-0000a1ace3c4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 13:34:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
