<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:01:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>VMI superintendent blames ‘bias, emotion, and ideology’ for decision by military college’s board not to extend his contract</title>
      <description>Cedric T. Wins, a retired Army major general, was named the first Black superintendent of the Virginia Military Institute in 2021 amid allegations of widespread racism at the college. His contract expires at the end of June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de01d871-facc-11ef-8dbf-0000a1acec19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump extends one-month tariff reprieve to some goods from Canada, following a similar move for Mexico</title>
      <description>The pause on tariffs applies only to imports that comply with the free-trade agreement between the United States, Canada and Mexico, signed in late 2018. Financial markets continue to be down for the day after the whiplash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03d66480-fac8-11ef-a8bf-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies in the U.S. are disappearing at a ‘catastrophic’ rate, study finds, with potentially dire effects on ecosystems</title>
      <description>The number of butterflies in the contiguous United States declined by 22 percent this century, according to a study released Thursday in the journal Science. Shrinking habitat, rising temperatures and a toxic array of pesticides are killing off the delicate insects, it said, with potentially dire implications for ecosystems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab135ab2-fabd-11ef-ab0e-0000a1acef03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE seeks access to sensitive income data kept by federal child support office</title>
      <description>The Elon Musk-led U.S. DOGE Service clashed with Health and Human Services career staffers over a system that tracks most U.S. workers’ wages. It wasn’t immediately clear whether DOGE’s access request was granted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a04ae80-fab1-11ef-aeb5-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump suspends tariffs on most products from Mexico until April 2 after phone call with Sheinbaum</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump made the announcement after a call with Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum, saying it was an accommodation based on their good relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cd3e640-faac-11ef-b5ea-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A wartime onesie in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc2fe10-faa5-11ef-9cb4-0000a1acef7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to censure Rep. Al Green (D-Texas) for disrupting President Donald Trump during his Tuesday address to Congress</title>
      <description>The Republican-sponsored resolution accuses Green of a “breach of proper conduct.” In a social media post shared Thursday morning, Green said he was being reprimanded for “standing up to President Trump.” A censure of a House member falls short of expulsion and has become a more common disciplinary action in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ced9811-faa0-11ef-ab5b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dalai Lama writes in an op-ed: My hope for the Tibetan people</title>
      <description>Tibetans have spent nearly 75 years fighting for freedom. Their struggle should continue beyond my lifetime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cd5dc50-fa9d-11ef-9078-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE is driving broad cuts to the Social Security agency and will make mistakes, acting head says privately</title>
      <description>The Social Security Administration’s acting commissioner, Leland Dudek, told senior leaders and disability rights advocates that members of Elon Musk’s cost-cutting team are outsiders who are unfamiliar with the nuances of the agency’s programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ff34311-fa90-11ef-a762-0000a1ace904</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 13:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Federal job cuts. Abortion ban. Gaza aid. Vanishing sea ice. Pig rescue. Eagle chicks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f0bb1a0-fa82-11ef-8634-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to sign executive order calling for the closure of the Education Department</title>
      <description>A draft of the order that circulated Wednesday called on Education Secretary Linda McMahon to “take all necessary steps” to facilitate the closure of the department “to the maximum extent appropriate and permitted by law." McMahon has acknowledged that congressional approval is needed to close the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeb5b690-fa40-11ef-91b2-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 04:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court allows Trump to fire independent watchdog Hampton Dellinger without cause — for now</title>
      <description>A lower court judge had reinstated Hampton Dellinger as head of the Office of Special Counsel, which protects whistleblowers and federal employees. But a U.S. appeals court said Dellinger could be removed for now while courts decide whether the president has the authority to fire the head of the independent watchdog agency without cause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa63eed0-fa23-11ef-87d5-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials are reopening a sprawling detention center in Texas to hold migrant children and their parents</title>
      <description>Four years after the Biden administration stopped detaining migrant children, a private prison contractor says it has reached an agreement with ICE to reopen the South Texas Family Residential Center. It can hold up to 2,400 people, making it one of the largest ICE detention centers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ec8ba0-fa13-11ef-936d-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 22:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s one word to describe Trump’s address? Three columnists discuss.</title>
      <description>President Trump’s address to Congress was historically long and unusual in its style. Some Democrats booed and heckled him, and Trump did his own trolling of Democrats too. What does this address tell us about our politics and the future of Trump 2.0? Columnists Ruth Marcus, Dana Milbank and Ramesh Ponnuru get into it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">099d5b70-fa06-11ef-96fb-0000a1ace18d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 21:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump White House allows one-month delay on tariffs for autos coming from Canada and Mexico</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has vowed to move ahead on April 2 with a new plan calling for "reciprocal" tariffs, which are expected to result in sharp increases in U.S. border levies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31099f80-f9f6-11ef-8f00-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents want to tell daughter no wedding funds till she’s 25</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents want to tell daughter no wedding funds till she’s 25</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23d10cd0-f9e3-11ef-90e1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How do you handle a takeout fail once you’re home?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How do you handle a takeout fail once you’re home?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff1bf0f0-f9db-11ef-aa0b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s rally-style speech was not the true test, our chief correspondent writes. Harder days lie ahead.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has called for dramatic and often controversial change. Whether he can turn early disruption into effective governance and tangible results is a far different issue, chief correspondent Dan Balz writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cc18320-f9d6-11ef-a0e3-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Supreme Court says judge can force Trump administration to resume paying nearly $2 billion in frozen foreign aid</title>
      <description>The 5-4 ruling means the U.S. Agency for International Development and the State Department must restart payments for work already completed. The decision drew a sharp dissent from four conservative justices who said a district court judge in D.C. probably lacks the power to compel the federal government to make such payments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfb632b0-f9cf-11ef-9eba-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phasing out this platform in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f8d1540-f9ce-11ef-84c9-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 14:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pauses major parts of intelligence sharing with Ukraine, squeezing the information used to strike at targets inside Russia</title>
      <description>The rupture in intelligence sharing includes targeting data supplied by U.S. spy agencies to Kyiv to launch American-provided weapons at Russian targets. Some Ukrainian missile operators say they are no longer receiving information needed to hit targets inside Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aabe3b0-f9c9-11ef-9f03-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 13:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s speech. Ukraine’s offer. Trade war. Air pollution. ‘Gladiator fights.’ Paxlovid study. Pricey strawberry. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54a15560-f9b9-11ef-84c9-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pleads for patience on tariffs, and other takeaways from his first speech to Congress</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s speech claimed credit for the drop in crossings at the southern border and poked at Secretary of State Marco Rubio, while Democrats registered signs of protest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d49ecd62-f97d-11ef-92f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 04:53:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Something frightening about the palpable rage in the chamber’: 9 columnists react live to Trump’s address to Congress</title>
      <description>‘There is something frightening about the palpable rage in the chamber’: 9 columnists discuss Trump’s address to Congress</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df441560-f96c-11ef-8596-0000a1acef88</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 02:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is addressing a joint session of Congress, weeks into his controversial second term. Get live analysis from Post reporters.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump will address lawmakers and the nation in his first prime-time speech since returning to the White House six weeks ago. The address comes amid a backdrop of economic uncertainty stemming from the Trump administration’s decision to place steep tariffs on U.S. trading partners and an effort led by Elon Musk to slash the size of the federal government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27bfecf1-f964-11ef-95fa-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 01:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. mayor signals city will paint over Black Lives Matter Plaza after Republican lawmaker proposes bill to strip funding over it</title>
      <description>Mayor Muriel E. Bowser’s stance represents a remarkable retreat from her defiant posture toward President Donald Trump during his first term that led her to order the creation of Black Lives Matter Plaza. The move comes after Rep. Andrew Clyde (R-Georgia) proposed a bill to withhold federal highway funding from the city unless it renamed the plaza "Liberty Plaza."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1e017a0-f959-11ef-a53b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:36:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catch up quickly with The 7: Tracking Trump newsletter. Get 7 key updates every weeknight during his first 100 days
in office.</title>
      <description>Catch up quickly with The 7: Tracking Trump newsletter. Get 7 key updates every weeknight during his first 100 days
in office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58b9bbb0-f928-11ef-bdd1-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 18:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: If she marries her boyfriend, what’s in it for her?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: If she marries her boyfriend, what’s in it for her?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a98060c0-f91f-11ef-bbb0-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong company sells its majority share of Panama Canal ports to U.S. consortium led by BlackRock after Trump pressure</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump had threatened to take over the canal because of increased Chinese influence in the area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b40962a1-f918-11ef-8d23-00000a1ace77</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky says he’s ready to work with Trump to reach a Ukraine-Russia ceasefire and peace deal after U.S. froze military aid</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky issued a statement reiterating that Ukraine values what the United States has done to help his country. He proposed a limited ceasefire with Russia, described the Oval Office argument as “regrettable” and said Kyiv is ready to sign a minerals deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f911320-f914-11ef-84c9-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court strikes down EPA rules on discharge of water pollution, narrowing landmark Clean Water Act</title>
      <description>The justices restricted the types of rules the Environmental Protection Agency can impose on cities that discharge sewage and other pollutants into bodies of water. The unusual case featured one of the nation’s greenest cities, San Francisco.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c4a7af1-f912-11ef-97ab-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 16:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know your Oscar winners in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f974ef0-f905-11ef-89c5-0000a1aceb27</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 14:32:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade war escalates as China, Canada and Mexico plan retaliatory tariffs after U.S. levies take effect</title>
      <description>China said it was imposing tariffs of up to 15 percent on a raft of U.S. farm products and blacklisted more than 20 U.S. companies, marking a major escalation in a brewing trade war between the world’s two largest economies. Meanwhile, Mexico said it would announce tariffs on U.S. products on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b523260-f904-11ef-a77f-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 14:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine aid. Tariffs impact. Trump speech. Pope Francis. Tornado threat. Microplastics. Swearing benefits. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">290556f0-f8f0-11ef-a77f-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police officers pardoned in fatal pursuit of a young Black man have been reinstated to full duty</title>
      <description>Officer Terence Sutton and Lt. Andrew Zabavsky were convicted for their roles in a pursuit that killed Karon Hylton-Brown in 2020 and sparked civil unrest. President Donald Trump pardoned them in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bee9d5f0-f8a6-11ef-a834-0000a1ace97d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to pause all deliveries of U.S. military aid to Ukraine, officials say</title>
      <description>In the wake of President Donald Trump and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s disastrous Oval Office meeting on Friday, the U.S. president is halting the provision of weapons and military assistance critical to Ukraine’s fight against Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de69a7e0-f890-11ef-b255-0000a1aceb26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is dominating almost every technology needed for the green energy revolution. Here's how it did it.</title>
      <description>China has pulled ahead of the United States in almost every key clean tech sector, from electric vehicles to solar panels. Its lead is likely to widen as President Donald Trump boosts fossil fuel production and cuts funding for clean energy projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be203cd2-f884-11ef-8837-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 23:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial markets slide as Trump confirms 25 percent tariffs on Mexico and Canada will take effect Tuesday</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 fell more than 2 percent and the tech-heavy Nasdaq was down around 3 percent, as the president’s comments came amid signs that tariff threats are beginning to sap the economy’s momentum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d91dd70-f874-11ef-89f9-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: In-laws never offered condolences after father’s death</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: In-laws never offered condolences after father’s death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d55d751-f851-11ef-9558-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 17:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A tribute to this actor in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d7ad100-f83c-11ef-ae9d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASN agreement between Nationals and Orioles is dissolved; Nationals will control their own broadcast rights after 2025 season</title>
      <description>MLB announced Monday morning the dissolution of the contentious agreement, which was in place since the Montreal Expos franchise moved to Washington in 2005 and gave the Nationals’ TV rights to the Orioles-controlled Mid-Atlantic Sports Network.

Nationals games will air on MASN for one more season in 2025 under the terms of a new agreement, but the team can sell its broadcast rights for future seasons to the highest bidder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10515f40-f838-11ef-b71f-0000a1ace43c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Oscar moments — from showstopping performances to big wins</title>
      <description>“Anora” and lead actress Mikey Madison had a huge night, the stars of "Wicked" put on a dazzling show and some celebrities shared political messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45879a30-f833-11ef-a48a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 13:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Ukraine. Elon Musk. Gaza aid. Oscar winners. Wildfires. Moon landing. Gray homes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e7edf0-f827-11ef-bbb0-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Anora’ wins best picture at the Oscars, with star Mikey Madison also winning best actress</title>
      <description>A varied field of movies walked away with statuettes at the Academy Awards, where numerous winners offered messages about Ukraine, Gaza and American politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d30b460-f7e2-11ef-be7b-0000a1ace22d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin commutes sentence of ex-officer who fatally shot unarmed man</title>
      <description>Former Fairfax County Police Sgt. Wesley Shifflett was sentenced to three years in prison on Friday. A jury had convicted him of recklessly handling a firearm but acquitted him of a more serious involuntary manslaughter charge during the 2023 encounter in which he chased and shot a man thought to have shoplifted a pair of sunglasses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0668d3d1-f7d6-11ef-b7f2-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for a dramatic Oscars, where several movies have a shot at best picture. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Will Adrien Brody and “The Brutalist” dominate? Will “Anora” sweep? Could Demi Moore finally take home a best actress statuette? Join our writers as the show begins at 7 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a34c771-f7be-11ef-812b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Tesla owners feel buyer’s remorse — and get egged — as Elon Musk tears through the government</title>
      <description>For many D.C.-area owners, the car has gone from progressive icon to a badge of shame now that Musk has become a central figure in President Donald Trump’s administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b11db181-f7b1-11ef-9308-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1062ad50-f788-11ef-bdcc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 17:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DOGE set off a crisis at a highly sensitive nuclear weapons agency</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s dismissal of workers who maintain America’s nuclear weapons — now mostly reversed — is an example of how its scattershot approach caused deeper damage to agencies than anticipated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b672e9b0-f785-11ef-943d-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The house color that tells you when a neighborhood is gentrifying</title>
      <description>Rowhouses in D.C., craftsmans in Nashville, Victorian-style homes in San Francisco and many other styles of houses in gentrifying neighborhoods across the country have increasingly been painted shades of gray, altering the aesthetics of American cities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87a8a7f0-f77b-11ef-b0eb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
