<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 14:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Jittery markets open lower after a record-breaking day as tariff hikes on Chinese imports fan fears of a U.S.-China trade war</title>
      <description>Major stock indexes have been volatile all week as Wall Street reacts to a stream of tariff news. After the United States and the European Union paused plans to impose tariffs on each other, some investors Thursday turned to the impact of a potential U.S.-China trade war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1781f20-1611-11f0-9ac4-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This state’s flower is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb62aa0-160f-11f0-af4d-0000a1ace7f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased more than expected in March, before most of Trump’s tariffs took effect</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed a slower pace of growth for inflation in March in good news for the economy, according to new data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10371480-1608-11f0-a2b7-0000a1ace126</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.U. announces 90-day pause on retaliatory tariffs targeting U.S. goods after Trump delays certain levies</title>
      <description>The E.U. move came a day after the bloc approved levies on a broad range of U.S. imports and after President Donald Trump subsequently paused U.S. tariffs on countries in Europe and elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1ec0d50-1602-11f0-8012-0000a1ace1fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff pause. Republican infighting. Prisoner swap. Immigrant monitoring. Police shooting. Masters. Lost city. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0952980-15fa-11f0-a167-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia frees American Ksenia Karelina from a penal colony ahead of diplomatic talks with the U.S. in Istanbul</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio announced the release on X the same day the U.S. and Russia began talks on normalizing their diplomatic missions. Karelina, a Russian-American dual national and beautician from Los Angeles, had been sentenced to 12 years in prison for treason after donating $50 to a Ukrainian humanitarian agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb33cd6-15ee-11f0-a891-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian markets rebound in morning trading as Trump pauses tariffs — except for those on China</title>
      <description>The Nikkei and Kospi rose after President Donald Trump paused tariffs on Japan and South Korea, among other nations. Hong Kong's Hang Seng was also up, along with indexes in Shanghai, Taiwan and Australia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45ada8e0-15b8-11f0-80ef-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 18 hours that changed President Trump's mind on tariffs</title>
      <description>From Tuesday evening to Wednesday afternoon, Trump and his trade advisers spoke to several Republican lawmakers and top foreign leaders. They raised concerns about the faltering global markets and the growing concerns of a worldwide recession, urging Trump to take action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77064ec1-15a3-11f0-aa78-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governments around the world want more babies. But does pronatalism put reproductive freedoms in danger?</title>
      <description>Low fertility rates have sparked panic and pronatalist initiatives around the world. Some experts are more concerned about the ethics of pushing for more births and say the framing of low birth rates as a “crisis” is an ideological choice — not an objective description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">387180a0-158d-11f0-9dea-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 21:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock markets rally, closing with big gains after Trump pauses most tariffs</title>
      <description>Major indexes surged, closing well up for the first time since the White House announced new import taxes. The S&amp;P 500 closed up 9.5 percent, the tech-heavy Nasdaq was up more than 12 percent and the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained nearly 8 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db562d0-157e-11f0-8aa2-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Supreme Court to let him fire independent regulators</title>
      <description>The Trump administration on Wednesday asked the Supreme Court to allow the president to remove a pair of independent regulators whose cases have broad implications for at least two dozen other agencies, including the Federal Reserve Board. The cases involve Gwynne Wilcox of the National Labor Relations Board and Cathy A. Harris of the Merit Systems Protection Board and a 90-year-old Supreme Court precedent the administration is seeking to overturn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1fa8a0-1575-11f0-b242-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 19:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel removed as ATF director, replaced with Army secretary</title>
      <description>The Trump administration removed FBI Director Kash Patel as interim head of the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, replacing him with the Secretary of the Army Dan Driscoll, according to two sources familiar with the decision who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a personnel matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1030a0-1573-11f0-9f09-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he is pausing higher tariff rates for most countries for 90 days, while raising tariffs more for China. Markets surged.</title>
      <description>In a social media post, President Donald Trump also said that 10 percent tariffs will remain for countries getting a reprieve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2853b811-1569-11f0-b3aa-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it time to hide cash under your mattress? Three columnists react to the tariff news.</title>
      <description>How many ‘shocks to the system’ can America take?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d6dd8f0-155e-11f0-a5c2-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Widow seeks a polite ‘no’ to … well, everyone</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Widow seeks a polite ‘no’ to … well, everyone</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40364b80-155c-11f0-9358-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market opens flat, bonds retreat as trade war heats up with retaliatory tariffs from China and Europe</title>
      <description>U.S. markets had a muted opening Wednesday after the Trump administration’s harshest tariffs yet went into effect, followed by retaliatory moves from China and the European Union. The S&amp;P 500 and tech-heavy Nasdaq composite index were essentially unchanged in early trading, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average declined slightly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3ff000-1548-11f0-8da7-0000a1ace740</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Piper, nooo!’ It’s time for today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c497110-1547-11f0-a405-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Union hits back at Trump’s steel tariffs, imposing up to 25 percent levy on broad list of U.S. goods</title>
      <description>The 27-nation bloc approved the response on Wednesday. A copy of the E.U. plan, seen by The Washington Post, targeted U.S. products including soybeans, meat, iron, steel, textiles, tobacco and ice cream. The E.U. has yet to retaliate against other tariffs by President Donald Trump as it tries to coax Washington toward trade negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53e1d081-1545-11f0-a1e7-0000a1ace706</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China raises tariffs on U.S. goods to 84 percent in response to Trump’s latest levies, as global markets reel</title>
      <description>Beijing's planned increase more than doubled a previously announced minimum 34 percent duty set to take effect Thursday. The announcement came after China said it was willing to talk but would take "forceful measures" to protect the Chinese economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf288bb0-1539-11f0-8f7b-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer and ex-MLB players among the dead as toll reaches 113 in Santo Domingo nightclub collapse</title>
      <description>Former major league pitcher Octavio Dotel and Tony Blanco, who played with the Washington Nationals in 2005, were killed in the collapse. Dominican singer Rubby Pérez, who was performing with his band when the roof collapsed early Tuesday, was also killed, his manager said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e371c91-1535-11f0-a58c-000a1ace00cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Federal workers. IRS turmoil. River flooding. Egg prices. National Recording Registry. Dire wolves. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb2e10e0-1531-11f0-8ff8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the few freedoms North Koreans enjoyed have vanished since the pandemic</title>
      <description>The city of Hyesan, just over the river from China, once offered a glimpse of a more open North Korea. Now it exemplifies Kim Jong Un’s mounting authoritarianism, with residents and escapees describing how the regime has tightened its grip on trade and communication with the outside world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">631fdc20-14d4-11f0-bcc7-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acting IRS chief to resign over deal to share taxpayers’ private data with immigration officials</title>
      <description>Acting IRS commissioner Melanie Krause clashed with Treasury officials over taxpayer privacy concerns, according to two people familiar with the situation. Treasury Secretary Scott Bessent and Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem this week signed an agreement allowing the practice, which IRS lawyers said probably violates privacy laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10c72330-14ce-11f0-9d1b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders White House to temporarily lift ban on Associated Press</title>
      <description>A judge ordered the White House to temporarily lift a nearly two-month-long set of access restrictions it placed on the Associated Press while the news organization’s lawsuit against three Trump administration officials plays out. Since Feb. 11, AP reporters have been prevented from being at presidential events because the news organization refused to use the name Gulf of America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc638640-14c6-11f0-81c4-0000a1acef85</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 22:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As avian flu hits egg production, some corporations profit</title>
      <description>By wiping out millions of laying hens, the flu has slowed egg production for many companies. But the price increases — and government payments for culled hens — have led to record profits for at least one large producer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb84a6b0-14c0-11f0-85e5-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 21:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 reaches its lowest level in more than a year as signs of negotiations fail to calm markets before tariffs go into effect</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq composite index ended the day in negative territory after an early rally fizzled Tuesday, extending a retreat that began last week after President Donald Trump levied steep tariffs on imports from dozens of countries. Administration officials are engaged in talks with countries such as Japan and South Korea, but there is no immediate prospect of talks with China, which faces 104 percent tariffs going into effect at midnight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">472f7021-14b6-11f0-b3b9-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 20:15:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court halts order to rehire roughly 16,000 probationary workers fired by Trump, saying plaintiffs lacked standing to sue</title>
      <description>The justices ruled 7-2 that unions and advocacy groups did not have standing to challenge the firing by the Office of Personnel Management of probationary employees from the departments of Agriculture, Defense, Energy, Interior, Treasury and Veterans Affairs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ce3c900-1495-11f0-b73d-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: As older partner declines, marriage now feels more like parenting</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: As older partner declines, marriage now feels more like parenting</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b07f2a30-1492-11f0-b298-0000a1ace400</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 16:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NCAA men’s basketball championship was on the line with 19.7 seconds left. Here’s how Florida won it.</title>
      <description>When Florida and Houston played for the national title Monday night in San Antonio, a tense final came down to the last possession. Let the players and coaches tell you what happened.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83c435e0-1487-11f0-8b30-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 14:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. stock market opens strongly after days of losses spurred by tariff anxiety</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500, Nasdaq composite index and Dow Jones Industrial Average opened Tuesday’s trading higher after steep declines in recent days. The gains for U.S. stocks come after Asian and European markets recovered despite Chinese threats of trade-war escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a86021-147f-11f0-ab89-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocking up on this imported beverage in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c5a7351-147e-11f0-9f73-0000a1acefdb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department says it will stop enforcement against cryptocurrency fraud</title>
      <description>In a memo sent to the Justice Department on Monday night, Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche said the department will largely stop bringing cases that violate the Bank Secrecy Act or contain unregistered broker-dealer violations — instead focusing on crimes that people commit with cryptocurrency, such as narcotic and human trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f71f9df0-147c-11f0-bd83-0000a1ace175</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 13:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff backlash. Supreme Court. Fired admiral. Iran talks. Weather opposites. Electric vehicles. Florida Gators. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e8424e0-1468-11f0-9c82-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida wins NCAA men’s basketball championship, beating Houston for first title since 2007</title>
      <description>The Gators topped the Cougars on Monday night in San Antonio, securing the third national championship in program history after they won back-to-back NCAA tournaments in 2006 and 2007. Houston fell one win shy of its first title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1d18bb0-1427-11f0-9c10-0000a1acecd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 03:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Supreme Court allows use of wartime law to deport alleged Venezuelan gang members</title>
      <description>The high court ruled 5-4 that the Venezuelan immigrants who sought to block their removals under the Alien Enemies Act did so in the wrong court. The justices also said the government must give potential deportees notice and a chance to challenge their removal before they can be removed from the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc76cdc2-1409-11f0-91f1-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 23:41:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. admiral at NATO fired, latest ouster in Trump's military purge</title>
      <description>Vice Adm. Shoshana Chatfield is one of at least nine senior military leaders — and the fourth woman — removed since Trump’s return to Washington less than three months ago. She had spoken favorably about diversity and was viewed as a trailblazer within the Navy. She was notified of her removal over the weekend, three officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">113d2db0-13f6-11f0-a555-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 21:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court temporarily pauses lower-court order to bring back Maryland man who was mistakenly deported to El Salvador</title>
      <description>Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. on Monday paused the deadline to bring back the Salvadoran immigrant who the Trump administration says was deported in error. The brief administrative order, which did not address the underlying legal issues, will allow time for a full Supreme Court review.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d936790-13ec-11f0-beb1-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stocks close mostly down for third day in a row after Trump threatens even higher tariffs on China</title>
      <description>Losses on two major indexes Monday weren’t as sharp as they were last week, and one closed narrowly up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e48c6c0-13eb-11f0-bc79-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 20:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does ‘America First’ mean to workers at U.S. steel? Salena Zito visited a Pennsylvania mill to find out.</title>
      <description>On the ground with U.S. Steel workers lobbying Trump to approve a foreign deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e77976d0-13de-11f0-a3f0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does spouse get a say in whether wife cuts ties with her family?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does spouse get a say in whether wife cuts ties with her family?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfadfb91-13c9-11f0-98b1-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 16:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens an additional 50% tariffs on China, which could bring the tariff rate for some Chinese imports to more than 100%</title>
      <description>As U.S. financial markets extended losses, President Donald Trump said in a Truth Social post that the United States would impose the additional tariffs Wednesday if China did not withdraw its 34 percent counter-tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8054f870-13c6-11f0-8a1a-0000a1acec8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:39:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Supreme Court to block order to return Maryland man mistakenly deported to El Salvador, as midnight deadline nears</title>
      <description>Kilmar Abrego García has been detained at a mega-prison since he was deported last month, despite a court order forbidding his removal. The Trump administration says it has no power to bring back Abrego García, a Salvadoran immigrant who has been in the United States since he was a teenager and is married to a U.S. citizen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d2a5e40-13c6-11f0-8c7a-000a1ace9f0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 15:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Republican senator is leading the charge against Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Sen. Rand Paul — a right-wing firebrand from a deep-red state — is in some ways an unlikely figure to articulate a searing case against President Donald Trump’s agenda.

But the senator from Kentucky is issuing a stark warning to fellow Republicans that Trump’s tariff policies could lead to a generational political loss for the party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f126380-13be-11f0-bde7-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 14:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. stock sell-off extends into third day as Trump’s tariffs rattle global markets</title>
      <description>The Dow, S&amp;P 500 and Nasdaq open the trading week with steep losses as the deepening trade war threatens the global economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7a92b70-13b4-11f0-b43f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Val Kilmer role in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5951521-13b2-11f0-96ce-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 13:19:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock markets. Trump protests. Measles death. Israeli troops. Severe storms. March Madness. Alex Ovechkin. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74c8cd50-139f-11f0-bdb7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian, European stock markets fall sharply as Trump tariffs spark recession fears</title>
      <description>Asian leaders have issued a flurry of statements to shore up confidence and attempt to avert crisis for their economies, with U.S. partners like Japan, South Korea and Taiwan striking a conciliatory tone and pledging to negotiate. Trump administration officials had spent the weekend defending the president’s tariffs on almost all trading partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f26f42e0-1398-11f0-b5ea-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 10:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut wins NCAA women’s basketball championship, beating South Carolina for its record-extending 12th title</title>
      <description>The Huskies routed the defending champion Gamecocks on Sunday in the national championship game in Tampa, securing their first title since 2016. South Carolina was trying to become the first repeat champion since Connecticut won four straight titles from 2013 to 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b71340-132b-11f0-8657-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 21:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Ovechkin scores his 895th career goal to pass Wayne Gretzky and set a new NHL record</title>
      <description>With his goal on Sunday afternoon, Ovechkin passed Gretzky to claim sole ownership of the record. It was a remarkable feat for Washington’s 39-year-old captain, who has long captured the hockey world’s attention with his sheer joy and relentless scoring ability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e651ff1-130f-11f0-9aea-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 17:50:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The economy is about to collapse, and you idiots have no idea’: The 2008 weekend that shook the world, from leaders who lived it</title>
      <description>The weekend that shook the world</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a4c55f0-1307-11f0-b3ac-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 16:49:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
