<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 18:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Big Food and dietitian influencers are pushing ‘anti-diet’ advice even as obesity rises</title>
      <description>The anti-diet movement, which began as an effort to combat weight stigma and an unhealthy obsession with thinness, is now drawing global food marketers. One company in particular, General Mills, maker of Cocoa Puffs and Lucky Charms cereals, has launched a multi-pronged campaign that capitalizes on anti-diet teachings, an investigation by The Washington Post and The Examination, a nonprofit newsroom that covers global public health, has found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8699b520-f1e1-11ee-8aa7-0000a1acecb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Ignatius and Jim Geraghty just visited Ukraine. Listen to them describe what they saw in the latest episode of ‘Impromptu.’</title>
      <description>What we saw on the ground in Ukraine</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7725790-f1dd-11ee-8b90-000a1ace17c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 17:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: How do you keep salad from wilting so quickly in the refrigerator? Our food writers answer your questions.</title>
      <description>Food writers Aaron Hutcherson and Becky Krystal answer your cooking conundrums in their weekly chat. Today’s topics include cooking wines and garlic clove sizing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20d3de91-f1d8-11ee-ad26-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith fires back at Judge Cannon’s order that could disrupt Trump classified documents case</title>
      <description>The prosecutor asked U.S. Judge Aileen M. Cannon to rule quickly on Donald Trump's claim that he is protected by the Presidential Records Act, so the government can appeal before trial. The filing represents the most stark and high-stakes confrontation yet between Cannon and the special counsel, illustrating the extent to which a ruling that legitimizes Trump's position could eviscerate the historic case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed104aa8-f1d5-11ee-bc44-000a1ace7d81</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 16:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How do you get over someone you don’t want to get over?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How do you get over someone you don’t want to get over?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc76570-f1d3-11ee-8fa1-000a1ace4fbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Name that coach in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">528b86a0-f1be-11ee-b348-000a1ace2984</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 13:30:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan earthquake. Israeli strike. Trump rebuke. Russia warning. Bird flu. Keto diet. Eclipse lawsuit. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52010670-f1a9-11ee-bc4e-0000a1ace3d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnitude 7.4 earthquake prompts tsunami alerts in Taiwan, Japan</title>
      <description>The earthquake off the east coast of Taiwan was the largest recorded in 25 years and was followed by several aftershocks, leading authorities to tell people on Taiwan's east coast and one of Japan's southern islands to take shelter and seek higher ground.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9efe4710-f156-11ee-bd39-0000a1ace581</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 01:08:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council votes to spend $515 million to modernize Capital One Arena after Ted Leonsis agrees to keep Wizards, Caps in the city</title>
      <description>The move is separate from a nonbinding, 14-page term sheet detailing the more specific elements of an agreement signed last week between D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) and Leonsis, the teams' owner, to keep the teams playing downtown. The funds, which will be spent over the next three years, also will go toward helping Leonsis’s company expand into part of the area surrounding the arena.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d1a6011-f13c-11ee-b10c-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:59:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft faulted by government review board for a ‘cascade’ of failures in Chinese hack</title>
      <description>The independent Cyber Safety Review Board’s report knocks the tech giant for shoddy cybersecurity practices, lax corporate culture and a deliberate lack of transparency in obscuring the origins of the breach that targeted Cabinet and top State Department officials, including the U.S. ambassador to China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e187da0-f139-11ee-bcf2-0000a1ace01b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:36:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gave Russia a specific warning about terrorist plot against concert hall over two weeks before the attack, officials say</title>
      <description>More than two weeks before the bloody assault at Crocus City Hall in suburban Moscow, the U.S. government shared highly specific information about the possible location of a terrorist plot, according to people familiar with the outreach. That directly contradicts Russia’s claims that the warning was too general to prevent an attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c38e8a0-f134-11ee-9fbe-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 21:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: The relative he’s avoiding happens to be Black. Coincidence?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: The relative he’s avoiding happens to be Black. Coincidence?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85c110d0-f10f-11ee-84a4-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 16:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wes Moore, a rising Democratic star, showcases his ‘won’t flinch’ attitude amid the Key Bridge crisis</title>
      <description>The freshman Maryland governor was an ascendant figure for Democrats who had already faced high expectations. Now he tackles his first major test in a moment of crisis. A behind-the-scenes look at how a rising political star confronted a catastrophe — and the bigger challenge that lies ahead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53170000-f109-11ee-8585-0000a1aceb9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 15:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some chatter about a magpie in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58110bf0-f0f5-11ee-95e7-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 13:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu says Israeli forces ‘unintentionally hit innocent people’ after World Central Kitchen says strike killed 7 workers</title>
      <description>Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu’s comments were the first in which Israel directly took responsibility for the attack. “Unfortunately, there was a tragic incident in which our forces unintentionally hit innocent people in the Gaza Strip,” Netanyahu said. “As it happens in war, we are investigating the matter fully, we are in contact with the governments, and we will do everything possible to prevent this from happening again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">643f72b0-f0e9-11ee-937f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strike. Trump bond. Abortion ban. Alex Murdaugh. Bird flu. Google data. Caitlin Clark. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26633340-f0e0-11ee-8d08-0000a1acedc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World Central Kitchen suspends aid operations in Gaza, says 7 workers killed in Israeli strike</title>
      <description>The food aid nonprofit said in a statement that the dead included a U.S.-Canada dual national. The Israel Defense Forces said earlier it was aware of reports of the incident and was conducting a “thorough review.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93760fd0-f0bc-11ee-9c43-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 06:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The women’s Final Four is set: Connecticut, Iowa, South Carolina and North Carolina State will play for a national championship</title>
      <description>Undefeated top overall seed South Carolina will face No. 3 seed N.C. State in one national semifinal Friday in Cleveland, and No. 1 seed Iowa will meet No. 3 seed Connecticut in the other.
The semifinal winners will play Sunday afternoon for the national title.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42e23300-f0a3-11ee-b919-0000a1ace729</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 03:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military launches investigation after reports of World Central Kitchen aid workers killed in Gaza strike</title>
      <description>The food aid nonprofit’s founder, celebrity chef José Andrés, said that several employees had been killed in an Israeli strike. The Israel Defense Forces said it was aware of the allegations and would conduct “a thorough review” after photos appearing to show the killed aid workers circulated on social media.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ae5d5e0-f08a-11ee-a653-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:46:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump posts $175 million bond to keep N.Y. authorities from seizing his property after civil fraud judgment</title>
      <description>The former president’s posting of the bond was necessary to keep New York Attorney General Letitia James from initiating legal steps to take over his properties, including Trump Tower. An appeals court panel recently ruled to reduce the bond from $464 million in the massive civil fraud judgment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6fcc340-f087-11ee-8dc5-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 00:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rematch of 2023 title game, Caitlin Clark and Iowa face Angel Reese and LSU for spot in Final Four. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>After their epic, taunt-filled matchup in last year’s national championship game, Clark’s Hawkeyes are about to take on Reese’s Tigers in the NCAA women’s basketball tournament’s Albany Region 2 final.
Follow our coverage for live updates, highlights and analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b5cd4e1-f07b-11ee-a5d0-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 23:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our reporters went into Gaza’s largest hospital for the first time in months. Mass destruction and the smell of death awaited them.</title>
      <description>Washington Post reporters were among a handful of foreign journalists taken inside al-Shifa hospital in Gaza City by the Israeli military on Sunday after two weeks of heavy fighting with militants. The hospital, once Gaza’s premier medical facility, has been destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06ce8d21-f06f-11ee-90a5-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 21:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Supreme Court allows strict state abortion ban to take effect, but greenlights putting the issue on the November ballot</title>
      <description>Florida’s conservative high court ruled that the state’s constitution does not protect abortion rights. But in a separate decision it also ruled that voters can decide in November whether an amendment enshrining the right to an abortion should be approved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d289dbf0-f064-11ee-b815-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 20:17:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Republicans texted and emailed their way into a money problem</title>
      <description>Small-dollar donations to Donald Trump and the GOP are way down since 2019 and 2020. But the former president’s team says they see a turnaround coming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64e33690-f056-11ee-bc7a-0000a1acec87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 18:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says an Israeli strike killed a senior Iranian commander in Syria</title>
      <description>A strike near Iran’s embassy in Damascus killed Mohammad Reza Zahedi, a senior commander in Iran’s Revolutionary Guard Corps, according to Iranian state media. Syrian state media reported that at least five people were killed in the strike.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bfaadf0-f04d-11ee-9090-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bird flu detected in person who had contact with infected Texas cattle, the second case of a human sickened by this strain in U.S.</title>
      <description>A highly virulent bird flu detected in dairy cows in five states has now been confirmed in a human patient in Texas. The case raises growing concern about mammal-to-mammal transmission of the virus and questions about whether this pathogen is now more easily transmitted among mammals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34adc180-f04b-11ee-bc9e-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 17:13:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: It’s tough to split kid duty with someone who runs 15 hours a week</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: It’s tough to split kid duty with someone who runs 15 hours a week</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04a22620-f041-11ee-82a2-0000a1acef87</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disgraced ex-lawyer Alex Murdaugh sentenced to 40 years for laundering millions, AP reports. He is already serving 2 life sentences.</title>
      <description>Murdaugh, who is also serving life sentences for the murder of his wife and son, admitted to 22 financial crimes, including stealing settlements meant for a quadriplegic man’s family.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43289b30-f03d-11ee-b651-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America suddenly has a record number of bees. What happened to colony collapse?</title>
      <description>The new Census of Agriculture shows that America’s honeybee population has rocketed to an all-time high. But the census has limitations, so The Post’s Department of Data dug deep into the numbers and found two big forces behind the boom, one surprising and one quite familiar. What we didn’t find was good news for native pollinators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42a0eb10-f031-11ee-a08b-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 14:08:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A much-debated movie prop is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e37113d0-f02c-11ee-8942-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 13:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel protests. Baltimore cleanup. Trump attacks. Major storm. AT&amp;T breach. March Madness. Skin-bound book. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9c3a780-f016-11ee-af5e-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The men’s Final Four is set: North Carolina State, Purdue, Connecticut and Alabama will compete for a national championship</title>
      <description>Top overall seed Connecticut will continue its championship defense against sharpshooting Alabama on Saturday in Glendale, Ariz., and fellow No. 1 seed Purdue will take on No. 11 seed N.C. State.
The semifinal winners will play for the national title April 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d46dff0-efb7-11ee-a5d8-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls his globe-trotting ex-diplomat ‘my envoy.’ Neither is in office.</title>
      <description>Richard Grenell is meeting with far-right foreign leaders, attacking President Biden and offering a glimpse at what U.S. foreign policy could be like in a second Trump term.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b0509bf0-efa1-11ee-8ff3-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 21:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">598f2d50-ef7d-11ee-a062-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 16:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solar eclipse towns have two big concerns as they welcome a tourism boom: Traffic and port-a-potties</title>
      <description>Small towns in the path of totality are pulling off logistical feats to welcome visitors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f339480-ef6c-11ee-9ae3-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 14:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cf80ef0-ef63-11ee-9f0c-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 13:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. Marines are testing out new, more nimble and lethal regiments designed to gain the advantage if there’s a war with China</title>
      <description>Across an island-hopping battlefield in Asia, the Marines are embedding new forces that would partner with allies to sink ships and down fighter planes if Beijing moves to take Taiwan or challenge for supremacy in the South China Sea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40e0ee10-eedd-11ee-8eaa-000a1acedd61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 21:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Steven Mnuchin’s plan to buy TikTok, but not its algorithm, has some insiders bewildered</title>
      <description>The former treasury secretary is telling investors he aims to buy TikTok without its export-blocked code, according to two people familiar with the pitch who spoke on the condition of anonymity. The plan would require Mnuchin to rebuild a service built on billions of lines of code — including the popular video app’s coveted recommendation algorithm — an idea observers said suggests a lack of familiarity with how tech companies actually work.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98434ee0-eec5-11ee-9ea1-0000a1ace22d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: He told me he saw a future with me. Now he has a new girlfriend.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: He told me he saw a future with me. Now he has a new girlfriend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd7f93d0-eeb2-11ee-b99b-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 16:31:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is pushing EVs. Who actually wants them? Listen to the latest episode of ‘Impromptu,’ our new podcast.</title>
      <description>The Biden administration wants America to transition to electric cars. But who’s actually opting in? Post Opinions columnists talk about how to navigate the speed bumps and what needs to happen to rev up this revolution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">703c8a40-eeae-11ee-bee0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 15:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSU’s Kim Mulkey holds grudges, battles everyone and keeps winning</title>
      <description>As the women’s game finally takes center stage, Mulkey is viewed by some as college basketball’s cartoonishly ornery supervillain and an essential part of the show. But some former players say that while her coaching approach gets results, including four national titles, it also takes a toll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3e5f0a80-eea3-11ee-9fce-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 14:38:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f502cd0-ee99-11ee-a19e-0000a1ace946</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 13:27:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We are trying to find some way not to retreat,’ Ukrainian President Zelensky tells David Ignatius</title>
      <description>President Volodymyr Zelensky delivered a stark message to Congress in an interview on Thursday as Russian missiles were pounding southern Ukraine: Give us the weapons to stop the Russian attacks, or Ukraine will escalate its counterattacks on Russia’s airfields, energy facilities and other strategic targets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1267300-ee01-11ee-a285-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration greenlights more bombs and warplanes for Israel despite widening rift with Netanyahu</title>
      <description>The State Department in recent days quietly approved the transfer to Israel of billions of dollars in bombs and fighter jets despite Washington’s concerns about an anticipated military offensive in southern Gaza that could threaten the lives of hundreds of thousands of Palestinians. The arms packages include more than 1,800 MK84 2,000-pound bombs, which have been linked to previous mass-casualty events.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ece4480-edfc-11ee-b486-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 18:42:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My fiancé and I are minimalists. My dad keeps sending us junk.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My fiancé and I are minimalists. My dad keeps sending us junk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">968462e0-edeb-11ee-ab2e-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials guarded Baltimore’s Key Bridge from terrorism and decay for decades. They didn’t foresee a ship collision.</title>
      <description>After the Sept. 11 attacks and the 2007 Minneapolis bridge collapse, Maryland officials scrambled to ensure the bridge was safe from similar events. Then, this week, a 95,000-gross-ton container ship hit it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e788964-ede1-11ee-bc10-000a1ace0f0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 15:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a8cbb61-eddc-11ee-aa1d-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 14:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louis Gossett Jr. dies at 87. He was the first Black man to win the best supporting actor Oscar.</title>
      <description>In a career spanning nearly seven decades, Gossett became one of the most recognizable actors of his generation. He worked on Broadway and other stages starting in the 1950s, appearing in dramas such as Lorraine Hansberry’s landmark “A Raisin in the Sun.” The boundary-breaking actor later won an Emmy for “Roots” (1977) and an Academy Award for “An Officer and a Gentleman” (1982).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db365470-edd2-11ee-959b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden seeks to accelerate the nation’s transition to electric trucks and buses, a follow-up to tougher rules on cars</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency finalized a rule requiring manufacturers to reduce emissions from new trucks, delivery vans and buses.

The rule — aimed at reducing climate impacts — could also cut harmful air pollution in disadvantaged communities. Some truck makers had lobbied to weaken it and might challenge it in court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80afcbe0-edcc-11ee-8976-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 13:01:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyoncé’s new record, ‘Cowboy Carter,’ dropped at midnight — and it's a lot of album. Here are our takeaways.</title>
      <description>The record was hyped as the R&amp;B and pop star’s first “country” full-length. It ain’t, she would later clarify. So what kind of album is it? It’s a journey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2149ad0-edc5-11ee-b70b-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 12:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
