<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 18:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>It could feel like 105 degrees in D.C. on Saturday. Officials have issued a heat advisory for the region.</title>
      <description>Temperatures could be the highest in the region since August 2016. Sunday’s heat is expected to be similarly intense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74458940-2ff2-11ef-8857-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 17:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dfb780e1-2feb-11ef-945e-0000a1ace489</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 16:32:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds gun ban for people subject to domestic-violence restraining orders in rare victory for firearms restrictions</title>
      <description>A federal law that strips guns from those deemed dangerous was among a number of firearms restrictions imperiled after the Supreme Court’s conservative majority bolstered gun rights in its 2022 decision, known as New York State Rifle &amp; Pistol Association v. Bruen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c2ee9c1-2fda-11ef-a975-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 14:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fcbbcc0-2fd2-11ef-a975-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Winnett will not join The Post as editor</title>
      <description>Winnett, deputy editor of London’s Telegraph Media Group, who was to lead The Washington Post newsroom, faced questions about his work in England, including stories based on illicitly obtained records. Early Friday, the editor of the Telegraph, Chris Evans, told staff Winnett will stay with the paper.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f541eaf0-2fc7-11ef-ab4e-0000a1ace8c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 12:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump donation surge. Heat wave. Donald Sutherland. Murder suspect. AI emissions. Chimp medicine. Ancient beach. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5da05dd1-2fbd-11ef-ae8b-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s felony conviction fuels a donation surge that narrows Biden’s advantage</title>
      <description>The Trump campaign and an allied super PAC received a huge influx of cash in the days following his May conviction on 34 felony counts of falsifying business records. The surge in post-conviction donations — captured in part in May reports filed to the Federal Election Commission on Thursday — is giving Trump a significant boost as he tries to narrow the Biden campaign’s once-enormous cash advantage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30610b00-2f75-11ef-ae59-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 02:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bayer is pushing Congress for legislation — and helped shape a provision — that could help fight lawsuits tying Roundup to cancer</title>
      <description>The company has paid billions of dollars in settlements, even as it maintains its weedkiller is safe and denies wrongdoing. A Bayer-backed provision in the House’s sweeping agricultural bill could halt some lawsuits, according to documents viewed by The Washington Post and seven people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd9bfe50-2f51-11ef-919c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 22:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Prince George’s County councilman Mel Franklin charged with embezzling campaign funds for personal expenses</title>
      <description>At least $130,000 of his campaign funds were used to pay for personal expenses, including his rent, loans and cosmetic procedures for him and a close friend, prosecutors allege. Franklin abruptly resigned Friday from his seat after serving on the council for nearly 14 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54bd39a0-2f49-11ef-86fa-0000a1ace675</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 21:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles Lakers to hire JJ Redick as head coach. The former NBA player co-hosts a podcast with Lakers star LeBron James.</title>
      <description>Redick, 39, had a 15-year NBA playing career but has no previous coaching experience. He replaces Darvin Ham, who was fired last month.
Redick hosts multiple popular basketball-related podcasts, including one he launched with James in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">216de1c0-2f3b-11ef-9d3c-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 19:27:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Sutherland dies at 88. The actor had a stunning range in films such as ‘Ordinary People’ and ‘The Hunger Games.’</title>
      <description>Tall, expressive and possessing remarkable versatility, his roles ranged from an irreverent G.I. in “The Dirty Dozen” to the antiwar comedy “M.A.S.H.” and the campus romp “Animal House” in the 1970s to the dystopian leader in the recent “Hunger Games” franchise.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63542f31-2f2d-11ef-a8e5-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:49:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Tara: My ex-husband lives two doors from me. How do I stop feeling he is too close?</title>
      <description>Well+Being editor Tara Parker-Pope answers your questions with science-based advice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4437c6e0-2f2b-11ef-8021-0000a1acefff</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TikTok files brief to challenge potential ban, kicking off a consequential legal battle between the popular app and U.S. government</title>
      <description>The brief, filed by TikTok and a group of eight creators, argues that a law demanding TikTok’s China-based owner, ByteDance, sell its U.S. operations by Jan. 19 or face a nationwide ban would violate Americans’ First Amendment right to free expression. TikTok also went on the offensive, sharing for the first time internal documents from years of failed negotiations with the federal government that it says show the Biden administration was not operating in good faith.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d79e980-2f27-11ef-a5c0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 17:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to fix low self-esteem so it doesn’t drag down a marriage?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to fix low self-esteem so it doesn’t drag down a marriage?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">799fe0e0-2f1e-11ef-88e3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 16:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds Trump’s tax on off-shore earnings, rejecting lawsuit that could have disrupted U.S. tax system</title>
      <description>The case asked whether an obscure provision of then-President Donald Trump’s 2017 tax package is permitted under Congress’s limited powers of taxation. Some saw the lawsuit as an effort to preemptively block Congress from creating a wealth tax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b5a6ab0-2f0e-11ef-8387-0000a1ace9c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 14:07:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A notable memoir in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78a6c060-2f09-11ef-a7e1-0000a1aceb59</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dutch leader Mark Rutte is poised to become new NATO secretary general, replacing Jens Stoltenberg, after competition drops out</title>
      <description>The change in leadership, which could be announced within days, comes amid worry over the return of former U.S. president Donald Trump. The prime minister of the Netherlands is known for his pragmatic outlook and willingness to work with Trump should he win the 2024 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d3e4e01-2f03-11ef-a6d3-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 12:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Despite a Biden-Xi agreement to crack down on fentanyl, Chinese sellers are open for business</title>
      <description>A booming online marketplace for shipping small but potent packages of the chemicals used in the production of fentanyl from China to Mexico remains largely unhindered, a Post investigation found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b07e5e50-2efd-11ef-89ac-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 12:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat wave. Ten Commandments. Hajj deaths. Stonehenge. Alzheimer’s hope. Wet bag. Summer solstice. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32f771f0-2ef4-11ef-9f20-00000a1ace40</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2024 ‘Deciders’: Who are they and what makes them tick?</title>
      <description>In a nation where many voters have made up their minds in the upcoming presidential election, 6 in 10 voters in key battleground states turn out sporadically or are not firmly committed to President Biden or Donald Trump.
These Deciders skew young and non-White and are even more sour on major candidates than the broader electorate. The Washington Post and the Schar School of Policy and Government at George Mason University surveyed 3,513 registered voters in six key states to find out what they think.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cc30e60-2e8b-11ef-bdbc-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 22:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rare gene mutation helps people resist Alzheimer’s disease, study finds — a hopeful clue for new therapies</title>
      <description>In a study published Wednesday in the New England Journal of Medicine, researchers reported 27 members of an extended Colombian family carry extreme genetic risk for Alzheimer’s, along with a copy of a protective gene called Christchurch. Cognitive decline in this singular group was delayed by about five years, suggesting that a drug that emulates the gene could have similar effects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">396465e0-2e7f-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 21:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran signals a major boost to nuclear program at key site</title>
      <description>The expansion in Iran’s most heavily protected nuclear facility could triple the site’s production of enriched uranium and give Tehran new options for quickly assembling a nuclear arsenal if it chooses to, according to confidential documents and analysis by weapons experts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9903320-2e65-11ef-809a-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom dumped stepdad and wants to coo about her new love to her kid</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom dumped stepdad and wants to coo about her new love to her kid</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9d0d70-2e55-11ef-82de-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: A nail-biter in the 5th District, and four other takeaways from Virginia’s primary election results</title>
      <description>Virginia, home to several competitive districts and virtually a permanent bellwether for national politics, never lacks for drama in its congressional races. Here are our takeaways from Tuesday’s primary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebbd7c60-2e50-11ef-b647-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 15:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China backed the ringleaders of a global scam network — then turned on them</title>
      <description>Crime syndicates in Kokang, Myanmar, near the border with China, operated more than 300 compounds running online fraud schemes, often with trafficked workers. That made Kokang a key hub in what Interpol estimates is a $3 trillion global online scam industry, a Washington Post investigation found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5a1af50-2e48-11ef-8516-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Juneteenth! Play today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16388a40-2e45-11ef-ab3c-0000a1ace62b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 14:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heat wave. Nvidia surge. Presidential debate. Willie Mays. Justin Timberlake. Childhood obesity. Black hole. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">090d6940-2e2b-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>North Korea’s Kim Jong Un declares ‘full support’ for Russian war in Ukraine during Vladimir Putin’s visit to Pyongyang</title>
      <description>The Russian president, looking for diplomatic and military support, signed a “comprehensive” agreement with Kim during a rare visit to North Korea. They gave no details, but the United States and its allies are concerned North Korea will ship more munitions to Russia to help it sustain its war against Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7cf58eb0-2e25-11ef-aafb-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 10:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Army Green Beret Derrick Anderson wins GOP Va. primary for Rep. Abigail Spanberger’s (D) 7th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The GOP hopes to flip the seat, which Spanberger is vacating to run for governor. Democrats have generally fared better in recent elections in this district, which stretches from rapidly growing, diverse exurbs outside D.C. to rural foothills in the Piedmont.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2b5e770-2ddb-11ef-8c9c-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Va. state Sen. Suhas Subramanyam wins Democratic primary for Jennifer Wexton’s (D) 10th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The seat is open after Wexton announced she is not seeking reelection because of health reasons. Wexton had flipped the seat in 2018, and Democrats hope to hang onto it in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">550ef9e1-2dda-11ef-b6c3-0000a1ace20d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:21:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Willie Mays dies at 93. The legendary baseball player of peerless power and grace was the ‘Say Hey Kid’ who could do it all.</title>
      <description>With sublime athletic grace, Mays excelled in every facet of the game as a center fielder with the New York and San Francisco Giants in the 1950s and ’60s, hitting 660 home runs and becoming arguably the best all-around player in baseball history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cd7f800-2dd8-11ef-aeee-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 01:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eugene Vindman, a Trump whistleblower, is projected to win Democratic nomination in Va.’s 7th Congressional District</title>
      <description>Vindman, a former Army colonel who helped file a report prompting the first impeachment inquiry into President Donald Trump, had used his celebrity on the national stage to catapult to the front of the crowded Democratic primary. He hopes to succeed Rep. Abigail Spanberger (D), who is running for governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6fe2791-2dd1-11ef-b378-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2024 00:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech company executive Mike Clancy wins GOP primary for Rep. Jennifer Wexton’s (D) 10th District seat, AP projects</title>
      <description>The seat is open after Rep. Jennifer Wexton announced she is not seeking reelection because of health reasons. Wexton had flipped the seat in 2018, and Republicans hope to flip it back in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee4f540-2dce-11ef-9971-0000a1ace569</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:55:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polls have closed in the Virginia primaries. Follow The Post’s coverage to see results in crucial House races and more.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post is bringing you live coverage of election results, analysis and more as votes are tallied in several contested House primaries across the state, as well as local races.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10442d20-2dc7-11ef-8ce5-0000a1ace053</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 23:04:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says it is nearing the end of its Rafah offensive, potentially shifting to a new, less-intense phase of the conflict</title>
      <description>Israeli forces are making progress against Hamas in Rafah, a senior military official said, destroying the group’s infrastructure and cutting the supply of weapons coming through tunnels from Egypt. A shift to more targeted operations across Gaza could bring respite to civilians who have spent months in the line of fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4e6240-2dbe-11ef-a0e2-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. won’t meet CNN debate requirement for ballot access</title>
      <description>The independent presidential candidate has said he has qualified for enough state ballots, but state election officials have said that’s not true.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92543800-2db8-11ef-8cc3-0000a1aced16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 21:20:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nvidia becomes the world’s most valuable public company, pushing past Apple and Microsoft</title>
      <description>The company’s computer chips and software are crucial to training the artificial-intelligence algorithms behind image generators and chatbots like OpenAI’s ChatGPT. As the tech and business worlds throw themselves into the AI boom, demand for Nvidia's chips has skyrocketed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33d4de50-2daf-11ef-a0e2-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 20:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The national debt will grow to more than $50 trillion by 2034, CBO projects, as defense costs and safety net spending rise</title>
      <description>This year’s federal deficit will grow to $1.9 trillion, according to the Congressional Budget Office. A large debt balance could keep federal interest rates high and present risks in bond markets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6a32cf0-2d9c-11ef-ae40-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Does age make a person less gracious — or better at boundaries?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Does age make a person less gracious — or better at boundaries?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ed001f0-2d8c-11ef-b0d0-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 16:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A major awards show is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc98581-2d76-11ef-9730-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration rule. Heat wave. Putin visit. Mark Robinson. Social media warning. Ian McKellen. NBA Finals. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">def80ad0-2d61-11ef-b168-0000a1ace076</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boston Celtics beat Dallas Mavericks in NBA Finals, securing the franchise’s record 18th championship</title>
      <description>The Celtics won Game 5 on their home floor Monday night to claim their first NBA title since 2008 and cap a dominant postseason in which they went 16-3. Boston moves ahead of the rival Los Angeles Lakers, who pulled even with their 17th championship in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67bb8281-2d20-11ef-ac39-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 03:11:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden to announce program allowing undocumented immigrants married to U.S. citizens to apply for legal residency</title>
      <description>Biden will unveil the policy Tuesday in one of the most expansive immigration programs of his presidency, according to two federal sources with knowledge of the plans. About 500,000 people are expected to be eligible to apply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20e069d0-2d01-11ef-a840-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 23:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS to enact rules that would prevent businesses and wealthy individuals from manipulating the value of assets to lower their taxes</title>
      <description>The agency wants to crack down on those who repeatedly depreciate the value of their assets. New audits could bring in an extra $5 billion a year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f4fdf90-2cd1-11ef-88bb-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:43:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: I'm married to a ‘secret bigot.’ How do I reconcile the vile things he says?</title>
      <description>I'm married to a ‘secret bigot.’ How do I reconcile the vile things he says?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d89c0de1-2cc5-11ef-8a42-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 16:22:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A $50 billion pay package in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7234100-2cad-11ef-ad96-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 13:30:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin traveling to North Korea on Tuesday amid concerns about growing military cooperation between the countries</title>
      <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin and Kim Jong Un are expected to pledge public support for each other and rebuff U.S.-led efforts to isolate Russia over its invasion of Ukraine. Moscow is in desperate need of the munitions that North Korea can provide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb1009a0-2c9b-11ef-bca2-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza fighting. Brutal heat. Biden ad. Marijuana pardons. Baby genomes. Screen time. Princess Kate. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b35c5a81-2c98-11ef-9bbb-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Stereophonic’ and ‘The Outsiders’ win big at the 2024 Tony Awards</title>
      <description>Daniel Radcliffe and Jeremy Strong also took home prizes at the ceremony honoring Broadway’s best.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f45167c1-2c56-11ef-b360-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 03:09:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incoming Post editor tied to self-described ‘thief’ who claimed role in his reporting</title>
      <description>Unpublished book drafts and other documents raise questions about Robert Winnett’s journalistic record just months before he is to assume a top newsroom role at The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28250aa0-2c40-11ef-91af-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 00:25:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
