<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:01:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>EPA proposes that companies no longer be required to report their planet-warming emissions</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency’s proposal, published Friday, amounts to a major regulatory rollback that would eliminate the primary means of tracking climate goals. EPA Administrator Lee Zeldin described it as a cost-cutting measure that would save businesses up to $2.4 billion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68cb9540-9019-11f0-9a81-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man fatally shot by ICE officer in Chicago after allegedly resisting arrest</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security said Friday that a federal immigration officer fatally shot a man in the Chicago area during an attempted arrest after the man drove his vehicle toward the law enforcement officials, hitting one of them.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb392270-9009-11f0-9b46-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:53:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli intelligence agency balked at Netanyahu’s strike in Qatar</title>
      <description>The Mossad had planned a ground operation targeting Hamas leaders but declined to execute it, forcing Israel to carry out the unsuccessful airstrike, Israelis say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">219b2840-9008-11f0-8a3e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: After abusive stepdad’s death, mom says she was a victim, too</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: After abusive stepdad’s death, mom says she was a victim, too.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e743ce00-8ff7-11f0-bee5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump health officials plan to link coronavirus vaccines to 25 child deaths, alarming career scientists</title>
      <description>The data is set to be included in a presentation next week to the CDC vaccine advisory committee that is considering new coronavirus vaccine recommendations, according to several people familiar with the situation. The data appears based on reports to a federal database that is not designed to assess whether vaccines caused deaths. The move has alarmed career scientists who say that coronavirus vaccines have been extensively studied, including in children, and that dangers of the virus itself are being underplayed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d13965b0-8ff3-11f0-abf0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says National Guard will be deployed in Memphis to fight crime</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said during an interview on Fox News that Memphis will be the next city in which the National Guard is tapped following the deployment in D.C. Trump had previously floated deploying the Guard in Chicago but state and local officials have resisted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5512682-8fef-11f0-9a81-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family friend turned in 22-year-old suspect in Charlie Kirk shooting, Utah governor says. Follow live updates.</title>
      <description>Tyler Robinson confessed to the shooting of the conservative commentator at Utah Valley University to a family member, who told a family friend who in turn reached out to authorities, Utah Gov. Spencer Cox said at a news conference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1717f6c1-8fe3-11f0-aea4-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 14:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c739090-8fdd-11f0-a149-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:33:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Charlie Kirk shooting suspect is in custody</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said authorities have a “high degree of certainty” that they’ve found the suspect in the Wednesday shooting of conservative commentator Charlie Kirk, who was speaking at a Utah Valley University event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8196a3d0-8fd3-11f0-8883-0000a1ace826</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 12:25:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk. Trump’s response. Jair Bolsonaro. Senate rules. Inflation tips. Chronic pain. Lanternfly swarms. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2510d10-8fc7-11f0-b363-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Officials release new video of suspect fleeing in Charlie Kirk shooting, still lack a name or location</title>
      <description>Law enforcement released a new video showing a person climbing down from the edge of a roof, dropping to the ground and moving across a grassy area near a parking lot. Officials said they had still been unable to find or name the person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec04a320-8f83-11f0-8b62-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:55:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A single exercise session may slow cancer cell growth, a new study shows</title>
      <description>The study involved 32 women who had survived breast cancer. After a single session of interval training or weightlifting, their blood contained higher levels of certain molecules, and those factors helped put the brakes on laboratory-grown breast cancer cells.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4024cbe1-8f59-11f0-8429-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:49:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans change Senate rules to speed up confirmation of Trump nominees as nearly 150 await votes</title>
      <description>Senate Republicans invoked the “nuclear option” to change the chamber’s rules to allow all executive branch nominees — with the exception of Cabinet posts and judges — to be approved in groups and with less debate. Democrats had drawn out the process of voting on President Donald Trump’s nominees because they argue the nominees are unqualified.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec4fe850-8f54-11f0-81d5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:18:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ex-Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro found guilty in 2022 coup and assassination plot to stay in power</title>
      <description>Brazil’s supreme court ruled the right-wing former president attempted a military coup to reverse his 2022 election loss, a plot that included plans to assassinate President Luiz Inácio Lula da Silva, the man who defeated him. President Donald Trump, a Bolsonaro ally and friend, imposed tariffs on Brazilian products and sanctions on individual justices in July to pressure them to drop the prosecution, which he called a witch hunt.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3df91440-8f43-11f0-9aa5-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI releases two photos of person of interest in Charlie Kirk shooting</title>
      <description>Authorities are seeking the public’s help in identifying a person they believe may be connected to the shooting. The images show a man in a black shirt, sunglasses and dark hat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc207b1-8f29-11f0-b91b-0000a1ace852</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants it to be college son’s idea to call more</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants it to be college son’s idea to call more</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b8776e0-8f28-11f0-90c7-0000a1ace0b1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Working fewer hours in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2860c30-8f17-11f0-a173-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk’s shooter remains at large, but investigators say they have footage of a suspect and recovered a rifle</title>
      <description>Investigators have video footage of the shooter, but they do not plan to release it at this time, a Utah official said at a news conference. They also have found what they believe to be the weapon used to kill Kirk. Follow our live coverage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">024b4d61-8f15-11f0-a9e9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:41:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation picked up in August, as Trump’s tariffs continue to pressure prices across more of the economy</title>
      <description>The hotter inflation data, released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics, combined with a weakening labor market, presents a tricky decision for the Federal Reserve, which will consider interest rate cuts at a meeting next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fb5d2c0-8f0b-11f0-8027-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:33:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Koreans detained at Georgia Hyundai plant are headed home, but Trump offered to let them stay and train Americans, Seoul says</title>
      <description>The 316 South Koreans who were arrested at the Hyundai-LG plant in Georgia are now on their way home. The raid and the treatment of the workers could make South Korean companies “very hesitant” about operating in the United States, the country’s president said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30aa33e1-8f03-11f0-a2b3-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk. FBI lawsuit. Kamala Harris. Housing costs. Cancer and exercise. Humid summer. Life on Mars. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78cd1930-8efe-11f0-9925-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.K. dismisses its ambassador to the U.S., citing new information about his links to Jeffrey Epstein</title>
      <description>British Prime Minister Keir Starmer said he withdrew Peter Mandelson from his post after new information emerged about the ambassador’s links to the American sex offender.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a960c6c0-8efc-11f0-b91b-0000a1ace852</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Kirk, dead at 31, leveraged his debate skills to create viral moments that captured audiences across the political spectrum</title>
      <description>The Turning Point USA founder had an audience of millions of fervent conservative fans and fierce liberal critics, emerging as one of the most prominent — and often controversial — voices in the age of Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86091370-8eb2-11f0-a208-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person of interest in Charlie Kirk shooting is in custody, Utah governor says</title>
      <description>Utah Gov. Spencer Cox (R) said at a news conference that the person is being interviewed by officials. Cox said the shooting was a “political assassination” and vowed to hold the killer “accountable to the furthest extent of the law.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37fddd50-8e99-11f0-b493-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 22:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conservative activist Charlie Kirk dies at 31 after he was shot onstage at Utah college event, Trump says</title>
      <description>Kirk, the founder of Turning Point USA, was shot while speaking at an event at Utah Valley University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18184be0-8e87-11f0-84be-000a1ace778b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 20:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Right-wing activist Charlie Kirk shot at Utah college event, two people familiar with matter say</title>
      <description>Kirk is the founder of Turning Point USA, an organization for young conservatives. He was speaking at an event at Utah Valley University. The school said the suspect was in custody, according to parents whose children received an email from the university.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a037ee0-8e79-11f0-ae8b-0000a1ace2c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former FBI leaders sue Director Kash Patel, alleging they were unlawfully fired over perceived political disloyalty</title>
      <description>Former acting FBI director Brian Driscoll alleged in the federal lawsuit that a Trump administration official asked questions including: “Who did you vote for?,” “When did you start supporting President Trump?” and “Have you voted for a Democrat in the last five elections?”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b259c80-8e6c-11f0-8e00-0000a1ace431</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In new memoir, Kamala Harris says it was ‘recklessness’ to defer to Joe Biden’s decision to run at age 80</title>
      <description>In her forthcoming book, “107 Days,” Harris said she “perhaps” should have weighed in but worried it would have looked “incredibly self-serving” and disloyal for her to do as Biden’s vice president. She also wrote about not feeling supported by his staff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a617eb51-8e62-11f0-9c07-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:24:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: This dad is so consumed by disapproval, it ate his marriage, too</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: This dad is so consumed by disapproval, it ate his marriage, too</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c2d9b61-8e5f-11f0-a6e1-000a1acec938</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Is drunk brunch getting out of control?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Is drunk brunch getting out of control?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43f54140-8e5b-11f0-b36b-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rocks found on Mars are some of the strongest clues yet of past life on the dusty planet</title>
      <description>Detailed analysis of images of speckled rocks found by NASA’s Perseverance rover has confirmed a “potential biosignature.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a378330-8e57-11f0-9fce-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard documents say public finds D.C. mission wasteful and some veterans feel ‘shame’</title>
      <description>The assessments, which have not been previously reported, underscore how domestic mobilizations that are rooted in politics risk damaging Americans’ confidence in the National Guard. They also reveal, with a rare candor in some cases, that military officials have been kept apprised that their mission is viewed by a segment of society as wasteful, counterproductive and a threat to long-standing precedent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21857e50-8e50-11f0-bfab-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More political drama for this country in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72489991-8e4a-11f0-8331-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Qatar. National Guard. Trump’s signature. Russian drones. Rising prices. Missing storms. New iPhones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d2dbf60-8e35-11f0-9170-0000a1acedb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 11:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poland says it shot down Russian drones that violated its airspace while attacking targets in Ukraine</title>
      <description>Russia’s actions posed “a real threat” to Polish citizens, the Polish military’s Operational Command said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bd8fb20-8e03-11f0-9974-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 05:04:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily blocks Trump’s firing of Federal Reserve board member Lisa Cook</title>
      <description>In a setback for the president, the judge ruled that Cook had shown strong evidence that the effort to dismiss her was illegal. The board will meet next week to consider an interest rate cut.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3838e130-8dee-11f0-9e25-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 02:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired CDC director Susan Monarez, who clashed with RFK Jr. over vaccines, will testify before Senate next week</title>
      <description>The hearing will be Monarez’s first public appearance to address the tumult at the CDC. She has said Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. pressured her to alter vaccine policies and fire staff. Kennedy told senators last week that Monarez lied about their interactions and said she was untrustworthy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">712f88e0-8dd0-11f0-b3d3-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:58:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court agrees to quickly weigh the legality of most of Trump’s tariffs in major economic case</title>
      <description>The far-reaching case is expected to determine the fate of a cornerstone of President Donald Trump’s economic agenda and could alter the course of the U.S. economy and global trade.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967b6550-8dbd-11f0-8000-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:43:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oliver North quietly married his former secretary Fawn Hall, four decades after their roles in the Iran-contra scandal</title>
      <description>The couple tied the knot on Aug. 27 in Virginia, according to a marriage license obtained by The Washington Post. As a National Security Council staffer under President Ronald Reagan, North was accused of illegally arranging the sale of U.S. weapons to Iran to fund a secret war against communists in Nicaragua. Hall, his young secretary at the time, had shred documents and even smuggled evidence out of the office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">507e4e90-8db4-11f0-b82a-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:36:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation wiped out income gains in 2024, but richest 10 percent of households got richer, census finds</title>
      <description>Most Americans’ household income remained steady last year, but women and Black people lost ground, the U.S. Census Bureau said Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f34aa000-8db0-11f0-b1b7-000a1ace0896</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri state House becomes latest to pass Trump-backed congressional map as partisan redistricting fight escalates</title>
      <description>The plan is expected to give Republicans one more U.S. House seat ahead of the midterm elections. It now heads to the state Senate, where it is expected to pass this month and later receive the signature of Gov. Mike Kehoe (R).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7657dd50-8da7-11f0-a94e-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Son’s classmate told him her mom is abusive. Report it?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Son’s classmate told him her mom is abusive. Report it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32aee960-8d96-11f0-921f-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge throws out charges against Michigan Republicans who claimed to be electors after Trump lost 2020 election</title>
      <description>The dismissal of the charges is a victory for President Donald Trump and his allies and a blow to Michigan’s Democratic attorney general.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">558119a1-8d8b-11f0-a2f4-000a1ace9959</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:43:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: U.S. revises jobs reports down by 911,000 for year ending in March. A previous alert said 910,000.</title>
      <description>The revisions by the Bureau of Labor Statistics are the latest round of significant changes to labor market data, which has faced heightened scrutiny after President Donald Trump took the unprecedented step of firing the BLS commissioner over updated reports. A previous alert misstated the revised number. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87659c10-8d87-11f0-b6e1-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. revises jobs reports down by 910,000 for year ending in March, showing slower economy before Trump took office</title>
      <description>The revisions by the Bureau of Labor Statistics are the latest round of significant changes to labor market data, which has faced heightened scrutiny after President Donald Trump took the unprecedented step of firing the BLS commissioner over updated reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">195c0344-8d86-11f0-ba66-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A canceled award ceremony in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93d530e0-8d83-11f0-9915-0000a1aced86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel targets senior Hamas leadership in Qatar as explosions are heard in Doha</title>
      <description>The Israel Defense Forces said Tuesday that it carried out a strike targeting the senior leadership of Hamas. It did not say where the strike took place, but Qatar’s Foreign Ministry confirmed an attack on Hamas political leaders in the capital, Doha.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138f2ae0-8d82-11f0-9b6a-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein sketch. Chicago raids. E. Jean Carroll. Murdoch empire. Test scores. ‘Kissing bug’ disease. Banksy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1eef9ed0-8d6c-11f0-8ec7-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘acoustic terror’ of Russia’s blasts makes people wonder if they are dead. Hear it for yourself.</title>
      <description>This summer, there were no quiet nights for Ukraine. Russian attacks have increased more than fivefold since January, deafening people with sirens, drones and ballistic missiles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0908bb20-8d07-11f0-9552-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Murdoch family resolves dispute over ownership of media empire in billion-dollar deal</title>
      <description>Lachlan Murdoch, whose politics are in line with those of his 94-year-old father, will remain in control after Rupert Murdoch’s death, with three other siblings splitting a $3.3 billion settlement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72682aa0-8cf9-11f0-855e-0000a1ace46b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
