<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 15:03:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Internet runs wild with conspiracy theories in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a541bb20-dbc6-11ee-a6de-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 14:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley. Kyrsten Sinema. State of the Union. Gaza talks. Bitcoin. Coronavirus shots. Mr. Darcy. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d0b9020-dbb1-11ee-94b7-0000a1ace178</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 11:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley to suspend her presidential campaign, according to several people familiar with her plans</title>
      <description>The former U.N. ambassador is set to make the announcement this morning in South Carolina, according to several people familiar with her plans. The only woman in the Republican contest, Haley campaigned on her foreign policy experience and general election appeal, casting her candidacy as a generational change that could bring more voters into the party. But her message struggled to appeal to a base that overwhelmingly supports former president Donald Trump, who now stands as the presumptive nominee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79041580-dbad-11ee-b0b1-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 11:34:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Adam Schiff (D) and Steve Garvey (R) will move on to the general election for Senate seats in California, AP projects</title>
      <description>Schiff and Garvey were the top two vote-getters in California’s all-party primary and will now be on the ballot in November to replace the late Sen. Dianne Feinstein (D), the Associated Press projected. Schiff was also projected one of the top vote-getters in the special primary to fill out the remainder of Feinstein’s term.
Schiff faced two other Democratic House members after he scored some heavyweight endorsements and spent heavily on TV ads. Garvey, a former professional baseball player, didn’t run a single ad but may have benefitted from Schiff’s ads calling him “too conservative.” Schiff will be favored to win in the deep-blue state this fall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2214efe1-db78-11ee-a4b9-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 05:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley scores a surprise upset against Trump in Vermont, AP projects, racking up her second win of GOP nomination contest</title>
      <description>The former U.N. ambassador beat Donald Trump in Vermont, the Associated Press reported, despite lagging far behind him in the GOP delegate count. Haley also triumphed in the D.C. primary Sunday.

A third of delegates are awarded tonight — still not enough for Trump to clinch the nod. Haley had committed to staying in the race at least until Super Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">466ebc70-db6b-11ee-a9b0-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 03:40:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump wins 10 states so far on Super Tuesday, AP projects, moving into a commanding delegate lead over Haley</title>
      <description>Fifteen states cast their ballots tonight in the most consequential night of voting so far, with a third of Republican delegates awarded. But Trump can’t officially clinch the nomination until at least March 12, the Associated Press projects. Haley had committed to staying in the contest until at least Super Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a75e9101-db60-11ee-bdd5-0000a1ace4dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 02:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Robinson, the controversial lieutenant governor endorsed by Trump, wins N.C. GOP gubernatorial nod, AP projects</title>
      <description>Robinson beat several other contenders for the open seat of outgoing Gov. Roy Cooper (D), the Associated Press reported. The race will be one of the most competitive gubernatorial contests in the country, as many say Robinson, the first Black person to hold the lieutenant governor post, is too extreme to win the state’s general election.

Robinson has mocked school shooting survivors, called Michelle Obama a man, insulted transgender people and used antisemitic tropes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dffe4470-db55-11ee-89d2-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 01:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Super Tuesday, and a third of delegates are up for grabs as Trump aims to decisively defeat Haley. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Fifteen states vote and a third of delegates are awarded today in the race for the GOP presidential nomination. Donald Trump has won every nominating contest except one, though he cannot officially clinch the nomination until at least March 12, the AP projects. President Biden is also on the ballot but faces minor competition, while high-profile down-ballot races for governor, Senate and House are being held North Carolina, Texas and California. The Associated Press reports the earliest Biden can secure the Democratic nod is March 19.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62ede7a0-db4c-11ee-a7c9-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Council passes massive public safety package with harsher punishments for more offenses, following spike in violent crime</title>
      <description>The Secure D.C. Omnibus Amendment Act makes it easier for judges to order adults charged with violent offenses detained while they await trial, expands the definition of carjacking to make the cases easier to prosecute, and revives a 1990s-era tool that would allow officers to create temporary drug-free zones.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12a557c1-db4b-11ee-8c51-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 23:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Bob Menendez and wife Nadine Menendez are charged with more bribery counts in Egyptian and Qatari influence-peddling case</title>
      <description>Federal prosecutors added about a dozen counts to their case that says the couple and associates conspired to have Sen. Menendez (D-N.J.) act as an illegal foreign agent on behalf of the Egyptian and Qatari governments. The Menendezes have pleaded not guilty to previous charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b300ec0-db3b-11ee-b0ba-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 21:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dana Milbank voted as a Republican in the D.C. primary. Surprised? He explains why.</title>
      <description>My month of living Republicanly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a691c7c1-db37-11ee-8a89-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 21:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Kyrsten Sinema (I-Ariz.) will not seek reelection. She left the Democratic Party in 2022 and faced stiff competition.</title>
      <description>(D-Ariz.) and Kari Lake (R) that could help determine which party controls the Senate next year. Sinema announced her decision in a video posted on social media, saying, “I believe in my approach, but it’s not what America wants right now.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff51ea30-db27-11ee-af50-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 19:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dartmouth men’s basketball team votes to unionize in a case that could alter college sports. But there’s still a long road ahead.</title>
      <description>Dartmouth players voted 13-2 in favor of unionization Tuesday, allowing them to collectively bargain with the university over pay, practice hours and other working conditions. A lengthy appeals process is certain to play out, but if the athletes’ status as employees is upheld, the amateur model in college sports will be upended.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd298591-db1f-11ee-bed8-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 18:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liberty University fined a record $14 million as Education Department says it repeatedly violated law aimed to keep campuses safe</title>
      <description>The long-anticipated finding comes months after The Washington Post reported that a preliminary review by the department found that the private university in Lynchburg, Va., had discouraged people from reporting crimes, underreported alleged incidents and failed to warn the campus of safety concerns.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e5928e1-db1a-11ee-b26c-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 18:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Facebook and Instagram are back up, Meta says, after a widespread outage affected thousands of users</title>
      <description>The problems with Meta’s platforms blocked thousands of users from logging onto their social media accounts. The interruption had affected more that 570,000 Facebook users and more than 90,000 Instagram users by 10:30 a.m. Eastern time, according to Downdetector, a service that tracks online glitches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7643960-db17-11ee-8ee0-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: When stepsiblings fight, parent feels guilty for blending family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: When stepsiblings fight, parent feels guilty for blending family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f1d3960-db12-11ee-93c9-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 17:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>History is made in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01b03410-dafd-11ee-9d2f-000a1ace0186</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration announces rule to limit most credit card late fees to $8, setting up potential clash with banks</title>
      <description>The new Consumer Financial Protection Bureau rule would take effect this spring. It’s part of a suite of new rules the administration is rolling out Tuesday to promote competition and crack down on unfair, illegal or predatory pricing. But banks are expected to sue to block the rule.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67bf3f10-dafa-11ee-8ac3-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 14:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Super Tuesday. Hamas report. France abortion. Birth control. Credit card fees. Tax filing. Tumbleweeds. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e73c3fd0-dae7-11ee-9f16-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2024 12:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter is warming almost everywhere in the U.S. This is how the season has changed in your city since 1980.</title>
      <description>Look up your city to see how winter temperatures have changed over the past decades. Most regions across the United States have seen warmer winters, with New England warming the fastest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f371470-da79-11ee-9d76-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 22:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: 4 takeaways from the Supreme Court’s ruling on Trump and the 14th Amendment</title>
      <description>The ruling in Trump v. Anderson reverses the Colorado Supreme Court’s disqualification of Donald Trump from the state 2024 primary ballot. But the court did not discuss whether he actually engaged in insurrection on Jan. 6, 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5eeb1a0-da6d-11ee-adeb-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 21:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New U.N. report finds ‘reasonable grounds’ to believe people were sexually assaulted during Hamas’s Oct. 7 attack on Israel</title>
      <description>As part of its inquiry, a team of experts interviewed survivors and witnesses of the Oct. 7 attacks — though they did not speak with any survivors of the alleged sexual violence and did not attribute the violence to specific armed groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9bce20-da67-11ee-bd7a-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 20:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Kelce, the Philadelphia Eagles’ longtime center, will retire after a stellar 13-year NFL career</title>
      <description>Kelce’s six all-pro nods and victory in Super Bowl LII almost certainly will earn him a place in the Pro Football Hall of Fame. Off the field, Kelce gained even more fame thanks to the podcast he hosts with his brother, Kansas City Chiefs tight end Travis Kelce, and his boisterous, shirtless celebrations as the Chiefs advanced to this year’s Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a04e4230-da56-11ee-bf66-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>France becomes first country to explicitly enshrine abortion rights in its constitution — a response to U.S. restrictions</title>
      <description>French lawmakers meeting in a special session at Versailles voted to add abortion to the constitution as a “guaranteed freedom.” Activists and politicians have been transparent that this is a response to the U.S. Supreme Court ruling that abortion protections are not inferred from the Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d30fe590-da4f-11ee-bf66-00000a1acedc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 17:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A lifelong gun owner wondered how he'd react if an intruder ever broke in. Then he found out.</title>
      <description>I never sleep with a gun under my pillow. But one night not long ago, I wished I had.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7146e580-da4e-11ee-9088-000a1ace148d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 17:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Under pressure to forgive ailing mom for abandoning them as kids</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Under pressure to forgive ailing mom for abandoning them as kids</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db04f620-da48-11ee-b700-000a1ace0045</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 17:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Trump Organization financial officer Allen Weisselberg pleads guilty to perjury charges</title>
      <description>The perjury charges mark the latest legal peril for Allen Weisselberg, who in recent years pleaded guilty to multiple felonies, including grand larceny and criminal tax fraud; served months behind bars; and was penalized $1 million in a civil fraud trial.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd10fa50-da43-11ee-a39b-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 16:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court rules Trump can remain on primary ballots, ending a bid to disqualify him over his role in the Jan. 6 riot</title>
      <description>The decision resolves a lawsuit filed by Colorado voters who argued that the Constitution bars Donald Trump from holding office because his actions surrounding the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the Capitol amounted to insurrection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f07fb20-da38-11ee-91ad-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 15:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBlue and Spirit call off $3.8 billion merger after antitrust challenge</title>
      <description>JetBlue had sought to acquire Spirit Airlines, but a judge had blocked the deal after the Justice Department sued to stop it on grounds that it would stifle competition and reduce options for fliers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0595e30-da34-11ee-ba1e-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:36:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A viral tribute to beloved dog Dipper in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9d23d50-da33-11ee-8dc4-0000a1ace082</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 14:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican race. Israel-Gaza war. Health-care hack. Blizzard. Abortion pills. Caitlin Clark. Dino discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b835c631-da1e-11ee-9f83-00000a1acec3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 11:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haley pulls off her first 2024 GOP win in D.C., AP projects. Trump is still heavily favored to clinch the nomination.</title>
      <description>Nikki Haley beat Donald Trump in the nation’s capital, the Associated Press reported. But only 19 delegates were at stake, so her campaign still significantly lags as the race heads to what could be a decisive Super Tuesday on March 5, when 15 states and a third of delegates are awarded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb97d6a0-d9c7-11ee-b63c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 01:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s restrictions on Gaza aid put the enclave on the brink of famine</title>
      <description>Thursday’s aid convoy tragedy highlighted the ongoing obstacles to delivering aid to war-battered Gaza. Humanitarian officials say Israel’s limiting of entry points for aid, its onerous inspection process, and its military’s attacks on aid convoys and the police who guarded them have produced a “manmade” hunger crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e140e10-d9b0-11ee-b700-000a1ace0045</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 22:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I don’t want kids. Should I have them to make my parents happy?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I don’t want kids. Should I have them to make my parents happy?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9627610-d999-11ee-b4e4-0000a1ace5d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 20:07:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa star Caitlin Clark passes Pete Maravich to become the all-time NCAA Division I basketball scoring leader</title>
      <description>Clark, whose No. 6 Iowa Hawkeyes faced No. 2 Ohio State on Sunday, needed 18 points to surpass Maravich for the record. Last week, the senior guard broke a pre-NCAA scoring record set by Lynette Woodard for women’s major college basketball and announced her intention to enter the 2024 WNBA draft, where she's widely expected to be the No. 1 overall pick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cd1ad10-d990-11ee-9e49-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:58:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ba14030-d98c-11ee-b503-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Relisha Rudd was 8 when a janitor at a homeless shelter befriended her, then took her. A decade later, she haunts a changed city.</title>
      <description>Nearly three weeks passed before D.C. authorities realized she was missing. She still has not been found. Her disappearance forced a reckoning in how the city treats its poorest and most vulnerable residents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">436c2960-d97f-11ee-84d2-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 16:58:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Offensive comments by N.C. Republican gubernatorial hopeful Mark Robinson stand out, even in Trump’s party</title>
      <description>Robinson is favored to advance to a November showdown against Democratic Attorney General Josh Stein, who has a much more measured tone — setting up a clash that echoes the choice between former president Donald Trump and President Biden. To many Republicans, Robinson is a conservative Christian firebrand with Trump-like appeal. To others, he is a glaring liability in a battleground race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc947b0-d973-11ee-b848-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 15:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e4b2671-d96a-11ee-a008-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 14:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump sweeps GOP primary contests in Michigan, Idaho and Missouri, AP projects, bringing him closer to clinching nomination</title>
      <description>Donald Trump won all three nominating contests Saturday, the Associated Press projected, putting him in a stronger position for March 5, the day 15 states and a third of delegates are awarded as part of Super Tuesday. Nikki Haley, Trump’s main rival for the GOP nod, has vowed to press on until then, despite losing every primary and caucus so far.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29407740-d8f2-11ee-9d52-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 00:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a CVS drugstore in D.C. became a symbol of America's shoplifting panic</title>
      <description>It became a horror story of Late Capitalism. Tales were told on social media, and in the comments sections of local news stories, and they were full of spooky scenes (harsh fluorescent lights shining on bare shelves!) and jump scares (hordes of teenagers reportedly ransacking the stores!).</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60767470-d8da-11ee-a050-000a1ace86f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 21:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An examination of Robert F. Kennedy’s early years as a lawyer reveals a controversy long before he trained his sights on vaccines</title>
      <description>As a young attorney at Riverkeeper, Kennedy Jr. opened a schism by hiring a new staff scientist just released from federal prison. His crime: running an international wildlife smuggling ring that prosecutors said had damaged rare bird populations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa1b5c60-d8c8-11ee-832a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Maryland halts all fraternity, sorority events amid hazing concerns</title>
      <description>The University of Maryland has suspended all “new member” fraternity and sorority events and any events with alcohol while officials look into hazing allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f137eba0-d8b8-11ee-9432-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 17:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After a scary ‘incident,’ spouse wants husband out for good</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After a scary ‘incident,’ spouse wants husband out for good</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ad1a770-d8b7-11ee-8ca3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 17:09:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘greenest’ car in America might surprise you. Hint: It’s not an EV.</title>
      <description>A new analysis finds that the greenest car in America this year isn’t an electric vehicle — it’s the Toyota Prius Prime, a plug-in hybrid that can go 44 miles on all-electric power. The result shows that size and efficiency, not just drivetrain, matter when buying a new car.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0115171-d8af-11ee-b802-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 16:12:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military airdrops aid into Gaza as relief agencies warn of mass starvation</title>
      <description>Three U.S. officials confirmed Saturday that the airdrops were carried out by C-130 cargo plane. The operation followed similar moves from countries including Egypt, France, Jordan and the United Arab Emirates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">422cf4b1-d8a5-11ee-a9b5-0000a1acecd6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 14:57:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84155970-d8a1-11ee-8137-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 14:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iris Apfel has died at 102. The designer, known for her oversized, owlish spectacles, became a ‘geriatric starlet’ in her 80s.</title>
      <description>Apfel, who died at her home in Palm Beach, Fla., appeared regularly in the style pages of the New York Times and starred in advertising campaigns for Kate Spade and Coach handbags. Stu Loeser, a spokesman for her estate, confirmed her death in a statement but did not provide a specific cause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">560b0030-d832-11ee-8d4a-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 01:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to launch airdrop campaign over Gaza, Biden says, as humanitarian crisis worsens</title>
      <description>The announcement comes with Gaza on the brink of famine, humanitarian groups say. Aid convoys have struggled to make deliveries amid Israel’s bombardment of the Palestinian enclave and disruptions at border crossings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa7dc480-d801-11ee-b514-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 19:26:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Final arguments are underway on whether Fani Willis should be disqualified from case against Trump. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Defense attorneys and prosecutors in the election interference case against former president Donald Trump and his allies are scheduled to make their final arguments this afternoon on whether Fulton County District Attorney Fani T. Willis (D) and her office should be disqualified from the case. Fulton County Superior Court Judge Scott McAfee has suggested that he does not plan to rule from the bench today, and he has not provided a timeline for his decision. The misconduct allegations threaten to derail the criminal case against Trump, one of four he faces as he again runs for president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c503f10-d7f7-11ee-9302-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 18:12:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
