<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:02:17 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>FDA limits approval for new coronavirus vaccines to those considered high risk</title>
      <description>Trump administration officials have criticized the previous public health approach to broadly recommend annual coronavirus vaccines. The new approach limits approvals to those ages 65 and older or those with a medical condition that elevates their risk of severe disease. It's unclear if others will be able to access shots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb8fb771-836c-11f0-8dd5-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration moves to bar states and nonprofits, such as Red Cross, from helping undocumented immigrants after disasters</title>
      <description>The new Homeland Security requirements for receiving federal funds have sparked concern among organizations that provide relief in the aftermath of disasters. The rules also say that states and volunteer organizations must comply with immigration officials and enforcement operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57c5fad0-836a-11f0-a3ab-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis gunman fired on students at worship service, killing 2 children, injuring 17 people before shooting self, officials say</title>
      <description>The shooter, a man in his early 20s with three weapons, is dead from an apparent self-inflicted gunshot wound, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7158cef0-8360-11f0-886f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:11:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple children injured in shooting at Minneapolis Catholic school, hospital says; police say shooter is no longer a threat</title>
      <description>Family members of students at Annunciation Catholic School rushed to the scene, which police had cordoned off with vehicles and yellow tape.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bbfd491-8359-11f0-8c8c-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury declines to indict D.C. man arrested for throwing a sandwich at federal law enforcement</title>
      <description>The failure by federal prosecutors to secure an indictment Tuesday is the latest example of President Donald Trump’s surge of policing on the streets of D.C. meeting resistance in the city’s federal courthouse. This month, Sean Charles Dunn, a Justice Department employee, was charged with “assaulting, resisting, or impeding certain officers and employees of the United States.” Prosecutors could try again to secure a grand jury indictment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">316bbb70-8358-11f0-a121-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A draw at the Kennedy Center in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6690960-8349-11f0-a774-0000a1ace413</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. judges and grand jurors push back on Trump policing surge</title>
      <description>A federal magistrate judge said one arrest in D.C. was preceded by the “most illegal search I’ve seen in my life.” In another case, a grand jury refused three times to issue an indictment against a woman accused of assaulting a federal officer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adf9a800-8344-11f0-b629-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:52:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Transportation Department plans to take over D.C.’s Union Station</title>
      <description>It’s not clear how dramatic the change will be for the transit hub, which connects regional trains and buses to the Metro system. But it is another example of the White House exerting power over the District as National Guard soldiers and federal law enforcement officers continue to patrol the city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4d60060-833b-11f0-b55e-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:49:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death penalty. FEMA letter. Federal Reserve. School ‘swattings.’ AI test. Cracker Barrel. Taylor Swift’s ring. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7151c0-8334-11f0-bc98-0000a1ace758</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration places several FEMA employees on leave after they signed a letter criticizing the agency’s leadership</title>
      <description>Federal Emergency Management Agency officials informed some staffers that they were no longer on active duty after about 180 current and former employees sent a letter Monday arguing current leaders’ inexperience and approach could result in a disaster on the level of Hurricane Katrina, according to documents reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe84b630-82e4-11f0-8d5c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s latest attempt to erode the Fed’s independence is dangerous, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>Frustration with the central bank is understandable, but trying to fire Lisa Cook is not the answer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d60577f0-82a6-11f0-804a-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce announce their engagement on Instagram</title>
      <description>The pop star and Kansas City Chiefs tight end have dated since 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce072b80-82a0-11f0-9baa-0000a1ace4c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:19:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Nieces prefer getting cash gifts and not sending thank-you notes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Nieces prefer getting cash gifts and not sending thank-you notes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ba99810-8296-11f0-ad75-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge dismisses Justice Department lawsuit against all 15 of Maryland’s judges over handling of deportations</title>
      <description>Judge Thomas T. Cullen ruled that the Maryland bench was within its rights to pause deportations for two business days in cases where a habeas corpus petition was filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1003c770-8290-11f0-a759-0000a1acef4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A controversial redesign in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeed4fc0-8280-11f0-9775-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The six factions of Trumpworld: The president melds a contentious coalition</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s coalition is built for internal conflict — held together by fealty to him but riven by differences on immigration, tariffs, abortion and other policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b78c70d0-827e-11f0-804a-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Reserve. Flag burning. Epstein files. Israeli attack. Screwworm. World map. Teacherless school. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8dfff40-826b-11f0-b551-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia accuses Iran of directing antisemitic attacks, expels its ambassador</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Anthony Albanese said Australia’s security agency determined Tehran was behind at least two attacks on Jewish institutions in Sydney and Melbourne.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8451de71-8239-11f0-8b53-0000a1ace575</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump moves to fire Fed governor Lisa Cook over allegations of mortgage fraud, saying there’s ‘sufficient cause’ for removal</title>
      <description>The president cited his authority to fire governors for cause in a letter posted to Truth Social. The move could lead to a major test of the Federal Reserve’s independence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ae4e260-8216-11f0-af9e-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Lloyd Wright’s iconic Fallingwater is leaking. See inside the $7 million effort to save it.</title>
      <description>For the past two years, staff at Wright’s terraced masterpiece in the Pennsylvania woods have found themselves in the middle of a home improvement project on steroids. And they’re doing it all while hewing to strict historic preservation standards and managing the expectations of visitors from around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9fd7c70-81fe-11f0-addc-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House committee subpoenas Epstein estate, requesting ‘birthday book’ allegedly prepared by Maxwell and any ‘client list’</title>
      <description>House Oversight Committee Chairman James Comer (R-Kentucky) demanded documents from Jeffrey Epstein’s estate that might shed light on the federal sex-trafficking investigation into the financier. The subpoena, which demands documents by Sept. 8, asks for any book gifted by Ghislaine Maxwell to Epstein for his 50th birthday and anything that could be construed as a “client list” and Epstein’s “Black Book” of contacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8ac61d0-81f2-11f0-a46c-000a1acecc1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diamond baron Maurice Tempelsman dies at 95. He became a major Democratic donor and drew attention as Jackie Onassis’s companion.</title>
      <description>Urbane and intensely private, Tempelsman was as comfortable in the palaces of African autocrats as he was visiting the White House or working back channels with U.S. diplomats. He rose to became the largest player in the U.S. diamond market and gained additional notice for his strolls in Central Park with former first lady Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis, his partner from the early 1980s until her death in 1994.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32d804b1-81ef-11f0-9dc3-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 20:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s xAI sues Apple and OpenAI, alleging they colluded to favor ChatGPT in the App Store over his chatbot Grok</title>
      <description>The suit takes aim at a deal Apple struck to use OpenAI’s artificial intelligence software on iPhones and other devices after struggling to compete with its own AI features. Musk’s company seeks billions of dollars in damages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e51f9b0-81e9-11f0-a64b-000a1ace3d25</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily bars Kilmar Abrego García’s deportation to Uganda</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Paula Xinis issued the order from the bench Monday, hours after Homeland Security officials detained Abrego during a required check-in at the U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement field office in Baltimore. Xinis said she wants to hear evidence to ensure that the Trump administration will give him an opportunity to contest his deportation to Uganda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbe0ebd0-81e5-11f0-9a35-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 19:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family wonders how to ask childless uncle whether he has a will</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family wonders how to ask childless uncle whether he has a will</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0ffa111-81d5-11f0-b9db-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star wide receiver Terry McLaurin and Commanders agree on three-year contract extension</title>
      <description>McLaurin’s extension will pay him $96 million with the chance to escalate, a person familiar with the deal said. The 29-year-old has not practiced all summer as he sought a new deal in line with the league's top receivers. This puts him as the sixth-highest paid receiver in the NFL by average annual salary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29337690-81ce-11f0-9f51-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:11:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOP-led House committee is investigating allegations that D.C. police faked lower crime rate data, echoing Justice Department probe</title>
      <description>The House Oversight Committee is investigating whether D.C. police manipulated data at the direction of department leadership, according to records reviewed by The Washington Post. The inquiry comes on the heels of a Justice Department probe into similar matters and as D.C. officials continue to cite local crime statistics to protest President Donald Trump’s takeover of city law enforcement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a1ed2e0-81cc-11f0-bf9f-00000a1ace9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive orders cracking down on cashless bail and flag burning</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump seeks to force Washington, D.C., to abandon its no-cash-bail law and pressure states with similar policies. Another order aims to overturn a Supreme Court decision that said the First Amendment protects flag burning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c40a38b0-81c5-11f0-9d4c-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 15:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A big launch for this network in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30d9efc0-81b8-11f0-abc4-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In public letter, FEMA staff warn Trump officials’ actions risk Katrina-level disaster</title>
      <description>About 150 Federal Emergency Management Agency employees sent a letter Monday to members of Congress and other officials, arguing that the agency’s direction and current leaders’ inexperience harm the agency’s mission and could result in a disaster on the level of Hurricane Katrina. The letter, on which more than two dozen FEMA staff signed their full names, is the latest example of federal employees speaking out against the Trump administration’s actions and policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c350b1e0-81b3-11f0-bd6e-0000a1ace117</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilmar Abrego García detained by U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement after arriving at the agency’s Baltimore field office</title>
      <description>The detention comes three days after the undocumented immigrant was freed after a federal judge determined he didn't pose a flight risk or a danger to the community while he awaits trial on human smuggling charges. ICE notified Abrego shortly after his release Friday that the agency could deport him to Uganda within days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45f4ecd1-81ad-11f0-81de-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:16:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard. Russia-Ukraine. Tuition breaks. Postal pauses. Longer summer. AI job threat. 92-year-old sprinter. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8416b31-81a2-11f0-bc73-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard members in D.C. now carrying weapons</title>
      <description>Guard members will carry their service-issued weapons, which may include M4 carbine rifles and M17 pistols, and “detentions may occur leading to arrests,” a spokesman from Joint Task Force-D.C., the military mission that includes Guard members from D.C. and six states that are involved in the deployment, said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8e5d5cb0-8152-11f0-95c9-0000a1aced3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 01:26:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s not just you — summer really is getting longer. See how temperatures have changed in your town.</title>
      <description>The hottest stretch of the year is expanding beyond any calendar definition of summer. These regions are experiencing the biggest change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c62022d0-8135-11f0-9607-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 22:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s really going on in D.C.? White House videos compete with bystanders’.</title>
      <description>In the weeks since President Donald Trump declared a crime emergency in D.C., the internet has been awash with footage taken on city streets. The videos coming from the White House and the public offer split-screen narratives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1eb0a70-811c-11f0-b7c2-000a1acecf40</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 19:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">929a5c00-8103-11f0-8b8a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s what science considers a path to a good life</title>
      <description>Happiness and meaning are important, but scientists are studying what it means to live a life that’s psychologically rich, with novel experiences, perspective-shifting insights and complexity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">365912d0-80f7-11f0-97f0-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 14:32:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e64de8d0-80ef-11f0-9a92-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 13:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plans military deployment in Chicago as Trump eyes crackdown</title>
      <description>Officials have weighed mobilizing at least a few thousand members of the National Guard as soon as September in Chicago, while also discussing deploying active-duty troops. The show of force, if approved, could be a model the administration uses in other cities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d371be0-807f-11f0-acc3-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 8 Gen Z habits are baffling. Our Zoomer staffers explain.</title>
      <description>There are reasons why phone greetings, uppercase letters and bar tabs are going the way of the dodo. Dad’s old point-and-shoot, on the other hand, is making a comeback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe05dfb1-8067-11f0-a0fb-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 21:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My partner ignored a friend’s racist joke. Is our relationship toast?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My partner ignored a friend’s racist joke. Is our relationship toast?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00b26610-803c-11f0-9117-0000a1ace45d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drowning in cases, an immigration lawyer is ‘tired of losing.’ And his phone keeps ringing.</title>
      <description>Christopher Kinnison, a lawyer in Alexandria, Louisiana, faces increasing challenges as ICE detentions rise under President Donald Trump. His clients, often detained in rural Louisiana, face high denial rates as he struggles with a backlog of cases, changing policies and remote court hearings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc12aac0-8031-11f0-abff-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 15:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21e1bcc0-8026-11f0-8418-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:36:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Senate passes Trump-backed election map</title>
      <description>In a quick, party-line 18-11 vote that took Democrats by surprise early Saturday, the Republican-controlled chamber approved the map, which aims to help the GOP hold its narrow U.S. House majority in the midterms by creating five new districts in areas Trump won by double digits in 2024. The plan now heads to Gov. Greg Abbott (R), who is expected to swiftly sign it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03e5a540-7fe7-11f0-96e1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:04:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lyle Menendez, who killed his parents in their Beverly Hills home, is denied parole alongside his brother</title>
      <description>The denials are a setback in the campaign to release the brothers, who are serving life sentences for murdering their parents in 1989. The Menendez family has largely supported the siblings, who maintain that they carried out the slayings  in self-defense after suffering alleged physical and sexual abuse at the hands of their father.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98746c90-7fcf-11f0-96e1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 03:16:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kilmar Abrego García is released in Tennessee, lawyer confirms, despite Trump administration’s insistence he should ‘never go free’</title>
      <description>The Maryland man illegally deported to El Salvador was released Friday as he awaits trial on human smuggling charges. Federal officials obeyed a pair of court orders to release Abrego García and allow him to return to Maryland. Immigration officials may seek to quickly deport him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932c0fa0-7f8d-11f0-a1ef-0000a1ace205</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:24:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ releases full transcript, audio from interview with Jeffrey Epstein associate Ghislaine Maxwell</title>
      <description>Deputy Attorney General Todd Blanche conducted two days of interviews with Maxwell in Florida in July amid growing pressure on the Trump administration to release more information about Epstein, the wealthy sex offender. On Friday, Blanche said he was releasing the interview with Maxwell, who is serving a 20-year sentence for sex trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e38b1fa0-7f8c-11f0-8281-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 19:19:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intel’s CEO has agreed to give the U.S. government $10 billion, Trump says</title>
      <description>The president equated the payment to 10% of the American chipmaker’s value, saying he told CEO Lip-Bu Tan that “it would be good having the United States as your partner” and that “they've agreed to do it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13534730-7f88-11f0-a1af-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:44:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center to host the 2026 World Cup draw in December, Trump announces</title>
      <description>The 2026 World Cup, set to begin in June, will be staged in the United States, Canada and Mexico. Washington will not host matches, but a draw at the Kennedy Center allows the District to join the festivities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cc8f11-7f80-11f0-9aca-0000a1ace061</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration purge of national security agencies widens with firing of DIA chief Lt. Gen. Jeffrey Kruse</title>
      <description>Secretary of Defense Pete Hegseth’s sacking of Kruse, the director of the Defense Intelligence Agency, marks the latest removal of a senior military or intelligence officer in a wider purge of national security agencies’ top ranks, according to two people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae41fe21-7f7f-11f0-af09-00000a1ace0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 17:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
