<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 20:01:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Evict ‘at risk’ sister from family home you inherited?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Evict ‘at risk’ sister from family home you inherited?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59ff0ce0-c700-11f0-ae93-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 17:34:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the ultrarich seized unprecedented power over American politics</title>
      <description>The concentration of wealth among the richest Americans is unlike anything in history — and so is billionaires’ influence in politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">084788e1-c6ed-11f0-8eb6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b571e00-c6e7-11f0-b310-0000a1ace87d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pushing Ukraine to sign peace deal by Thanksgiving or lose support</title>
      <description>The U.S. is now sending signals that everything could be off the table if Kyiv does not quickly sign a proposal that was drawn up by special envoy Steve Witkoff, according to two officials familiar with the talks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d99ede0-c6da-11f0-b9eb-0000a1aceffc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In reversal, Coast Guard classifies swastikas, nooses as hate symbols</title>
      <description>The new order came hours after The Post initially reported the service no longer planned to classify the swastika as a hate symbol but instead as “potentially divisive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d346780-c6d6-11f0-bd69-0000a1ace53b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 12:32:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billionaire donors. Trump’s ‘treason’ claim. Swastika rules. Drilling. Musk chatbot. Flight ‘civility.’ Frida Kahlo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">92f35350-c6d1-11f0-bc0e-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC in turmoil after agency backpedals on debunking vaccines’ link to autism</title>
      <description>Sen. Bill Cassidy (R-Louisiana), who voted to confirm Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. after Kennedy pledged not to remove language stating vaccines do not cause autism from the CDC website, condemned the change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7ddca00-c656-11f0-8e85-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 21:22:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to halt ‘unlawful’ Guard deployment in D.C. while lawsuit plays out in court</title>
      <description>A judge granted an injunction in D.C.’s lawsuit against Trump’s National Guard deployment, but it won’t take effect for 21 days so the government can appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">617c0bb0-c653-11f0-aa26-0000a1ace4f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:56:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Coast Guard will no longer classify swastikas, nooses as hate symbols</title>
      <description>The military service, which falls under the Department of Homeland Security, has drafted a new policy that classifies such items “potentially divisive.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">957a2f10-c63e-11f0-8f71-0000a1acec26</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend just found out he’s the father of his ex’s baby</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend just found out he’s the father of his ex’s baby</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">afb6e9b0-c632-11f0-a843-0000a1acec21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 5 cities help explain why homicide rates are down across the U.S.</title>
      <description>Homicides are down nearly 20 percent this year in 52 of America’s largest cities, according to a Washington Post analysis, a decline that spans both red and blue states.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3eb9a10-c62f-11f0-a5d0-0000a1ace3b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing the Epstein files in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6df3b9d0-c62e-11f0-a317-0000a1ace398</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s the ‘most important fish in the sea.’ And it’s disappearing.</title>
      <description>If the menhaden decline continues, striped bass could be next to vanish.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53a13b0-c628-11f0-abfb-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 15:51:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live now: Emma Grede. Rep. Lisa McClain. Ukraine Amb. Olga Stefanishyna. Misty Copeland. Watch our Global Women’s Summit.</title>
      <description>Live now: Emma Grede. Rep. Lisa McClain. Ukraine Amb. Olga Stefanishyna. Misty Copeland. Watch our Global Women’s Summit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c0f1230-c61d-11f0-b147-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delayed jobs report shows hiring grew in September</title>
      <description>Employers added 119,000 jobs in September, before the government shutdown. Still, the unemployment rate ticked up to 4.4 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47bb73a0-c617-11f0-a6cd-0000a1aced57</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. MAGA fallout. RFK Jr. AI laws. Falling homicide rates. Cold December. Gay sheep. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6784f490-c608-11f0-8464-0000a1ace780</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Summers steps back from teaching as Harvard investigates Epstein ties</title>
      <description>Harvard is reviewing information of people associated with the university — including Summers, its president from 2001 to 2006 — that were featured in the Epstein documents to “evaluate what actions may be warranted,” spokesperson Jason Newton said Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db140050-c5bc-11f0-8976-00000a1ace07</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:58:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs bill directing Justice Department to release Epstein files</title>
      <description>Despite Trump’s signature, the legislation calling for the release of the files includes major loopholes. The department has said little about its plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2213f0d1-c5b5-11f0-a176-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 02:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House drafts order directing Justice Department to sue states that pass AI regulations</title>
      <description>The proposal, which could conflict with legal limits to presidential power, comes after Republicans failed to get a federal block on state AI legislation approved in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae6e56d0-c5b3-11f0-941b-0000a1ace190</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 most anticipated movies of the holiday season</title>
      <description>The final weeks of the year bring Oscar contenders, horror flicks, animated sequels and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">586caf90-c5ac-11f0-8b29-0000a1ace635</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security scraps plan to limit disability benefits after uproar</title>
      <description>The policy would have fundamentally altered who qualifies for the two federal disability programs by eliminating or limiting a person’s age as a factor to consider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18740450-c599-11f0-adc3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump-appointed panel concluded FEMA should be strengthened. Noem wants to take it in a different direction.</title>
      <description>Instead of further shrinking and dismantling the agency, the FEMA Review Council wants to make it more independent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62c063e0-c595-11f0-adc3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in James Comey case questions whether the indictment of the former FBI director was properly approved by a grand jury</title>
      <description>The grand jury rejected an earlier three-count indictment. The judge noted that transcripts show no indication the panel saw the revised two-count version. Prosecutors acknowledged that they’d never presented it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df5712c0-c570-11f0-a8d2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commitment jewelry from his ex broke. He’s fixing it. Hax readers give advice.</title>
      <description>When his bracelet broke, she thought a last trace of his ex was gone. But he’s so set on fixing it that she is starting to crack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5869760-c569-11f0-853c-0000a1ace468</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the deadliest roads in America. See if you live near one.</title>
      <description>The number of pedestrians killed by vehicles in the United States has surged amid neglect and lack of investment by transportation authorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5664650-c55d-11f0-8ed8-0000a1ace11f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Summers leaves OpenAI as Harvard opens inquiry into his Epstein ties</title>
      <description>Documents released by Congress showed the former treasury secretary kept in contact with convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein after he pleaded guilty to solicitation of prostitution in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9e82590-c556-11f0-adbc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World leader White House visits in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa8541f0-c554-11f0-9e6a-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Mohammed bin Salman. Education Department. West Bank. Deadliest roads. Volcano energy. ‘Brain rot.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d479bc0-c53f-11f0-9e42-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Things happen’: Trump’s comments on Khashoggi were weak, crass and of no strategic benefit to America</title>
      <description>Trump's distortions dishonor our colleague's legacy, the Editorial Board writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02116d21-c4d5-11f0-a441-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress to send bill to Trump forcing disclosure of Jeffrey Epstein files</title>
      <description>Hours after the bill passed the House on a 427-1 vote, the Senate agreed to deem the legislation passed as soon as it arrived. Senate Minority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-New York) offered a motion that received unanimous consent and will require no further action by the chamber. Trump said Monday that he would sign the bill if it reaches his desk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46358680-c4d0-11f0-827b-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes overwhelmingly to compel release of Epstein files after months-long impasse, sending bill to Senate</title>
      <description>The vote was the remarkable culmination of a bipartisan crusade by Reps. Thomas Massie (R-Kentucky) and Ro Khanna (D-California) that until Sunday had met fierce resistance from President Donald Trump, who repeatedly insisted that the focus on the Jeffrey Epstein files was a “hoax” promoted by Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e542460-c4b7-11f0-8147-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court blocks GOP-friendly Texas voting map — a ruling that is likely to help Democrats keep 5 seats in 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>In a stinging setback for President Donald Trump and Republicans, a federal court blocked a newly drawn congressional map in Texas that Republicans hoped would have given them an edge in five more House races.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fdd20b0-c4b0-11f0-bd03-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is not an illegal monopoly, judge rules, dealing a major blow to government efforts to rein in tech giants</title>
      <description>The ruling by U.S. District Judge James E. Boasberg agreed with Meta that its purchases of the photo sharing app Instagram and messaging app WhatsApp, which it bought in 2012 and 2014, respectively, did not violate antitrust laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01ee1861-c4ae-11f0-bbbf-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman over killing of Post columnist Jamal Khashoggi, saying ‘things happen’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said he did not hold the Saudi leader responsible for the 2018 murder, despite a U.S. intelligence report assessing the opposite. Trump’s dismissive language was the highest-level confirmation yet that Mohammed will face few consequences for the killing, as the crown prince makes his first visit to Washington since Khashoggi was dismembered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">503473d0-c4a8-11f0-9f56-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Bridge deaths could have been prevented, federal investigators find</title>
      <description>The six workers who died would have had 1 minute, 29 seconds to escape had they been alerted, the National Transportation Safety Board said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d2725e0-c4a5-11f0-b138-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: In their family, it’s holiday tradition for siblings to do squat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: In their family, it’s holiday tradition for siblings to do squat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be87aee1-c4a0-11f0-b017-0000a1ace936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to announce dismantling of much of Education Department</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump signed an executive order in March seeking to close the department, but only Congress has the power to do that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">135a5bc0-c497-11f0-8b81-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How baby boomers got so rich, and why their kids are unlikely to catch up</title>
      <description>The wealthiest generation holds more than $85 trillion in assets thanks to economic conditions Gen X, millennials and others would be hard-pressed to replicate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">670147f1-c48f-11f0-8fe1-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chowing down on fast food staples in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a635f10-c48b-11f0-8b2e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first look at Venezuela’s ‘Freedom Manifesto’ from Nobel Peace Prize winner María Corina Machado</title>
      <description>Nobel Peace Prize winner María Corina Machado pens a precursor to a new Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb582070-c47e-11f0-acc0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Saudi crown prince. Supreme Court. Gaza peace plan. Clinical trial cuts. Boomer wealth. Wolf video. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12f449f0-c476-11f0-a951-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Summers is stepping back from public commitments over Jeffrey Epstein emails, saying he is ‘deeply ashamed’</title>
      <description>“I take full responsibility for my misguided decision to continue communicating with Mr. Epstein,” Summers said in a statement. It was unclear whether the Democratic former treasury secretary would exit a wide array of boards and think tanks or if those organizations would cut ties with him. Summers is also a former president of Harvard University, where he still holds a professorship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05099960-c423-11f0-8395-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This video may be the first recording of a wild wolf using a tool — a trait once thought to be unique to humans</title>
      <description>A wolf in British Columbia was filmed fishing in 2024, pulling in a crab pot from the water and eating the bait. Although the intelligence of wolves is well known, the discovery adds to an expanding list of animals capable of manipulating tools to forage for food.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30b0a420-c417-11f0-9575-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N. Security Council approves Trump’s 20-point peace plan for Gaza</title>
      <description>The U.S.-sponsored resolution turns President Donald Trump’s plan into an international mandate, allowing stalled security and reconstruction measures to move forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4440890-c40c-11f0-90f5-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 23:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he won’t rule out sending troops into Venezuela, despite his claim that U.S. may be open to talks with Maduro</title>
      <description>“I don’t rule out anything, we just have to take care of Venezuela,” President Donald Trump said when asked at a news conference about putting American personnel “on the ground.” His remarks appeared startlingly at odds with his claim Sunday night that the administration “may be having some discussions” with Nicolás Maduro, Venezuela’s strongman president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e81b1090-c3ff-11f0-a51e-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blasts Justice Department over Comey case, citing government misconduct that could lead to dismissal of charges</title>
      <description>U.S. Magistrate Judge William Fitzpatrick ordered prosecutors to swiftly turn over to a judge the full transcripts and audio of the grand jury proceedings that led to former FBI director James B. Comey’s indictment in September on charges that he lied to Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc08620-c3e4-11f0-8596-0000a1ace539</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA leader resigns after short tenure and criticism for being inaccessible during Texas floods</title>
      <description>David Richardson resigned as acting head of the Federal Emergency Management Agency, according to sources familiar with the situation, ending a brief tenure leading an agency the administration had publicly expressed a desire to dismantle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c064ddf1-c3dd-11f0-af63-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grown kid’s rent-free deal with mom makes dad and stepmom ‘crazy’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grown kid’s rent-free deal with mom makes dad and stepmom ‘crazy’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2ce4b60-c3d9-11f0-9992-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump loyalist prosecutor is probing former top Obama administration officials</title>
      <description>Jason Reding Quiñones's appointment to lead an office he left last year after poor performance reviews is a case study in how the administration is operating U.S. attorney’s offices across the country, plucking Trump backers with little support from staffers to serve in high-powered positions, according to people familiar with the Justice Department’s operations. 

In several cases, including Reding Quiñones’s, the appointments have led to a staff exodus and a sharp drop in morale as the appointees embrace the administration’s most controversial investigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ca6ec41-c3d6-11f0-a8fd-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Gretchen Whitmer: If we’re going to do tariffs, let’s do them right</title>
      <description>The White House’s chaotic tariff strategy is making everything more expensive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b84890f0-c3d1-11f0-a51e-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
