<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 22:01:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 50 best airports in America, ranked</title>
      <description>To build our best airports list, The Washington Post analyzed feedback from more than 2,300 readers and collected data on 450-plus U.S. locations to build the definitive ranking. Turns out, bigger isn’t better.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6359900-542b-11f0-92a3-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 14:27:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5da15c90-5423-11f0-8e81-0000a1ace1c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 13:25:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DOGE Service loses control of process for awarding billions in federal funds, in latest sign of its declining influence</title>
      <description>Federal officials were instructed Thursday to stop routing the grant-making process through DOGE, the fate of which has remained uncertain since Elon Musk departed the government.
The move follows fears that months of DOGE-linked delays would lead to the impoundment of federal funds, according to emails obtained by The Post and two people familiar with the situation, both of whom spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe a sensitive situation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">223222c0-539c-11f0-b9bd-00000a1acefc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 21:17:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>S&amp;P 500 squeaks out record high after Trump ends trade talks with Canada</title>
      <description>The U.S. stock market has been a roller coaster this year, rising to record levels in February and then tumbling in April after President Donald Trump announced tariffs on all imported goods. Since then, easing trade tensions with China and other nations, as well a U.S. pullback from the steepest levies, helped push shares higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dab1c01-5392-11f0-9040-0000a1acecbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 20:06:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran nearly succeeded in orchestrating an assassination of former secretary of state Mike Pompeo in Europe in 2022, book reveals</title>
      <description>The forthcoming book also reveals that Donald Trump and his campaign were told by intelligence officials last September that Iran had recruited hit men who remained active on U.S. soil at the time. Security threats to Trump and his aides, including from Iran, dramatically changed their practices and worldview on the campaign trail, according to an account from the book, obtained by The Washington Post. The book, “2024: How Trump Retook the White House and the Democrats Lost America,” was written by current and former Washington Post reporters Josh Dawsey, Tyler Pager and Isaac Arnsdorf.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c782dd80-538a-11f0-ad3f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 19:13:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump calls off trade talks with Canada and threatens tariffs on Canadian goods, saying he objects to new digital services tax</title>
      <description>The Canadian tax on big tech companies is set to take effect Monday. Trump said he would announce tariff rates for goods from Canada within seven days.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e91a9520-5383-11f0-8816-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:24:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>University of Virginia President James E. Ryan tells board he’ll resign amid Justice Department pressure against DEI initiatives</title>
      <description>A person familiar with the situation said Justice Department officials had previously indicated to Ryan that they’d like him to step down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b9db4310-537c-11f0-a614-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 17:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My teen feels pressured by her boyfriend’s pushy mom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My teen feels pressured by her boyfriend’s pushy mom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0dc4520-5373-11f0-94f9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:27:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials plan to resettle 1,000 Afrikaners by end of September, document shows</title>
      <description>The plan to ramp up the arrival of White South Africans comes as officials simultaneously move to block refugees from other countries. A federal judge had ordered the Trump administration to admit certain refugees, but a court record shows the administration is now moving to halt their entry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">124208a1-5372-11f0-ba9d-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds law requiring age checks for porn sites</title>
      <description>More than 20 states require age verification to protect young people from accessing lewd online content. The justices rejected arguments from the porn industry that the Texas law violates the First Amendment rights of adults by requiring them to share identifying information that could be sold, misused or hacked.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70e65f30-536a-11f0-b9e3-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 15:21:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court sides with religious parents seeking to opt out of lessons with LGBTQ storybooks</title>
      <description>The 6-3 decision backed a group of parents seeking to withdraw their children from public school lessons featuring gay and transgender characters, a case that mixed parental rights and religious freedom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2e9b6c40-5367-11f0-b783-0000a1acec64</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:58:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds Affordable Care Act’s preventive-care mandate</title>
      <description>The justices ruled against a Christian-owned business and individuals who objected to being forced to offer medications intended to prevent the spread of HIV among at-risk populations. The challengers argued that the panel that determined what care must be covered was improperly appointed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05621910-5366-11f0-94f9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court limits nationwide orders blocking Trump’s birthright citizenship ban</title>
      <description>The 6-3 ruling will impact decisions by lower-court judges to block President Donald Trump’s ban on birthright citizenship and probably other Trump administration initiatives. The president asked the justices to scale back those injunctions, which halted his policies nationwide while legal challenges to them were pending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c47bfe2-5361-11f0-803e-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 14:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court is ruling on major remaining cases, including nationwide injunctions and birthright citizenship. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The justices have left some of the most important and contentious cases until the end. They are slated to release six opinions, including decisions that will deal with injunctions regarding President Donald Trump’s ban on birthright citizenship, whether parents can opt their children out of school lessons involving LGBTQ books, and a Texas law that requires age verification to view online porn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4908740-535d-11f0-8236-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE enters ATF with mandate to slash gun regulations as Trump administration pushes to drastically reduce number of inspectors</title>
      <description>The U.S. DOGE Service is working with the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives general counsel to cut more than 50 regulations. Gun-control advocates fear the changes will more easily allow potentially dangerous people to obtain weapons with little recourse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed0d28b0-535a-11f0-9808-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court. DOGE and guns. Young Democrats. Iran strikes. Diddy trial. Another heat wave. Fireball video. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4fa7d00-5345-11f0-b383-0000a1acefd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 10:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Moyers dies at 91. The acclaimed journalist won renown for bringing discussion of ideas — both timely and timeless — to TV.</title>
      <description>He was White House press secretary under Lyndon B. Johnson and Newsday publisher before beginning a television career that would bring him more than 30 Emmy Awards, including one for lifetime achievement. He was mainly associated with PBS, and although he frequently explored societal ills, he was happier speaking with poets and philosophers than he was with pollsters or politicians.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b008ef0-52c8-11f0-be1d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 20:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. appointees vote to effectively remove a flu shot preservative, advancing a priority of anti-vaccine activists</title>
      <description>The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — overhauled by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. — voted Thursday to stop recommending flu shots containing the preservative thimerosal, which research has shown is safe. Most flu shots are thimerosal-free, but public health experts said the move could make shots more expensive and harder to receive. Many also expressed concern that anti-vaccine rhetoric is becoming official government guidance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04347e80-52b6-11f0-b6b9-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:50:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother’s two broken engagements have family balking at his third</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother’s two broken engagements have family balking at his third</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8aa5420-52a6-11f0-8cd6-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our analysis of the NBA draft’s winners and losers: Mavericks made the easy choice with Cooper Flagg, but Pelicans took risks</title>
      <description>Dallas selected the Duke star with the No. 1 pick in the draft Wednesday night, before other teams followed more questionable paths. NBA writer Ben Golliver analyzes all of the biggest decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df5e6e21-52a3-11f0-9215-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 15:40:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court paves way for states to defund Planned Parenthood, ruling Medicaid patients cannot sue for non-abortion care</title>
      <description>The case addressed whether a provision of the federal Medicaid Act allows individuals to sue for access to their provider of choice. It was brought by a woman who wants South Carolina to resume Medicaid funding to Planned Parenthood for non-abortion health care.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08bb76f0-529a-11f0-bcaf-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In closing arguments of Sean Combs trial, prosecutors say he ‘used power, violence and fear to get what he wanted.’ Follow live.</title>
      <description>The jury in Sean “Diddy” Combs’s sex-trafficking case has heard more than six weeks of testimony from 34 witnesses. Now, the prosecution and defense will make their final pitches to the jurors deciding Combs’s fate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16be2789-5299-11f0-be1d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 14:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This ecosystem is in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce01b7c0-5291-11f0-afad-0000a1ace20b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 13:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigration is driving population growth in a graying America, census data shows. See how your county’s population has changed.</title>
      <description>Children still outnumber older adults, but the gap is narrowing as baby boomers age, the data found. A historic rise in immigration, particularly among Hispanics and Asians, has counteracted some of the decline in births.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dbd0ced0-5288-11f0-ac4a-0000a1aced9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligence leak. Unprecedented lawsuit. Kids’ vaccines. Zohran Mamdani. Aging population. Heat dome. Bear escape. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aca45ac0-527c-11f0-ac99-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dallas Mavericks select Duke forward Cooper Flagg with No. 1 pick in NBA draft</title>
      <description>Flagg, an 18-year-old from Maine, is widely considered the best American prospect to enter the league in more than a decade. He immediately becomes the face of a Mavericks franchise that traded superstar Luka Doncic to the Los Angeles Lakers in February.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38f2d750-5222-11f0-b407-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to limit intelligence sharing with Congress after leaks undermined president’s claims about Iran strikes</title>
      <description>Details of an early intelligence assessment leaked to the press this week undermined President Donald Trump’s claim that U.S. strikes “obliterated” Iranian nuclear facilities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29225de0-521e-11f0-a07c-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 23:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dept. of Housing and Urban Development to move from D.C., displacing National Science Foundation in nearby Alexandria, Virginia</title>
      <description>It will be the first major federal agency to relocate its headquarters outside of Washington, part of a larger plan to reorganize the federal government's real estate footprint. About 2,700 HUD workers would make the move, pushing out about 1,800 employees at the NSF, which has faced massive spending cuts under the Trump administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f517123-5214-11f0-9aa1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 22:31:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump DOJ sues 15 federal judges in Maryland over deportation order. Legal experts call it an unprecedented attack on judiciary.</title>
      <description>Government lawyers say they’re aiming to preserve President Donald Trump’s constitutional authority over immigration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d643d0f0-5208-11f0-aa23-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 21:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can’t do a road trip this summer? Try our tour of East Coast recipes, from Maine lobster rolls to Florida key lime pie.</title>
      <description>Can’t do a road trip this summer? Try our tour of East Coast recipes, from Maine lobster rolls to Florida key lime pie.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f4322b0-51fa-11f0-a8bd-000a1ace282c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 19:27:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr.’s new vaccine panel to review childhood immunization schedule, a move that could change how and when kids receive shots</title>
      <description>The newly formed vaccine advisory committee handpicked by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. announced it would examine the cumulative effect of the childhood vaccine schedule and reevaluate hepatitis B immunization recommendations. Kennedy, who founded an anti-vaccine group, has long called for an investigation into the number of shots children receive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f37f7280-51e2-11f0-93fd-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:39:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Look out: The number of nuclear countries could double</title>
      <description>What’s making some countries daydream about nukes again?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b6c7e31-51df-11f0-85ec-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:14:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Old friend’s new wife spills awkward secret at dinner</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Old friend’s new wife spills awkward secret at dinner</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e9f07d0-51dd-11f0-9aa1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much would you save or lose with Trump’s ‘big’ tax bill? Try our calculator to find out.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and Republicans in Congress are on the cusp of passing legislation to extend tax cuts and reduce spending on safety net programs. See how the bill would affect your finances — and those of other Americans — using our tool.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">659da3d0-51d1-11f0-8ef1-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 14:33:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration prepares to test law by delaying or withholding spending, officials say, which could shift power from Congress</title>
      <description>The White House denies any funds have been “impounded.” But congressionally mandated projects have been put on hold or frozen across the government, potentially setting up a clash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d452ca71-51c8-11f0-aa73-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special delivery in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f8c48d1-51c8-11f0-95c8-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 13:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran poll. NYC primary results. Trump’s tax bill. ‘Alligator Alcatraz.’ Heat wave. Microplastics. Bezos’s wedding. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80e62e50-51b3-11f0-9610-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cuomo concedes to Mamdani in New York City’s Democratic mayoral primary</title>
      <description>“Tonight was not our night,” the former governor told supporters. He said of Mamdani: “Tonight is his night. He deserved it. He won.” Mamdani, a democratic socialist, is now poised for a major upset in the Democratic race after jumping out to a lead after the first round of ballots were tallied Tuesday. Final results in the ranked-choice voting primary are expected to come next week. The Democratic nominee is expected to begin as a favorite in the general election in a heavily blue city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e51394c0-5173-11f0-b9cb-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 03:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani leads Andrew M. Cuomo on 1st round of counting in New York Democratic mayoral primary</title>
      <description>Mamdani, who would be New York’s first Muslim mayor, didn’t break the 50 percent mark in the first round of counting, the Associated Press reported. But it was still a good performance for the 33-year-old democratic socialist state assemblyman, a relative newcomer who was facing off with a former governor with copious campaign cash and prominent endorsements. Under the city’s ranked choice system, officials will now drop the candidate who finished last and continue counting votes until a candidate bests 50 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13fd4760-5168-11f0-9610-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 01:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We texted 1,000 Americans about Trump’s Iran strikes. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post flash poll finds the airstrikes remain unpopular, but Republican support surged after President Donald Trump ordered the strikes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39076840-5147-11f0-8f0d-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 22:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. bombs set back Iran's nuclear program by months, but did not destroy it, say people familiar with secret Pentagon assessment</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump and top aides have claimed that U.S. airstrikes obliterated Iran's nuclear program, but people familiar with an initial report by the Defense Intelligence Agency say that core components of Tehran's enrichment program remain intact.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47778f61-5140-11f0-a92e-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 21:14:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend’s sudden death brings acute sense of last moments</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend’s sudden death brings acute sense of last moments</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">898fe4f0-5114-11f0-ac1b-0000a1ace99b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 16:01:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When heat rises, here are 3 ways to protect your mind and body</title>
      <description>Persistent heat can cause chronic health problems. Here's how to avoid heatstroke, manage summer depression and, when temperatures are not dangerous, enjoy nature's healing benefits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">343c8010-5102-11f0-a208-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new label law in todayʼs On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">872c10e0-50ff-11f0-a208-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump accuses Israel and Iran of violating ceasefire hours after its start</title>
      <description>As Israel and Iran traded accusations, President Donald Trump said the two countries need to “calm down. Ridiculous.” Trump had announced the ceasefire deal on Monday as an end to what he said should be called the “12-day war.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db7e3560-50f0-11f0-bb5a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shaky ceasefire. Supreme Court. New York primary. Abortion rights. Food labels. Humidity. Space images. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5642e7c1-50ea-11f0-8a8f-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel agrees to Trump’s proposed ceasefire with Iran</title>
      <description>Israel said it achieved its military goals in Iran and thanked President Donald Trump and the U.S. “for their participation in removing the Iranian nuclear threat.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bb47290-50c7-11f0-af4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 06:47:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claims Iran and Israel have agreed to a ceasefire and an imminent end to their war</title>
      <description>In his announcement on social media, President Donald Trump congratulated both countries, saying the conflict “could have gone on for years, and destroyed the entire Middle East.” There was no immediate corroborating announcement from either the Israeli or Iranian governments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f96c2f40-5083-11f0-a4e9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu decided on Iran war last year, then sought to recruit Trump</title>
      <description>The Israeli prime minister issued a general order in the fall to prepare for a strike, current and former officials say. Israel also tried to sway the U.S. with intelligence about Iran’s nuclear plans, but American analysts did not conclude Iranian leaders had decided to build a bomb.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e214530-507e-11f0-bb98-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 22:06:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court for now allows Trump to deport migrants to ‘third countries’</title>
      <description>The six conservative justices cleared the way for the Trump administration to deport citizens of other countries to a third nation, temporarily blocking a decision by a lower court judge who said migrants must have a “meaningful opportunity” to contest their removal. The case is one of several testing the Trump administration’s aggressive efforts to ramp up deportations, in this case to conflict-ridden South Sudan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91386d50-5077-11f0-96b9-0000a1acecd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 21:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
