<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:29:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Is a giant data center planned for your area? Check our map.</title>
      <description>New data center projects are starting to transform landscapes and communities across the United States, sparking debates about what our energy systems and environment can sustain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94000701-da1a-11f0-bf64-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 01:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon plan calls for major power shifts at highest ranks of military, slashing number of generals who report to Hegseth</title>
      <description>The effort, still subject to approval by President Donald Trump and Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth, would include reducing in prominence three major headquarters — European Command, Central Command, and Africa Command — and putting them under a new International Command.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b38c8cb0-da10-11f0-bf64-00000a1ace70</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 23:49:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities release new images of a person of interest in Brown University shooting along with $50,000 reward. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The images, captured about two hours before the shooting, show a person wearing dark clothes and a mask over the lower half of their face.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a6f42f0-da09-11f0-a9a2-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders quarterback Jayden Daniels will be out for the rest of the season</title>
      <description>The second-year star had missed Sunday’s win over the New York Giants after aggravating a left elbow injury a week earlier. When he was reevaluated Monday, team doctors still did not clear him for contact. The team then decided it would be best for Daniels to remain sidelined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7945d871-d9f9-11f0-9f42-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 21:03:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dad thinks cancer survivor dyed hair purple for attention</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3086a30-d9d7-11f0-b2bd-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:01:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Director Rob Reiner’s 32-year-old son arrested after the deaths of his parents, records show</title>
      <description>Nick Reiner was booked into custody Monday morning on unspecified charges. Rob Reiner, whose career spanned decades in Hollywood, and photographer Michele Singer Reiner were found dead at their residence Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf002b0-d9cf-11f0-a527-0000a1acebc9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 16:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A growing chorus of Trump’s most faithful voters warns that his coalition is checking out. Will he listen?</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s advisers say he is preparing to hold near-weekly rallies to spend more time with the base, but he has faced criticism from within MAGA in the meantime over cost-of-living issues, aligning himself too closely with billionaires, his handling of the Jeffrey Epstein case and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3838ed0-d9ca-11f0-83c0-0000a1aceb58</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make sure you fixate on today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad92fea1-d9c2-11f0-aa1c-0000a1acec50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia shooting. Brown University shooting. Rob Reiner dies. MAGA discontent. Trump library. Data centers. NFL. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8975e562-d9ad-11f0-a778-000a1ace389d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood director Rob Reiner and his wife found dead</title>
      <description>Reiner, the director behind beloved films like “When Harry Met Sally…” and “The Princess Bride,” and his wife, photographer Michele Singer Reiner, were found Sunday afternoon, according to officials.
The deaths were confirmed in statements by Los Angeles Mayor Karen Bass and California Governor Gavin Newsom.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde0e551-d979-11f0-853b-0000a1ace07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 05:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authorities release person of interest detained after Brown University shooting</title>
      <description>Rhode Island Attorney General Peter Neronha said late Sunday there was “some degree of evidence” that pointed to a 24-year-old Wisconsin man that authorities detained Sunday morning, adding that the "evidence now points in a different direction."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">757f43b0-d96e-11f0-8fe8-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 04:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong court convicts pro-democracy newspaper founder Jimmy Lai</title>
      <description>The verdict exemplifies the reach of Hong Kong’s national security law and is being seen as further proof that Beijing has swept away any last remaining press freedoms and judicial independence in the once-freewheeling city.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">218334a0-d960-11f0-aeae-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 02:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a top food safety expert won’t order for dinner</title>
      <description>Bill Marler has litigated foodborne illnesses cases for decades. But even experts like him struggle to handle the risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c230d580-d940-11f0-9153-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 23:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Person of interest in Brown U. shooting is 24-year-old from Wisconsin, officials say</title>
      <description>The person of interest authorities took into custody in connection with the shooting at Brown University is Benjamin Erickson, a 24-year-old originally from Wisconsin, two people briefed on the investigation told The Washington Post on the condition of anonymity. Erickson has not been named as a suspect or charged in connection with the Saturday attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbee51d0-d931-11f0-a51b-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 killed in Bondi Beach shooting carried out by father and son, Australian officials say</title>
      <description>The death toll of Sunday’s shooting at a Hanukkah celebration at Australia’s Bondi Beach rose to 15, with at least 40 injured, Australian officials said. Authorities identified one of the gunmen as a 50-year-old man, who was also killed, and the suspected second shooter as his 24-year-old son, who was hospitalized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca723ce0-d92f-11f0-b11c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 20:59:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bad3fd30-d90e-11f0-87d9-0000a1ace3f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:02:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you living a good life? Take this quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>Now is a good time to reflect on the life you’re leading — and what you want out of it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">671fd620-d90c-11f0-bd39-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e443bf0-d8fa-11f0-ad23-0000a1acec34</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:38:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s one of the driest countries in the world. The floods keep getting worse.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post investigation found that in one of the planet’s most arid regions, extreme rain and floods have become frequent and deadly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0f37a50-d8f5-11f0-988e-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:04:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police take person of interest into custody after Brown University shooting, Providence mayor says</title>
      <description>Authorities said earlier that a gunman opened fire inside a campus engineering building on Saturday, killing two students and injuring nine others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4d9993b0-d8eb-11f0-a91d-0000a1aceb6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:49:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police declare Bondi Beach shooting a terrorist incident targeting the Jewish community</title>
      <description>The attack in Australia left 11 people dead and 28 others injured after two men opened fire Sunday evening during an event near the beach marking the first day of Hanukkah, authorities said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63c1c160-d8e8-11f0-843b-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 12:28:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine killed in shooting at Australia’s Bondi Beach</title>
      <description>At least 12 others were injured in a shooting at Sydney’s popular Bondi Beach. One gunman was also killed, and another suspect is in custody, police said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34533f71-d8d5-11f0-ac52-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 10:11:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fernando Mendoza wins Heisman Trophy, the latest step in Indiana’s stunning rise to national prominence</title>
      <description>The quarterback won the award Saturday night in New York over Vanderbilt quarterback Diego Pavia, Ohio State quarterback Julian Sayin and Notre Dame running back Jeremiyah Love. Mendoza’s Hoosiers, who had never had a Heisman winner, are 13-0 heading into the College Football Playoff.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dff0ebc0-d88a-11f0-8a6e-0000a1ace1f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 01:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 2 dead, 8 injured in shooting at Brown University, authorities say</title>
      <description>Providence Mayor Brett Smiley (D) said the investigation is still ongoing and that the accounts of casualties may change. The injured victims are in critical condition, but stable, at a local hospital, Smiley said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60990ff0-d881-11f0-bcc0-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect at large after multiple people shot around Brown University in Providence, Rhode Island, police say</title>
      <description>Students remain under lockdown, and campus and city police are responding to the incident.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f801c20-d877-11f0-9fe4-0000a1acedf6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 22:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happened when Dr. Oz took charge of a wonky health agency</title>
      <description>The former TV doctor, now running the Centers for Medicare &amp; Medicaid Services, has garnered positive reviews — even from some Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d62fb540-d866-11f0-a456-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 21:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 U.S. soldiers, civilian interpreter killed during attack in central Syria</title>
      <description>A joint U.S.-Syrian security patrol was attacked in the city of Palmyra, the Pentagon and Syria’s state news agency reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb77d3a0-d84b-11f0-a694-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:47:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This former conservative journalist, now trans comedian, can take a joke</title>
      <description>Jamie Mack came out as transgender at 49, after years of struggling with their identity. Could comedy help them work through their new life?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">426bcbc0-d841-11f0-ae58-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a96b59a0-d830-11f0-ab26-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VA plans to abruptly eliminate tens of thousands of health care jobs</title>
      <description>Strains on the Veterans Affairs system could grow with the elimination of as many as 35,000 mostly unfilled health care positions, including doctors, nurses and support staff. The cuts come after a massive reorganization effort already resulted in the loss of almost 30,000 employees this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1f18410-d81e-11f0-9145-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 12:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOJ report on D.C. police says chief created ‘culture of fear’ that may have tainted crime statistics</title>
      <description>A draft report on a crime statistics investigation by U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro’s office takes aim at Pamela A. Smith, who on Monday announced her resignation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f81b6810-d795-11f0-9915-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 20:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fired Michigan coach Sherrone Moore faces three charges, including felony</title>
      <description>He was charged with third-degree home invasion and misdemeanor stalking and illegal entry.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f5ae850-d789-11f0-ac31-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:35:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department sues Georgia county as Trump pushes debunked 2020 election fraud claims</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has increasingly pressured his administration to find widespread voter fraud in the 2020 election, despite those claims having been debunked and dismissed in dozens of cases by the courts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0be8fa60-d787-11f0-9b63-0000a1ace537</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 18:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified my mom is going to kidnap my son</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m terrified my mom is going to kidnap my son</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eff50a0-d784-11f0-9f52-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:59:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Trust sues to stop Trump’s ballroom construction</title>
      <description>The organization, which is charged by Congress with historic preservation, has retained President Barack Obama’s former lawyer as it seeks to pause the project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4fe82472-d773-11f0-9302-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret meetings between FBI and Ukraine negotiator spark concern</title>
      <description>FBI Director Kash Patel and his deputy, Dan Bongino, met with Kyiv’s top peace negotiator, Rustem Umerov, amid a U.S. pressure campaign to end the war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e4b43320-d76c-11f0-93bb-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 15:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b520bbb0-d767-11f0-af95-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 14:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge bars ICE from rearresting Kilmar Abrego García at check-in</title>
      <description>Abrego left the ICE building to cheers from supporters shortly after a mandatory check-in at the agency’s facility in Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68bbcb70-d762-11f0-a43e-0000a1ace09b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 13:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kristi Noem. AI rules. Venezuela campaign. Sudan kidnappings. Oral exams. Record cold. Tiny robots. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">08065c10-d752-11f0-9482-0000a1ace3bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 11:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs order directing government to sue states that attempt to regulate AI — despite growing bipartisan opposition</title>
      <description>The executive order comes as an increasing number of Republicans are speaking out against the president’s support of the tech industry’s ambitions for artificial intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b1fc060-d6f8-11f0-bc9b-00000a1ace57</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 01:16:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is expected to dramatically loosen federal restrictions on marijuana, according to six people familiar with the discussions</title>
      <description>An executive order would direct agencies to classify marijuana as a Schedule III drug, similar to some common prescription painkillers. Rescheduling marijuana would not legalize or decriminalize cannabis, but it would ease barriers to research and boost the bottom lines of legal businesses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0abd7d80-d6e9-11f0-82ff-0000a1ace3c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 23:28:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana redistricting effort fails as GOP lawmakers deliver rare rebuke of Trump</title>
      <description>Some GOP state senators, who hold the majority, sided with Democrats to kill a plan to alter Indiana’s voting map, delivering President Donald Trump the biggest blow yet in his nationwide effort to create safer Republican congressional districts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc4fd20-d6da-11f0-86f6-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 21:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grand jury again declines to indict New York Attorney General Letitia James, a prominent Trump foe, in mortgage fraud case</title>
      <description>The decision marked another loss for the Trump administration as its officials attempt to charge James in a case that career prosecutors have long viewed as weak.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65869ae1-d6cf-11f0-9f9d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 20:24:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate blocks Democrats’ bill to extend ACA subsidies, all but ensuring they will expire at the end of the year</title>
      <description>The vote was the culmination of Democrats’ months-long push to extend the subsidies and prevent premiums from rising for millions of Americans — a campaign that helped trigger the longest federal government shutdown in history. Republicans promised to hold the vote as part of a deal to end the shutdown.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5352820-d6be-11f0-ba02-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 18:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Siblings at odds over funeral arrangements for abusive mother</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Siblings at odds over funeral arrangements for abusive mother</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09ac6b30-d6b3-11f0-9c5d-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I was there when ‘Napalm Girl’ was photographed. This is what I saw.</title>
      <description>“The Stringer” does nothing to shake my strong belief that Nick Ut captured the famous image.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b44f12e0-d6ae-11f0-a1db-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 16:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders ‘immediate release’ of Kilmar Abrego García from ICE custody</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Paula Xinis said she ordered his release in part to ensure that he had a fair immigration process after the Justice Department and an Immigration and Customs Enforcement witness last month said immigration officers had no other option but to deport him to the African nation of Liberia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd716a90-d6a7-11f0-9d7c-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:41:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Homeland Security Secretary Kristi Noem is expected to face tough questions on immigration at a House panel hearing</title>
      <description>Noem’s appearance before the House Homeland Security Committee today is billed as a discussion about global threats the United States faces, but much of the focus is expected to be on her role in the Trump administration’s controversial immigration policies. Follow our live coverage and reporter insights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c7b3230-d6a4-11f0-8f2b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:17:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A retail giant stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f914a7f0-d69f-11f0-aa58-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hundreds quarantined as South Carolina outbreak accelerates in the wake of Thanksgiving travel and a lack of vaccinations</title>
      <description>Authorities traced a sizable outbreak to a church in the state’s northwest. Of the 111 measles cases recorded in that area, 105 involved people who were unvaccinated while three involved those who were partially vaccinated, state epidemiologist Linda Bell said at a news briefing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ed82b00-d69d-11f0-a65f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
