<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 16:01:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s adtech unit is an illegal monopoly, court rules. The tech giant may be forced to sell the profitable division.</title>
      <description>The case, brought by the Justice Department in a federal court in Virginia, revolved around the major role that Google plays in brokering the sale of online advertisements to news outlets and other website operators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23ab6330-1b9f-11f0-ba18-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 15:17:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world’s heaviest known invertebrate in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1750bb20-1b91-11f0-8b37-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 13:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health cuts. El Salvador. Trump vs. Harvard. Puerto Rico outages. Lying chatbots. Storm waste. Sign of alien life. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b9f56c0-1b7b-11f0-9aa0-0000a1ace0fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE, DOGE seek sensitive Medicare data as Trump administration's immigration crackdown intensifies</title>
      <description>The targeted database, which is managed by the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services and includes health and personal information, contains home addresses sought by Immigration and Customs Enforcement officials, according to a person familiar with the matter and documents reviewed by The Post. Current and former health officials said they were deeply concerned by what appears to be an unprecedented use of the Medicare database as part of immigration enforcement efforts, and they were uncertain if the process was legal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">364ffac1-1b20-11f0-bd00-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 00:09:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration asks IRS to revoke Harvard’s tax-exempt status</title>
      <description>The directive to the Internal Revenue Service escalates President Donald Trump’s feud with Harvard University, other Ivy League institutions and nonprofit groups his administration views as "woke."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c96c051-1b0b-11f0-b5a1-0000a1ace075</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 21:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House seeks to cut $40 billion in funding for the Department of Health and Human Services, internal document shows</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's proposed reductions would be about one-third of the agency's discretionary budget. Public health experts warned that the move would be catastrophic.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81f8991-1b04-11f0-b563-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 20:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials say destroying endangered species’ habitats isn’t ‘harm’</title>
      <description>A proposed rule would narrow the definition of harm under the Endangered Species Act and could open the door to more mining, construction and other activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5999510-1af6-11f0-b52f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 19:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariffs are ‘highly likely’ to raise inflation in short term, with risks of longer-term damage, Fed chief Powell warns</title>
      <description>Federal Reserve Chair Jerome H. Powell on Wednesday cautioned in remarks before the Economic Club of Chicago that President Donald Trump's tariffs could have more persistent effects on inflation in his sharpest warning yet about the consequences of a trade war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c21ef930-1ae8-11f0-b52f-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 17:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge to launch contempt proceedings on whether Trump officials defied order not to remove migrants under Alien Enemies Act</title>
      <description>Chief U.S. District Judge James E. Boasberg’s order is the latest development in a standoff between the Trump administration and the federal judiciary, which has blocked or slowed many of the White House’s far-reaching actions. Boasberg had pressed the Justice Department for weeks on why the administration sent more than 130 Venezuelan deportees to a Salvadoran mega-prison without due process, hours after he ordered the administration not to do so.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">842d5270-1ade-11f0-87f6-0000a1ace4b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 16:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: His mom is nice to their faces, then lets parenting critiques rip</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: His mom is nice to their faces, then lets parenting critiques rip</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01487b21-1adc-11f0-b728-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 16:01:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s D.C. U.S. attorney pick appeared on Russian state media more than 150 times</title>
      <description>Ed Martin did not disclose RT and Sputnik appearances from 2016 to 2024 to the Senate. The State Department has said the networks act like arms of Russian intelligence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27b38560-1ad8-11f0-9d50-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 15:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why do restaurants ask if we’ve dined there before?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why do restaurants ask if we’ve dined there before?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57f2f870-1ad6-11f0-a4df-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 15:20:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘God's architect’ in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0cb3f620-1ac7-11f0-97a0-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 13:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department says it will sue Maine Education Department over its refusal to comply with a trans athlete ban</title>
      <description>The Justice Department announced Wednesday it will sue Maine’s Department of Education over its refusal to comply with demands to ban transgender athletes from participating in women’s sports, an escalation of a months-long standoff over the issue between the Trump administration and the state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f17a62c0-1ac3-11f0-9779-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 13:08:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrongly deported man. Weaker dollar. Joe Biden. Abortion. Climate tipping point. Homemade levee. Colossal squid. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1feda30-1ab1-11f0-b96d-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two U.S. troops assigned to Trump’s southern border mission killed, another seriously injured, after vehicle rollover in New Mexico</title>
      <description>Tuesday’s incident marked the first known military fatalities since President Donald Trump ordered the domestic deployment of thousands of active-duty service members as part of his aggressive bid to crack down on illegal migration and secure the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">209f41e0-1a71-11f0-b728-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 03:16:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world’s fastest electric ferry speeds commutes and cuts pollution. See it fly over the water.</title>
      <description>Stockholm’s battery-powered boats rise above the waves on hydrofoils, making them faster and better for the climate than traditional diesel ferries. The shipbuilder, Candela, says it’s planning to launch more around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">641f2bd0-1a47-11f0-8331-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 22:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders the Trump administration to produce details of attempts to return wrongly deported man from El Salvador</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has argued that it has no power under the agreement to facilitate the return of Kilmar Abrego García, who was mistakenly deported to a notorious Salvadoran prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0aeab0a1-1a3f-11f0-8331-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 21:17:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autism rate rose slightly, according to a new CDC report that contradicts RFK Jr. on the cause of the increase</title>
      <description>In a sample of communities, the biennial autism report found that 1 in 31 8-year-olds had the condition. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention attributed the increase to better screening. Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has linked the rising prevalence of autism to vaccines, despite voluminous scientific research that has debunked that claim.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c2d9350-1a24-11f0-90a4-0000a1aceff5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 18:05:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Do an affair, separate lives and eight sexless years mean divorce?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Do an affair, separate lives and eight sexless years mean divorce?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fab0ce31-1a12-11f0-be15-0000a1ace953</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 16:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE is collecting federal data to remove immigrants from housing and jobs</title>
      <description>The Trump administration is pushing agencies to turn over information on where people work, study and live. Such data is normally protected from dissemination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95971a50-1a02-11f0-87a5-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 14:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘baby Catholic’ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef2a9151-19fd-11f0-9769-0000a1ace95b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 13:31:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador. Harvard funding freeze. Detained student. Pakistani militants. Storms. Brisk movements. Katy Perry. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0903a30-19e8-11f0-b1b0-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut’s Paige Bueckers is selected by the Dallas Wings with the top pick in the WNBA draft</title>
      <description>The three-time all-American guard was drafted by the Wings eight days after winning the national championship with the Huskies in her final collegiate game. She joins a franchise seeking a reboot after it finished 9-31 and missed the playoffs last season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eedd2c0-198a-11f0-96fc-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s unpredictable tariffs war is sparking uncertainty for North Carolina farmers</title>
      <description>Midway through the spring planting season, farmers worry that the tariffs have jeopardized their access to foreign markets. Politicians and political observers have begun to question whether the fallout could upset the GOP’s grip on federal elected offices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca1f1cb0-1975-11f0-a7e7-0000a1ace954</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 21:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t look at your 401(k), experts say. Monica Hesse looked anyway.</title>
      <description>The myth of the 401(k) is that we are all in charge of our own destinies. What does that matter now?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b80b3a0-1970-11f0-96ab-0000a1ace35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 20:39:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard rejects Trump administration demands for oversight, putting nearly $9 billion of the school’s federal funding at risk</title>
      <description>Harvard University officials on Monday rejected the Trump administration’s demands for changes at the school, saying the government’s directives amount to overreach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc10550-1956-11f0-ae10-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 17:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department’s budget would be slashed by nearly half under Trump plan, internal memo says</title>
      <description>The document, reviewed by The Washington Post, targets spending on humanitarian assistance, global health and international organizations such as the United Nations and NATO. The blueprint represents a decline of $27 billion from funding levels approved by Congress for 2025, though it is unclear whether lawmakers would approve such steep cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58a52a30-1951-11f0-b851-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:56:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>El Salvador’s president says he won’t return wrongly deported Maryland man to U.S.: ‘Of course I’m not going to do it’</title>
      <description>Salvadoran President Nayib Bukele said Monday during a meeting with President Donald Trump that he did not plan to return Kilmar Abrego García to the United States. Abrego García is at the center of an ongoing court battle after the U.S. government wrongly deported him to El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0f64b80-194b-11f0-8bf2-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family annoyed that golden goose is conscious of credit card debt</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family annoyed that golden goose is conscious of credit card debt</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9909fe0-1949-11f0-8674-00000a1ace04</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 16:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Which home energy upgrades will save you money? We did the math.</title>
      <description>Going green at home can reduce emissions — but may also raise your utility bills, even with tax credits. The Washington Post asked experts to analyze a real-life scenario for a fairly typical American home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41ce6470-193d-11f0-9273-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new award in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77c22a61-1935-11f0-9060-0000a1ace86c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 13:36:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with attempted murder and terrorism in fire at Pennsylvania governor’s home. He told police of his hatred for Shapiro.</title>
      <description>According to a police affidavit, Cody Balmer told police that he set the fire and that he would have attacked the Gov. Josh Shapiro with a hammer if he’d found him on the property.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcbcc741-1928-11f0-ad12-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 12:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff confusion. Arson attack. Wrongly deported man. Detained student. Home prices. Car pollution. Masters drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a13d11e1-191f-11f0-be09-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 11:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mario Vargas Llosa dies at 89. The Nobel Prize-winning author from Peru probed authoritarian rule in Latin America in his novels.</title>
      <description>He helped lead the Latin American “boom” of literary fiction in the 1960s, which produced some of the era’s most-acclaimed novels. He also sought to remedy social ills — as he insisted intellectuals must — with a quixotic run for the presidency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e489d650-18d3-11f0-a183-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:57:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration official who oversaw dismantling of USAID leaves State Department</title>
      <description>During his three months at the agency, Pete Marocco worked closely with tech billionaire Elon Musk, with both recommending severe cuts to USAID and State Department programs, according to U.S. officials familiar with the situation who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss personnel matters. It was not immediately clear why Marocco stepped down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f80b9190-18cf-11f0-8567-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 01:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A State Department memo said the Trump administration produced no evidence that a Tufts student supported antisemitism or terrorism</title>
      <description>The internal memo, prepared days before Rumeysa Ozturk was detained by ICE agents, raises doubts about the Trump administration’s public claims that the doctoral student engaged in activities “in support of Hamas.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b125c880-18c6-11f0-8d24-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rory McIlroy wins the Masters in a playoff over Justin Rose, completing the career Grand Slam with his fifth major championship</title>
      <description>McIlroy began Sunday with a two-shot lead but needed to survive some late misadventures that left him tied with Rose, who started the day seven shots behind. It's the first green jacket for McIlroy, who becomes just the sixth man to complete the career Grand Slam.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5613ad1-18bd-11f0-8bec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 23:20:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>38-year-old man in custody after arson attack on Gov. Josh Shapiro's mansion, Pennsylvania police say</title>
      <description>Cody Balmer of Harrisburg was taken into custody Sunday in connection with what Shapiro (D) described as a “targeted” attack hours after he and his family celebrated the Jewish holiday of Passover at the governor’s mansion. Officials said they did not yet know a motive and charges haven't been filed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79dadd30-18b1-11f0-8bec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:51:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paris said au revoir to cars. Air pollution maps reveal a dramatic change.</title>
      <description>The shift in pollution levels shows how ambitious policymaking can directly improve health in large cities. Air pollution is often described by health experts as a silent killer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab32cc81-18ac-11f0-ae10-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 21:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro’s home was set on fire in an act of arson that caused ‘significant’ damage, state police say</title>
      <description>Shapiro and his family awoke to police banging on their door as they responded to the fire at the governor’s mansion in Harrisburg. The family was safely evacuated with no injuries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77922250-1888-11f0-9c58-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 16:58:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81b5c820-1880-11f0-addb-0000a1ace9d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 16:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hollywood’s intimacy coordinator field faces growing pains as A-list stars decline coaching</title>
      <description>Gwyneth Paltrow and Mikey Madison are among the stars who have opted to work without sex scene advisers. Those in the emerging profession defend their role on sets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff86e970-1874-11f0-8382-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 14:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f54fa450-186b-11f0-a82c-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What happens when 3,000 heavy metal fans take a Caribbean cruise</title>
      <description>On the 70,000 Tons of Metal cruise, metalheads from around the world sail from Miami to Jamaica with bands playing on a pool deck stage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b64c87a0-17df-11f0-8978-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 20:50:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials have the private goal of deporting at least 1 million immigrants this year. Analysts say that's unrealistic.</title>
      <description>Deporting 1 million immigrants in one year would surpass previous statistics, as the highest number was more than 400,000 a year when Barack Obama was president. But there’s a reason that goal remains a private one, and immigration officers and analysts are increasingly skeptical that officials can meet that target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0098ef0-17ce-11f0-b565-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa442280-17c9-11f0-b2ae-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was torn from her birth mother 30 years ago. Then they found each other.</title>
      <description>Korean adoptees can remind the world that these are deeply personal losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5cfe460-17bb-11f0-99f5-0000a1ace11d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones and other electronics will be exempted from reciprocal tariffs, Trump administration says, including Chinese imports</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's exemptions on electronic components coming out of China was announced late Friday. Beijing placed a 125 percent tariff on all U.S. goods earlier in the day, saying it would “fight to the end.” The exemptions on electronic components will likely be welcomed by tech companies like Apple, which produces the bulk of its iPhones in China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82a3770-17ae-11f0-bab4-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 15:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87d9bce0-17a2-11f0-b02b-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
