<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 08:02:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk and his PAC to keep spending on politics despite campaign loss in Wisconsin and doubts in the GOP</title>
      <description>The billionaire, whose network of allies poured more than $20 million into the Wisconsin Supreme Court race, will be heavily involved in elections going forward, according to two people familiar with the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c83e4290-1010-11f0-8101-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 22:21:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces 10% tariffs on all imports and higher taxes on goods from about 60 countries, in sharp escalation of trade war</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump unveiled the details of the broadest import taxes in decades in a Rose Garden ceremony, the first of his second term. The tariffs will take effect immediately, the White House has said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaa20810-1002-11f0-ae31-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 20:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump team has weighed deal to avert TikTok ban in U.S. that would leave algorithm in Chinese ownership</title>
      <description>The White House has considered a menu of options in recent weeks. They include a scenario where investors outside of China would increase their ownership of TikTok while Beijing-based ByteDance would retain ownership of the powerful algorithm that recommends what people see on the popular video app, according to two people familiar with the deliberations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e02b2750-0fe4-11f0-91bf-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 17:06:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump claimed the Smithsonian is filled with ‘corrosive’ art. Monica Hesse found something different.</title>
      <description>What exactly does Trump think is in the Smithsonian?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">91037f81-0fdd-11f0-ae56-0000a1ace06d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Silenced by marriage and divorce, the ex now has something to say</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Silenced by marriage and divorce, the ex now has something to say</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71147300-0fdd-11f0-b77b-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 16:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: A reader who has been called a mom and a cougar by servers has a PSA</title>
      <description>Dining chat: A reader who has been called a mom and a cougar by servers has a PSA</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e9e6730-0fd4-11f0-87cb-0000a1ace176</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of African American museum on leave as Smithsonian faces Trump pressure, email shows</title>
      <description>Kevin Young, an acclaimed poet who was named director of the National Museum of African American History and Culture in 2021, is on personal leave for an “undetermined period,” according to an email obtained by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d8261d0-0fd3-11f0-b937-0000a1acefd1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California man to plead guilty in 2022 plot to assassinate Supreme Court Justice Brett Kavanaugh, lawyers say</title>
      <description>Nicholas Roske is accused of approaching Kavanaugh's Maryland home carrying burglary tools and a handgun before turning himself in.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ad64320-0fd0-11f0-91e1-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:39:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds FDA’s rejection of fruit-flavored vape liquids popular with youth</title>
      <description>The unanimous decision upheld the Food and Drug Administration's denial of applications to market liquids the agency says are popular with young people and put them at risk of getting hooked on nicotine. The FDA has rejected more than 1 million fruit-, candy- and dessert-flavored e-cigarette liquids in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">897ee600-0fce-11f0-a0dc-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:26:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge dismisses corruption case against New York Mayor Adams after effort by Trump’s Justice Department to terminate it</title>
      <description>A judge on Wednesday dismissed a corruption indictment against Eric Adams after a controversial push by the Justice Department to end the case, a move by Trump administration officials that led to the resignations of several federal prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19047440-0fcd-11f0-8313-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 30th anniversary of this singer's death in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7679140-0fc6-11f0-b982-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s ‘unforced error,’ and other takeaways in this analysis of the Wisconsin Supreme Court and Florida special elections</title>
      <description>Democrats had a good night Tuesday. High turnout in Wisconsin helped power a Democratic win in the state supreme court election. Elon Musk had invested heavily in the race. In elections for U.S. House seats in Florida, Democrats narrowed their margins in districts that voted heavily for Donald Trump in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cea1061-0fc1-11f0-bf66-000a1ace0fb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 12:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Election results. Michael Waltz’s email. Cory Booker. Luigi Mangione. Val Kilmer. Baby hippo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3975f80-0fb1-11f0-b1c2-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: Val Kilmer dies at 65. The actor achieved stardom in such films as ‘Top Gun’ and ‘Batman Forever.’ A previous alert misstated the Batman movie he starred in.</title>
      <description>Kilmer lost his natural voice after a surgery for throat cancer in 2015, forcing him to adopt AI technologies that could re-create his projection levels and emotion in subsequent roles. An earlier headline incorrectly stated he appeared in “Batman Returns” instead of “Batman Forever.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc6292f0-0faa-11f0-8313-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Val Kilmer dies at 65. The actor achieved stardom in such films as ‘Top Gun,’ ‘Batman Returns’ and ‘The Doors.’</title>
      <description>Kilmer lost his natural voice after a surgery for throat cancer in 2015, forcing him to adopt AI technologies that could re-create his projection levels and emotion in subsequent roles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90a864a0-0f84-11f0-87cb-0000a1ace176</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 05:37:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic-backed Susan Crawford is projected to win Wisconsin Supreme Court race that attracted Musk, Soros and other big names</title>
      <description>According to an Associated Press projection, Crawford defeated Brad Schimel, a Waukesha County judge and former Republican state attorney general, in the most expensive judicial race in U.S. history. The win by Crawford, a Dane County judge, ensures the court will maintain a liberal majority ahead of its expected consideration of cases on key issues, including reproductive rights.
Elon Musk and his affiliated groups invested more than $20 million to support Schimel. Crawford’s campaign benefited from large donations to the state Democratic Party from liberal billionaires, including Illinois Gov. JB Pritzker, George Soros and LinkedIn co-founder Reid Hoffman.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a998c6f0-0f69-11f0-be66-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 02:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House studying cost of Greenland takeover, long in Trump’s sights</title>
      <description>It’s the most concrete effort yet to turn President Donald Trump’s desire to acquire the Danish territory into actionable policy, despite widespread outrage from Denmark and other allies. The administration is also attempting to estimate what revenue to the U.S. Treasury could be gained from Greenland’s resources.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5445fa20-0f5e-11f0-a604-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 01:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-backed Jimmy Patronis is projected to win Florida special election for Gaetz’s House seat</title>
      <description>Florida’s chief financial officer defeated Democratic gun-control activist Gay Valimont, according to an Associated Press projection, in a race for the 1st District seat formerly held by Republican Matt Gaetz.

Patronis was outraised by his Democratic opponent in the solidly red district that President Donald Trump won by more than 30 percentage points in November. His victory provides a crucial vote for House Republicans as they try to enact Trump’s agenda with a narrow majority in the chamber.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab867910-0f5c-11f0-945b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:51:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-backed Randy Fine is projected to win special election in Florida’s 6th District</title>
      <description>The Republican state senator defeated Democrat Josh Weil, according to an Associated Press projection, in the race for the seat formerly held by Michael Waltz. Waltz resigned earlier this year to join President Donald Trump’s Cabinet as national security adviser.

Fine’s opponent had fundraised millions more in a race that was expected to be an early indicator of President Donald Trump’s second-term popularity. It also helps reinforce House Republicans’ narrow majority as they look to enact Trump’s agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc6f28a0-0f53-11f0-b015-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 23:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker breaks modern record for longest speech from Senate floor</title>
      <description>The Democratic senator from New Jersey broke the record Sen. Strom Thurmond set in 1957 with a speech that held the floor for just over 24 hours to stop the passage of the Civil Rights Act.

Booker's remarks launched Monday with a vow to disrupt “the normal business of the United States Senate for as long as I am physically able” to protest President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12f7e950-0f51-11f0-9fa4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 23:28:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nine GOP House members defy Speaker Mike Johnson on proxy voting measure — a stunning rebuke that forces Republicans to regroup</title>
      <description>Johnson unsuccessfully sought to block a measure from coming to the House floor that would allow new parents in Congress to vote remotely. The nine Republicans sided with Democrats to deliver Johnson an embarrassing defeat on a procedural vote. Republican leadership called off votes for the rest of the week to regroup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeb93f50-0f30-11f0-87b6-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 19:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump national security adviser Michael Waltz and staff used personal Gmail accounts for government communications, officials say</title>
      <description>The use of Gmail, a far less secure method of communication than the encrypted messaging app Signal, is the latest example of questionable data security practices by top national security officials already under fire for the mistaken inclusion of the Atlantic’s editor in a group chat about high-level planning for military operations in Yemen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a12898f0-0f2e-11f0-ad25-0000a1ace082</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 19:22:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland hires Buzz Williams of Texas A&amp;M as its next men’s basketball coach</title>
      <description>Williams, 52, will take over the Terrapins after Kevin Willard left to take the same job at Villanova this weekend.
Williams spent the past six seasons at Texas A&amp;M, leading the Aggies to the past three NCAA tournaments, after previous head coaching stints with Virginia Tech, Marquette and New Orleans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134faa40-0f25-11f0-a9bc-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 18:13:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A compulsive liar wants out of all the lies</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A compulsive liar wants out of all the lies</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85ebdaa0-0f12-11f0-bfd2-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration says it wrongly deported a Maryland immigrant to a Salvadoran prison but is unable to rescue him</title>
      <description>In court documents, the government blamed “an administrative error” for the mistaken deportation of Kilmar Abrego Garcia, a Salvadoran immigrant married to a U.S. citizen. Officials claim they’re unable to return him to his family in Maryland.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4079f340-0f11-11f0-83ba-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:52:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department will seek death penalty for Luigi Mangione in UnitedHealthcare CEO killing, Attorney General Pam Bondi says</title>
      <description>Bondi called the killing of Brian Thompson “a premeditated, cold-blooded assassination that shocked America.” Mangione has been charged in a federal complaint, but no indictment has been unsealed. It is highly unusual for prosecutors to announce they will seek the death penalty before an indictment is made public.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9b79aa0-0f0f-11f0-ae90-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:41:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Days of flooding rains, tornadoes and heavy snow are coming. Here’s where the life-threatening storms will hit hardest.</title>
      <description>Extreme rainfall beginning Wednesday could fuel flooding across a swath of states, particularly from Arkansas to western Kentucky. The rain won’t relent in this region until Sunday, and in some spots, more than a foot may fall. There’s also a threat of tornadoes in 15 states Tuesday and Wednesday; high-risk cities include Oklahoma City, Tulsa, and Kansas City, Missouri.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">309ff960-0f0c-11f0-9d14-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 15:15:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple leaders purged at NIH, CDC and FDA as massive layoffs begin at U.S. health agencies</title>
      <description>Senior leaders at the National Institutes of Health, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, and Food and Drug Administration have been put on administrative leave and some were offered reassignment to remote locations at the Indian Health Service. Meanwhile, federal employees have begun receiving layoff notices as part of a massive “reduction in force” at the Department of Health and Human Services, led by newly confirmed leader Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d2f7250-0f07-11f0-9fa4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 14:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulling rabbits out of hats in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1daa120-0efd-11f0-ac6d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special elections. Trump’s tariffs. Harvard funding. Abortion ruling. Murder trial. Storm forecast. Hooters. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76e16590-0ee8-11f0-b626-0000a1ace9bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The women’s Final Four is set. South Carolina, UCLA, Texas and Connecticut will meet in Tampa for the national title.</title>
      <description>Three No. 1 seeds and No. 2 seed Connecticut advanced to the national semifinals of the NCAA women's basketball tournament, which has been short on major upsets. South Carolina will face Texas and UCLA will meet Connecticut on Friday before the winners play for the national championship Sunday afternoon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4c98b50-0ea9-11f0-be66-00000a1ace1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 03:31:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge temporarily blocks Trump administration from ending deportation protection for about 350,000 Venezuelans</title>
      <description>The order prevents the Department of Homeland Security from allowing temporary protected status for Venezuelan migrants to expire on April 7. The decision comes as President Donald Trump has ramped up his efforts to quickly arrest and deport Venezuelans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfaa3e90-0e85-11f0-a4e6-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 23:13:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fast-food drive-throughs most likely to mess up your order, according to our Department of Data</title>
      <description>For almost a quarter-century, secret shoppers have been dispatched to each of the top 10 fast-food outlets throughout the United States, focusing on the lunch and dinner hours. Here’s the data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3ae5190-0e73-11f0-863f-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 21:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration targets billions in federal funding to Harvard, saying the university mishandled campus protests, antisemitism</title>
      <description>The Education and Health and Human Services departments, along with the U.S. General Services Administration, announced a review of billions in contracts and grants to Harvard and its affiliates, a move that follows dramatic cuts at Columbia University.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60eea790-0e6e-11f0-a8e3-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 20:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Technician sports dramatic new look. Does it warrant a comment?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Technician sports dramatic new look. Does it warrant a comment?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb27c580-0e4a-11f0-b04e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 16:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA beef in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3510340-0e34-11f0-a4e6-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 13:33:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Far-right French leader Marine Le Pen convicted of embezzlement and barred from running in 2027 election, French media report</title>
      <description>Le Pen, the guiding force of the anti-immigrant National Rally party, has been regarded as a leading contender in France’s next presidential election. She accused prosecutors of seeking her “political death” in bringing charges that her party embezzled nearly $5 million of E.U. funds. Le Pen is expected to appeal the verdict.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43141ea0-0e2b-11f0-9376-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 12:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s third term remarks. Elon Musk. Quake damage. West Bank. Air pollution. Richard Chamberlain. Final Four. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a0e46b0-0e1f-11f0-b3b4-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The men’s Final Four is set. Florida, Duke, Houston and Auburn will meet in San Antonio for the national championship.</title>
      <description>All four No. 1 seeds advanced to the national semifinals of the NCAA men’s basketball tournament for the second time in history and the first since 2008.
Duke will face Houston and Florida will meet Auburn on Saturday before the winners play for the national title next Monday night.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62bfa701-0dbe-11f0-b9b6-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 23:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50586271-0d80-11f0-998a-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craft distillers are hit hard as tariffs mix with 1930s rules for alcohol, making it more difficult to expand in the U.S.</title>
      <description>Alcoholic drinks have become the subject of dueling tariff threats between the United States and its neighbors, especially Canada. But some craft distillers say they feel particularly battered because they had seen these other countries as better targets for growth than parts of the highly regulated and crowded U.S. market.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6738360-0d73-11f0-a5e5-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 14:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Men’s basketball coach Kevin Willard is leaving Maryland to take Villanova job after leading Terps to NCAA tournament’s Sweet 16</title>
      <description>Rumors that Willard would soon be departing intensified over the past couple of weeks, after the coach declined to sign a contract extension and aired concerns about the school’s financial commitment to its men’s basketball program.

In three seasons at Maryland, Willard led the Terrapins to two NCAA tournaments, including this year’s run to the Sweet 16, their first since 2016.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40de1290-0d6c-11f0-b147-0000a1ace1cc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:38:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f82f300-0d6b-11f0-8aeb-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 13:32:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Chamberlain dies at 90. The TV heartthrob was ‘king of the miniseries,’ including ‘Shogun’ and ‘The Thorn Birds.’</title>
      <description>The 1960s TV series “Dr. Kildare” drew millions of viewers and made Chamberlain a household name.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ca0bbc0-0d5f-11f0-9a11-000a1ace2140</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 12:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Trump administration has downplayed the Signal chat scandal</title>
      <description>“Mistake.” “Glitch.” “Entirely permissible.” “Hoax.” See the varied and shifting responses President Donald Trump and his allies have offered as they have reacted to this security breach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">178cd360-0ce3-11f0-94fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 21:16:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Pentagon strategy memo on China and homeland defense has Heritage Foundation fingerprints</title>
      <description>Internal guidance from Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth is reorienting the Pentagon to deter China’s seizure of Taiwan and focus the military on homeland defense. According to a Washington Post analysis, in some instances, the planning document is a nearly word-for-word facsimile of a report from the conservative think tank behind Project 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5e1a3e1-0cd4-11f0-92ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 19:34:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I want to rekindle my bond with my sister, but she remains distant</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I want to rekindle my bond with my sister, but she remains distant</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbcd9901-0cb6-11f0-8ccf-0000a1ace7d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 15:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What legendary French chef Jacques Pépin taught our food writer about omelets and life</title>
      <description>It’s impossible to calculate how many classic omelets the beloved 89-year-old chef has prepared since dedicating himself to the art and technique of the dish. “There’s no failure,” he said. You eat your mistakes and move on.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e26b6cb0-0caa-11f0-8c76-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 14:34:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33694e60-0ca2-11f0-80d8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 13:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correction: At least 1,000 dead, 2,700 injured in Myanmar earthquake, according to country’s military. An earlier alert had an incorrect link.</title>
      <description>The powerful 7.7-magnitude earthquake struck Myanmar on Friday, killing at least 1,000 people, according to the country’s military junta, with deadly tremors felt hundreds of miles away in Thailand.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c5e900-0c66-11f0-a131-000a1ace66fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 06:22:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
