<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 08:02:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Faizan Zaki, 13, of Texas wins the Scripps National Spelling Bee. The runner-up from last year was competing in his fourth bee.</title>
      <description>Nine students competed in Thursday’s final rounds held in Maryland. The national spelling contest celebrated its 100th anniversary this year, and the winner takes home a championship trophy and $50,000 among other prizes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36be29b0-3cfd-11f0-bdb0-0000a1ace900</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 02:24:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garbled citations in White House MAHA report bear hallmarks of AI, experts say</title>
      <description>Citations in the initial version of the sweeping health report, which was written in response to an executive order from President Donald Trump, included incorrect authors, and several studies cited do not exist at all.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53a9810-3cf0-11f0-b0f4-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 00:55:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs can remain in place for now, appeals court says, temporarily pausing a trade court ruling that found them illegal</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had asked the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit to make a ruling. Most of the White House’s “reciprocal” tariffs will remain in effect as litigation proceeds.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2191090-3cc6-11f0-a783-0000a1ace336</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 19:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge grants Harvard a temporary reprieve from Trump administration’s attempt to bar its enrollment of foreign students</title>
      <description>Judge Allison D. Burroughs ordered that a temporary restraining order she issued last week remain in place until a preliminary injunction is issued. The ruling grants Harvard a reprieve, for the time being, in one of the most high-stakes battles in its ongoing war with the administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4af7a000-3ca8-11f0-afd9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Middle-aged and still getting dismissed as ‘the baby’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Middle-aged and still getting dismissed as ‘the baby’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85ee9ad1-3ca6-11f0-bc27-0000a1ace6bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 16:03:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court narrows scope of federal agencies’ environmental reviews of highways, pipelines and other projects</title>
      <description>The decision centered on a rail line in Utah that would carry billions of gallons of oil and sets new parameters for how far agencies may go in assessing environmental impacts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65615050-3c97-11f0-bf5b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:15:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making duck calls in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c38f111-3c91-11f0-991e-00000a1ace93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 13:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariffs ruling. Student visas. Elon Musk’s exit. Vaccine confusion. Gaza chaos. Climate warning. Genetic ‘trucks.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">114c7500-3c7c-11f0-9901-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk is leaving his role in the Trump administration after a tenure marked by contentious efforts to slash government spending</title>
      <description>The billionaire behind the U.S. DOGE Service wrote on X that his “scheduled time” as a special government employee had come to an end. A day earlier, in a major break with President Donald Trump and Republicans, Musk said he did not approve of the president’s One Big Beautiful Bill, with its massive tax cuts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d9c1aa0-3c2f-11f0-9f94-0000a1ace01f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 01:49:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Air Force One deal with Qatar is not final, despite the administration's claims</title>
      <description>The Qatari government has asked the United States to clarify that the luxury jetliner's pending transfer was initiated by the Trump administration and that Qatar was not responsible for any future transfers of the plane's ownership, officials told The Washington Post. The delay reflects lingering concerns about legal liabilities stemming from the White House's maneuver to transform what was originally a sale between two countries into a “gift."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">161a2a50-3c27-11f0-9bd1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:51:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rubio says Trump administration will ‘aggressively revoke’ visas for Chinese students</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio has announced that the State Department will collaborate with the Department of Homeland Security to strip the visas of Chinese students with ties to the Chinese Communist Party and those studying in “critical fields.” The plan also includes a revision of all visa criteria for China and Hong Kong, marking the latest escalation in the Trump administration's confrontational relations with Beijing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96ef1c20-3c23-11f0-82ad-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:26:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trade court blocks Trump's tariffs, saying they are illegal</title>
      <description>The Court of International Trade ruled that President Donald Trump exceeded his authority in imposing tariffs on all imported goods. The president invoked a law that granted him emergency powers over the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d194dbf0-3c1c-11f0-9bd1-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 23:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to upend one of the nation's largest affirmative action programs to settle lawsuit with White-owned businesses</title>
      <description>The $37 billion Transportation Department initiative, which dates to 1983 and serves an estimated 49,000 businesses, would be prohibited from awarding contracts based on race and sex, effectively ending its founding mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4f8410-3be6-11f0-8820-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend of nine years ‘distant and angry’ when marriage comes up</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend of nine years ‘distant and angry’ when marriage comes up</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ab758c0-3bdd-11f0-9ea2-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:02:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would you cut it in the Scripps National Spelling Bee? Try to catch these 24 misspellings.</title>
      <description>Is knowing how to spell still relevant?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8cbbc80-3bdc-11f0-961b-00000a1ace7f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 16:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new land in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f990571-3bc8-11f0-a751-000a1ace9706</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 13:31:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts Putin. Student visas. Elon Musk. Coronavirus shots. Prison escape. Drying river. Flight etiquette. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8203e10-3bb2-11f0-887b-0000a1ace6f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After launching into space, SpaceX loses another Starship in test flight</title>
      <description>A Starship spacecraft came apart midflight Tuesday evening after a successful launch to space. There was no crew aboard the test flight. It was the third loss of a Starship in a row and dealt another setback to Elon Musk’s dreams of using the spacecraft to reach the moon and Mars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eb43b80-3b5e-11f0-a6a0-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 00:54:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge tosses Trump executive order punishing law firm WilmerHale</title>
      <description>The ruling is the third time a federal judge has struck down one of President Donald Trump’s orders targeting a prominent law firm. Trump has taken aim at several law firms with ties to his perceived enemies, directing that they be blocked from government contracts and federal buildings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">553aafd1-3b4f-11f0-be86-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 23:07:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you know these winning words from the national spelling bee? Test your skills.</title>
      <description>Jacques Bailly, a past Scripps National Spelling Bee winner, has served as the competition’s head pronouncer for decades. For our quiz, he picked and pronounced 10 words from 100 years of America’s most famous spelling contest.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0c96290-3b40-11f0-afd9-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 21:23:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is the ‘meaningful’ job worth the physical and mental consequences?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is the ‘meaningful’ job worth the physical and mental consequences?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5f0a5c0-3b15-11f0-b766-0000a1aceff6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 16:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. ends covid vaccine recommendation for healthy children and healthy pregnant women</title>
      <description>In a rare move, the health and human services secretary bypassed the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and announced the new policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f165b4f1-3b12-11f0-9318-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:54:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beef Wellington mystery in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db7a1280-3afe-11f0-9f79-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth’s inner circle of advisers is riven by dysfunction and distrust, current and former officials say</title>
      <description>Hegseth purged several top political appointees in April, after internal feuds burst out into the open. But his attempts to portray a new sense of unity among his remaining brain trust are belied by unresolved personality conflicts, inexperience, vacancies in key leadership roles and a steady-state paranoia over what political crisis could emerge next.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c5ca370-3afc-11f0-8a02-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:13:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s speech. Republican split. Liverpool car incident. Gaza school. Cancer risk. Hot weather. Mysterious bucket. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc7ac9c0-3ae9-11f0-b3bb-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>81 years after he died in World War II, a young aviator was buried in his California hometown</title>
      <description>Second Lt. Thomas V. Kelly Jr. was 21 when he perished with 10 other men on a B-24 bomber shot down near New Guinea on March 11, 1944. Two years ago, his remains and those of three other crew members were recovered from the underwater crash site. Kelly was buried Monday beside family members in Livermore, California.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1178a7f1-3a75-11f0-847c-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 21:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How well do you understand your dog’s emotions? Here’s what research tells us.</title>
      <description>Dog owners don’t understand their pet’s emotions as well as they think they do.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef605c30-3a5b-11f0-a834-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:04:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charles Rangel dies at 94. He was the first African American chairman of the House Ways and Means Committee.</title>
      <description>The New York Democrat was a powerful voice for Harlem in Congress but was forced to relinquish his chairmanship because of a series of financial transgressions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">611a2990-3a4e-11f0-847c-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:27:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Stepparent resents husband’s ex over teen’s support agreement</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Stepparent resents husband’s ex over teen’s support agreement</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d75d4411-3a4a-11f0-b4e9-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 16:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See what happened when these Post readers stopped mowing their lawns</title>
      <description>Whether you have a small yard or acres to spare, these reader-submitted photos show that retiring your lawn mower can mean less work, more wildlife and a display of blooms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41efe6f0-3a3e-11f0-bfd6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six veterans reflect on Memorial Day — and 364 other days we should not forget</title>
      <description>How to honor Memorial Day? Reach out to veterans’ families. Honor the Constitution. Remember the privilege as well as the sacrifice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b87752e1-3a39-11f0-8451-0000a1acef62</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 14:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy long weekend! Play today’s On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Memorial Day points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">444329f0-3a37-11f0-9442-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:42:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump scolds Putin. Tariff delay. Elon Musk’s future. Firebomb plot. Credit scores. Vaccine rules. Beauty ratings. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3d19f0-3a20-11f0-bfd6-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s been five years since George Floyd’s murder. Much of the promised ‘racial reckoning’ never emerged.</title>
      <description>His murder by Minneapolis police in 2020 set off a summer of protests and promises to address the country’s racial inequality. Five years later, many of those efforts have either been reversed or never materialized.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf5c73f0-39b2-11f0-86ca-0000a1ace341</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 21:54:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This teen lost her mother and sister in the DCA crash. They’d wanted her to win an upcoming piano competition. And so she played.</title>
      <description>For Anne Valerie Ter, the piano was an extension of herself, from the time she first laid eyes on the instrument as a 1-year-old. After the death of her mother and sister, she pounded her grief into the piano keys as she faced Rachmaninoff’s daunting Piano Concerto No. 2.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ee688960-3984-11f0-8130-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7b0b120-3981-11f0-975e-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 16:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where do you stand on this fierce generational divide? Swipe through our test to find out.</title>
      <description>A breakdown of why young people insist on recording videos vertically — and why older folks hate it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd430141-3974-11f0-b060-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 14:29:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21ddcdb0-3970-11f0-89e2-000a1ace4d5d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 13:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This scientist spent years studying ‘super agers.’ Here’s the lifestyle change he focuses on most.</title>
      <description>Cardiologist Eric Topol, 70, previously emphasized aerobic exercise. His research led him to significant changes in his routine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4ca9d20-38e9-11f0-86ca-0000a1ace341</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 21:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Kansas family farm, barely getting by, grapples with Trump’s cuts</title>
      <description>Farmer Jacob Thomas was “barely making it” before the federal cuts this year. Then he and his wife lost 10 percent of their business when the Agriculture Department cut a billion dollars from funding to grow local food for schools and food banks. Other grants they hoped to use to expand are up in the air or have evaporated.
“For the first time in my life,” Thomas said, “I don’t trust the government is going to follow through on their word.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">637ee190-38ae-11f0-84c9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 14:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6647eda0-38a3-11f0-8b38-0000a1aced7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immigrant arrests at courthouses signal new tactic in Trump’s deportation push</title>
      <description>U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement officers have been instructed to arrest people immediately after a judge has ordered them to be deported or after prosecutors move to drop their cases. The coordinated operation is the government’s latest attempt to quickly remove people from the country — even if officials have to bypass the courts — as concern grows in the White House that President Donald Trump won’t be able to fulfill his campaign promise to remove millions of undocumented immigrants from the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03985390-38a1-11f0-99af-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 13:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House abruptly dismisses NSC staffers in significant reorganization</title>
      <description>The dismissals, part of a plan to downsize the coordinating body, follow President Donald Trump’s recent ouster of his national security adviser.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fff59220-3823-11f0-8bfd-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 22:19:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge strikes down Trump's executive order targeting Jenner &amp; Block law firm</title>
      <description>It is the second time a federal judge has ruled that President Donald Trump's unprecedented actions to punish a law firm are unconstitutional.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40371e50-3818-11f0-b7de-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 20:55:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks Trump administration’s effort to ban Harvard University from enrolling international students</title>
      <description>A federal judge in Massachusetts granted Harvard an order on Friday that prevents the Department of Homeland Security from revoking the school’s certification to enroll international students. The decision comes one day after DHS told the school that foreign students must transfer from the university or risk losing their visa status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7f8be91-37f1-11f0-ab79-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 16:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body slamming? Officer aggression? The clash with ICE that led to charges against a Democratic congresswoman.</title>
      <description>The Washington Post analyzed hours of witness video to assess conflicting accounts of a tussle this month involving Rep. LaMonica McIver (D-New Jersey) and Immigration and Customs Enforcement at a Newark detention center.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6f0d730-37e6-11f0-af42-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 15:02:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55380be0-37da-11f0-93bd-0000a1ace9f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 13:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proposes 50 percent tariff on European Union, takes aim at Apple</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump proposed a 50 percent tariff on all goods from the European Union, declaring that trade negotiations with the E.U. were “going nowhere.” 

In a separate media post, Trump threatened Apple with a minimum 25 percent tariff if the tech giant did not make iPhones for American customers in the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef065eb0-37d1-11f0-a8da-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvard suing Trump administration over the abrupt revocation of its ability to enroll international students</title>
      <description>The university said it was filing a lawsuit Friday morning against the administration, challenging its decision Thursday to block the school’s certification to admit foreign students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c9f69c0-37d1-11f0-a6b8-0000a1aceb26</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 12:28:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harvard. Budget bill. Crypto dinner. D.C. shooting. Supreme Court. Vitamin D. Bear cub. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11776e10-37c5-11f0-a20a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
