<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 15:01:30 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6a1e620-4dda-11f0-84c6-000a1acebf5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 13:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s decision. Dodger Stadium. Threats to lawmakers. Listeria outbreak. Plastic bag fees. Roman puzzle. ‘Jaws.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad2d7960-4dc5-11f0-a44c-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 10:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump allowed to keep California National Guard in Los Angeles, appeals court rules</title>
      <description>A federal appeals court in San Francisco said that President Donald Trump appears to have lawfully deployed the California National Guard in Los Angeles without consulting the state’s Gov. Gavin Newsom (D), delivering a win for the president as he aims to use the military to police protests against his deportation efforts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77526d60-4d92-11f0-a28b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 04:53:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the Minnesota shooting suspect was found: A driver spotted a man hiding and waved down an officer</title>
      <description>Interviews with witnesses, victims’ friends and people who know the suspect, along with court records, provide an account of the days leading up to the attacks and more than 40-plus hour search for the suspect that followed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">788c15c0-4d59-11f0-aa18-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 22:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Have knee pain? Here’s what really works.</title>
      <description>Knee braces, hydrotherapy and exercise are some of the most effective ways to address arthritis-related knee pain and stiffness, a new study shows.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25982f42-4d48-11f0-a66d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 20:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will make a decision on striking Iran within two weeks, sees opportunity for negotiations first, White House says</title>
      <description>Trump’s statement Thursday, delivered by White House spokeswoman Karoline Leavitt, extends the timeline for a decision from days to weeks. In what she said was a direct quote from Trump, the president cited “a substantial chance of negotiations that may or may not take place with Iran in the near future.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1459d980-4d3a-11f0-a75b-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch in effect until 9 p.m.</title>
      <description>Storms capable of producing damaging winds and dangerous lightning are expected to come through the Beltway area between about 4 and 7 p.m. A flood watch is also in effect because of the possibility of torrential rain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0a412f0-4d37-11f0-b0ca-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grieving a beloved dog is hard. The guilt is making it worse.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grieving a beloved dog is hard. The guilt is making it worse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a35fb5a0-4d26-11f0-88fb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the American Dream still alive? Test your knowledge of generational mobility with this quiz.</title>
      <description>There is widespread skepticism that the American Dream is still possible. Is it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53ee84e1-4d23-11f0-959f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 15:37:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 280,000 eggs were stolen in America’s scramble over prices and profit</title>
      <description>The shipment from egg giant Cal-Maine was supposed to travel from Maryland to Florida. Then came a ransom note from the supposed trucker: “You need to zelle or wire $7500 if you want your eggs.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">209c5490-4d1a-11f0-8112-000a1ace08bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Juneteenth-themed On the Record</title>
      <description>Play now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a426bbb0-4d11-11f0-b879-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s ultimatum. Social media checks. Transgender care. Social Security. Karen Read. Heat wave. Longevity test. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8366fe40-4cfc-11f0-aa18-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian attack hits key Israeli hospital, medical center and IDF say</title>
      <description>The strike caused “extensive damage” in several areas of the Soroka Medical Center, the hospital said. Iran said it was targeting military and intelligence headquarters near the hospital. Israeli Defense Minister Israel Katz said he instructed the Israeli military to “intensify strikes against strategic targets in Iran and government sites in Tehran,” in retaliation. Israeli police reported no casualties but said there was property damage.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a009b80-4ce4-11f0-98f7-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 08:07:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We asked 1,000 Americans if they support U.S. strikes on Iran. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post flash poll finds Americans opposing U.S. airstrikes against Iran by a 20 percentage-point margin — 45 percent to 25 percent. A sizable 30 percent said they are unsure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5b4adc0-4ca6-11f0-a44e-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:46:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘I’m just so scared’: Lawmakers reckon with safety after Minnesota slayings</title>
      <description>Safety concerns are already prompting lawmakers to change the way they live, especially in places like Minnesota, which has a civic culture that promotes close contact with constituents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad345ae0-4c8b-11f0-821c-0000a1ace993</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 21:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Department to require visa-seeking students to make social media accounts public for scrutiny of anti-U.S. sentiments</title>
      <description>The State Department is restarting interviews for new student visas and planning to review online posts for hostility toward the United States, according to a cable sent to embassies and consulates Wednesday and obtained by The Washington Post. The move comes after the department suspended foreign students’ visa appointments last month in what it described as a move against universities allegedly fostering antisemitism and other national security issues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe275530-4c84-11f0-8c37-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 20:44:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Karen Read was found not guilty of killing police officer boyfriend John O’Keefe, a year after first case ended in a mistrial</title>
      <description>Read’s dramatic and complex case divided a Massachusetts community and drew national attention. Prosecutors alleged she hit O’Keefe with her car after an argument. Her lawyers argued she was framed in a law enforcement cover-up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">292d3360-4c78-11f0-b445-0000a1acec73</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 19:12:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed leaves interest rates unchanged but warns about risks of inflation and slower growth</title>
      <description>Six months after the Federal Reserve hit pause on interest-rate cuts, the central bank remains firmly in wait-and-see mode as it gauges the fallout from President Donald Trump’s trade war and other policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61a60870-4c6e-11f0-9cb4-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches issued, fueled by intense humidity</title>
      <description>Severe thunderstorms could be capable of producing flooding rain, damaging winds and dangerous lightning. Storms are expected to be most numerous between 2 and 7 p.m.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ddfb960-4c67-11f0-9d42-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 17:11:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Time to tell future in-laws to stop meddling in their son’s life?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Time to tell future in-laws to stop meddling in their son’s life?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78ac1b60-4c5d-11f0-b395-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caitlin Clark and a night of skirmishes: The WNBA product is getting out of control, our columnist writes</title>
      <description>Basketball is evolving in the WNBA, but the inadequate officiating is not, columnist Candace Buckner writes. That was evident during the Indiana Fever’s game with the Connecticut Sun last night, a contest that was boiling from the beginning before overheating past the point of control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54740570-4c5b-11f0-ab2d-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State Sen. Ghazala F. Hashmi (Richmond) is projected to win Democratic nomination for Virginia lieutenant governor</title>
      <description>Hashmi goes on to face Republican lieutenant governor nominee John Reid in the November general election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb5b6820-4c56-11f0-ab2d-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:14:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: An acclaimed N.Y. restaurant says yes, then no, to a diner’s special request</title>
      <description>Dining chat: An acclaimed N.Y. restaurant says yes, then no, to a diner’s special request</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47b29630-4c56-11f0-b081-0000a1acedfb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows state bans on gender transition care for minors, a major setback for transgender community</title>
      <description>In a 6-3 vote, the justices cleared the way for Tennessee to ban certain gender transition treatments for minors, a polarizing national issue the Trump administration has seized on in initiatives targeting transgender rights.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04ae93d0-4c50-11f0-a103-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 14:24:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Foreboding strings in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ae3da30-4c48-11f0-892c-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran's supreme leader warns that U.S. military intervention would bring 'irreparable damage'</title>
      <description>Ayatollah Ali Khamenei also said "the U.S. President threatens us" and warned that Iran would not surrender. Israel and Iran traded attacks for a sixth day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ca9f1f60-4c3c-11f0-8a88-000a1ace4113</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five takeaways from Virginia’s primary elections determining November's battle for top posts in Richmond</title>
      <description>Here's a look at the commonwealth’s off-year election results and what stood out as this fall's matchups came into view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25521022-4c38-11f0-ad76-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:34:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump weighs Iran strikes. ICE raids. Democratic infighting. Food dyes. Anne Burrell. Amazon and AI. Statue debate. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">554bcf02-4c33-11f0-bbbf-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida Panthers win the Stanley Cup, beating the Edmonton Oilers in six games to repeat as champions</title>
      <description>The dynamic, dominant Panthers topped the Oilers on Tuesday night, 5-1, to claim the Stanley Cup in a rematch of last season’s finals. Edmonton star Connor McDavid was again denied hockey’s greatest prize. No Canadian team has won the Stanley Cup since the Montreal Canadiens in 1993.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18a68ac0-4bef-11f0-9f48-000a1ace6795</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 02:51:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former state delegate Jerrauld C. ‘Jay’ Jones (Norfolk) is projected to win Democratic nomination for Virginia attorney general</title>
      <description>The winner goes on to face Republican Attorney General Jason S. Miyares, who is running for reelection, in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b26ea00-4be8-11f0-9d62-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 02:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anne Burrell dies at 55. The Food Network star was known for hosting ‘Worst Cooks in America.’</title>
      <description>The chef was known for her spiky, bleached-blonde hair and was a staple of the network’s programming. She died Tuesday in her New York home, her family confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fc046d0-4bd1-11f0-a685-0000a1ace3f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump demands ‘unconditional surrender’ from Iran, says U.S. knows where supreme leader is but won’t kill him, ‘at least for now’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump posted the comments to social media as he gathered top security advisers Tuesday at the White House to weigh U.S. involvement amid ongoing missile exchanges between Iran and Israel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a36c4370-4b9f-11f0-bf10-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:22:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend slow to move his belongings to make room for partner’s</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Boyfriend slow to move his belongings to make room for partner’s</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85480ce0-4b94-11f0-a601-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 16:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See where humidity will soon surge to extreme levels</title>
      <description>Humidity levels will reach high or extreme points in around 40 states over the next two weeks, a result of surging ocean temperatures in the Gulf of Mexico and western Atlantic. The surge is expected to fuel a summer of higher-than-average humidity across the East. Our maps also show what U.S. states and cities will experience temperatures above 90 degrees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">281f10e0-4b8a-11f0-aec0-0000a1ace3df</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 14:48:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Canadian province stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58ebe5f0-4b7f-11f0-99bd-0000a1ace201</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 13:31:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican budget bill faces nearly 2-to-1 opposition with many Americans unaware of the legislation, Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Overall, 42 percent of Americans say they oppose the sweeping tax-and-spending bill that won narrow passage last month in the Republican-controlled U.S. House of Representatives. 

That’s compared with 23 percent of Americans who support the legislation, which aims to extend tax cuts from President Donald Trump’s first term while cutting Medicaid spending and authorizing new spending on immigration enforcement and national defense.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4be092e0-4b6e-11f0-a198-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 11:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel-Iran conflict. ICE raids. Russian strikes. Minnesota shooting. Humidity map. Overtourism. Office snacks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d7e3db1-4b6a-11f0-8ab7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 10:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian barrage of missiles, drones on Ukraine’s capital kills 15 in the deadliest strike of the year</title>
      <description>Russia pummeled Kyiv and its suburbs with 175 drones, 14 cruise missiles and two ballistic missiles, Tymur Tkachenko, head of the Kyiv city military administration, said in a post on Telegram. At least 114 people were injured.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25d4d490-4b4f-11f0-9122-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 07:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump reverses position, signs G-7 statement criticizing Iran and backing Israel’s right to defend itself</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump initially declined to sign the statement, but changed course following discussions with other leaders in the group and changes to the initial draft, according to a U.S. official who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe the sensitive conversations. An earlier draft of the statement called for both Iran and Israel “to show restraint,” according to a copy viewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f41b7fa0-4b38-11f0-a311-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 05:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE agents should continue conducting immigration raids on farms, hotels and restaurants in a reversal of guidance, officials say</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security on Monday told staff it was reversing guidance issued last week that agents were not to conduct immigration raids at farms, hotels and restaurants. Last Thursday's decision had been at odds with President Donald Trump’s previous calls for mass deportations of anyone without legal status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0fe4e801-4b1d-11f0-a311-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 01:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump leaves G-7 summit a day early, returns to Washington to attend to Mideast conflict, White House says</title>
      <description>The president had been scheduled to spend another day in Alberta, Canada. The announcement comes after he declined to sign onto a statement by the other leaders calling for de-escalation of the conflict between Israel and Iran.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15b26c60-4b10-11f0-9a82-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 00:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Iranian state TV headquarters in Tehran mid-broadcast on fourth day of conflict, sending presenter running for cover</title>
      <description>In footage of the live broadcast, an explosion tears through the studio and debris falls into frame. Israel’s military, which had issued a warning order for the area earlier Monday, said the building was concealing military infrastructure. The claim could not be verified independently.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da794801-4adb-11f0-80c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged in Minnesota shootings visited four politicians’ homes as he carried out attacks Saturday, officials say</title>
      <description>The suspect allegedly stopped at the homes of at least two more Minnesota lawmakers’ homes in between the shootings that killed two and injured two others, said Joseph H. Thompson, acting U.S. attorney for the District of Minnesota.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d66e870-4ad0-11f0-9f3f-0000a1ace293</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:40:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Brother has a wife and young kids and cheated with a 22-year-old</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Brother has a wife and young kids and cheated with a 22-year-old</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d25d300-4acb-11f0-82b3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wanted a military spectacle. Instead, he got a history lesson, our art critic writes.</title>
      <description>It was a family-friendly conclusion to a celebratory day, with events on the Mall and fireworks at the end. What had been billed as an overwhelming display of military might turned out to be a display of civics, not power, Philip Kennicott writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e17745d0-4abd-11f0-8139-0000a1aceb35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 14:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A heat advisory in this state in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e82dbbe0-4ab6-11f0-ad82-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 13:36:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota shooting. Israel and Iran. Travel ban. Trump protests. Deadly floods. Flight turbulence. AI confessions. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a19abd1-4aa1-11f0-baa3-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect captured after manhunt following shootings that killed a Democratic Minn. lawmaker and her husband, and wounded two others</title>
      <description>Authorities have detained Vance Boelter, 57, in two shootings. One killed a top Democrat in the state House, Rep. Melissa Hortman, and her husband. Another wounded Democratic state Sen. John Hoffman and his wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a440f5e0-4a5d-11f0-9840-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 02:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.J. Spaun wins the 125th U.S. Open for the first major title of his career</title>
      <description>Spaun, 34, entered the week having never finished higher than 23rd at a major championship. The Los Angeles native was the only player to finish under par at Oakmont Country Club.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4d58c30-4a46-11f0-b810-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 00:12:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As floods keep coming, this small city can’t afford to let people leave</title>
      <description>The federal government has long bought the homes of people who live in flood-prone areas. But officials in Barre, Vermont, which had devastating floods in 2023 and 2024, are rejecting applicants because the city can’t afford to lose their tax revenue.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7f237f0-4a2b-11f0-b1b7-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jun 2025 21:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
