<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:01:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I resigned from the CDC. Here are three questions for RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>I resigned from the CDC. Here are three questions for RFK Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68025630-88e4-11f0-a7cd-0000a1ace239</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:38:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wedding opens new front in cold war with late wife’s sister</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wedding opens new front in cold war with late wife’s sister</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9eb35f60-88e1-11f0-89de-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida moves to end vaccine mandates to attend school, the first state to do so</title>
      <description>Florida Surgeon General Joseph A. Ladapo’s stances on vaccines and other measures have drawn criticism from public health experts and advocates, who have warned that the overhaul of vaccine policies could cause a resurgence of preventable diseases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18150d10-88e0-11f0-aea6-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:07:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A high-profile split in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">450a7551-88ca-11f0-8d52-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deportation ruling. Space Command. Epstein files. China parade. ChatGPT controls. Wildfires. SNL cast. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">241528f0-88b5-11f0-8956-0000a1acecc3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appellate panel rejects Trump’s deportations under Alien Enemies Act</title>
      <description>The appellate panel ruled Tuesday that President Donald Trump unlawfully invoked the centuries-old wartime law to deport Venezuelan migrants, finding no invasion or “predatory incursion” had occurred to justify using the statute to fast-track migrant removals. The decision is widely expected to be appealed to the Supreme Court.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa0095f0-887c-11f0-a9d7-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:17:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At an ICE career expo, a Marine veteran and a former MMA fighter are among thousands vying to carry out Trump’s deportation agenda</title>
      <description>The administration is aiming to hire 10,000 new immigration officers next year, drumming up interest through militaristic branding and a signing bonus of up to $50,000 for top recruits. Applicants said they were not deterred by waning public support for the president's hardline approach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88388041-8854-11f0-9464-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:28:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First batch of Epstein files released by Congress</title>
      <description>The House Oversight and Government Reform Committee released 33,295 pages of documents related to convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein. The committee said it was the first in a series of expected releases as a bipartisan group of lawmakers seeks more transparency from the Trump administration on the subject.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9285c392-884b-11f0-b797-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 22:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. conducts ‘lethal strike’ on alleged drug vessel in Caribbean, a dramatic escalation as Trump intensifies focus on cartels</title>
      <description>Administration officials said the operation targeted a boat that departed Venezuela and was operated by a “designated narco-terrorist organization.” It appeared to mark the first known time the Trump administration used deadly force to target illicit drug shipments originating in Latin America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d5da8f0-8842-11f0-802c-0000a1acefb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 21:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge bars Google from exclusive deals for its search engine but says it can keep Chrome in high-profile monopoly case</title>
      <description>Judge Amit P. Mehta rejected prosecutors’ call to break up the Silicon Valley giant as he laid out remedies for his finding last year that it has an illegal monopoly in search.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22eea361-883e-11f0-aca6-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:48:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Mayor Bowser welcomes federal law enforcement presence indefinitely, a sign of compliance with Trump</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s federalization of the D.C. police force lasts 30 days and is set to expire next week. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser’s plans may quell a showdown over what happens after that deadline passes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e09ac1b0-8838-11f0-a9a9-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump intends to move U.S. Space Command headquarters from Colorado to Alabama, reversing Biden-era plan</title>
      <description>The announcement, expected from President Donald Trump later Tuesday, marks the latest twist in a years-long partisan battle over the agency’s home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7a82101-8822-11f0-8b49-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:31:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grandma’s offhand swipe at adoption gives couple pause</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grandma’s offhand swipe at adoption gives couple pause</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">628c1110-8816-11f0-80e5-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:03:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s deployment of National Guard troops to Los Angeles violated the law, judge rules in case brought by Gov. Gavin Newsom</title>
      <description>The judge concluded that National Guard troops carried out domestic law enforcement actions, violating federal law. The judge did not order the remaining troops withdrawn but blocked them from certain actions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8d86610-8807-11f0-b375-0000a1ace328</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 14:19:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A shakeup comes to this show in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42011f40-8801-11f0-bd7a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:32:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shutdown watch. Labor Day protests. Israel-Gaza. Gun safety. Green cement. Microplastics. Hat snatcher. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">facbf420-87eb-11f0-a54a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We ranked 5,700 holidays. Which one's most popular on your birthday?</title>
      <description>The Department of Data found the most (and least) official holidays for every day on the calendar.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">274b8832-876a-11f0-bf14-0000a1ace536</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This tracking protects a $600 billion economy. Cutting it is foolish.</title>
      <description>This tracking protects a $600 billion economy. Cutting it is foolish.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24fcdb10-875b-11f0-9687-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 17:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After a move and a baby, neither husband nor marriage is working</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After a move and a baby, neither husband nor marriage is working</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b39b3410-874d-11f0-ac00-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:07:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Labor Day quiz in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30dacf50-8738-11f0-bdfa-0000a1aceb79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 13:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Afghan quake. Blocked deportation. Trump’s power. Gaza plan. Medicaid cuts. Age verification. Geese trouble. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3a25940-8722-11f0-bdfa-0000a1aceb79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 10:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More than 600 dead in earthquake in Afghanistan, officials say</title>
      <description>The Taliban-run Interior Ministry said more than 1,500 others were injured after the 6.0-magnitude earthquake struck eastern Afghanistan. Damage and casualties were reported across the region, and the quake was felt in Kabul and neighboring Pakistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b4af9d0-8702-11f0-8f67-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 07:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postwar plan for Gaza circulating within the Trump administration envisions 'voluntary' relocation of entire population</title>
      <description>It's not clear that the 38-page prospectus — which calls for turning Gaza into a trusteeship administered by the United States for at least 10 years while it is transformed into a tourism resort and manufacturing hub — is what President Donald Trump, who has vowed to "take over" the enclave, has in mind. But major elements of it, according to two people familiar with the planning, were designed to make real the president’s vision of a “Riviera of the Middle East.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b72a79c2-86a7-11f0-a17c-00000a1acef4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 20:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders administration to temporarily halt deportation of hundreds of Guatemalan children</title>
      <description>A federal judge rushed an emergency hearing after learning that the Trump administration was moving to deport children to Guatemala despite an order she had issued early Sunday. The Justice Department said the government would ground planes carrying the children to their country of origin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df62c6c0-869f-11f0-8db7-0000a1acecdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 19:22:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">323ae151-8684-11f0-9733-0000a1ace364</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 16:04:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Gray rocking’ is a way to deal with difficult people. Here’s how it works.</title>
      <description>Offering calm, disengaged responses — often referred to as the “gray rock method” — has become something of a phenomenon. Experts say the technique might quell conflict in some situations, but it’s not a long-term strategy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52208ae0-8677-11f0-9ca1-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 14:32:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">207cb160-866f-11f0-8db3-0000a1ace6f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 13:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: ‘Heartbroken’ mom doesn’t believe her adult kid is trans</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: ‘Heartbroken’ mom doesn’t believe her adult kid is trans</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd4d99e1-85c4-11f0-8ebf-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 17:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how Africa wants to redraw the world map</title>
      <description>The Mercator projection, a centuries-old map style from the age of sail, still prevails in the internet age. Here’s what the African Union wants to use instead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93a7d960-85ae-11f0-8c3a-0000a1ace9fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 14:35:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6bb4670-85a5-11f0-af02-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 13:32:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks Trump administration from rapidly deporting most unauthorized immigrants without due process</title>
      <description>The ruling comes after immigrant rights groups challenged the president’s broad expansion of expedited removal for migrants in the United States illegally and marks a setback for his mass deportation agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e61aa10-8544-11f0-905f-000a1ace796d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missouri’s Republican governor calls a special session to redraw the state’s congressional districts</title>
      <description>Gov. Mike Kehoe announced a special session next week with the aim of gaining one more GOP seat in the U.S. House of Representatives. President Donald Trump has increased pressure on states to redraw congressional districts in hopes of beefing up his party’s chances of holding onto the House in the 2026 midterms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f4ce8a0-852a-11f0-938c-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials fire more than half a dozen EPA employees for signing letter criticizing the agency's leadership and direction</title>
      <description>The move to terminate at least seven staffers marks an escalation in the administration’s effort to clamp down on dissent within the federal bureaucracy. EPA leaders had placed a total of 144 employees on leave for signing the letter nearly two months ago. Agency officials confirmed the firings, but did not say how many people had been let go.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c35bfdd0-8527-11f0-b88b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:30:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal appeals court strikes down Trump's tariffs, a key part of his economic policy</title>
      <description>The U.S. Court of Appeals for the Federal Circuit ruled that a 1977 law, called the International Emergency Economic Powers Act, or IEEPA, could not be used to impose most of Trump’s tariffs. The law is used in the case of threats against the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cf6a7c3-8524-11f0-938c-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 22:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10 best college football towns in the country, according to our sports and travel writers</title>
      <description>Fall colors. Buzzing student bodies. Alumni reliving glory days. If you visit any one of these towns before kickoff, you’ll feel the magic, and maybe learn a new cheer or two.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c55ef030-851b-11f0-897c-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 21:04:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republican Sen. Joni Ernst will not seek reelection in Iowa, people familiar with her decision say</title>
      <description>The decision creates an opportunity for Democrats next year in their long-odds push to regain control of the Senate. Ernst was first elected to the Senate in 2014 and comfortably won reelection in 2020. Iowa has been a staunchly Republican state in recent elections, though the GOP has faced some political headwinds there this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29f84d20-8503-11f0-b88b-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Northern Virginia school districts sue Education Department as agency seeks to freeze funding over gender policies</title>
      <description>The lawsuits filed by Arlington and Fairfax County public school districts come after the Education Department said it would require five Northern Virginia districts to seek reimbursement for certain federal grants, as well as begin the process of pulling other funding, in response to local leaders rejecting a call to change policies that allow students to use facilities like bathrooms and locker rooms that match their gender identity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a21c3cf0-84fc-11f0-a1f4-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:21:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Do you need a prescription for the new coronavirus vaccines? We’re answering your questions.</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration narrowed approval of new coronavirus vaccines to those 65 and over or those with conditions that make them more susceptible to severe illness. Meanwhile, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention is reeling after the White House fired its director. What questions do you have about the new vaccine policy and the state of the CDC? The Post’s health team is answering your questions during a live chat now. Send in your questions here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">038befe0-84f2-11f0-a42b-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Trump’s latest test of Congress’s spending authority, White House cancels nearly $5 billion in previously approved USAID funding</title>
      <description>The administration says it can act with or without approval from lawmakers, under a little-tested theory called a “pocket rescission.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96b204d2-84ed-11f0-b16c-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a hacker uncovered the data behind Tesla’s $243 million wrongful death verdict</title>
      <description>The carmaker long said it didn’t have an electric vehicle’s stored digital account of its fatal 2019 crash involving Autopilot. The way that data finally was discovered is believed to have played into a Florida jury’s recent landmark finding that Tesla was partially liable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3015680-84e0-11f0-8d73-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8519af91-84dc-11f0-98f2-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:31:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump revokes Kamala Harris’s Secret Service detail, which had been extended by Biden</title>
      <description>The president’s decision comes as his 2024 Democratic opponent prepares to travel nationwide for a book tour. Federal law gives vice presidents six months of Secret Service protection after they leave office, though President Joe Biden had lengthened her detail into 2026 before he left the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a772fa0-84d9-11f0-823d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC revolt. Minneapolis victims. Newsom vs. Trump. Tesla. Ultra-processed foods. Weekend forecast. Holiday ranking. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4eaf6040-84c7-11f0-9414-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. has an ‘impostor nurse’ problem, and it’s grown since the pandemic</title>
      <description>Authorities in numerous states have reported people falsely claiming to be licensed nurses or working in positions that require a nursing license without valid credentials. Staffing shortages, underfunding and a lack of oversight have exacerbated the problem, one expert said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50411150-845a-11f0-9a06-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 21:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House picks top RFK Jr. deputy to be acting CDC director</title>
      <description>The selection of Jim O'Neill reflects Robert F. Kennedy Jr.'s influence as he seeks to remake federal vaccine policy. It comes a day after the White House fired Susan Monarez, the Senate-confirmed director of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, which prompted a series of resignations of other top CDC officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a8c5c60-8451-11f0-823d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 20:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold-case killer gets 22 years in prison for 2001 murder of his ex-girlfriend’s mother in Chevy Chase, Maryland</title>
      <description>Eugene Gligor admitted he murdered Leslie Preer but claimed he doesn’t remember how it happened. And another element remains unknown to authorities: his motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75e0e8e0-8441-11f0-9b40-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil at CDC as three agency leaders condemn RFK Jr., resign over director’s ouster; GOP senator urges vaccine meeting delay</title>
      <description>As the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reeled from the ousting of its director, three senior leaders who resigned in protest told The Washington Post they were asked to participate in an unscientific vaccine recommendation process that they believe could harm the health of Americans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ece90ba0-843e-11f0-bd4a-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blocks Kari Lake from firing the director of Voice of America</title>
      <description>Judge Royce Lamberth ruled that only a majority vote from the Senate-confirmed board of the broadcaster can fire its director, Michael Abramowitz, dealing a blow to the Trump administration’s effort to dismantle the service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cee3be0-843d-11f0-8494-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Conversational calisthenics with mother-in-law who is never direct</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Conversational calisthenics with mother-in-law who is never direct</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b543ce0-8428-11f0-ba0c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed governor Lisa Cook sues Trump to block effort to remove her, in a case that could decide central bank independence</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has accused Cook of making false statements on mortgage applications. Cook has yet to respond substantively to the allegations, which have yet to be proved.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8a60760-8415-11f0-8a59-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
