<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 10:02:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic donors are funding a preliminary vetting process for running mates should Harris replace Biden as nominee</title>
      <description>The effort, described by four people familiar with the process, suggests that influential figures in the party are growing increasingly restless and concerned about the time remaining to mount a national campaign.

In recent days, people involved in the effort have contacted the teams of top Democratic figures, including Pennsylvania Gov. Josh Shapiro and Kentucky Gov. Andy Beshear, the people said, speaking on the condition of anonymity to discuss a sensitive effort. The donors are also interested in vetting North Carolina Gov. Roy Cooper, Michigan Gov. Gretchen Whitmer and Arizona Sen. Mark Kelly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fa1ebc0-46f1-11ef-bd1c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 23:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service said to have denied requests for more security at Trump events</title>
      <description>Top officials repeatedly rejected requests from Donald Trump’s security detail for more personnel and gear at events before attempted assassination, at times citing lack of resources at short-staffed agency, person familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">993c4450-46ea-11ef-b36c-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 22:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A double life: The cocaine kingpin who hid as a professional soccer player</title>
      <description>Sebastián Marset used his vast drug proceeds to buy and sponsor soccer teams in South America and Europe, investigators say. And then, to fulfill a boyhood fantasy, inserted himself under false identities into the starting lineups — even though he’s not good enough to play at the professional level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c5c1821-46e1-11ef-9f34-0000a1aceb12</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 21:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When should you salt food while cooking? Here’s what’s best for meat, eggs, vegetables and more.</title>
      <description>When you add salt to a recipe can be just as important as how much you add, and that timing impacts more than flavor. Depending on the food, salting before, during or after cooking will yield optimal results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779b52d0-46ce-11ef-a03c-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 19:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli jets strike Houthi targets in Yemen, military says, one day after a drone attack in Tel Aviv</title>
      <description>The strikes in the port city of Hodeida hit an oil depot and power station, a Houthi spokesman said. Israel launched the attack after a drone attack claimed by the Houthis hit a building in central Tel Aviv early Friday, killing one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd9c6730-46bc-11ef-aa77-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 17:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: After so many racist incidents, I’m afraid White people think I’m ugly</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: After so many racist incidents, I’m afraid White people think I’m ugly</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65d8d6c1-46b1-11ef-8902-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes as President Biden lost control of the Democratic Party</title>
      <description>People working inside Democratic politics and government described the first three weeks of July as a kind of nightmare — too extraordinary to be real, too unexpected to be believed. Biden and his campaign team still maintain that nothing has changed, even as calls increase for him to leave the presidential race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c782de0-46a1-11ef-9ac3-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 14:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3195d441-469c-11ef-b35f-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To people in this Russian city, war in Ukraine is a must-win fight against the West, even as cemeteries fill with soldiers’ bodies</title>
      <description>Washington Post journalists visited Kirov, in western Russia, where President Vladimir Putin’s war in Ukraine is filling cemeteries with the bodies of killed soldiers. Residents say the bloodshed is a necessary sacrifice because their country is in an existential struggle against the United States and its NATO allies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eac84af2-468e-11ef-834a-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 11:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Rep. Sheila Jackson Lee dies at 74. The Texas Democrat was a prominent champion of African American and women’s rights.</title>
      <description>During three decades in Congress, she helped make Juneteenth a federal holiday and reauthorize the Violence Against Women Act. She announced in June that she had pancreatic cancer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17eeabe0-4645-11ef-b3bf-0000a1aced81</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 03:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twelve more Democratic lawmakers, including Sens. Sherrod Brown and Martin Heinrich, call on Biden to drop out as campaign digs in</title>
      <description>The calls from two senators and 10 House members marked the largest wave of lawmakers asking Biden to step aside in a single day since his politically damaging debate performance in June. A total of 37 Democratic lawmakers have called on him to abandon his candidacy, even as his campaign manager said he was "absolutely" staying in the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62766cf0-4624-11ef-8f85-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 23:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a botched update from a software security leader triggered a global systems crash</title>
      <description>Hacking experts said CrowdStrike's catastrophically faulty code was inadequately tested and included random data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19ae4190-4616-11ef-a9ac-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 21:30:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaked document reveals J.D. Vance’s anti-woke campaign holding up key State Deptartment nominations</title>
      <description>Before he became Donald Trump’s running mate, the Republican senator was known in the most powerful offices of the State Department as the single biggest obstacle in the Senate to confirming career ambassadors. He held up dozens of President Biden’s nominations over hot-button social issues involving gay and lesbian rights, gender transition care, and hiring practices related to diversity, equity and inclusion, according to a questionnaire obtained by The Post, offering a glimpse into his anti-establishment views.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ac68d01-4609-11ef-a7e5-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 19:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My parents are hurt my daughter favors my father-in-law</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: My parents are hurt my daughter favors my father-in-law</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4256f180-45eb-11ef-acf5-0000a1acedd8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:23:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 2025 is a threat to American values, GOP Senate nominee Larry Hogan of Maryland writes</title>
      <description>"There is no clearer example of the threat to our way of life."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46959780-45e9-11ef-ab0d-0000a1aceb1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 16:09:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top U.N. court says Israel should end occupation, pay reparations</title>
      <description>Israel should withdraw from illegal settlements, stop building new ones and pay reparations to Palestinians who have lost property in areas occupied since 1967, the International Court of Justice said on Friday. The advisory opinion is not legally binding but could have political and diplomatic implications.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">115316a0-45e5-11ef-b521-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Microsoft outage continues to disrupt systems globally. What caused it? Who’s affected? Here’s what we know. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>A technical problem affecting systems running Windows led to widespread confusion and outages across an array of sectors, with airlines canceling or delaying thousands of flights and hospitals putting off non-urgent medical appointments, among other reported issues. The CEO of cybersecurity company CrowdStrike said he was “deeply sorry” for the company’s role in the crisis, which appeared to be resolving.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42d685f0-45e4-11ef-9e25-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 15:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It's the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It's the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a6976c0-45d2-11ef-911c-0000a1aceb07</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 13:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia convicts Wall Street Journal reporter Evan Gershkovich of espionage in a case the U.S. denounced as hostage-taking</title>
      <description>Gershkovich, who was accredited by the Russian Foreign Ministry, was arrested on a reporting trip to Yekaterinburg in March 2023 on spying charges he vehemently denied. After a secret trial in which no evidence was made public, he was sentenced to TK years in prison. The widely expected conviction, in a trial closed to the media and public, clears the way for a potential prisoner exchange.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0119881-45c8-11ef-8406-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s speech. Biden pressure. Microsoft outage. Rally shooter. Covid wave. Bob Newhart. Musket balls. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d09e5f0-45be-11ef-9d37-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major U.S. air carriers ground flights as mass IT outage hits Windows users</title>
      <description>American Airlines, United and Delta are grounding flights citing communications issues, according to the Federal Aviation Administration’s advisory page, as mass IT outages affect businesses across the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ffcf740-45a9-11ef-b366-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 08:33:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump recounts his assassination attempt in his RNC acceptance speech: ‘I’m not supposed to be here tonight.’</title>
      <description>The former president started his speech with a description of the assassination attempt at his rally Saturday. He said this would be the only time he would retell that day’s events because it was too painful to recount.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc77300-457a-11ef-bfb0-0000a1ace468</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 02:59:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Am I imagining this?’: Follow along as nine columnists discuss Trump’s RNC speech</title>
      <description>Follow our columnists as they discuss Trump’s speech at the Republican convention</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81526ef0-4578-11ef-9b0a-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 02:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump caps RNC with tonight’s keynote address, less than a week after assassination attempt. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The former president will take the stage in Milwaukee to formally accept the Republican Party’s nomination for president five days after a gunman opened fire at Trump's Pennsylvania campaign rally.
This week’s convention continues the momentum for a man who left the White House a twice-impeached pariah who tried to overturn his 2020 election defeat and was widely blamed for weighing down his party during the 2022 midterms. His speech comes amid growing calls from Democrats for his opponent, President Biden, to leave the race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1601fe51-4559-11ef-abf6-0000a1ace734</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:57:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelosi has told some House Democrats she believes Biden can be convinced soon to exit the presidential race</title>
      <description>The former speaker, who left her leadership post in 2022 but still wields enormous clout, has told California Democrats and some members of House leadership that she thinks President Biden is getting close to deciding to abandon his presidential bid. Some Democrats fear that by staying in, Biden will end up handing the White House to Donald Trump, three Democratic officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0194e7c1-4554-11ef-bc6a-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 22:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lou Dobbs dies at 78. The conservative commentator was a fierce critic of immigration with close ties to the Trump administration.</title>
      <description>Dobbs was one of the original stars of CNN at the cable giant’s founding before his conservative politics took him into a career as a pundit. His Fox Business Network show was canceled after his airing of false election-fraud theories prompted lawsuits from voting machine companies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a885930-454b-11ef-b2e6-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 21:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Newhart dies at 94. The comic and actor’s understated routines emphasized the absurdities of life.</title>
      <description>Newhart, the star of two long-running TV sitcoms — “The Bob Newhart Show” and “Newhart” — had a staid “button-down” style that was marked by his uninflected delivery, carefully placed pauses and stutters. By looking at familiar situations from fresh angles, he uncovered an original brand of humor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">610e10f0-4540-11ef-a019-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jason Wright, first Black team president in NFL history, to leave Commanders by end of season</title>
      <description>Wright, who will assume the title of senior adviser while the search for a new team president begins, was often the face of the organization as it attempted to change its workplace culture after allegations of widespread sexual harassment and verbal abuse. “This feels like the right moment for me to explore my next leadership opportunity,” Wright said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18a7ff91-452e-11ef-b587-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:49:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it weird to talk to your dog like a toddler? Chat with us all about your pets.</title>
      <description>Is it weird to talk to your dog like a toddler? Chat with us all about your pets.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6fdfd00-4529-11ef-b260-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 17:19:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obama tells allies Biden needs to seriously consider his viability to win reelection, according to people briefed on the matter</title>
      <description>Former president Barack Obama has spoken with President Biden only once since the debate, and he has been clear in his conversations with others that the future of Biden’s candidacy is a decision the president has to make. He has emphasized that his concern is protecting Biden and his legacy, and has pushed back against the idea that he alone can influence Biden’s decision-making process.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2e53a40-451f-11ef-8e5a-000a1ace3c80</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Family ‘won’t let’ him marry until his partner speaks fluent French</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Family ‘won’t let’ him marry until his partner speaks fluent French</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed6bb8d0-451e-11ef-9b76-00000a1ace52</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 16:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Babydog’s big moment in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc6a4931-4509-11ef-b944-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 13:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Francis Ford Coppola, Bonnie Raitt and the Grateful Dead are among this year’s Kennedy Center honorees</title>
      <description>The Kennedy Center will also honor the historic Apollo theater along with celebrated Cuban American trumpeter and composer Arturo Sandoval in a ceremony on Dec. 8. The 47th edition of the Kennedy Center Honors will be broadcast Dec. 23 on CBS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5eacfcd0-44fb-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>J.D. Vance. Biden crisis. Secret Service. Drug kingpin. Emmys. Paris Olympics. Pompeii skeletons. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1b502a1-44f4-11ef-b32d-000a1ace7857</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratic leaders Hakeem Jeffries and Charles E. Schumer told Biden his candidacy imperils the party’s ability to win Congress</title>
      <description>In their separate meetings with the president last week, each congressional leader discussed their members’ concerns that he could deprive them of congressional majorities, giving Republicans a much easier path to push through legislation, according to four people briefed on the meetings who spoke on the condition of anonymity to describe private encounters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66daa700-449b-11ef-9fd5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:19:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RNC will learn more about Sen. J.D. Vance as the vice-presidential pick delivers the keynote on Night 3. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The onetime Trump critic, who has emerged in recent years as one of the former president’s most vocal and fervent backers, is scheduled to give a prime-time address in Milwaukee. Other speakers include Vance’s wife, Usha Vance, and Donald Trump Jr.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">196762c1-4490-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:58:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden tests positive for covid while campaigning in Las Vegas, is experiencing ‘mild symptoms,’ according to White House</title>
      <description>The president, 81, will return to his home in Rehoboth Beach, Del., to isolate, White House press secretary Karine Jean-Pierre said in a statement. Biden’s doctor said the president has received his first dose of Paxlovid and is experiencing a runny nose, cough and “general mailaise,” according to the White House.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa833360-448b-11ef-87c7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 22:29:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGBTQ flags and quinoa: Here’s the liberal Va. enclave where Trump’s VP pick J.D. Vance lives</title>
      <description>Vance, an arch conservative and a self-professed Trump acolyte, lives in the Del Ray neighborhood of Alexandria, which went for Joe Biden by more than 80 percent in 2020. His neighbors aren't thrilled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">16c55e21-4484-11ef-845f-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 21:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for D.C. area as highs reach the triple digits for record fourth straight day</title>
      <description>Storms could contain damaging winds, lightning and torrential rain, while putting an end to the historic heat wave. Temperatures have reached at least 100 daily since Sunday, making this only the third time there have been four consecutive highs at or above the century mark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a388b590-4476-11ef-a238-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. ends its troubled Gaza pier mission, shifts humanitarian operation to Israeli port, officials say</title>
      <description>The project was beset by challenges from almost the moment President Biden announced it months ago. Though U.S. officials say the floating structure enabled delivery of millions of pounds of food, aid groups in Gaza were reluctant to distribute much of it, citing safety concerns amid Israel’s ongoing war with Hamas.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71647690-4470-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 19:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret Service was alerted that police did not have the resources to watch the building scaled by the Trump rally shooter</title>
      <description>Officials are still investigating how the gunman was allowed to reach the roof of the building, where he opened fire on the former president. But local law enforcement's warning of insufficient manpower adds to questions about whether there was adequate security for the high-stakes campaign visit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a85c3b1-446c-11ef-bd87-0000a1ace017</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Adam Schiff (D-Calif.) calls on Biden to drop out of the presidential race, questioning his ability to beat Trump</title>
      <description>Schiff, who is heavily favored to win a Senate seat in November, is among the highest-profile members of his party urging President Biden to abandon his bid. Schiff said he believes it is time for Biden “to pass the torch.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b030e40-4464-11ef-a213-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The sleeper hit of Emmy nominations was ‘The Morning Show.’ See the list.</title>
      <description>The 76th Emmy Awards cover shows aired between June 1, 2023, and May 31, 2024. The ceremony will be held Sept. 15.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5d817b0-445f-11ef-845f-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 17:12:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Casa Ruby founder pleads guilty to fraud after diverting pandemic relief money from her nonprofit focused on homeless LGBTQ+ youth</title>
      <description>Ruby Corado received more than $1.3 million in 2020 and 2021 from the Paycheck Protection Program and the Economic Injury Disaster Loan program. The FBI said she stole at least $150,000 by transferring the money to bank accounts in El Salvador that were hidden from the IRS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">528056f0-445b-11ef-87a7-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:40:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent hits the ceiling over ‘egregious’ class superlatives</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent hits the ceiling over ‘egregious’ class superlatives</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a312ec50-4455-11ef-8147-0000a1ace142</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 16:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Which chain restaurants are the best? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Which chain restaurants are the best? Our food critic responds and answers your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b600ac50-444e-11ef-ade8-000a1ace6c43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 15:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ‘clown prince of fitness’ stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1a0e60-4440-11ef-84cc-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 13:31:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nikki Haley. Rally shooting response. Supreme Court. Bob Menendez. Elon Musk. Amazon tribe. Rare whale. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3d57cd0-442b-11ef-92fd-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Trump’s former rivals make the case for him, and other takeaways from Day 2 of the GOP convention</title>
      <description>Seventy-two hours after the attempted assassination, Republicans returned to their ominous and combative posture as they went hard after Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd8f68f0-43f0-11ef-89c5-000a1ace4bbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 03:58:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obstructed view may have delayed Secret Service sniper response at Trump rally, according to a 3D analysis by The Washington Post</title>
      <description>The analysis found two countersniper teams likely faced difficulty seeing the gunman before he fired. The examination, based on more than 40 videos and photos, established that the units may have been hampered by the slant of the roof where the shooter was positioned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47cfd9b0-43cf-11ef-b892-0000a1ace8f0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 23:58:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
