<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 02:24:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration breaks with Elon Musk, telling federal agencies they can ignore his order on email reply</title>
      <description>The Office of Personnel Management told HR officials that employees wouldn’t be let go for not replying to an email asking what they did last week — nor did staff have to respond to the email. It marks a major break with the billionaire, who has exerted significant power to slash the 2.3 million-person federal workforce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67361621-f2f2-11ef-ba12-0000a1ace8f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 21:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump repeals directive that aimed to ensure allies don’t use U.S. weapons in violation of human rights laws</title>
      <description>The decision to rescind the order, which President Joe Biden imposed as his administration struggled to reconcile its support for Israel’s war against Hamas militants in the Gaza Strip and its alarm about the widespread civilian toll there, comes as the Trump administration puts its “America First” mark on U.S. foreign policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c681d040-f2ea-11ef-bc1b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:06:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clint Hill dies at 93. The Secret Service agent tried to shield President John F. Kennedy when he was assassinated.</title>
      <description>Mr. Hill dove onto Kennedy’s uncovered limousine in a heroic attempt to shield him from the fatal gunshots of Lee Harvey Oswald. “I have a great deal of guilt,” Mr. Hill later said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8965c00-f2e9-11ef-944a-0000a1ace07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 20:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Previous homeowners drop by unannounced, expecting to see inside</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Previous homeowners drop by unannounced, expecting to see inside</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">faca3880-f2d4-11ef-a2a5-0000a1ace45c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:30:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. sides with Russia to vote against a U.N. resolution condemning Moscow for the Ukraine war</title>
      <description>Washington’s dramatic shift on the conflict marks a major break with its European allies and coincides with the Trump administration’s bid to repair relations with the Kremlin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21142630-f2d1-11ef-8d0d-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 17:02:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salena Zito is on a year-long quest to solve the riddle of Pennsylvania politics. First stop: Braddock, birthplace of U.S. steel.</title>
      <description>Two senators from opposing parties focus on the commonwealth’s industrial heritage, not politics. </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f1f09c1-f2cd-11ef-82d5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 16:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roberta Flack dies at 88. The Grammy-winning singer and pianist was known for hits including ‘Killing Me Softly With His Song.’</title>
      <description>Flack, a classically trained pianist, taught in the D.C. school system before launching a singing career that made her one of the most popular performers of the 1970s, with No. 1 hits including “The First Time Ever I Saw Your Face.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23b6a200-f2c7-11ef-87de-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 15:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This magazine’s anniversary is in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7045ca0-f2bc-11ef-9012-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 14:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Dan Bongino. German election. Ukraine war. Measles outbreak. Black plastic. Weight-loss drugs. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0952b60-f2a6-11ef-af9c-0000a1ace726</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Several administration officials tell federal workers not to respond to Musk email demanding accounting of their work</title>
      <description>Top officials at the Defense Department, Homeland Security and HHS were among those who told employees that they don’t need to immediately comply with the request to more than 2 million workers over the weekend. Other agencies offered different guidance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0447c11-f246-11ef-9bd2-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 00:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weight-loss drugs aren’t just slimming waists. They’re shifting the economy.</title>
      <description>Roughly 16 million people, or 6 percent of American adults, take GLP-1 weight-loss drugs such as Ozempic, Mounjaro and Wegovy. These “over-consumers” are already reshaping food, travel, health care and other industries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2c246340-f237-11ef-9aac-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 22:40:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Center-right conservatives are poised to win German election, exit polls show, as far-right AfD makes historic gains</title>
      <description>Friedrich Merz’s Christian Democratic Union has won a plurality in the Bundestag, preliminary exit polls released by public broadcasters ARD and ZDF suggested Sunday, while the anti-immigrant Alternative for Germany party, boosted this month by Vice President JD Vance and tech billionaire Elon Musk, will finish second. Merz will now be tasked with forming a coalition; the mainstream parties have said they will block the AfD.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7111e6f0-f20d-11ef-b0d4-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3d2ca70-f207-11ef-af9c-0000a1ace726</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most parents have a ‘favorite’ child. A new study reveals who and why.</title>
      <description>The idea of parental favoritism might seem inherently subjective (what do we mean by “favorite,” exactly?), but researchers have developed ways to identify differences in the ways parents treat their children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">63d46050-f1fc-11ef-bdc3-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 15:39:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d9b59370-f1f2-11ef-81df-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 14:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal workers must answer email asking what they did last week — or lose their jobs, Musk says</title>
      <description>Elon Musk wrote on X that he was acting on Donald Trump’s orders, apparently referencing a social media post from the president earlier Saturday encouraging the billionaire to be harsher in slashing the federal workforce.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79b16890-f167-11ef-9023-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 21:53:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: Widow who moved closer to family still has a lonely life</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: Widow who moved closer to family still has a lonely life</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7002b000-f140-11ef-9881-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 17:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is cheap cashmere worth buying? We put it to the test.</title>
      <description>Brands such as Quince, Uniqlo and Naadam sell cashmere sweaters for as low as $60. One stood out in our test at the Fashion Institute of Technology, where our sweaters were professionally destroyed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6412bb30-f133-11ef-af24-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 15:40:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b7772d0-f12a-11ef-8fe9-0000a1ace821</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:36:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Social Security chief was being investigated when Musk team tapped him</title>
      <description>Leland Dudek, a data analyst working in a small anti-fraud office, was suspected of sharing unauthorized access to information with representatives of Elon Musk’s U.S. DOGE Service and had been put on paid leave. Now he’s the acting Social Security commissioner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ffd05e0-f127-11ef-9fa8-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 14:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body of Israeli hostage Shiri Bibas returned, family says</title>
      <description>After Hamas handed over an unidentified body Thursday rather than that of Israeli hostage Shiri Bibas, placing strain on the Gaza ceasefire deal, the correct body has been returned, her family said on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cbcb7f0-f0ec-11ef-8142-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 07:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he's replacing Gen. Charles Q. Brown Jr., chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff, in shake-up of Pentagon leadership</title>
      <description>In a statement Friday night, President Donald Trump called Brown a "fine gentleman and an outstanding leader." Trump said he will nominate Air Force Lt. Gen. Dan Caine to replace Brown.
Trump's defense secretary, Pete Hegseth, had mused about firing Brown even before Trump nominated him for the job, complaining that the general had been too focused on diversity initiatives.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">738d22a0-f0b9-11ef-9759-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 01:07:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge temporarily blocks key portions of Trump's executive orders to end DEI in the federal government</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Adam B. Abelson’s preliminary injunction bars portions of President Donald Trump’s orders to cancel federal contracts tied to diversity, equity and inclusion initiatives. A coalition of diversity officers and restaurant worker advocates that filed a lawsuit over Trump’s actions argued that the president’s orders were too vague and chill free speech.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a28ef40-f0b4-11ef-b1e4-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 00:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon to fire 5,400 workers starting next week, an ‘initial’ purge as Trump moves to cull its civilian staff by up to 8 percent</title>
      <description>In a statement Friday, the Defense Department said the cuts are necessary "to produce efficiencies and refocus" the Pentagon on President Donald Trump's national security priorities.  "It is simply not in the public interest to retain individuals whose contributions are not mission-critical," the statement says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99071720-f0aa-11ef-b1e4-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 23:21:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On podcasts, D.C. U.S. attorney discussed investigating Trump’s foes</title>
      <description>Conservative legal activist Ed Martin had conversations last year about potential targets for prosecution. Now he and the  Justice Department have power to bring cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">646435d0-f09f-11ef-82b8-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back in their districts, GOP lawmakers get an earful on DOGE and Musk</title>
      <description>Town halls from Georgia to Wisconsin to Oregon grew heated this week as voters showed up to vent, outraged at the firing of federal workers and DOGE’s access to sensitive data.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe8750a0-f09c-11ef-9759-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 21:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s blitz is unnerving many of President Donald Trump’s senior advisers</title>
      <description>Political appointees in charge of Cabinet agencies have been irritated as Musk’s team acts without consulting them, more than 30 current and former officials or their advisers told The Washington Post. White House Chief of Staff Susie Wiles has asked Musk for better coordination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5592961-f08d-11ef-96a3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Salman Rushdie attacker Hadi Matar found guilty of attempted murder and assault</title>
      <description>The jury deliberated for less than two hours before coming to a verdict. Sentencing is scheduled for April 23.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c68bf10-f08b-11ef-8790-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 19:39:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge appoints outside lawyer to review Justice Dept. effort to dismiss case against New York Mayor Eric Adams</title>
      <description>Eight veteran prosecutors resigned rather than carry out the Trump administration’s order to drop bribery and corruption charges against Adams. U.S. District Judge Dale E. Ho on Friday refused to immediately close the case and said Paul Clement, who was U.S. solicitor general under President George W. Bush, would advise the court on the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6337da0-f083-11ef-97c1-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 18:43:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Female breadwinner tired of loved ones disrespecting her career</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Female breadwinner tired of loved ones disrespecting her career</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0867f8d0-f07b-11ef-9533-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a10f3e0-f060-11ef-91a2-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 14:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s orders. Kash Patel. Mass firings. Israel bus explosions. Rainstorm. Narcissist study. Birkenstocks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54edf8b0-f04b-11ef-9533-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An ‘anonymous, unidentified’ body was returned by Hamas instead of the body of hostage Shiri Bibas, IDF says</title>
      <description>Hamas had promised the remains of three members of the Bibas family, who had been taken hostage: Shiri and her two young children. The Israel Defense Forces said it identified the two sons, but not their mother.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">613932b0-eff1-11ef-8bd4-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 01:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to fire Postal Service board and let his administration control the U.S. mail system, officials say</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is expected to issue an executive order as soon as this week to fire the members of the Postal Service’s bipartisan governing board and place the agency under the control of the Commerce Department. Experts call the move legally questionable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d9fb8b0-efec-11ef-874e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department deletes database tracking federal police misconduct after a Trump executive order undid a Biden-era program</title>
      <description>The database was first proposed by Donald Trump in 2020 after the police killing of George Floyd, but it was enacted by the Biden administration. The DOJ deleted the database, which included thousands of disciplinary records of federal officers, after a Trump executive order negated the Biden-era program.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21cea130-efdf-11ef-9079-000a1ace80c2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects unions’ request to pause federal worker firings, clearing roadblock for Trump administration as it makes sweeping cuts</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Christopher R. Cooper, who was appointed by President Barack Obama, declined to issue a temporary restraining order pausing President Donald Trump’s moves to fire thousands of employees who are on probationary status or deemed nonessential.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebfa68a0-efcf-11ef-9cbe-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 21:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel narrowly confirmed as FBI director, putting Trump loyalist atop storied law enforcement agency</title>
      <description>Katel, a former White House aide, faced fierce opposition from Democrats over his history of incendiary rhetoric and his calls for retribution against perceived enemies of President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9904441-efc0-11ef-b522-00000a1aced1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spurs star Victor Wembanyama will miss rest of NBA season because of blood clot in his shoulder</title>
      <description>The Spurs announced Thursday that their 21-year-old phenom was diagnosed with deep vein thrombosis in his right shoulder after returning to San Antonio from this past weekend’s All-Star Game.

Wembanyama is one of basketball’s brightest young stars and is widely considered the future face of the league.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06877910-efb7-11ef-b44b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 18:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York sues Puff Bar, MYLE and other popular vape brands, accusing them of deceptively marketing to young people</title>
      <description>State Attorney General Letitia James alleged that the 13 companies fueled a public health crisis by promoting “deceptive and misleading” messages about e-cigarettes’ safety and breaking a state law banning flavored vapes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb30b9c0-efb2-11ef-bca8-00000a1ace75</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:47:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s separation isn’t public, but husband’s new ‘friend’ is</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Couple’s separation isn’t public, but husband’s new ‘friend’ is</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36cf8dc0-efac-11ef-ad09-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Mitch McConnell will not seek reelection next year, according to a speech preview, ending his decades-long tenure in chamber</title>
      <description>“Representing our commonwealth has been the honor of a lifetime. I will not seek this honor an eighth time,” McConnell (R-Kentucky) said in a preview of a Senate floor speech shared with the Associated Press. McConnell, first elected in 1984, relinquished his Republican leadership post after last year’s elections. He has faced health challenges in recent years, including injuries from falls.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f80f3640-efaa-11ef-b206-0000a1ace257</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 16:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This senator stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbc8c0c1-ef9b-11ef-b094-000a1acec8c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:02:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many of Trump’s actions in his first month are unpopular among Americans, a Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has opened his second term with a flurry of actions designed to radically disrupt and shrink the federal bureaucracy. But reviews from Americans are mixed to negative on many of his specific initiatives, and 57 percent say he has exceeded his authority since taking office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2f757f0-ef91-11ef-833c-0000a1ace35b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:50:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Ukraine. Federal firings. Israeli hostages. Delta payout. Tomb discovery. New iPhone. ‘Doomsday’ fish. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa8b0a0-ef82-11ef-ae21-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 11:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration orders Pentagon to make plans for sweeping budget cuts, exempting border security and a select few programs</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has ordered senior leaders at the Pentagon and throughout the U.S. military to develop plans for cutting 8 percent from the defense budget in each of the next five years, according to a memo obtained by The Washington Post and officials familiar with the matter — a striking proposal certain to face internal resistance and strident bipartisan opposition in Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef3cab20-eefa-11ef-aa4c-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Transportation Department revokes approval of New York City congestion pricing toll on drivers</title>
      <description>Transportation Secretary Sean P. Duffy said the toll, which went into effect in January in an effort to cut planet-warming emissions and fund improvements to the city's transportation system, was a “slap in the face to working class Americans.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f18c24f1-eef0-11ef-97ea-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mother wants to leave money to only one of her two children</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74733971-eee3-11ef-88e1-0000a1ace156</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 17:03:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, without evidence, accuses Zelensky of being a ‘Dictator without Elections’ — echoing rhetoric from Russia</title>
      <description>The outburst is President Donald Trump's latest attack on Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky and Ukraine, which previously had U.S. support in its fight against Russia's invasion. Many of Trump's recent criticisms of Zelensky have been previously made by Russian President Vladimir Putin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">301e2930-eee1-11ef-b6e6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:47:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Why can’t restaurants update their menus online?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">059f0c60-eedc-11ef-94d5-0000a1acecbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 16:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Across the breadth of Africa, Islamist extremism is spiking, military coups are spreading and Russian influence is on the rise</title>
      <description>As these ominous forces converge, the stakes are high for the region, and the reverberations could be felt beyond its borders. Read the stories of a jihadist, a Russian mercenary, a defiant broadcaster and others, both African and outsider, who are shaping this new chapter of African history.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b4d24c0-eed6-11ef-8807-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 15:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
