<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 02:30:37 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Colleges can directly pay athletes after judge grants final approval of landmark settlement</title>
      <description>Judge Claudia Wilken ruled Friday to approve the revised terms of the $2.8 billion settlement in the House v. NCAA antitrust case, establishing that college athletics programs can pay their varsity athletes via revenue sharing starting in the 2025-26 academic year and beyond.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c6c5ffa0-4343-11f0-9912-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 02:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colleagues question whether Del. Eleanor Holmes Norton is still the best warrior to fight for D.C.</title>
      <description>Several elected officials and allies of the longtime delegate in the House are publicly raising questions about whether the deeply respected civil rights icon is the effective and vigorous leader the city needs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24153a60-4324-11f0-9342-0000a1ace7c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 22:18:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon inquiry into Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth's Signal usage explores whether he, or an aide, shared military attack plans</title>
      <description>The Defense Department inspector general’s office also has questioned potential witnesses about whether Hegseth's aides were ordered to delete sensitive messages from the unclassified chat application, according to people familiar with the inquiry and communications reviewed by The Washington Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34226fb1-431d-11f0-b490-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 21:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Supreme Court lets DOGE access Social Security data of millions of Americans</title>
      <description>The conservative justices sided with Trump administration on two emergency requests related to the U.S. DOGE Service, clearing the way for its employees to access sensitive data and internal systems at the Social Security Administration while litigation continues and shielding DOGE from having to immediately disclose records to a government watchdog group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b893fe51-431b-11f0-948e-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 21:17:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland man who was wrongly deported to El Salvador now in U.S. custody and charged with human smuggling</title>
      <description>The criminal charges against Kilmar Abrego García in Tennessee come weeks after the Supreme Court ordered Trump officials to facilitate his return from the Salvadoran prison where he was erroneously sent. The ruling ignited a standoff with the president, his lawyers and Cabinet members.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ab729f0-4310-11f0-b62b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 19:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proud Boys leaders sue Justice Department over Jan. 6 prosecutions</title>
      <description>Henry “Enrique” Tarrio and four others convicted after the Jan. 6 Capitol breach say the government violated their constitutional rights. They’re seeking $100 million.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eab20950-4301-11f0-ade7-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 18:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police lieutenant sentenced to 18 months for leaking to Proud Boys</title>
      <description>Shane Lamond said he was merely gathering intelligence from Henry “Enrique” Tarrio, but a judge convicted him of obstructing justice and making false statements to investigators.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">075aaf50-4300-11f0-b05c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amid fallout from Trump's attacks on law firms, former Manhattan U.S. attorney leaves firm that made deal with the president</title>
      <description>Damian Williams, the former top federal prosecutor in Manhattan, is leaving the law firm Paul Weiss to join Jenner &amp; Block, defecting from a firm that struck a deal with the Trump administration to sign on with one that fought it in court.

Williams is the highest-profile attorney to join the exodus from firms that made deals with President Donald Trump this year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1ca58ea0-42f8-11f0-b1a8-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Friend wrongly cut me off. Her daughter wants us to reconnect.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Friend wrongly cut me off. Her daughter wants us to reconnect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a954e7e0-42f5-11f0-ba59-0000a1ace3f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:45:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration is racing to fix a big mistake: DOGE fired too many people</title>
      <description>Even before Elon Musk and President Donald Trump split this week, agencies across the federal government were scrambling to hire back workers who were let go or pushed to take early resignation offers by the U.S. DOGE Service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cb1da90-42e6-11f0-99d1-0000a1ace423</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A timeline of Musk and Trump’s insults and threats as their bromance imploded</title>
      <description>Over the past two days, the relationship between President Donald Trump and billionaire Elon Musk has unraveled, as they took jabs at each other from their respective social media platforms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5116bbf1-42df-11f0-badf-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 14:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dupont Circle Park will be closed for Pride despite city officials’ pushback: Crews fence off area per National Park Service order</title>
      <description>The closure will last until 6 p.m. Sunday. Local officials and advocates have called for the park at the center of D.C.’s historic LGBTQ neighborhood to remain open.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7fa0710-42da-11f0-8472-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fa0a8e0-42da-11f0-9ef1-0000a1ace9cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 13:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 139,000 jobs in May, a solid showing even as businesses and households grapple with economic uncertainty</title>
      <description>The unemployment rate held steady at 4.2 percent, according to the Bureau of Labor Statistics, as the labor market continues to grow, although more slowly, amid economic turmoil from tariffs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5358980-42d2-11f0-92fa-0000a1aced97</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 12:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Musk. Travel ban. Russian strikes. Job threats. Supreme Court. Storms. Medieval ‘murder map.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6673a1d0-42c5-11f0-8fbb-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 11:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aaron Rodgers poised to sign contract with Pittsburgh Steelers after disappointing two-year stint with New York Jets</title>
      <description>Rodgers was a four-time NFL MVP with the Green Bay Packers, but he didn't replicate that success with New York. The 41-year-old quarterback will join a Steelers team that hasn’t appeared in the Super Bowl since losing to Rodgers and the Packers in 2011.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">212d1f60-4244-11f0-9b6c-0000a1ace005</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C.’s National Airport is expected to close for up to four hours on June 14 during Army’s birthday bash on the Mall</title>
      <description>The celebration, which coincides with President Donald Trump’s 79th birthday, will include a military parade with 50 Army helicopters flying overhead, as well as parachutists and fireworks. Two people with knowledge of the discussions told The Washington Post that airlines are being notified about the closure but that the timing remains fluid.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71d51c10-423f-11f0-916e-0000a1aceb04</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. bought $12 million in contraceptives and HIV medications for poor nations. Under Trump, the supplies may be destroyed.</title>
      <description>Aid organizations have been in talks about taking control of the supplies, but those negotiations have stalled amid shifting directives from the government, including demands that the groups pay for the materials and that any USAID labeling be removed, a Post examination found. Much of the material is already closer to expiration than many countries would typically accept.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2499b90-4233-11f0-8278-000a1ace7f32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he is ‘very disappointed’ in Elon Musk after the tech billionaire’s criticism of his spending bill</title>
      <description>“Elon and I had a great relationship,” President Donald Trump said. “I don’t know if we will anymore.” The remarks marked a highly public inflection point in the alliance between Trump and Musk, which has sharply deteriorated in recent weeks as the tech billionaire left his post at the U.S. DOGE Service and began publicly criticizing the cornerstone of Trump’s legislative agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a81395b1-422e-11f0-83c8-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents at impasse on letting unwed adult kids room with partners</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents at impasse on letting unwed adult kids room with partners</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ed6aee1-4227-11f0-aded-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 16:07:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court backs Catholic Charities in tax exemption case that could impact other religiously affiliated organizations</title>
      <description>The Wisconsin Supreme Court said Catholic Charities, unlike the church, had to pay into the state unemployment fund, because its activities were “primarily charitable and secular” in nature.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b60b8a0-4219-11f0-8b96-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court unanimously blocks Mexico’s lawsuit against U.S. gunmakers</title>
      <description>The unusual lawsuit sought to hold major U.S. firearms manufacturers accountable for gun violence south of the border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c80d5d0-4218-11f0-b165-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court makes it easier for those in majority groups to claim workplace discrimination, ruling for straight White Ohio woman</title>
      <description>Marlean Ames said members of minority groups who sue over bias in the workplace should not have a lower standard of proof for such claims than people who are straight, White or otherwise belong to majority groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba83f810-4216-11f0-8d9c-000a1ace8f8c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 14:09:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This pest is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80b8b030-4211-11f0-b649-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Travel ban. Biden investigation. Elon Musk. Murder suspect. NBA Finals. Cold plunges. Clever cockatoos. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">36e35ec0-41fc-11f0-bfc6-0000a1ace325</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says it has recovered bodies of Israeli American couple killed on Oct. 7, 2023, the day of Hamas-led attacks</title>
      <description>Gadi Haggai and Judi Weinstein Haggai were a husband and wife in their 70s who lived in southern Israel when they were killed. The bodies of two other Americans, who also have Israeli nationality, remain in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe3fdbc0-41fb-11f0-941d-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 10:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump orders investigation into alleged cover-up of Biden’s decline</title>
      <description>The unprecedented action accuses Biden aides of concealing what the president claims is his predecessor’s cognitive decline. The order focuses on the use of an autopen to sign hundreds of executive actions and directs White House counsel, with help from Attorney General Pam Bondi, to conduct the investigation.
In a statement Wednesday, the former president dismissed the allegations, saying: “I made the decisions during my presidency. ... Any suggestion that I didn’t is ridiculous and false.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17eb4921-41bf-11f0-b4eb-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 03:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump proclamation tries to restrict foreign students from studying at Harvard</title>
      <description>The president’s action comes days after a federal judge blocked his administration’s attempts to revoke Harvard University’s ability to host foreign students and scholars.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b55fac0-41b2-11f0-b933-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 02:10:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces travel ban on 12 countries in sweeping expansion likely to draw swift legal challenges</title>
      <description>The administration announced the ban, which takes effect June 9, on travelers to the United States from Afghanistan, Burma, Chad, Republic of the Congo, Equatorial Guinea, Eritrea, Haiti, Iran, Libya, Somalia, Sudan and Yemen. There will be restrictions on people entering from Burundi, Cuba, Laos, Sierra Leone, Togo, Turkmenistan and Venezuela. Officials said the order is aimed at bolstering national security. The president had vowed during his campaign to impose an expanded version of the travel ban.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c36de800-41a3-11f0-8edc-0000a1ace231</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defying Trump, National Portrait Gallery Director Kim Sajet is still at work</title>
      <description>The president said he had fired the museum leader — setting up a standoff between the White House and the Smithsonian.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2b132e0-419d-11f0-ada4-000a1ace7223</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 23:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A surprise drone strike devastated Russia’s air force. The U.S. is vulnerable, too.</title>
      <description>The audacious Ukrainian attacks on Russian airfields showed the power of unconventional, asymmetric warfare — and highlight the threat to U.S. strategic bases and ports, experts say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47399450-418f-11f0-afb5-00000a1acefd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 22:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge bars Trump administration from deporting family of Boulder attack suspect</title>
      <description>The development came after lawyers for Mohamed Sabry Soliman’s wife and children filed an emergency petition arguing their detentions were illegal. On Tuesday, the Trump administration announced it had detained the family and would deport them immediately.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32a56000-4185-11f0-941b-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 20:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI arrests man who allegedly shipped explosive material to Palm Springs fertility clinic bomber</title>
      <description>Daniel Park, 32, was arrested at John F. Kennedy International Airport in New York. He allegedly traveled to Palm Springs, California, to meet with Guy Bartkus and help plan Bartkus’s May attack on American Reproductive Centers, which injured four and killed Bartkus in what the FBI labeled an intentional act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cf01071-416a-11f0-b531-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin said he will retaliate against Ukraine for attacks on Russia’s bombers, Trump says</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said on social media that he had a good call with Russian President Vladimir Putin but “not a conversation that will lead to immediate Peace.” Trump said the call included discussion of Ukraine's surprise drone attack on Russia's long-range bombers on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a4f9530-4167-11f0-91ce-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 17:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Retired parent blamed for son’s spiraling marriage and finances</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Retired parent blamed for son’s spiraling marriage and finances</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc797a0-415d-11f0-9e8a-0000a1acecd5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 16:01:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: The chain restaurant our food critic turns to when he’s on the road</title>
      <description>Dining chat: The chain restaurant our food critic turns to when he’s on the road</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df67410-4155-11f0-b8b4-00000a1ace32</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you thought the first nuclear weapons age was scary, buckle up</title>
      <description>Why we should worry about nuclear weapons again</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62651201-4152-11f0-91f2-00000a1ace83</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 14:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Another European election in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d54f2fc0-4149-11f0-aa81-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 13:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edmund White, acclaimed novelist of gay life, dies at 85</title>
      <description>Across a wide-ranging literary career, he also co-wrote a sex manual for gay men and was a Pulitzer finalist for his biography of author Jean Genet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2cc9a30-413b-11f0-b786-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 12:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk vs. Trump. Boulder suspect. New tariffs. Bridge attack. Saharan dust. AI hallucinations. Centuries-old condom. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">101a9340-4133-11f0-84bd-0000a1ace374</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE is taking into custody family of suspect in Colorado attack against Jewish group</title>
      <description>Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem said on X that the agency is investigating “to what extent” Mohamed Sabry Soliman’s family knew about the attack, which is being investigated as a targeted act of terror, and whether they provided any support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18527670-40ae-11f0-8a76-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 19:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk calls Trump’s sweeping legislation ‘pork-filled’ and ‘a disgusting abomination’</title>
      <description>Elon Musk, who recently left his cost-cutting role in President Donald Trump’s administration, issued his strongest condemnation to date of the massive tax and immigration bill making its way through Congress. “Shame on those who voted for it: you know you did wrong,” Must wrote on social media. “You know it.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">291738c0-40a3-11f0-a69f-000a1ace0965</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 17:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sorry, Mother, I like our dog sitter too much to share the number</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sorry, Mother, I like our dog sitter too much to share the number</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cc1b610-4096-11f0-8ae5-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center subscription sales fall 36 percent from a year ago, internal data show</title>
      <description>Sales for ticket packages across all genres are down about $1.6 million compared to the same point in 2024, a window into the arts center’s challenges following President Donald Trump’s takeover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15176e80-4094-11f0-9a85-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 16:01:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Service cancels plan to close Dupont Circle Park during WorldPride festivities this weekend</title>
      <description>A plan to bar people from celebrating Pride in the park at Dupont Circle this weekend has been canceled less than 24 hours after the closing was announced, a D.C. Council member said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9fcfa1c0-4088-11f0-9bdf-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 14:39:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 10th president stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21a4ad30-407f-11f0-a97d-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 13:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea set to elect liberal president, following impeachment of leader who declared martial law</title>
      <description>Exit polls showed that Lee Jae-myung had secured a commanding lead in the election, which comes after former president Yoon Suk Yeol was impeached.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">553a8a20-4070-11f0-93fe-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colorado suspect. Trump’s posting frenzy. Hurricane ‘joke.’ Ukraine talks. Jonathan Joss. Wildfire smoke. Volcano. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e971f9f0-4069-11f0-8369-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 11:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dupont Circle park to close during next weekend’s WorldPride parade and parties, National Park Service says</title>
      <description>A Park Service spokesman said the decision was made at the request of D.C. police "to keep the community and visitors safe and protect one of D.C.’s most treasured public spaces.” The park is at the center of Washington’s historic LGBTQ neighborhood, and disappointed local officials said they weren't consulted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c390520-4021-11f0-b8ca-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 02:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suspect in Colorado attack is charged with a hate crime, accused of planning attack on Jewish group for a year</title>
      <description>Officials filed a hate-crime charge Monday against Mohamed Sabry Soliman, who is accused of attacking an event organized by a Jewish group, just before he was set to appear in court in Boulder, Colorado. Authorities said they are investigating the incident, in which eight people were injured, as a targeted act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be46d961-3fda-11f0-b427-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 17:55:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
