<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 23:04:52 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump is considering an executive order to ‘save TikTok’ from a ban in the U.S., people familiar with the matter say</title>
      <description>The potential executive order would suspend enforcement of the TikTok sale-or-ban law for 60 to 90 days, according to two people familiar with the talks, as President-elect Donald Trump looks to bolster his reputation as a powerful dealmaker. His allies have also floated the idea of reviving Project Texas, the $1.5 billion corporate-reform package that TikTok unsuccessfully offered to the Biden administration in exchange for staying afloat, one of the people said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d0eb8d1-d389-11ef-9c32-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 21:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American hostages will be released in first phase of Gaza ceasefire deal, Biden says</title>
      <description>In remarks from the White House, President Joe Biden announced that U.S. hostages still in Gaza would be returned home during a 42-day ceasefire between Israel and Hamas. Of the seven Americans held captive in the enclave, three are believed to still be alive. Four others have been declared dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1389fb30-d37c-11ef-b3f2-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 20:05:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hamas agree to ceasefire in major breakthrough, including release of Israeli hostages, senior U.S. official says</title>
      <description>The first phase of the agreement brokered by the United States, Qatar and Egypt will halt, for now, a 15-month war that changed the Middle East. It includes plans for a limited withdrawal of Israeli troops from Gaza and a surge in humanitarian aid to the enclave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17f07680-d364-11ef-9fcf-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Retired parents are too reserved to ask for help from nearby family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Retired parents are too reserved to ask for help from nearby family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b19a4d31-d362-11ef-9ff2-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 17:03:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What's next for LeBron James? Kevin Merida dives into the past, present and future of a basketball superstar.</title>
      <description>LeBron James: A sense of where he is</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">220874d0-d362-11ef-bb0b-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: Are branches of famous restaurants as good as the original?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: Are branches of famous restaurants as good as the original?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4038540-d35f-11ef-9e7d-0000a1ace01d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 16:44:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A minister accused of sex abuse landed one high-profile job after another</title>
      <description>Jeff Taylor went from the pulpit to the Red Cross to a college nonprofit. Now, his alleged victims are speaking out, and the FBI is investigating.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c82d00b0-d358-11ef-b06f-0000a1ace17c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:52:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrected link: FDA bans controversial red dye used in bubblegum, candy and fruit cocktail that is linked to cancer in rats</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration's action affects red dye No. 3, which was approved for permanent use more than 50 years ago. Studies have shown high doses could cause cancer in rats, but the agency maintains there is no evidence that ingesting the coloring causes cancer in humans.

A previous alert linked to the wrong story. This alert has been corrected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5ef09e1-d352-11ef-b06f-0000a1ace17c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 15:08:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA bans controversial red dye used in bubblegum, candy and fruit cocktail that is linked to cancer in rats</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration's action affects red dye No. 3, which was approved for permanent use more than 50 years ago. Studies have shown high doses could cause cancer in rats, but the agency maintains there is no evidence that ingesting the coloring causes cancer in humans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1779ba80-d351-11ef-b2f0-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer-only bathrooms in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3af5ecc0-d34e-11ef-a0ca-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:37:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Cabinet picks Pam Bondi and Marco Rubio are on the Hill for confirmation hearings. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Rubio, the senator from Florida and onetime presidential rival to President-elect Donald Trump, has been tapped for secretary of state. Trump selected Bondi, a former state attorney general who served on the defense team for Trump's first impeachment, for attorney general after his initial pick withdrew. Trump's picks for CIA director, transportation secretary, Office of Management and Budget director and energy secretary will also be on the Hill today to answer senators' questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9ffbef0-d34b-11ef-93d8-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:21:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation heated up again in December with prices continuing to weigh on Americans as Trump takes office</title>
      <description>Price increases eased throughout much of 2024, but progress on inflation slowed toward the end of the year, thanks in large part to robust household spending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b4422e1-d345-11ef-b3ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 13:32:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth. Los Angeles fires. Trump’s tariffs. South Korea. Transgender students. Neil Gaiman. Travel tips. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3dc4c631-d338-11ef-9008-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korea’s impeached president has been detained after police executed arrest warrant, prosecutors say</title>
      <description>Yoon Suk Yeol, who is facing insurrection charges after his effort to impose martial law last month, becomes the first South Korean president to be detained while in office. Prosecutors now have 48 hours to formally arrest him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7ef7ec0-d2e5-11ef-b95c-0000a1ace6fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 02:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The SEC sues Elon Musk over late disclosure of Twitter share purchases, citing an underpayment of $150 million</title>
      <description>The Securities and Exchange Commission ordered Musk to pay a civil penalty and other remedies over what the regulator alleged was an act of “unjust enrichment.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cfcf280-d2d4-11ef-9008-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden establishes new national monuments in California, making more than 850,000 acres off limits to development</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden signed proclamations Tuesday creating the 624,000-acre Chuckwalla National Monument and the 224,000-acre Sáttítla Highlands National Monument. The move bans oil and gas drilling, mining and other industrial activities on these vast swaths of public land, which several Native American tribes have considered sacred for thousands of years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b505c720-d2d0-11ef-95ef-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 23:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth faced Democrats’ ire over his views on women in combat, and claims of sexual assault and excessive drinking</title>
      <description>Senate Democrats on Tuesday hammered Hegseth, President-elect Donald Trump’s pick for defense secretary, in an early test of Republican loyalty as lawmakers take up the incoming administration’s slate of unconventional and contentious Cabinet picks. The hearing quickly became a heated, rhetorical battle along partisan lines — marked at times by raised voices.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3a86e1-d2c3-11ef-aa34-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 22:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is lifting Cuba’s state sponsor of terrorism designation, just days before leaving the White House</title>
      <description>The Cuban government is expected to free “a significant number of political prisoners” under an agreement it has made with the Catholic church, according to a senior Biden administration official.

The incoming Trump administration is almost certain to reverse the lifting of the terrorism designation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3531b40-d2b4-11ef-94b2-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 20:19:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes bill banning transgender students from women’s sports teams. Its fate in the Senate is unclear.</title>
      <description>Republicans, who elevated the issue as one of their 2025 priorities, argued that the legislation would protect girls and women from unfair competition and guard against safety concerns. Democrats called the measure a harmful and impractical distraction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaed3a22-d2b2-11ef-9e93-0000a1ace6b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 20:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six takeaways from the Trump Jan. 6 report by special counsel Jack Smith</title>
      <description>Smith’s report on Donald Trump’s alleged attempts to subvert the results of the 2020 election argues that Trump would have been convicted at trial and gives new insights into the investigative process. Here’s what we learned.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">749883c0-d29f-11ef-a99a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Unsure how to respond to the death of ‘hateful bigot’ dad</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Unsure how to respond to the death of ‘hateful bigot’ dad</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2236a311-d299-11ef-9e5d-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Can the Commanders keep up this winning streak against the top-seeded Lions? Our reporters take your questions.</title>
      <description>The Commanders keep winning — dramatically — and find themselves in the NFC divisional round against the Detroit Lions. Beating the Buccaneers in the first round was impressive, but the Lions (15-2) will offer another level of competition. Sports columnist Barry Svrluga and Commanders beat writers Nicki Jhabvala and Sam Fortier are answering your questions about the team and their playoff matchup.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b4bb4f40-d291-11ef-8135-00000a1ace73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 16:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pete Hegseth, Trump’s controversial pick to lead the Pentagon, faces a tough Senate confirmation hearing. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The former Fox News host tapped by President-elect Donald Trump to become defense secretary is expected to face questions about allegations of sexual assault, excessive drinking and sexism — allegations he’s denied. Senators are also likely to ask questions about his long history of public commentary deriding minorities and people with opposing political views.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02b3f980-d284-11ef-a441-0000a1ace9f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 14:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump report. Los Angeles fires. Pete Hegseth hearing. Ceasefire talks. AI arrests. Dementia risk. Cellphone ban. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11f3ae00-d26f-11ef-9569-0000a1ace1f9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 11:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump would have been convicted in D.C. if he wasn’t elected, special counsel Jack Smith says in report</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump tried to block the release of Smith’s report on his federal investigation of Trump’s alleged efforts to overturn Joe Biden’s 2020 election victory. The case was dismissed after Trump was elected in November, because Justice Department policy prohibits prosecuting a sitting president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">557d0770-d23d-11ef-a8c2-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 06:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel defends Hunter Biden prosecution, chides President Biden for questioning investigation</title>
      <description>The special counsel who investigated President Joe Biden’s son Hunter defended his prosecution on gun and tax charges in a report released Monday, pushing back on claims by the president and his family that the cases were politically motivated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2537cd1-d203-11ef-bfb6-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 23:10:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police use facial recognition as it was never intended: As a shortcut to finding and arresting suspects without further evidence</title>
      <description>Confident in unproven facial recognition technology, sometimes investigators skip steps, and at least eight Americans have been wrongfully arrested, a Washington Post investigation found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31d87301-d1fb-11ef-8290-0000a1ace5f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 22:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 in 5 U.S. adults are likely to develop some form of dementia after age 55, a sobering new study finds</title>
      <description>A study published Monday in the journal Nature Medicine projects that the risk people face over their lifetime of developing the memory-robbing condition is higher than some previous estimates. The new analysis is based on decades of close follow-up, including regular cognitive assessments, of a racially diverse group of people — a quarter of whom were Black and face an increased risk of dementia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">932ddea0-d1d9-11ef-8290-0000a1ace5f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 18:09:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Will rewards entice a traumatized kid to reengage with school?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Will rewards entice a traumatized kid to reengage with school?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fd35100-d1d0-11ef-9d5a-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 17:02:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How New Orleans failed to protect Bourbon Street from the deadly New Year’s truck attack, block by block</title>
      <description>A poorly positioned police SUV and a plan that called for only a single anti-vehicle barrier on the street that night were among the failures that allowed an ISIS-inspired attacker to drive a truck down the pedestrian thoroughfare in the early hours of Jan. 1, killing 14 people and injuring dozens, according to a Washington Post examination.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b8ef0d0-d1cd-11ef-b83f-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 16:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Albuquerque home is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b940dca0-d1bb-11ef-b2f8-00000a1ace20</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 14:36:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles fires. Trump inauguration. Ceasefire talks. TikTok ban. Pain pill. NFL playoffs. Bat surfing. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ebe0ec11-d1a5-11ef-9db6-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders beat Buccaneers in Jayden Daniels’s NFL playoff debut</title>
      <description>Washington won, 23-20, on Sunday night in Tampa and will play at the Detroit Lions in the second round next weekend. It is Washington’s first postseason victory since 2006 and continues a breakout season for the franchise and its rookie quarterback.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f762f5c0-d163-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 04:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Landlords are accused of colluding to raise rents. See whether this is happening near you.</title>
      <description>Millions of rents across the country may now be set using one company’s algorithmic software, according to a federal lawsuit and a Washington Post analysis. RealPage, a property management software company, uses a trove of data to suggest rental prices to landlords. The software has been widely adopted by property managers — and is now facing strenuous legal pushback. Look at just how widespread its use may be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c7383970-d134-11ef-856a-00000a1ace02</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 22:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: We moved to the suburbs, and I’m miserable. I blame my husband.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: We moved to the suburbs, and I’m miserable. I blame my husband.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9d15d50-d119-11ef-b5f4-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 19:18:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">910dc630-d107-11ef-aea7-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 17:06:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What makes Commanders wide receiver Terry McLaurin great? See for yourself.</title>
      <description>Washington’s star, who will appear in his second career playoff game Sunday night against the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, is elite at ball-tracking, a skill that is difficult — but not impossible — to measure.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e56efa50-d102-11ef-8ac7-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 16:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streets turned to ash: Before and after the Los Angeles fires, in photos and videos</title>
      <description>Multiple wildfires have devoured neighborhoods in Los Angeles. Here’s what some of these areas looked like before the catastrophic blazes — and what they look like now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75cc7630-d0fa-11ef-bb65-0000a1acef0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d94f18b1-d0f1-11ef-b8e6-0000a1ace658</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 14:31:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Smith, the special counsel named to oversee the federal cases against Donald Trump, resigns from the Justice Department</title>
      <description>The news came in a footnote of a court filing. Smith spent the last two months winding down the two federal criminal prosecutions of Trump and said he would resign before Inauguration Day.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e677bb31-d067-11ef-8678-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 22:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Largest of L.A. fires is creeping closer to the 405 freeway, triggering a new wave of alarm as flames spread. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>When flames from the Palisades Fire appeared to spread east to Mandeville Canyon, locals knew that meant the blaze was creeping closer to Interstate 405, near a busy mountain pass.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4dc94760-d05c-11ef-a58a-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 20:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The original, science‑backed 7‑minute workout to get fit fast</title>
      <description>Research shows this simple routine can rapidly improve endurance and health — no gym required. The workout features 30 seconds of familiar calisthenics — exercises that use your own body weight, such as jumping jacks and push-ups — capped with five seconds of rest. Each calisthenic exercise should be somewhat challenging, said Chris Jordan, the exercise physiologist who developed the workout, feeling like “about an eight on a scale of effort from one to 10.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5be5f750-d055-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 19:50:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See how a small fire in L.A. turned into a monster, hour by hour</title>
      <description>As winds near Pacific Palisades approached extreme levels, the first signs emerged of a fire that would later grow out of control. Videos and images taken by residents and area-camera networks show how each hour after that, the blaze grew stronger, spreading from hilltops and eventually through a densely populated and beloved community. In the coming days, the fire’s sheer devastation would become clearer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">879b5160-d032-11ef-8259-0000a1acedb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 15:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d70a2411-d028-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 14:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine captured two North Korean soldiers in Russia, Zelensky says, in move that could shed light on Pyongyang’s role in the war</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s announcement marks Ukraine's first confirmation it has detained North Korean troops since they were deployed late last year. He said that capturing them alive “was not an easy task.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eef8a8f0-d01c-11ef-9043-0000a1ace65b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 13:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Significant’ flare-up of Palisades Fire prompts expansion of evacuation orders in Los Angeles</title>
      <description>The upgraded orders now cover much of the Brentwood neighborhood. The Getty museum, a Los Angeles landmark, is in the area affected by the orders. A Cal Fire spokesperson said the flare-up is a “significant development” and that the Palisades Fire — which has burned more than 21,000 acres — is growing “really, really fast.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5282ae01-cfde-11ef-8abc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 05:38:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The death toll in the California fires rises to 11 people. Gov. Newsom launches a water supply investigation. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>As firefighters battle six blazes, California Gov. Gavin Newsom has launched a probe of lost water supply and pressure in Los Angeles’s municipal water systems during the fires.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ca87e51-cfa9-11ef-b1f0-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 23:20:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden shields nearly 1 million immigrants from Venezuela, El Salvador, Ukraine and Sudan from deportation for 18 months</title>
      <description>The Biden administration on Friday extended temporary humanitarian protections for nearly 1 million immigrants living in the United States, announcing the move days before the start of a possible deportation campaign by the incoming Trump administration. Advocates had been urging the Department of Homeland Security to extend the protected designation for these nationalities and others under a 1990 law that shields immigrants from being deported to countries engulfed in conflict or natural disasters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b56482a0-cf93-11ef-84cb-00000a1ace25</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 20:44:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We don’t cry — yet’: A Pacific Palisades native on what has been lost</title>
      <description>"The Pacific Palisades was a village, my village — and now it’s gone," E.A. Hanks writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de428ce0-cf88-11ef-8d93-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:27:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Winter weather advisory for light snow issued for D.C. area</title>
      <description>Snow is expected to move into the area around 10 p.m. Friday and continue into early Saturday morning. One to two inches could fall, causing slippery roads.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f1fff91-cf85-11ef-8b92-00000a1ace53</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 18:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
