<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 17:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Why not use bagged shredded cheese in recipes? We’re answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89f20890-6ada-11ef-a089-0000a1aceb59</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Imbalance in visits with in-laws vs. parents starts to chafe</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6820140-6ad6-11ef-a0b7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 16:01:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta’s oversight body says ‘from the river to the sea’ isn’t necessarily hate speech, a decision likely to fuel Israel-Gaza debates</title>
      <description>The company-funded oversight body ruled the social media giant shouldn’t automatically take down posts using the phrase, a decades-old rallying cry for Palestinian nationalism that has reignited debate about the boundaries of acceptable speech. The clash has forced the company to closely examine its content rules amid scrutiny from Jewish groups that have accused it of allowing antisemitism to surge and criticism from pro-Palestinian groups, which argue Meta has stifled political critique amid a deadly war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">201ec341-6ad5-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 15:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It was pitched as ‘an extraordinary opportunity’ to protect the planet and people. The Post found deep failures.</title>
      <description>C-Quest Capital said its stoves could improve people’s lives and reduce carbon emissions. But an investigation by The Washington Post in Mozambique reveals that the company promised more than it could deliver — a further hit to a troubled offsets market used by BP, Shell and other major corporations to meet their climate goals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc82a752-6ac7-11ef-91bb-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 14:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An unsettling new milestone for this city in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ceb86c81-6ac1-11ef-a59a-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russian strike. Trump vs. Harris. Gaza talks. School cop. Landslides. Cellphone study. Titanic. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca02062-6aac-11ef-882a-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian Foreign Minister Dmytro Kuleba resigns amid government shake-up</title>
      <description>Kuleba’s exit follows those of other high-ranking officials in Ukraine this week. Kuleba, who has been in the role since 2020, has been a key voice in Ukraine’s drive to receive foreign weapons and to push allies to loosen restrictions on how they are used.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">413b7d20-6a8f-11ef-8149-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2024 07:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A louder voice in fighting abortion bans: Men in red states</title>
      <description>Two years after the Supreme Court overturned federal protections for abortion, growing numbers of men in deeply conservative states are speaking out in defense of reproductive rights because of the harrowing experiences they’ve seen wives or partners go through when pregnancies went tragically awry.

They have an integral role in the debate, a legal expert says: “Men telling their own stories … is going to be a big way to change hearts and minds.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a68d420-6a42-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 22:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. charges Hamas leaders with terrorism, citing Oct. 7 attack, and is investigating killing of Hersh Goldberg-Polin</title>
      <description>Attorney General Merrick Garland stressed that Hamas was responsible for the Oct. 7 deaths in southern Israel and said the United States will investigate the killing of Goldberg-Polin, 23, whose body was found in Gaza last week, as an act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5e906f1-6a3e-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A school resource officer admitted to sexually abusing two students. A South Carolina judge just sentenced him to probation.</title>
      <description>Richland County Sheriff's Deputy Jamel Bradley kept his job for years despite multiple complaints of sexual misconduct with teen girls, a Washington Post investigation found. The judge ordered Bradley to register as a sex offender, against the recommendation of prosecutors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">783b3240-6a2e-11ef-8990-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 19:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Wife ‘ticks every box,’ but newlywed wants out of their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab9fcb30-6a0d-11ef-8557-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Opinions asked seven writers to find an amazing story from deep within government. First up, Michael Lewis’s discovery.</title>
      <description>The 2024 conversation has been driven by a handful of names. Trump. Harris. Biden. Vance. Walz. These individuals have put themselves forward to lead our government. But who really is our government? What is it made of? And what is at stake when politicians say they want to expand or dismantle it? To find out, we set seven stellar writers loose on the federal bureaucracy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7677a8c0-6a0c-11ef-aef7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:52:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Post investigation into Xi’s visit to San Francisco reveals how China extended its repression into a U.S. city</title>
      <description>Chinese diplomats and pro-China diaspora groups based in the United States organized demonstrations in San Francisco that harassed and silenced protesters opposed to Beijing’s policies, including through violence, during Chinese leader Xi Jinping’s visit to the city in November.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e85495e0-69fb-11ef-a90d-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new take on a head-scratching story in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b11935c0-69f8-11ef-aebd-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 13:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukrainian president says at least 41 people killed in Russian missile strike at the Communications Institute in Poltava</title>
      <description>President Volodymyr Zelensky said 180 people were injured when two ballistic missiles struck. The Defense Ministry said the time between the alarm and the impact was so short that many people were caught trying to reach shelters and were trapped under the rubble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2987d1e1-69ec-11ef-8fde-0000a1ace008</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 12:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris-Biden rally. Israel protests. Seized plane. China crackdown. Coronavirus shots. ‘Spy’ whale. Paralympics. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf413f0-69e3-11ef-bbf2-000a1acef238</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your ride is here. Take a trip with Uber driver Jon Rigsby in this comic from the Shifts series.</title>
      <description>The loneliness of the short-distance driver</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a84d3320-6970-11ef-aa6e-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 21:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Trump helped spark a culture war with his 1776 Commission on patriotism</title>
      <description>In his final months in office, President Donald Trump’s aides resisted as the president sought to ban the New York Times’ 1619 Project from the nation’s classrooms. Instead, he created a new commission on patriotism – and launched a culture debate that would reenergize his base after he left office. The little-noticed episode helps explain how Trump might view education if reelected.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35dc1190-695b-11ef-a4cc-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 18:43:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband declares daughter, 15, will ‘always be an underachiever’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband declares daughter, 15, will ‘always be an underachiever’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cfc0e60-6946-11ef-9f43-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 16:14:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crash of ‘dark’ tanker exposes the dangers of China’s thirst for cheap oil</title>
      <description>To bypass Western financial systems and shipping services, China relies on a fleet of aging, substandard tankers that operate illicitly, analysts say. The ships pose major safety threats and have alarmed global shipping groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab0f44b0-6941-11ef-be82-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 15:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A school cop was repeatedly accused of sexual misconduct with female students. He kept his job for years.</title>
      <description>In South Carolina, Richland County Sheriff’s Deputy Jamel Bradley continued working as a school resource officer despite multiple complaints that he was preying on teenage girls at Spring Valley High. Bradley, a former college basketball star, is now facing sex crime charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac8e32a0-6938-11ef-9f43-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 14:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origins of Labor Day in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c0f1870-692f-11ef-916c-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 13:27:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hostage deaths. Trump vs. Harris. Far-right victory. Hotel strike. Elon Musk. Hot summer. Cash incentive. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77dca5f0-691a-11ef-9bdb-0000a1acef07</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 10:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S., with Qatar and Egypt, preparing final ‘take it or leave it’ deal between Israel and Hamas</title>
      <description>The effort was underway before Israeli officials discovered the bodies of six hostages. But U.S. officials said the discovery adds new urgency to striking a deal, and that if Israel and Hamas do not agree to their final proposal it could mark the end of American-led negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb9eaf50-68ab-11ef-bc44-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 21:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What it’s really like to take the train from California to New York</title>
      <description>This summer, comic artist Christine Mi rode two Amtrak trains across 12 states and 3,397 miles, meandering her way alongside deserts, forests, mountains, rivers; through coal plants, suburban backyards, vast cornfields, and the occasional Big American City. See her illustrated Amtrak journey.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a7892a0-6895-11ef-999d-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 19:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protesters flood the streets of Israel, labor union announces general strike after recovery of six dead hostages in Gaza</title>
      <description>Families of hostages and their supporters are trying to pressure Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to agree to a deal with Hamas to bring home the remaining captives. The six hostages recovered by the military Saturday, including Israeli American Hersh Goldberg-Polin, were killed by their captors shortly before troops found them, Israel’s Health Ministry said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5d228b0-687f-11ef-b5db-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 16:32:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9ce05b70-687b-11ef-8f1c-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 16:02:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you spend money like a Gen Z-er, millennial or boomer? Take our quiz to see which generation you align most with.</title>
      <description>Your spending says a lot about your income bracket and whether you have kids. But there are also generational influences — and a growing gap between how older and younger generations spend money. Take this quiz to find out if you spend money more like an 18-year-old, a 78-year-old or somewhere in between.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">596f9c40-686f-11ef-9261-0000a1acec99</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 14:34:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbbc36f1-6865-11ef-9489-0000a1aceb06</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 13:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mass polio vaccinations begin in Gaza amid limited pauses in fighting, U.N. says</title>
      <description>The campaign to vaccinate more than 600,000 children against polio began in Gaza on Sunday, the U.N. agency for Palestinian refugees and the World Health Organization said. Israel said it would allow a "humanitarian corridor" for vaccination personnel and designate safe areas for administering the shots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af74f960-683c-11ef-87d6-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 08:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli American hostage Hersh Goldberg-Polin confirmed dead by family and White House</title>
      <description>The family of Hersh Goldberg-Polin, 23, who was kidnapped by Hamas on Oct. 7, said he had been killed. Their statement came after the Israeli military announced it had located a number of dead bodies in Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27b9bdd0-6819-11ef-8aff-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 04:17:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scientists are finding biases built into the Marshmallow Test and other common predictors of children’s success</title>
      <description>Developmental psychology aims to elucidate the “universals” in how the human mind develops but has often gleaned those insights by studying White, middle-class children from Western countries. So, if a child from a poor family or different culture doesn’t perform well, is the fault in the child or the test?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">906ec7e0-67dc-11ef-adb2-00000a1ace17</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 21:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sexual harassment scandal dogged Corey Lewandowski. Now he’s officially back in Donald Trump’s fold.</title>
      <description>Lewandowski, Trump’s first 2016 campaign manager, was reported to the police by three women who alleged unwanted physical contact, including a GOP donor in 2021 whose claims led Trump to call her directly, she said. Trump’s decision to bring back Lewandowski this month as a senior adviser shows his high tolerance for allies with political liabilities as long as they remain loyal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d41ec1-67b7-11ef-8d9e-0000a1ace01f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My dad says my brother gets the family estate because of ‘tradition’</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My dad says my brother gets the family estate because of ‘tradition’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d61143b0-67b2-11ef-b4f0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 16:05:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A reporter detailed tennis star Alexander Zverev’s alleged abuse of women — and is paying for it</title>
      <description>Accusations of emotional and physical abuse by Zverev — which he has repeatedly denied — cast a shadow over his ascent. But the resulting stories may have created more troubles for their writer, Ben Rothenberg, as he grapples with a costly lawsuit.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5bb8750-67a5-11ef-b4f0-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 14:31:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e974e80-679d-11ef-8c6e-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 13:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he opposes Fla. amendment granting right to abortion, one day after his confusing comments angered anti-abortion forces</title>
      <description>In an interview Friday, the GOP presidential nominee said he would vote no on the ballot initiative that would make abortion legal until a fetus becomes viable. A day earlier, he slammed Florida’s six-week abortion ban as too restrictive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0995c882-6715-11ef-9789-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 21:15:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge orders suspension of social media platform X in Brazil in battle over disinformation</title>
      <description>The order is a dramatic escalation in a months-long dispute between platform owner Elon Musk and Brazilian jurists over the limits of freedom of speech. The ruling came days after Musk declined to comply with a request that X reestablish a physical presence in the country. Justice Alexandre de Moraes says X needs a representative in Brazil to respond to government requests to suspend accounts found to be spreading fake news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbca6de1-6710-11ef-9963-0000a1ace913</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 20:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: Relative polices what everyone eats at family gatherings</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax is taking your questions now: Relative polices what everyone eats at family gatherings</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">abfa6c60-66ee-11ef-8926-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 16:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The completely legal reason some disabled U.S. workers are paid just pennies per hour</title>
      <description>A long-standing government program is supposed to prepare disabled workers for higher-paying jobs in the community. But many workers are paid low wages for years under a tangled bureaucracy that lacks accountability and oversight, a Washington Post investigation has found.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea736d90-66e2-11ef-86b1-0000a1ace305</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 15:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Md. Supreme Court upholds decision to reinstate ‘Serial’ subject Adnan Syed’s conviction but says case should return to lower court</title>
      <description>Today’s decision is not the end of the road for Syed. The state’s top court said the case should be sent back to a lower court to hold a new hearing on whether the case should be thrown out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2192fec0-66da-11ef-ab8b-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 14:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83b82cc1-66d4-11ef-8926-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 13:33:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: In CNN interview, Kamala Harris addressed position changes, walked fine line as a ‘change’ candidate, and other takeaways</title>
      <description>The interview was much anticipated, given that the vice president has yet to lay out an extensive policy agenda and given the dearth of questions she has answered during her five-plus weeks as the Democratic standard-bearer.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dff2f2d1-66cb-11ef-9a80-0000a1ace747</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 12:32:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Johnny Gaudreau, the dynamic NHL star known as ‘Johnny Hockey,’ dies at 31, his team confirms in a statement without citing a cause</title>
      <description>Gaudreau played left wing for the Columbus Blue Jackets, who on Friday morning released a statement confirming his death. Drafted by the Calgary Flames in 2011, the New Jersey native became one of the league’s more popular players thanks to a scoring prowess and flashy offensive style that belied his diminutive size. Gaudreau’s brother also died in the incident, the Blue Jackets said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ef8d840-66c7-11ef-8926-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:58:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris’s interview. Trump campaign. FBI problems. Polio vaccinations. Covid risk. College football. Chatty monkeys. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">013e9500-66bf-11ef-b9cd-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris pledges to name a Republican to her Cabinet if elected in her first major interview since Biden dropped out of the race</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris said such a move would reflect her interest in a variety of views.

“I have spent my career inviting diversity of opinion,” Harris told CNN in an early excerpt of an interview that was set to air in full later Thursday night. “I think it’s important to have people at the table when some of the most important decisions are being made that have different views, different experiences.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b24fb40-6650-11ef-b96c-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 21:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm and flood watches are in effect for large parts of the area into tonight</title>
      <description>Storms could produce damaging wind gusts, hail and areas of flooding. The severe thunderstorm watch covers much of the area, while the risk of flooding is highest west of Fairfax and Montgomery counties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ecdaae0-6643-11ef-8116-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 20:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Divorce complicates kids’ visits to their dying grandfather</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Divorce complicates kids’ visits to their dying grandfather</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0273b9e0-6620-11ef-9bb0-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 16:01:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army defends Arlington National Cemetery staffer who it says was ‘abruptly pushed aside’ by Trump campaign aides</title>
      <description>In a statement Thursday, Army officials said the employee “acted with professionalism” when she sought to enforce regulations that prohibit partisan political activity on cemetery grounds. The employee has decided not to press charges, Army officials said.

The former president was at the cemetery to mark the third anniversary of a suicide bombing that killed 13 U.S. troops in Afghanistan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f2b4970-661d-11ef-b69f-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years after Larry Nassar scandal, FBI is still falling short at handling child sex abuse cases, internal Justice Dept. report finds</title>
      <description>A new inspector general report found the FBI still often fails to quickly notify local authorities about alleged sexual abuse cases in their jurisdictions. In one especially egregious example, a suspect allegedly victimized another minor for 15 months after the FBI became aware of the allegations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98b2cb70-6617-11ef-a0db-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 15:01:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
