<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 21:03:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What if all you had to do was ask? Ask The Post AI delivers you AI-generated summaries from published Washington Post reporting.</title>
      <description>What if all you had to do was ask? Ask The Post AI delivers you AI-generated summaries from published Washington Post reporting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d3c7f20-a2ba-11ef-b00a-0000a1ace3fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 18:55:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband refuses to tell spouse why he’s unhappy in their marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband refuses to tell spouse why he’s unhappy in their marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc9ee820-a2a9-11ef-97ee-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 17:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A small-town police chief was accused of paying $100 to rape a teen — then using his connections to try to cover it up</title>
      <description>In the tiny West Virginia town of Gauley Bridge, Police Chief Larry Clay Jr. “was the law.” Then a teenager reported that she’d been sex trafficked by her stepmother when she was 17 years old. The buyer, she told investigators, wasn’t just anyone — it was Larry Clay. Would a jury believe her?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5962030-a299-11ef-8248-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 15:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A controversial lunch item is removed from schools in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1158e500-a295-11ef-986d-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 14:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Satirical news outlet the Onion wins auction to control Infowars, the far-right site founded by conspiracy theorist Alex Jones</title>
      <description>Jones was forced to sell Infowars and other personal assets in a court-ordered auction to pay the roughly $1.5 billion in damages he owes for claiming the Sandy Hook Elementary School shooting was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd145a40-a291-11ef-bf06-0000a1ace574</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 14:07:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz. House control. Trump and Biden. Cease-fire plan. Developing storm. Loneliness risk. Cancer experiment. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7f79940-a27f-11ef-bdb4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans are projected to retain a slim House majority, giving the GOP full control of Congress and the White House</title>
      <description>Republicans will remain the majority party in Congress’s lower chamber, the Associated Press reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09611e50-a239-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 03:32:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden endorses controversial road through wildlife refuge in Alaska</title>
      <description>The Interior Department recommended Wednesday a land-swap deal that could allow a road to be built through the Izembek National Wildlife Refuge. Supporters of the road say it could save lives. Opponents say it could undermine President Joe Biden’s environmental legacy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95f8280-a210-11ef-9f51-00000a1aceb1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 22:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netanyahu readying Lebanon cease-fire proposal as ‘gift’ to Trump after election victory, Israeli officials say</title>
      <description>An Israeli minister discussed the plan with Trump and Jared Kushner at Mar-a-Lago on Sunday, three current and former Israeli officials told The Washington Post, hoping to deliver an early foreign policy win to the president-elect, who campaigned on ending the wars in the Middle East. But the evolving proposal has yet to be presented to Hezbollah and could face resistance in Lebanon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">138fc7d0-a209-11ef-a744-0000a1ace931</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:48:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will nominate Rep. Matt Gaetz as attorney general and Tulsi Gabbard as director of national intelligence</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump announced plans Wednesday to nominate Gaetz (R-Florida) and Gabbard, a former Democratic congresswoman from Hawaii, to the respective posts.

Trump also confirmed he will nominate Sen. Marco Rubio (R-Florida) as secretary of state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79a25971-a1ff-11ef-9762-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>San Antonio Spurs Coach Gregg Popovich suffered a mild stroke earlier this month, the team announced</title>
      <description>The 75-year-old Popovich, a Hall of Famer and the winningest coach in NBA history, has been away from the team since Nov. 2, when he suffered what the Spurs originally referred to as a medical incident.

The Spurs said Popovich has begun a rehabilitation program and is expected to make a full recovery, but it is unclear when he will return to the sideline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6caf90-a1f1-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 19:01:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Republicans choose John Thune to replace Mitch McConnell as majority leader</title>
      <description>The leadership race, like much else, became a proxy battle over Republicans’ fealty to the president-elect.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a71a8a70-a1e2-11ef-805e-0000a1ace245</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is 15 diners, 11 dogs and seating for 4 a Thanksgiving math fiasco?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is 15 diners, 11 dogs and seating for 4 a Thanksgiving math fiasco?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27d74e71-a1e1-11ef-8faa-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 17:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump pledges smooth transition as he meets with Biden at White House</title>
      <description>During a cordial Oval Office meeting, President-elect Donald Trump said that “politics is tough,” but pledged a transition “as smooth as it can get.” In 2020, Trump did not invite Joe Biden to the White House after Biden won the election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59f8c7f1-a1df-11ef-ab5f-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 16:50:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re tracking Trump’s picks for his Cabinet and administration: Pete Hegseth, Kristi Noem and more</title>
      <description>Here are the people President-elect Donald Trump has picked or is considering to fill top positions in his incoming administration, based on our reporting.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">842412b0-a1d4-11ef-a380-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The world knows where the sun is‘ in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fac19b81-a1cb-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation picked up in October, as Americans prepared to vote on the economy</title>
      <description>Price increases have slowed significantly this year, but they weighed heavily on Americans who voted against incumbents in the November elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d01e5c40-a1c3-11ef-84d6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 13:33:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk. Trump’s return. Israel deadline. Discord leaks. Bird flu. Snow forecast. Lost luggage. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ccee64f0-a1b6-11ef-9747-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 11:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump says Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy will run ‘government efficiency’ commission</title>
      <description>The president-elect said his billionaire ally and his former Republican primary rival would lead an external entity — what Trump called the “Department of Government Efficiency” — to come up with plans to slash regulations and waste and “restructure” federal agencies. It is not clear how such an effort would be funded or run because governmental spending decisions are up to Congress and the president, not outside groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0d4aba1-a15b-11ef-9747-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 01:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump taps Pete Hegseth, an Army veteran and Fox News host, to be defense secretary</title>
      <description>Hegseth, who is a co-host on the weekend edition of "Fox &amp; Friends," has criticized the Biden administration’s approach to national security as weak and wrote a book describing the military’s leadership as more focused on diversity than confronting global threats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">697a8030-a156-11ef-a85e-0000a1ace00f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 00:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump says John Ratcliffe is his nominee to become CIA director</title>
      <description>Ratcliffe, a former congressman from Texas, served as the director of national intelligence toward the end of Trump's first administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc4eba70-a14b-11ef-b6bd-0000a1aceb7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 23:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discord leaker Jack Teixeira sentenced to 15 years in prison for massive disclosure of U.S. secrets</title>
      <description>Teixeira was a member of the Massachusetts Air National Guard when he smuggled out images of hundreds of classified documents and posted them on Discord, a chat platform popular with video gamers. Those materials revealed government assessments of the war in Ukraine, plotting by terrorist groups and espionage efforts by China. His case shook the U.S. national security establishment, revealing the speed and ease with which top-secret materials can spread online, and upset Washington’s relationships with several international partners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b32789f0-a13b-11ef-95f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 21:18:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA bans U.S. flights to Haiti for 30 days after Spirit plane was damaged by gunfire at Port-au-Prince airport</title>
      <description>The gunfire that struck Spirit Airlines Flight 951 on Monday came against a backdrop of political unrest and gang violence in Haiti after Prime Minister Garry Conille was fired over the weekend and replaced with Alix Didier Fils-Aimé.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62d29f00-a12f-11ef-bb0a-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 19:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he will nominate Mike Huckabee, the former governor of Arkansas, as ambassador to Israel</title>
      <description>Huckabee served as Arkansas governor from 1996 to 2007 and has remained active in politics since then, running for president in both 2008 and 2016. He is an ordained Southern Baptist pastor. Huckabee’s daughter, Sarah Huckabee Sanders, was White House press secretary during Donald Trump’s first term and now serves as Arkansas governor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39628130-a12a-11ef-98ff-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 19:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Friend pins hopes on big family trip with teens who don’t get along</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Friend pins hopes on big family trip with teens who don’t get along</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d096a80-a11b-11ef-95f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:25:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jury says defense contractor must pay $42 million over Abu Ghraib abuses</title>
      <description>A federal jury found that a Virginia-based defense contractor shared responsibility with the U.S. Army for abusing detainees at Abu Ghraib prison, awarding damages to three Iraqi men who said they were tortured there two decades ago. The verdict against CACI International marks the first time a civilian contractor has been held legally responsible for the inhumane treatment of detainees at the prison west of Baghdad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf879bf0-a117-11ef-b8d7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 17:01:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. gave Israel 30 days to surge aid to Gaza. The humanitarian situation there has only gotten worse, a Post analysis finds.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post analysis based on more than a dozen interviews with aid workers and officials found Israel has largely failed to comply with American demands outlined in an Oct. 13 letter, as humanitarian groups warn that parts of northern Gaza are edging closer to famine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d5dbed0-a110-11ef-b5fb-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 16:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Immunity decision for Trump’s New York conviction delayed as prosecutors weigh impact of presidential election</title>
      <description>The judge overseeing President-elect Donald Trump’s hush money trial did not issue a ruling as expected on whether the felony convictions should be dismissed. Instead, he set a deadline next week for prosecutors to determine how to proceed after Trump’s reelection as president. The delay further throws into question whether Trump will be sentenced as scheduled on Nov. 26.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">183b4900-a10d-11ef-8731-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 15:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Archbishop of Canterbury resigns over handling of Church of England abuse scandal</title>
      <description>Justin Welby stepped down after mounting pressure over his handling of allegations against John Smyth, a serial abuser who subjected boys at Christian camps in Britain and Africa to “traumatic physical, sexual, psychological and spiritual attacks,” a report found last week. Welby said the report exposed the Church of England’s “long-maintained conspiracy of silence” about Smyth’s abuses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">25800820-a109-11ef-800b-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 15:16:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Levi Strauss heir and newly elected mayor is the star of today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9de63110-a102-11ef-87bd-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 14:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Gov. Kristi Noem of South Dakota to serve as homeland security secretary, people familiar say</title>
      <description>Noem has served as South Dakota governor since 2019. Her choice as homeland security secretary was confirmed by people familiar with the selection who requested anonymity to discuss a decision not yet made public. Noem would lead a sprawling federal bureaucracy with a $60 billion budget and more than 230,000 employees. The role is key to President-elect Donald Trump’s domestic policy agenda, especially given his pledge to deport millions of undocumented immigrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">357c54e2-a0ff-11ef-9ecc-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 14:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s team. Final Senate call. Israel’s plans. Abortion pills. Brewing storm. Sunken ship. Uranus. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6a92150-a0ed-11ef-ad81-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Ruben Gallego (D) is projected to win Senate race in Arizona, defeating Trump-allied election denier Kari Lake (R)</title>
      <description>Gallego defeated Lake for the seat of retiring Sen. Kyrsten Sinema (I), according to the Associated Press. Gallego had been leading the Senate race for much of the contest, according to the polls. Lake, a former local TV news anchor and staunch supporter of Donald Trump, refused to concede she lost the 2022 gubernatorial race.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b224be31-a0b2-11ef-9063-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 04:58:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Rep. Michael Waltz (R-Fla.) to be his national security adviser</title>
      <description>Waltz is a retired Army colonel who has been a forceful critic of President Joe Biden’s foreign policy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c16015a0-a08c-11ef-962b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming of a move abroad? Here’s what it takes to immigrate to these 5 countries.</title>
      <description>Shortly after Donald Trump won the presidential election, searches for “move abroad” began surging in the United States. But if you’re serious about leaving the country, you’d better do your homework.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb5de10-a080-11ef-9624-000a1ace7ddf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 22:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taps former GOP congressman Lee Zeldin to head the EPA as he vows to push for environmental deregulation</title>
      <description>During his time in Congress, Zeldin sought to protect the Long Island Sound from dredge sediment dumping. But he largely opposed environment bills and has a lifetime score of 14 percent by the League of Conservation Voters, an environmental group.

In his announcement, Donald Trump said that Zeldin “will ensure fair and swift deregulatory decisions” to “unleash” American businesses “while at the same time maintaining the highest environmental standards.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8371160-a071-11ef-9063-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 21:12:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it unfair for spouses to vent to friends about their marriage?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it unfair for spouses to vent to friends about their marriage?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ca69581-a04e-11ef-b44e-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 17:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he would ‘fire’ special counsel Jack Smith in ‘two seconds’ if elected president</title>
      <description>In a radio interview, former president Donald Trump made clear he would seek the removal of Smith, who is pursuing federal cases on behalf of the Justice Department against Trump for allegedly conspiring to overturn the 2020 election and illegally hoarding classified documents. The latter case has been dismissed, but Smith is appealing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12d81310-920f-11ef-b0c2-000a1aceb08d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:51:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A 'monumental' arrest of the former head of this company in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f78dba0-920c-11ef-bfe8-0000a1ace1d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:33:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alsobrooks has a clear lead over Hogan in Maryland U.S. Senate race, Post-UMD poll finds</title>
      <description>Democrat Angela D. Alsobrooks maintains her lead over Republican Larry Hogan in Maryland’s closely watched U.S. Senate race, fueled in large part by voters' preference for Democrats to control the chamber, according to a Washington Post-University of Maryland poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0815990-9207-11ef-82d5-0000a1ace919</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 13:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New EPA rule declares any amount of lead dust detected in homes as hazardous, establishing an aggressive standard for cleanup</title>
      <description>Tens of millions of homes across the country still contain lead-based paint, which is especially dangerous for children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54a576c0-9200-11ef-a688-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 12:05:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris town hall. Russian misinformation. North Korea. Boeing. Infant mortality. Prime number. White House tour. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b775610-91f7-11ef-9270-0000a1ace081</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing workers vote down company’s latest contract offer, prolonging strike</title>
      <description>The rejection leaves the aerospace giant unable to resume production of most commercial airliners as its financial woes deepen with a $6.2 billion loss in the third quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42541b40-91ae-11ef-b6fb-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 02:18:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris says in CNN town hall she agrees Trump is a fascist following remarks from his former chief of staff</title>
      <description>“He himself has said he would terminate the Constitution of the United States,” Vice President Kamala Harris said after saying she agreed he was a fascist.

Her reaction came in response to a question about Donald Trump’s former chief of staff, John F. Kelly, who said this week that the former president fits the definition of being a fascist. Harris is increasingly focusing on what she and her allies portray as Trump’s authoritarian impulses, including threats to turn the military on his enemies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3ee5910-91a8-11ef-84a0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 01:38:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An American in Moscow who is creating deepfakes targeting the Harris campaign works with Russian intelligence, documents show</title>
      <description>John Mark Dougan, a former deputy Palm Beach County sheriff who has become one of Russia’s most prolific propagandists, was provided funding for his misinformation campaigns by an officer from the GRU, the country’s military intelligence service, according to Russian documents obtained by a European intelligence service and reviewed by The Washington Post. Dougan had long claimed to be working independently of the Russian government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4ffc0170-9188-11ef-8b34-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 21:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cooking chat: Is iodized salt needed in your diet? Our food writers are answering your questions now.</title>
      <description>Cooking chat: Is iodized salt needed in your diet? Our food writers are answering your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66c2d230-915b-11ef-a748-0000a1ace13f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:25:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A caregiver’s body is failing, but family’s needs persist</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A caregiver’s body is failing, but family’s needs persist</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fe111f0-9158-11ef-a4e5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 16:03:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Mystics let go of general manager Mike Thibault and coach Eric Thibault in an unexpected move</title>
      <description>Mike Thibault, who led the Mystics to their first WNBA title in 2019, had a long tenure with the organization, for years serving as coach and general manager before stepping away from his coaching role, while retaining his GM duties, in November 2022. His son, Eric, took over as coach and directed the Mystics to a 33-47 record over two seasons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f2e15d0-9156-11ef-8915-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Terrorist attack’ on Turkish defense and aerospace company kills at least 3 and injures 14, interior minister says</title>
      <description>Interior Minister Ali Yerlikaya confirmed the attack on the headquarters of Turkish Aerospace Industries near Ankara, the capital. No group immediately claimed responsibility. Apparent footage of the attack, broadcast on Turkish television and shared on social media but which has not been independently verified, shows gun-wielding assailants opening fire and smoke from an explosion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc823ac0-9151-11ef-a886-000a1ace9371</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 15:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How U.S. sanctions work, illustrated by a Russian oligarch’s $90 million yacht</title>
      <description>Following the yacht’s path to its seizure in Mallorca offers a step-by-step look at economic sanctions — and what happens to assets the U.S. wants to freeze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07a4a4a1-914b-11ef-8b0f-000a1ace74d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 14:28:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
