<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 20:01:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials have the private goal of deporting at least 1 million immigrants this year. Analysts say that's unrealistic.</title>
      <description>Deporting 1 million immigrants in one year would surpass previous statistics, as the highest number was more than 400,000 a year when Barack Obama was president. But there’s a reason that goal remains a private one, and immigration officers and analysts are increasingly skeptical that officials can meet that target.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e0098ef0-17ce-11f0-b565-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My parents traveled from India to tell me to leave my girlfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa442280-17c9-11f0-b2ae-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:14:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She was torn from her birth mother 30 years ago. Then they found each other.</title>
      <description>Korean adoptees can remind the world that these are deeply personal losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5cfe460-17bb-11f0-99f5-0000a1ace11d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smartphones and other electronics will be exempted from reciprocal tariffs, Trump administration says, including Chinese imports</title>
      <description>The Trump administration's exemptions on electronic components coming out of China was announced late Friday. Beijing placed a 125 percent tariff on all U.S. goods earlier in the day, saying it would “fight to the end.” The exemptions on electronic components will likely be welcomed by tech companies like Apple, which produces the bulk of its iPhones in China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f82a3770-17ae-11f0-bab4-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 15:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87d9bce0-17a2-11f0-b02b-0000a1ace4f7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:32:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump administration overrode Social Security staff to falsely list immigrants as dead, people familiar say</title>
      <description>The plan spearheaded by DOGE and the Department of Homeland Security aims to eliminate the ability of thousands of immigrants to legally earn wages. Many agency officials say the practice is illegal and risks wrongly labeling other people as dead.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e6b1050-179e-11f0-9d5d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE takes over federal grants website, wresting control of billions</title>
      <description>A DOGE engineer removed federal officials’ permissions to post to Grants.gov without telling them, according to four people with knowledge of the move. Now decisions affecting billions of dollars in grant opportunities are set to flow through a DOGE-controlled mailbox.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29b7e290-1743-11f0-a78b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 02:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los Angeles judge allows Menendez brothers to seek early release, bringing them closer to potentially reducing their life sentences</title>
      <description>The Menendez family has in recent years made a push for the brothers’ release, maintaining that Erik and Lyle Menendez killed their parents in self-defense after suffering physical and sexual abuse at the hands of their father. During their trial, however, prosecutors said the brothers murdered their parents for financial gain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34ca9cf0-1733-11f0-a664-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 00:15:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evidence reveals a disturbing narrative in the deaths of 14 emergency workers in Gaza</title>
      <description>Israel says the first responders were fired on for moving “suspiciously.” Dispatcher records, witness testimony, and video and audio evidence contradict Israel’s account in key regards, including the proximity of the gunfire to the victims.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa60ebc0-1726-11f0-9d67-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 22:45:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plan would eliminate NOAA climate research, slash agency budget</title>
      <description>A Trump budget proposal would make deep cuts to National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration research on weather, climate and oceans, eliminating labs and reducing its budget by 27 percent. The proposal, obtained by The Washington Post, said the programs were "misaligned" with the "will of the American people." Democrats and science advocates said the cuts would devastate global climate science and make weather forecasts less accurate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e321580-171b-11f0-b9a7-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 21:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana judge rules Columbia student Mahmoud Khalil is eligible for deportation, his lawyers say</title>
      <description>The Trump administration had accused the legal permanent resident of being a threat to U.S. foreign policy for his involvement in pro-Palestinian activism. Khalil has been detained since he was arrested at his New York City apartment last month and stripped of his green-card status.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a79f8e61-1711-11f0-adf1-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 20:15:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. doesn't comply with judge’s deadline for plan to return man wrongly deported, saying it needs more time</title>
      <description>Kilmar Abrego García, a Salvadoran immigrant married to a U.S. citizen, was among more than 200 people expelled to El Salvador on March 15 — despite a court ruling prohibiting his removal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8e80841-16f5-11f0-88c1-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m tired of my husband using me as Google</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I’m tired of my husband using me as Google</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8c7d9d0-16f3-11f0-8878-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 16:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive cuts to NASA science proposed in early White House budget plan, people familiar say, potentially impacting future missions</title>
      <description>NASA’s science budget, which supports space telescopes and interplanetary robotic missions, could be cut nearly in half under an early version of a Trump administration budget proposal to Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3592b311-16df-11f0-a25a-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">51e5bbd0-16d9-11f0-8281-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>While a majority of U.S. manufacturing workers who voted in 2024 backed Trump, most say tariffs would hurt them, Post poll finds</title>
      <description>The Washington Post asked more than 500 workers in manufacturing jobs across the country what they think about President Donald Trump’s tariffs. Most completed the survey before Trump announced he would pull back some tariffs but maintain a 10 percent levy on most foreign goods and raise tariffs on China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e57b700-16d5-11f0-b9e0-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 13:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. China. Supreme Court. Helicopter crash. Mass grave. Funding freeze. Extreme heat. Birthday tradition. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b818700-16c4-11f0-8878-00000a1acef5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China raises tariffs on U.S. goods to 125 percent as trade war deepens between the world's two largest economies</title>
      <description>Beijing hit back in response to the Trump administration’s move to raise tariffs on Chinese goods to 145 percent, saying it would “firmly retaliate and fight to the end.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc7aee70-16b2-11f0-9683-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6,000 living immigrants added to Social Security death database as part of Trump's crackdown</title>
      <description>The classification makes it hard for immigrants to work or receive benefits in the United States as administration officials put pressure on undocumented immigrants to leave the country. Some current and former Social Security officials question the legality of the practice. A White House official said the targets have criminal histories or terrorist ties but did not provide evidence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">29af9fe0-166c-11f0-a795-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI and other law enforcement agencies drafted to do welfare checks on migrant children and young people, alarming advocates</title>
      <description>The Department of Homeland Security has enlisted several other law enforcement agencies in recent weeks to conduct welfare checks on children and young people who came to the United States without their parents. These checks have gained some attention on social media, prompting questions and alarm.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">007ec310-1669-11f0-a181-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court upholds order directing Trump officials to return wrongly deported man from Salvadoran prison</title>
      <description>The court on Thursday upheld a lower-court order requiring the Trump administration to “facilitate” the return of a Maryland man who was mistakenly deported last month to a mega-prison in El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba8b2cc1-1660-11f0-a71d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 23:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helicopter crash in Hudson River kills all 6 on board, including 3 children, New York officials say</title>
      <description>All six people who were on board a Bell 206 helicopter that plunged into the Hudson River on Thursday afternoon have been declared dead, authorities said. The helicopter belonged to a tour company, city officials said, and carried one pilot, two adults and three children.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27c96ad0-1658-11f0-8139-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 22:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Staff cuts begin at the National Endowment for the Humanities, threatening programs across the U.S.</title>
      <description>The employee union said almost 75 percent of NEH staff members should prepare for reductions in their workforce, roughly a week after the agency's grants were canceled.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2120b590-164d-11f0-b25e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Markets closed down, reversing about a third of yesterday's gains, after White House clarified tariffs are 145% of Chinese imports</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P fell by more than 3 percent and the Nasdaq was down more than 4 percent, with banks and tech stocks driving some losses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56b18910-1647-11f0-b25e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 20:06:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From George F. Will: This is 10-thumbed, fumbling, overconfident governmental progressivism</title>
      <description>This is 10-thumbed, fumbling, overconfident governmental progressivism</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80216120-163e-11f0-8b09-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 19:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Will the IRS notice if you don’t file taxes? Columnist Michelle Singletary takes your questions ahead of Tax Day.</title>
      <description>With the April 15 deadline closing in, our personal finance columnist is answering your questions with tax expert Eric Bronnenkant. Send in your questions now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e8ab300-1627-11f0-b17c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:18:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A decade after he broke engagement, ‘I act like I don’t know him’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A decade after he broke engagement, ‘I act like I don’t know him’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe57dc50-1624-11f0-8a08-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 16:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s pick to oversee Bureau of Land Management withdraws after her criticism of Jan. 6 riot surfaces</title>
      <description>Kathleen Sgamma, whom the president nominated to head the agency, wrote in 2021 that she was “disgusted” by the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol, according to a document obtained by the investigative group Documented. Sgamma leads a Denver-based oil and gas industry trade group, the Western Energy Alliance, and was set to have her nomination hearing Thursday morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7f74f70-1620-11f0-ae2d-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 15:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jittery markets open lower after a record-breaking day as tariff hikes on Chinese imports fan fears of a U.S.-China trade war</title>
      <description>Major stock indexes have been volatile all week as Wall Street reacts to a stream of tariff news. After the United States and the European Union paused plans to impose tariffs on each other, some investors Thursday turned to the impact of a potential U.S.-China trade war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1781f20-1611-11f0-9ac4-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This state’s flower is the star of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fdb62aa0-160f-11f0-af4d-0000a1ace7f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation eased more than expected in March, before most of Trump’s tariffs took effect</title>
      <description>The consumer price index showed a slower pace of growth for inflation in March in good news for the economy, according to new data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10371480-1608-11f0-a2b7-0000a1ace126</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 12:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E.U. announces 90-day pause on retaliatory tariffs targeting U.S. goods after Trump delays certain levies</title>
      <description>The E.U. move came a day after the bloc approved levies on a broad range of U.S. imports and after President Donald Trump subsequently paused U.S. tariffs on countries in Europe and elsewhere.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f1ec0d50-1602-11f0-8012-0000a1ace1fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 11:57:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff pause. Republican infighting. Prisoner swap. Immigrant monitoring. Police shooting. Masters. Lost city. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0952980-15fa-11f0-a167-00000a1ace49</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia frees American Ksenia Karelina from a penal colony ahead of diplomatic talks with the U.S. in Istanbul</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Marco Rubio announced the release on X the same day the U.S. and Russia began talks on normalizing their diplomatic missions. Karelina, a Russian-American dual national and beautician from Los Angeles, had been sentenced to 12 years in prison for treason after donating $50 to a Ukrainian humanitarian agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adb33cd6-15ee-11f0-a891-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 09:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Asian markets rebound in morning trading as Trump pauses tariffs — except for those on China</title>
      <description>The Nikkei and Kospi rose after President Donald Trump paused tariffs on Japan and South Korea, among other nations. Hong Kong's Hang Seng was also up, along with indexes in Shanghai, Taiwan and Australia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45ada8e0-15b8-11f0-80ef-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 03:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the 18 hours that changed President Trump's mind on tariffs</title>
      <description>From Tuesday evening to Wednesday afternoon, Trump and his trade advisers spoke to several Republican lawmakers and top foreign leaders. They raised concerns about the faltering global markets and the growing concerns of a worldwide recession, urging Trump to take action.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77064ec1-15a3-11f0-aa78-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 00:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Governments around the world want more babies. But does pronatalism put reproductive freedoms in danger?</title>
      <description>Low fertility rates have sparked panic and pronatalist initiatives around the world. Some experts are more concerned about the ethics of pushing for more births and say the framing of low birth rates as a “crisis” is an ideological choice — not an objective description.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">387180a0-158d-11f0-9dea-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 21:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock markets rally, closing with big gains after Trump pauses most tariffs</title>
      <description>Major indexes surged, closing well up for the first time since the White House announced new import taxes. The S&amp;P 500 closed up 9.5 percent, the tech-heavy Nasdaq was up more than 12 percent and the Dow Jones Industrial Average gained nearly 8 percent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2db562d0-157e-11f0-8aa2-00000a1ace28</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 20:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Supreme Court to let him fire independent regulators</title>
      <description>The Trump administration on Wednesday asked the Supreme Court to allow the president to remove a pair of independent regulators whose cases have broad implications for at least two dozen other agencies, including the Federal Reserve Board. The cases involve Gwynne Wilcox of the National Labor Relations Board and Cathy A. Harris of the Merit Systems Protection Board and a 90-year-old Supreme Court precedent the administration is seeking to overturn.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d1fa8a0-1575-11f0-b242-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 19:05:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel removed as ATF director, replaced with Army secretary</title>
      <description>The Trump administration removed FBI Director Kash Patel as interim head of the Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, replacing him with the Secretary of the Army Dan Driscoll, according to two sources familiar with the decision who spoke on the condition of anonymity to discuss a personnel matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a1030a0-1573-11f0-9f09-00000a1acecd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:51:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he is pausing higher tariff rates for most countries for 90 days, while raising tariffs more for China. Markets surged.</title>
      <description>In a social media post, President Donald Trump also said that 10 percent tariffs will remain for countries getting a reprieve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2853b811-1569-11f0-b3aa-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 17:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is it time to hide cash under your mattress? Three columnists react to the tariff news.</title>
      <description>How many ‘shocks to the system’ can America take?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d6dd8f0-155e-11f0-a5c2-00000a1ace76</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:19:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Widow seeks a polite ‘no’ to … well, everyone</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Widow seeks a polite ‘no’ to … well, everyone</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40364b80-155c-11f0-9358-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stock market opens flat, bonds retreat as trade war heats up with retaliatory tariffs from China and Europe</title>
      <description>U.S. markets had a muted opening Wednesday after the Trump administration’s harshest tariffs yet went into effect, followed by retaliatory moves from China and the European Union. The S&amp;P 500 and tech-heavy Nasdaq composite index were essentially unchanged in early trading, while the Dow Jones Industrial Average declined slightly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3ff000-1548-11f0-8da7-0000a1ace740</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:42:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Piper, nooo!’ It’s time for today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c497110-1547-11f0-a405-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>European Union hits back at Trump’s steel tariffs, imposing up to 25 percent levy on broad list of U.S. goods</title>
      <description>The 27-nation bloc approved the response on Wednesday. A copy of the E.U. plan, seen by The Washington Post, targeted U.S. products including soybeans, meat, iron, steel, textiles, tobacco and ice cream. The E.U. has yet to retaliate against other tariffs by President Donald Trump as it tries to coax Washington toward trade negotiations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53e1d081-1545-11f0-a1e7-0000a1ace706</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China raises tariffs on U.S. goods to 84 percent in response to Trump’s latest levies, as global markets reel</title>
      <description>Beijing's planned increase more than doubled a previously announced minimum 34 percent duty set to take effect Thursday. The announcement came after China said it was willing to talk but would take "forceful measures" to protect the Chinese economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf288bb0-1539-11f0-8f7b-00000a1ace71</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:57:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Singer and ex-MLB players among the dead as toll reaches 113 in Santo Domingo nightclub collapse</title>
      <description>Former major league pitcher Octavio Dotel and Tony Blanco, who played with the Washington Nationals in 2005, were killed in the collapse. Dominican singer Rubby Pérez, who was performing with his band when the roof collapsed early Tuesday, was also killed, his manager said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e371c91-1535-11f0-a58c-000a1ace00cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:25:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Federal workers. IRS turmoil. River flooding. Egg prices. National Recording Registry. Dire wolves. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb2e10e0-1531-11f0-8ff8-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the few freedoms North Koreans enjoyed have vanished since the pandemic</title>
      <description>The city of Hyesan, just over the river from China, once offered a glimpse of a more open North Korea. Now it exemplifies Kim Jong Un’s mounting authoritarianism, with residents and escapees describing how the regime has tightened its grip on trade and communication with the outside world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">631fdc20-14d4-11f0-bcc7-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 23:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
