<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 23:04:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>I’ve reported on UFO sightings for decades — and come to this conclusion</title>
      <description>Aliens are sky gods for skeptics, deities for atheists and a secular alternative to replace the rapidly declining religiosity in the West.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4e70660-fd45-11f0-8228-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Funding vote fails in Senate ahead of potential government shutdown</title>
      <description>A procedural vote to advance a government funding package failed in the Senate, as Democratic leaders and the White House continue negotiations on measures to rein in the Department of Homeland Security after immigration officials killed Alex Pretti in Minneapolis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95aca50-fd3c-11f0-b384-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 18:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A nor’easter will bring snow and flooding. Here’s what to expect in your area this weekend.</title>
      <description>Areas from the Southeast to New England will be hit by blizzard conditions, damaging winds, flooding and icy cold.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe048b10-fd35-11f0-b169-0000a1acedd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 17:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A documentary is the focus of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fbd6420-fd20-11f0-9c10-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration plans to reduce immigration agent presence in Minnesota; senator says large-scale operations ended in Maine</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s border czar, Tom Homan, said his team is working on a plan to draw down the number of federal immigration enforcement agents they have in Minneapolis, pending cooperation with state and local officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61231260-fd1e-11f0-b5b4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 14:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MAGA blowback. Shutdown deadline. Fulton County. Danish anger. Kennedy Center. More snow. Film registry. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0098f590-fd0a-11f0-a5c0-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center’s new programming head resigns days after his hire was announced</title>
      <description>In a Jan. 16 news release, the Kennedy Center announced that Kevin Couch would be its new senior vice president of artistic programming. Less than two weeks later, he confirmed his resignation but declined to comment further.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79776a20-fcb3-11f0-b4da-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 01:40:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four symptoms of Parkinson’s disease that can show up decades before a diagnosis</title>
      <description>Many people think of a tremor as the quintessential warning sign of the neurological disorder. But other symptoms — many of them not involving changes in movement — can appear much earlier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c3692b0-fca3-11f0-afc4-000a1ace57b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 23:45:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Public Schools will open Thursday; some of the other schools in the area will remain closed</title>
      <description>Officials have attributed the closures to lingering icy conditions on some roads and sidewalks as a bitter cold settles in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0697ba30-fc9c-11f0-b105-0000a1aceb2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal government moves to sell Old Post Office, once home to Trump International Hotel</title>
      <description>Government officials are moving to sell the property to the bank that controls the long-term lease as “part of ongoing efforts to reduce the federal government’s footprint,” according to a letter sent to the city’s State Historic Preservation Office last month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e550ed40-fc98-11f0-88bb-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 22:30:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI executes search warrant seeking ballots from 2020 election in Georgia’s Fulton County</title>
      <description>The actions mark the latest apparent move in President Donald Trump’s campaign to find widespread voter fraud from that election despite five years of debunked claims and dozens of dismissed court cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61ec29d0-fc91-11f0-ad8a-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 21:36:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two federal agents involved in Alex Pretti shooting placed on administrative leave</title>
      <description>The development came a day after the Department of Homeland Security provided the first official timeline of the deadly encounter in a statement sent to some members of Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">885097a0-fc7d-11f0-ac15-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:14:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed holds rates steady, signaling patience despite pressure from Trump</title>
      <description>The decision marked the Fed’s first pause after cutting rates three times at the end of 2025, moves that officials and economists say were aimed at insulating the labor market as hiring slowed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">049bd0b0-fc7c-11f0-9070-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:03:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greenland isn’t the answer to U.S. Arctic security. This place is.</title>
      <description>The U.S. could start building a true Arctic fortress in Alaska tomorrow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be0cba80-fc6f-11f0-8fe2-0000a1ace359</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘My teen wrote a mean song about me’: Carolyn Hax readers give advice</title>
      <description>‘My teen wrote a mean song about me’: Carolyn Hax readers give advice</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71385f40-fc6d-11f0-9b5e-0000a1ace02b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 17:19:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In the middle of a great meal, the manager told our group, ‘Time’s up’</title>
      <description>In the middle of a great meal, the manager told our group, ‘Time’s up’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db3addd1-fc65-11f0-be06-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Greg Bovino went from little-known head of a state Border Patrol office to the face of Trump’s immigration policy</title>
      <description>Just months into President Donald Trump’s second term, Bovino emerged as a central figure in one of the most aggressive immigration crackdowns in U.S. history. Now that approach has turned into a political liability for the administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b56679d1-fc5f-11f0-be06-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 15:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 40th anniversary in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f341a270-fc55-11f0-8ee0-0000a1ace276</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 14:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ilhan Omar. Pretti killing. World Cup. Elon Musk. Bari Weiss. Parkinson’s symptoms. Snowfall map. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d79c8130-fc40-11f0-b29d-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Ilhan Omar attacked during town hall meeting in Minneapolis but appeared unharmed and continued speaking</title>
      <description>A man used a syringe to spray an unknown liquid at Omar, according to a police statement. He was immediately arrested and booked into jail on suspicion of 3rd degree assault, the statement added.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21bd7ce1-fbee-11f0-bff1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 02:07:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHS report says two officers shot Alex Pretti, does not describe him brandishing gun</title>
      <description>A preliminary review contradicts Trump administration comments in the immediate aftermath of the confrontation, when senior officials described the 37-year-old as a direct threat to federal officers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ec131a0-fbe0-11f0-9bf5-0000a1ace132</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:28:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA ignored warnings before ‘100 percent preventable’ DCA crash, federal investigators say</title>
      <description>The deadly midair collision above Reagan National Airport that killed 67 people last January was due to systemic failures, said Jennifer Homendy, chair of the National Transportation Safety Board.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">590242f0-fbdd-11f0-a3c8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 00:07:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Without strategy shift, ‘we are toast,’ Bari Weiss says at staff meeting as she announces new contributors from her opinion site</title>
      <description>Weiss, the editor in chief of CBS News, announced a new slate of network contributors — many of whom write for the Free Press, her conservative website. Weiss said she wanted the network to appeal to political moderates.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd80aad0-fbd1-11f0-975d-00000a1aceb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 22:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rules Virginia Democrats violated law with redistricting amendment</title>
      <description>The process Virginia Democrats used in an effort to create more blue-leaning congressional seats was invalid, a judge said. Democrats vowed to appeal. A referendum on the maps has been scheduled for April 21.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f05ebf0-fbca-11f0-b03c-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 21:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five key moments in the Alex Pretti shooting that raise red flags for policing experts</title>
      <description>The tactics U.S. Border Patrol agents used against Pretti in Minneapolis probably violate modern policing guidelines, several experts said, and add to a growing body of evidence that federal immigration officers are deviating from professional norms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12bd0f60-fbc3-11f0-b95a-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 20:59:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump aides declared these 16 DHS shootings justified before investigations were completed</title>
      <description>Most of these incidents since July involved officers firing at drivers during enforcement stops in cities such as Los Angeles and Chicago where Department of Homeland Security has surged federal immigration officers. The shootings have sparked alarm not only for their violence but also for the Trump administration’s response.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3aa5eb0-fbac-11f0-ad6f-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 18:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A high school bully is back decades later as friend’s new man</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A high school bully is back decades later as friend’s new man</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde48110-fba2-11f0-9494-0000a1ace474</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:09:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composer Philip Glass pulls world premiere from Kennedy Center</title>
      <description>The pioneering composer said “the values of the Kennedy Center today are in direct conflict with the message” of his Symphony No. 15: “Lincoln,” slated to be performed in June by the National Symphony Orchestra.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71953fa0-fb99-11f0-b467-0000a1acedf5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:01:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I discovered about Josh Shapiro at the Pennsylvania Farm Show</title>
      <description>Gov. Josh Shapiro champions a 67-county strategy to win voters in a critical battleground state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c57d6140-fb96-11f0-b29c-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 15:42:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The world’s most expensive album in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c647c1b1-fb8c-11f0-bd4d-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:30:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota chief federal judge orders the acting head of ICE to appear in court Friday, threatens contempt</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Patrick J. Schiltz has demanded Acting ICE Director Todd M. Lyons explain what the judge described as repeated failures to comply with dozens of court orders amid its enforcement efforts in Minnesota.“ The court’s patience is at an end,” the judge wrote in a filing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a350e280-fb83-11f0-9aa9-0000a1acedb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 13:25:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis fallout. Park sign removals. Another storm. Gaza hostage. AI books. Kanye West apology. Toddler screens. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab3dcf00-fb77-11f0-81fb-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Many D.C.-area schools and federal offices to remain closed Tuesday</title>
      <description>The closures come as frigid temperatures are making it difficult to clean up after Sunday’s winter storm. The Office of Personnel Management said “maximum telework” would be in effect for federal workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c3a7620-fb10-11f0-9b76-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 23:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Newlyweds disagree on response to brother’s theft of cash gifts</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Newlyweds disagree on response to brother’s theft of cash gifts</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac534170-fad9-11f0-b751-0000a1ace188</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs can’t cover a bill this staggering. The Editorial Board ran the math.</title>
      <description>Trump has promised to spend far more than what the tariff revenue could cover.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7c934a0-face-11f0-9f38-0000a1ace6bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel confirms remains of last hostage, Rani Gvili, returned from Gaza</title>
      <description>The return of the last hostage’s remains brings the years-long saga over the fate of the captives, both Israeli and foreign, to a close.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c08f82d0-fac4-11f0-9b4d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:38:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minneapolis shooting. Extreme cold. Trump speech. Media lawsuits. Super Bowl. Stove dangers. Bottled water vs. tap. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81f25041-faae-11f0-9ba8-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFL playoffs bracket: Seahawks and Patriots will meet in Super Bowl LX</title>
      <description>Seattle prevailed at home in a shootout against the Los Angeles Rams on Sunday after New England pulled out an ugly but effective win in the snow in Denver.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc920660-fa63-11f0-a623-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 03:06:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian forces massacred protesters fleeing a burning market, witnesses say</title>
      <description>A rare detailed account of Iran’s crackdown, produced by The Washington Post, reveals the brutality used by security forces in one of many such cities rocked by violence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b274881-fa39-11f0-b58b-00000a1aced9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The unjust killing of Alex Pretti marks a turning point in Trump’s second term</title>
      <description>The unjust killing of Alex Pretti marks a turning point in Trump’s second term</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b2a0120-fa32-11f0-8b58-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 1 million customers are without power as risk of dangerous ice moves into swaths of the East Coast</title>
      <description>Dangerous icing across the Southeastern U.S. has left customers without power — a problem that emergency agencies warned won’t go away just because the storm passes, with heavy ice expected to strain power lines in the coming days. At least five people across the country have died since the storm began, The Post has confirmed, all due to suspected hypothermia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6e08cd91-fa25-11f0-aa6b-0000a1ace76d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eleanor Holmes Norton ends House reelection campaign after serving as D.C.’s nonvoting delegate for decades</title>
      <description>Norton’s campaign filed a termination report with the Federal Election Commission on Sunday, signaling that the 88-year-old will not seek a 19th term. She has faced months of intense public scrutiny about her ability to adequately represent the nation’s capital during an unprecedented period of federal intervention.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">803bd4a0-fa14-11f0-80b2-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:37:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3fdbb80-fa0f-11f0-8df8-00000a1ace6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:03:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How bad is your stove for your health? Look it up.</title>
      <description>For home chefs, the love of cooking with gas is real. Stanford University scientists’ new model estimates exposure to the pollutant nitrogen dioxide based on home size, how often the stove is used and where people live.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19433881-fa0d-11f0-b19f-0000a1acefb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outages increase in South as brunt of storm hits Mid-Atlantic and Northeast with snow and ice. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Swaths of the East Coast woke up to several inches of snow, with many areas expected to see more than a foot of snow and destructive amounts of ice into Monday as a mix of snow, sleet and freezing rain is set to lash the Mid-Atlantic, including the D.C. area. Meanwhile, dangerous icing has driven more than 700,000 power outages as of early of Sunday, the hardest hit stretch from Texas to Tennessee.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ed940b0-f9fc-11f0-af35-0000a1ace445</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:43:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cba2330-f9fa-11f0-80a3-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:32:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal agents secured a handgun Minnesota man was carrying moments before shooting him multiple times, videos show</title>
      <description>As many as eight agents were attempting to detain Alex Pretti, a 37-year-old ICU nurse, videos show. One emerged from the scrum holding Pretti’s gun, and less than a second later, the first of what appear to be 10 shots was fired. It is not clear from the video whether the other agents realized Pretti — who local authorities believe had a permit to carry the weapon — had been disarmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bada2090-f9f0-11f0-8987-00000a1ace69</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Free Solo’ climber Alex Honnold successfully scales Taiwan’s tallest building</title>
      <description>Honnold completed the ascent without any assistance or safety net in under two hours — while being live-streamed to Netflix’s hundreds of millions of international subscribers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed61a720-f9a7-11f0-913d-0000a1ace753</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 04:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICU nurse fatally shot by federal agents in Minneapolis was dedicated to caring for veterans, say family, friends and co-workers</title>
      <description>The family of Alex Pretti said the 37-year-old killed Saturday worked at the Minneapolis VA hospital and "wanted to make a difference in this world.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6992ae1-f995-11f0-913d-0000a1ace753</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 22 states have declared a state of emergency as massive winter storm moves east across U.S.</title>
      <description>Parts of Oklahoma, Kansas, Arkansas, and Texas are experiencing snow and thick ice, and officials have urged residents to stay home and avoid dangerous roads. In the D.C. area, frigid air has descended as the region awaits one of the most severe winter storms in years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcbc1e80-f963-11f0-9d32-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 20:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
