<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:03:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Senate votes to dismiss impeachment charges against Homeland Security Secretary Alejandro Mayorkas</title>
      <description>Senate Democrats voted quickly to dismiss two articles of impeachment against Mayorkas that alleged he mismanaged an influx of migrants at the U.S.-Mexico border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adfa3910-fcf8-11ee-8612-0000a1ace371</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 20:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBA bans Raptors forward Jontay Porter for violating gambling policy, including limiting his playing time for betting purposes</title>
      <description>The league announced Wednesday that an investigation found Porter had disclosed confidential information to bettors, limited his participation in games for betting purposes and wagered on NBA games — an array of brazenly inappropriate actions that jeopardize the integrity of competition. The investigation was launched last month in response to suspicious betting activity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f9267ab0-fcdb-11ee-b33d-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 17:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Is it really better to crack an egg on a flat surface than on the edge of a bowl? Chat with our food writers.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Is it really better to crack an egg on a flat surface than on the edge of a bowl? Chat with our food writers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99703560-fcd7-11ee-a2c5-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:29:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Youngkin (R) and lawmakers agree to seek new state budget, aiming to avert a government shutdown</title>
      <description>Gov. Glenn Youngkin met with General Assembly leaders to find a way around a budget impasse over taxes and spending priorities, according to two people close to the arrangements who spoke on the condition of anonymity to share private negotiations. Lawmakers and the governor agreed to create a new budget and hold a special legislative session, probably in mid-May, to wrap up the budget process well before the June 30 deadline.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4b18360-fcd3-11ee-9df3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 16:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They criticized Israel. This X account upended their lives.</title>
      <description>Nearly three dozen people have been fired or suspended from their jobs after being featured by StopAntisemitism, according to the group’s X feed, part of a wave of digital activism related to the Israel-Gaza war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5cfb720-fccb-11ee-904a-0000a1ace9b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 15:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A ‘remarkable slowdown in demand’ for this company’s product in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1c1d4c0-fcbe-11ee-b71b-0000a1acec99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A secret Russian document offers a rare, official glimpse into Moscow’s campaign against the West</title>
      <description>The classified Russian Foreign Ministry document calls for an “offensive information campaign” and other measures spanning “the military-political, economic and trade and informational psychological spheres” against a “coalition of unfriendly countries” led by the United States. The document was provided to The Washington Post by a European intelligence service.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8b4fe20-fcbc-11ee-aae5-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 13:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump jurors. Supreme Court. House speaker. Pro-Palestinian protests. Camel milk. Cancer tests. Space junk. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8521bd0-fca9-11ee-9df3-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 11:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob Graham dies at 87. The former U.S. senator and Florida governor was a consensus-builder and an ardent opponent of the Iraq War.</title>
      <description>Mr. Graham, a moderate Democrat, served two terms as Florida’s governor and three terms as a senator. He made a short-lived bid for the 2004 Democratic presidential nomination, campaigning largely on his opposition to President George W. Bush’s invasion of Iraq.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cbf39d10-fc69-11ee-8e83-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 03:23:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Dead ships’: Before a cargo ship hit Baltimore’s Key Bridge, hundreds of others lost propulsion in U.S. waters in recent years</title>
      <description>A Washington Post analysis of Coast Guard records found that 424 cargo ships longer than 600 feet reported losing propulsion — meaning the engines were shut down — in U.S. waters during the three years before the Key Bridge disaster in Baltimore. About a quarter of the incidents occurred near a port, bridge or other infrastructure. Experts say a lack of consistent rules on when cargo ships should be escorted by supportive tug boats adds to the danger.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d0bcab0-fc45-11ee-9fa6-0000a1ace4b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 23:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven jurors picked to serve on Trump hush money jury, and other key takeaways</title>
      <description>Manhattanites spilled into a courtroom on Tuesday and were quizzed about their media diet, hobbies and families — all to see if they could be fair jurors in the criminal trial of former president Donald Trump,, who also happens to be the likely 2024 Republican presidential nominee. Seven were chosen, and some were passed over for problematic social media posts or other reasons. Opening statements could be as soon as Monday, the judge said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74f2b8a1-fc3e-11ee-9182-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 22:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom yearns for her kids to feel the same freedoms of her youth</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom yearns for her kids to feel the same freedoms of her youth</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">53720811-fc1c-11ee-a223-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 18:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momentum builds to oust House Speaker Mike Johnson as two fellow Republicans say they would vote to remove him</title>
      <description>Rep. Thomas Massie (R-Ky.) announced Tuesday morning he would join Rep. Marjorie Taylor Greene’s (R-Ga.) bid to depose Johnson (R-La.) after the speaker introduced a complex foreign aid package decoupling Israel from Ukraine aid.

Neither Massie nor Green has officially brought up the so-called motion to vacate, which would trigger a vote on Johnson’s leadership. But Republicans are now one vote short of being able to oust him if Democrats don’t step in to support him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05c20c20-fc15-11ee-aa54-0000a1aceb83</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 17:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court appears deeply divided over Jan. 6 obstruction charges in case that may impact Trump’s election interference trial</title>
      <description>After nearly two hours of argument, it was unclear whether the court would allow the Justice Department to apply to Jan. 6 rioters a statute that makes it a crime to obstruct or impede an official proceeding — in this case the joint session of Congress that convened to formally certify Joe Biden’s 2020 victory. Some conservative justices seemed wary of giving prosecutors too much discretion. The obstruction charge is also among the counts Donald Trump is facing in his federal trial for trying to block the 2020 election results.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f61e0140-fc0d-11ee-bf6c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 16:25:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palestinian paramedics said Israel gave them safe passage to save a 6-year-old girl in Gaza. They were all killed.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post examination of audio recordings and the damage to the car and ambulance, as well as the presence of Israeli forces in the immediate area that day, raise questions about Israel’s assertion that its forces were “not present near the vehicle or within the firing range.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7827c660-fc06-11ee-aef9-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Court is hearing arguments in a case that could undo convictions of Jan. 6 rioters. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Defense lawyers say prosecutors improperly stretched the law by charging more than 350 people with obstruction of an official proceeding, a case with implications for former president Donald Trump’s election interference trial in D.C. The high court’s ruling has the potential to undo the convictions and sentences of those who have already gone to trial or pleaded guilty and upend the charges still pending for many more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa94211-fbfc-11ee-b8b8-00000a1acebf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 14:18:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The gift of trees in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7ef37db0-fbf5-11ee-8657-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 13:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Jan. 6 case. Ukraine aid. ‘Rust’ sentencing. Coral bleaching. Caitlin Clark. Abba and Biggie. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7af6ba20-fbe0-11ee-969e-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They were liberal public school teachers. Now they teach kids to be anti-‘woke.’</title>
      <description>Kali and Joshua Fontanilla taught English in a deep-blue California district — but quit their jobs and moved to Florida to start their own school after growing convinced the curriculum was left-wing propaganda. While the claim that public schools promote left-wing “indoctrination” has become a commonplace on the right, it’s not usually an allegation repeated by teachers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24f6cbc0-fb85-11ee-981d-0000a1aced49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 00:06:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indiana Fever selects Caitlin Clark with first pick in WNBA draft, officially launching her professional basketball career</title>
      <description>Clark, a record-setting guard at the University of Iowa, was virtually certain to be taken with the No. 1 pick once she announced in February that she would enter this year’s draft. She joins the WNBA shouldering unprecedented expectations to increase its visibility after her college games drew sellout crowds and record television ratings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d631b981-fb81-11ee-99d0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 23:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court allows Idaho ban on gender-affirming care for minors to take effect as case continues</title>
      <description>While the underlying case concerns the constitutionality of a ban on gender-affirming medical care for minors, the court’s order did not address the merits of the issue – only whether the law could take effect for now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85622ae0-fb76-11ee-8348-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 22:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Severe thunderstorm watch issued for region until 10 p.m.</title>
      <description>Hit-or-miss storms could produce large hail and damaging wind gusts, in addition to dangerous lightning. The threat for storms gradually shifts southward through the region during the afternoon and into the evening.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86d6fe20-fb56-11ee-ad8b-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Rust’ armorer sentenced to 18 months for involuntary manslaughter in fatal on-set shooting of cinematographer</title>
      <description>Hannah Gutierrez-Reed was found guilty of involuntary manslaughter in June. She was accused of failing to ensure gun safety on the set of the low-budget Western movie in 2021. Alec Baldwin was rehearsing with a revolver on set when the gun went off, killing cinematographer Halyna Hutchins and wounding director Joel Souza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">192ae410-fb54-11ee-bb3f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 18:15:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you afford to buy a house? Take our quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>Homeownership is how many Americans accumulate wealth, but affording a home is a growing challenge for many. Mortgage rates have more than doubled and are now at nearly 7 percent on a typical 30-year loan. So, should you buy a home right now? To help you decide, take this quiz.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3f17d0-fb4a-11ee-840c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 17:08:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to know when kids are ready to handle their parents’ divorce?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">27864bb0-fb42-11ee-9eed-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 16:06:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘This should be a global wake-up call’: Corals are bleaching in every corner of the ocean, threatening its web of life, scientists say</title>
      <description>The fourth-ever bleaching event in history, declared by the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration and International Coral Reef Initiative, is the second in a decade. More than 54 percent of all the reef areas on the planet have experienced bleaching-level heat stress in the past year, and the overall amount could soon pass a record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bb41d0-fb39-11ee-a5c4-00000a1ace81</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla to shed more than 10 percent of its workforce as EV demand cools</title>
      <description>The move by CEO Elon Musk comes after the company, which employed more than 140,000 as of December, reported a sharp decline in vehicle deliveries in the first quarter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5664cd01-fb31-11ee-ac6b-0000a1ace217</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 14:06:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A historical location hosts a film festival in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bff74450-fb2c-11ee-9274-000a1aced311</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump arrives for the start of his hush money trial, the first criminal prosecution of a former U.S. president. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Jury selection is set to begin this morning in Manhattan, where Donald Trump is charged with falsifying business records ahead of the 2016 election to hide payments made to keep an adult-film actress quiet about an alleged sexual tryst.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2d784b1-fb29-11ee-bc53-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 13:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal criminal investigation opened into crash that brought down Baltimore’s Key Bridge</title>
      <description>Six construction workers died after the container ship Dali lost power and slammed into a pillar of the Francis Scott Key Bridge on March 26 in the Port of Baltimore.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a69a7a80-fb19-11ee-ac8d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump’s lawyers have done all they could to delay his criminal trials. The first one is set to start today.</title>
      <description>The former president's lawyers have pledged to argue every motion and request every possible document, hoping to delay his trials beyond November's election, people familiar with the strategy say. They have succeeded so far with pushing back Trump's trials in D.C., Florida and Georgia. But jury selection in the New York hush money case is slated to begin this morning.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d89de00-fb17-11ee-aa43-000a1ace4f60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 11:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Iran attack. Sydney stabbing. Trans bill. Tax Day. Scottie Scheffler. Pompeii paintings. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4da4f561-fb17-11ee-84cf-0000a1ace681</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottie Scheffler wins the Masters, securing his second green jacket in the past three years</title>
      <description>The world's No. 1 player finished the job Sunday after beginning the final round with a one-shot lead and holding off challenges by Ludvig Aberg and Max Homa. It was the second career major title for Scheffler, 27, who captured his first green jacket in 2022.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">66f62a10-fab4-11ee-a369-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 23:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Could you judge Trump impartially if you were on his hush money trial jury? Here’s what 12 New Yorkers said.</title>
      <description>When Donald Trump walks into a Manhattan courtroom on Monday, it will kick off a process unprecedented in American history: jury selection for a former president’s criminal trial. He is facing 34 felony charges for allegedly falsifying business records related to a hush money payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels during the 2016 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2770da10-faa1-11ee-8ba6-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 20:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This senator wants an online privacy law. She has slowed efforts for years.</title>
      <description>Sen. Maria Cantwell (D-Wash.) has been a primary reason for an impasse on legislation, according to more than a dozen current and former congressional aides in both parties, and others familiar with the dynamics of the committee she chairs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2641ea40-fa91-11ee-b2c7-00000a1acec4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 18:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Small-time investors in Trump’s Truth Social see their share values plunge — and see it as a test of faith</title>
      <description>The company has lost $3.5 billion in value since its public debut last month. But for some investors, the stock is a badge of honor — a way to show their devotion beyond buying Donald Trump’s merchandise, visiting Trump golf courses or donating to Trump’s presidential campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18c5b021-fa84-11ee-9510-00000a1aceb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 17:26:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3b32000-fa7f-11ee-8ac5-0000a1acecc5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 16:54:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now it’s up to Israel: De-escalate or retaliate against Iran? Max Boot writes about what could come next.</title>
      <description>Tehran’s barrage of drones and missiles was a face-saving maneuver, successfully repulsed. But the possibility of matters spinning out of control still looms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b082360-fa7a-11ee-8719-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 16:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Texas county at center of the border fight is overwhelmed by migrant deaths</title>
      <description>Record-level migration has brought record-breaking death to Maverick County, a border community that is ground zero in the feud between Texas and the Biden administration over migration.

First responders have run out of body bags and burial plots. Their rescue boats and recovery trucks are covered in dents and scratches. County officials say they don’t have the training or supplies to collect DNA samples of each unidentified migrant as required by state law.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f59cd000-fa70-11ee-b239-0000a1acecb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 15:09:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">48be9560-fa63-11ee-bea3-0000a1acebf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2024 13:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. forces have shot down Iranian attack drones targeting Israel, officials said</title>
      <description>The United States, attempting to walk a line of helping its ally without getting pulled deeper into a regional war, has targeted and downed some of the Iranian drones fired at Israel on Saturday, two U.S. officials confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ab2af31-f9eb-11ee-b3d6-000a1ace491b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 23:13:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli military says multiple drones launched from Iran now headed toward Israel. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The drones would take several hours to reach Israeli territory, a military spokesman said in a statement. Israel and the United States had braced for the attack after an Israeli strike in Damascus killed senior members of Iran’s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bac06ce0-f9d4-11ee-bc70-00000a1ace90</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 20:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our reviewer tried living with a $699 AI device on his chest. You probably shouldn’t bother with the Star Trek-style pin.</title>
      <description>If you’ve ever watched Star Trek characters tap their badges to communicate, you basically know how to use the AI Pin, meant to be worn on a shirt as it answers questions and sends messages. There’s a glimmer of a good product here, but using it can quickly get frustrating, Chris Velazco writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">791febc1-f9c6-11ee-87af-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 18:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A cheating scandal rocked the D.C. bar trivia scene. Here’s how it unfolded — and why so many people care.</title>
      <description>A team that won Red Bear Brewing Co.’s Wednesday trivia night several weeks running was found to be cheating using an Apple Watch. We had to investigate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9d429b60-f9bc-11ee-adf2-000a1ace1bd4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I want to move out. My parents might guilt me into staying.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I want to move out. My parents might guilt me into staying.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71224b50-f9af-11ee-a79a-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We mapped nature across the U.S., neighborhood by neighborhood. Look up where you live.</title>
      <description>Spending time in nature is linked to a longer, healthier life. But nature is not distributed fairly across the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37c29de1-f9a7-11ee-ab49-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 15:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today?</title>
      <description>Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">135743f0-f99a-11ee-8482-00000a1acec9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 13:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran says it has seized a Portugal-flagged ship near the Strait of Hormuz, saying the vessel is ‘connected to’ Israel</title>
      <description>Iranian state media shared a video that appeared to show a person rappelling from a helicopter to board a ship, which the report identified as the MSC Aries. The region has been on alert for Tehran’s promised retaliation to an Israeli strike near Iran’s embassy in Syria that killed two senior members of Iran’s Revolutionary Guard this month.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3cf7f50-f987-11ee-b69b-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 11:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A man killed five in a stabbing attack at an upscale mall in Sydney’s Bondi Junction before being shot dead, Australian police said</title>
      <description>Several are injured, including a small child, police said, adding that the attacker is not known to the police, and the motive is not clear. Police are carrying out a critical incident investigation and say they have not ruled out terrorism as a motive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">112f96e0-f977-11ee-8ba6-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A mysterious condition is striking young, highly trained athletes</title>
      <description>First described more than 150 years ago, POTS has proliferated since the coronavirus pandemic. The syndrome tends to strike suddenly, leaving previously healthy people unable to function, with no clear cause. In recent years, doctors have noticed a curious and disproportionate subset of patients: female athletes at peak fitness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8d394140-f900-11ee-a372-0000a1aceb39</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 19:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
