<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 21:02:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>In a place with a history of hate, an unlikely fight against GOP extremism — with a crucial test in tonight’s primary</title>
      <description>North Idaho has beaten the far right before. Now renegade Republicans are seeking to root it out of their own party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c0ef581-17ad-11ef-a95a-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 20:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A dark new biopic starring Sebastian Stan as a young Trump is the talk of Cannes</title>
      <description>“The Apprentice” drew spots of laughter from the Cannes Film Festival audience. But by and large, it is a chilling origin story.

Former president Donald Trump’s campaign called the film “pure fiction which sensationalizes lies.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d53dfb70-17a0-11ef-9aae-0000a1ace376</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: New mom with spendy lifestyle whines at having to go back to work</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e11816c0-178b-11ef-b330-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Europe is funding the draconian practice of detaining migrants in North Africa and dumping them in the desert, investigation finds</title>
      <description>A year-long joint investigation by The Washington Post, Lighthouse Reports and a consortium of international media outlets shows how the European Union and individual European nations are supporting and financing aggressive operations to push tens of thousands of migrants to remote areas in Morocco, Mauritania and Tunisia each year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de1f2640-1784-11ef-877c-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 15:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump will not testify in his N.Y. hush-money trial. The defense has rested, and jury deliberations will take place next week.</title>
      <description>Both sides have finished presenting evidence in Donald Trump’s trial over allegedly falsifying business records related to a payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels before the 2016 election. After the judge and the lawyers discuss jury instructions this afternoon, the trial will take a break until closing arguments, scheduled for next Tuesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">21a0da90-177f-11ef-8089-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 14:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A long-awaited film meets mixed reviews in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">295d87f1-1776-11ef-a553-00000a1acef3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 13:29:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Middle East. Trump’s trial. Campaign cash. Extreme weather. African migrants. Scarlett Johansson. Cockroaches. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47c4ef90-1761-11ef-915c-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scarlett Johansson threatens legal action against OpenAI, claiming it copied her voice for ChatGPT</title>
      <description>The actress alleges OpenAI CEO Sam Altman tried to hire her, then copied her voice when she said no. The artificial intelligence start-up said it would pause ChatGPT’s new voice features after drawing criticism that it sounded like Johansson’s character in the 2013 movie “Her.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e07d5870-16fe-11ef-9332-000a1ace5824</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boy Scouts love this scenic Virginia river. Locals say they’re killing it.</title>
      <description>Three hours southwest of D.C., the Maury River suffers as sediment flows from a dam at a campground owned by a scouting organization based in Bethesda, Md. The situation has created an unusual standoff between local residents and an organization known for honor and stewardship but plagued in recent years by controversy and financial trouble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">884c91a0-16f6-11ef-adda-00000a1ace88</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 22:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDIC Chairman Martin Gruenberg announces he will resign once successor is found after reports claimed he led hostile workplace</title>
      <description>Lawmakers have been calling for the resignation of Gruenberg, chair of the Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation, a banking regulatory agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">402a6940-16f3-11ef-9d42-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 21:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prosecution rests in Trump hush money trial after Michael Cohen’s testimony. The defense will call up to two witnesses.</title>
      <description>The prosecution rested and the defense said it would call no more than two witnesses in former president Donald Trump’s criminal trial for allegedly falsifying documents related to a hush money payment. Because of scheduling issues around Memorial Day weekend, the judge said the jury will begin deliberations next week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dadaa380-16dd-11ef-937c-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 19:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden calls International Criminal Court’s arrest warrant request for Netanyahu and other Israeli officials ‘outrageous’</title>
      <description>President Biden suggested the top global court’s prosecutor had implied equivalence between Israel’s leaders, including Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, and Hamas’s leaders, whose arrest is also being sought.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8df7c720-16cc-11ef-b701-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:15:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivan Boesky dies at 87. The 1980s Wall Street titan was at the epicenter of an insider-trading scandal.</title>
      <description>Audacious and extravagant, Boesky helped inspire Hollywood’s fictional financial mogul Gordon Gekko and his greed-is-good mantra.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ba3cc80-16c8-11ef-8005-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is it selfish or self-care to cancel plans, ‘etiquette be damned’?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is it selfish or self-care to cancel plans, ‘etiquette be damned’?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a70cea3-16c4-11ef-9788-0000a1ace214</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 16:18:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ship that destroyed Baltimore bridge is finally floated back to port, but its crew remains on board</title>
      <description>Nearly two months after knocking down the Francis Scott Key Bridge, the container ship Dali is back in port in Baltimore. Here’s what happens next to the ship and its crew.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b25b8950-16c0-11ef-8c5a-000a1ace8dc1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 15:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A crazy morning in Louisville in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fffb7e80-16ad-11ef-846b-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 13:36:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange can appeal his extradition to the U.S., Britain’s high court rules</title>
      <description>The legal victory for Assange means he will not be whisked away by U.S. Marshals to the United States, where he faces charges of espionage for releasing reams of sensitive military and diplomatic files via WikiLeaks back in 2010.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8569d10-16a3-11ef-82e8-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 12:24:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>International Criminal Court prosecutor applying for arrest warrants for Israeli and Hamas officials, including Benjamin Netanyahu</title>
      <description>The prosecutor is applying to the court for warrants against Yahya Sinwar, a Hamas leader, and Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu, for war crimes and crimes against humanity in the Gaza Strip. A panel of judges will consider the warrants. The court previously issued an arrest warrant for Russian President Vladimir Putin over the invasion of Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edbd2ca0-1699-11ef-88c5-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 11:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iran’s president. Trump trial. Biden speech. Sean Combs. Mosquitoes. PGA Championship. Ancient humans. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">17e8d670-1698-11ef-a386-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iranian President Ebrahim Raisi dead in helicopter crash, state media says</title>
      <description>Raisi was returning from Azerbaijan with Iran’s foreign minister and other officials Sunday when the helicopter went down in foggy conditions. He was elected in 2021, widely seen as the choice of Iran's supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, after a career in the judiciary. Raisi oversaw the crackdown on anti-government protests that erupted in late 2022 and Iran’s first-ever direct attack on Israel in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7fe02c2-1662-11ef-9e6d-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 04:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xander Schauffele wins the PGA Championship for his first major title</title>
      <description>Schauffele, 30, entered Sunday's final round tied for the lead with Collin Morikawa. The world's third-ranked player previously had 12 top-10 finishes in majors, including ties for second at the 2019 Masters and the 2018 British Open.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5b5eb010-1633-11ef-9f6d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 22:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 1920 shootout that may belie the Texas Rangers’ romanticized image</title>
      <description>A century after three Tejano men were shot to death, the story that descendants tell of their killing contradicts official accounts. The families blame the storied Texas Rangers, while history has cast the men as tequila smugglers who shot first. Whose story counts as Texas history?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e135e700-1622-11ef-8e3e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 21:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a3541f0-15fd-11ef-b7e9-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 16:33:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An island in Maryland holds tantalizing clues about when and how humans first made their way into North America</title>
      <description>The story of the first Americans has long stoked public and scientific fascination, sometimes fueled by vicious disagreements. Parsons Island in the Chesapeake Bay could rewrite American prehistory, with artifacts suggesting people may have inhabited the area more than 20,000 years ago, a discovery that could push the timeline of arrival earlier than most experts thought possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdbf1720-15f8-11ef-9771-0000a1ace793</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 15:59:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rescue teams trying to reach helicopter carrying Iranian president after ‘hard landing,’ state media said</title>
      <description>The incident occurred as President Ebrahim Raisi was traveling back from Azerbaijan with Foreign Minister Hossein Amir-Abdollahian and other officials, state-run IRNA reported. Rescuers are reportedly struggling to reach the helicopter due to foggy conditions and mountainous terrain.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2cb1542-15ef-11ef-9020-0000a1ace7f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 14:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready to dive into the Sunday Crossword? It’s time to play.</title>
      <description>Ready to dive into the Sunday Crossword? It’s time to play.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fca1591-15e8-11ef-97a6-0000a1ace480</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 14:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seize the Grey finishes first at Preakness, spoiling Mystik Dan’s Triple Crown bid</title>
      <description>This year’s Kentucky Derby champion, Mystik Dan, was in the Preakness field but fell short at Pimlico Race Course in Baltimore on Saturday. No horse has won the Triple Crown since Justify in 2018.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2fa15c10-156c-11ef-87c5-0000a1aced51</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 23:13:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The changing attitudes in restaurants: ‘We are in service. We are not servants.’</title>
      <description>Restaurants are increasingly saying no to large parties of diners and are closing during the “dead” midweek, among other trends.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">43e2c200-1561-11ef-80ee-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 21:54:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Biden and Trump running for president, people are talking about the aging brain. Here’s what science tells us.</title>
      <description>As voters consider the mental fitness of President Biden and Donald Trump, experts warn against misinformation about aging and cognitive decline. Judgment and emotional stability can improve with age, they say, and may be essential to effective leadership.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89434410-153d-11ef-accb-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 17:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I live with my parents and generational trauma ‘runs the house’</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I live with my parents and generational trauma ‘runs the house’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae46b6c0-1533-11ef-ab1d-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 16:28:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>She left the CIA in frustration. Now her spy novel is racking up awards.</title>
      <description>Ilana Berry served as a case officer and volunteered to go to Iraq in 2004. The pages that would become “The Peacock and the Sparrow,” a novel featuring a weary CIA officer caught in the turbines of Middle Eastern political change, include themes mined straight from her time at the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cedf3160-152d-11ef-9c6c-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 15:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Home prices are falling in some parts of the U.S. — and rising in others. We’ve broken it down by Zip code.</title>
      <description>In the past year, home prices increased 5.8 percent — a steadier rise after the volatile years of the early pandemic, according to a Washington Post analysis of home value data. Look up your Zip code to see how home prices are changing in your neighborhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5053930-1524-11ef-accb-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 14:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77ad3df0-151a-11ef-9b42-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 13:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden and Trump cut a deal on debates. Then the fighting started.</title>
      <description>The Trump and Biden campaigns, with the help of eager networks, found a way to come together for debates on CNN next month and ABC in September, even as animosity between the two camps remained high.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e7aad7a1-14a4-11ef-a32e-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 23:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dabney Coleman dies at 92. The actor excelled at portrayals of comic scoundrels.</title>
      <description>He created an acclaimed gallery of comically macho throwbacks in films including “9 to 5” and “Tootsie” and TV shows such as “The Slap Maxwell Story” and “Buffalo Bill.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f29b890-149d-11ef-8d25-0000a1ace9f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 22:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dow closes above 40,000 for the first time, passing a key milestone for the widely followed stock index</title>
      <description>The market’s gains, analysts said, reflect renewed confidence that the Federal Reserve can win its inflation fight without breaking the economy, contributing to a tech-driven rally in stocks that shows little sign of slowing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e8b41b02-1488-11ef-a573-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 20:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel says it has no plans to occupy Gaza. But its military has built a strategic corridor that suggests a long-term presence.</title>
      <description>Satellite images and other visual evidence show Israel has constructed roads, outposts and buffer zones along the Netzarim Corridor, which runs from the Israeli border to the Mediterranean Sea, despite insisting there are no plans to permanently occupy Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7495ec10-147b-11ef-8bf2-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 18:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: I was the other woman. Can I befriend the ex-wife who didn’t know?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: I was the other woman. Can I befriend the ex-wife who didn’t know?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">446e92b0-146e-11ef-9999-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Gaza, Israeli military recovers the bodies of three hostages who were killed on Oct. 7</title>
      <description>In an overnight operation based on intelligence, Israeli forces retrieved the bodies of Yitzhak Gelernter, Shani Louk, and Amit Buskila, a military spokesman said. The Israel Defense Forces said Palestinian militants killed the three Israelis on Oct. 7 and took their bodies back into Gaza.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85aaeae0-1468-11ef-b920-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 16:14:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70 years after Brown v. Board of Education, 1 in 3 Black people say integration didn’t help Black students</title>
      <description>The landmark ruling is overwhelmingly popular, but a Washington Post-Ipsos poll finds complex views on its legacy and the path forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d0123760-1462-11ef-b6b4-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 15:33:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scottie Scheffler says ‘a big misunderstanding’ led to his arrest near PGA Championship</title>
      <description>Scheffler, the top-ranked golfer in the world, was arrested Friday morning over a traffic-related incident as he was attempting to enter Valhalla Golf Club, the site of the PGA Championship. “It was a very chaotic situation, understandably so considering the tragic accident that had occurred earlier, and there was a big misunderstanding of what I thought I was being asked to do,” he said in a statement shortly before beginning his second round. Earlier in the day, traffic entering the golf club was backed up because of an overnight fatal accident involving a worker for a tournament vendor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44abef00-145c-11ef-afad-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98751090-1451-11ef-acd4-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 13:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World’s top-ranked golfer Scottie Scheffler arrested after a traffic-related incident near PGA Championship</title>
      <description>Scheffler was handcuffed and detained by Louisville police Friday morning, for a traffic-related incident as he was attempting to enter Valhalla Golf Club for the second round of the PGA Championship. Tournament officials delayed the start of Friday’s round, but Scheffler’s status was uncertain and it wasn’t clear Friday morning whether the world’s most dominant player would be on the tee box for the second round of the year’s second major championship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d5f8050-144a-11ef-878b-0000a1ace92b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 12:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial. Gaza pier. Houston storms. Black Lives Matter. Marijuana. City populations. Taco ruling. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dcf0c40-143c-11ef-ae44-000a1ace5193</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 11:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brazil to host 2027 women’s World Cup as tournament heads to South America for first time</title>
      <description>Brazil had been considered the front-runner and won out over a joint bid by Belgium, the Netherlands and Germany. The decision was announced at FIFA’s 74th Congress in Bangkok, and it was the first time a host was chosen through an open vote by the organization’s 211 member associations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59a6c010-1434-11ef-9b42-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 10:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. military begins Gaza aid deliveries from floating pier</title>
      <description>American military personnel have begun moving humanitarian aid to Gaza using a floating pier, officials said, adding that no U.S. troops went ashore. It marks the start of an operation directed by President Biden to help alleviate the humanitarian crisis in the enclave — but whose critics fear it will leave American troops vulnerable to attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b6fe650-1418-11ef-88da-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 06:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 dead as destructive thunderstorm blasts Houston; 800,000 lose power in Harris County</title>
      <description>At least four people were killed during a violent thunderstorm complex that ripped through downtown Houston and the surrounding area, the Houston mayor’s office said. Destructive winds downed trees and blew out skyscraper windows, according to social media reports.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">296f7710-13f9-11ef-abc2-00000a1ace1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 02:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas Gov. Greg Abbott grants former Army Sgt. Daniel Perry pardon in 2020 murder of Black Lives Matter protester</title>
      <description>The Texas governor has pushed for Perry’s pardon since his conviction last year. Perry was sentenced to 25 years in prison for the fatal shooting of a protester during a Black Lives Matter march.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70cf5b50-13c4-11ef-aad7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 20:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business titans privately urged New York City’s mayor to use police on Columbia protesters, WhatsApp chats show</title>
      <description>A group of billionaires and business titans working to shape U.S. public opinion of the war in Gaza privately pressed Mayor Eric Adams (D) last month to send police to disperse pro-Palestinian protests at Columbia University, according to communications obtained by The Washington Post and people familiar with the group.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cc4cafb0-13b9-11ef-885a-0000a1ace0d1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 19:23:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. to end coal leasing in nation’s largest coal-producing region, a win for climate activists</title>
      <description>The Biden administration announced it will end coal leasing on federal lands in the Powder River Basin, which produces nearly half the coal in the United States. The decision by the Interior Department’s Bureau of Land Management affects a vast coal-producing region that stretches more than 13 million acres across Montana and Wyoming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f95e5180-13ae-11ef-9e32-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 18:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
