<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 15:02:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Painting a zoo in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33e9dbe0-58af-11ef-bc60-00000a1ace37</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 13:31:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump hack. Rally crowds. Gaza strike. Uvalde videos. Boeing woes. Allergy spray. Tom Cruise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03375320-589a-11ef-9a14-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 10:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Olympics needed a reset. Merci to Paris for providing it, columnist Barry Svrluga writes.</title>
      <description>After lackluster Olympics in Tokyo and Beijing and disappointing hosts even before the coronavirus pandemic, these Summer Games were exactly what the whole enterprise needed and in a style no other city could provide, Svrluga writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143365a1-582d-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 22:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After two years of far-right rule in a Michigan county, the opposition had one chance to change it</title>
      <description>Divisive, Trump-style politics came to Ottawa County. Then moderate Republicans and some Democrats mobilized and fought back.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5df105a0-581c-11ef-bb78-000a1ace1b0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 20:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s plan to upend the federal workforce could rattle the DMV economy</title>
      <description>The Republican presidential nominee’s Agenda47 policy manifesto and his party platform seek to “shatter the Deep State” with actions such as moving up to 100,000 federal positions out of D.C., which experts say could be devastating to the area’s economy. Virginia, Maryland and D.C. are among the top four jurisdictions nationwide for federal civilian employees.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d1869f40-580b-11ef-a3ac-0000a1ace14b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 18:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 16 highlights from Paris Olympics: Team USA wraps up Games tied with China in gold medals and atop total medal count</title>
      <description>Sunday’s win over France in the women’s basketball final gave the United States a 40th gold, enough to finish the competition even with China. Team USA’s 126 medals overall easily topped China’s 91. American gymnast Jordan Chiles must return her bronze medal from the women’s floor exercise. And Dutch distance runner Sifan Hassan won the women’s marathon in Olympic record time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">757edca0-57ff-11ef-a7af-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 16:33:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69d37140-57fa-11ef-8c2c-00000a1ace65</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:57:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s basketball team, trailing in second half, comes back to beat host France and capture eighth straight Olympic gold</title>
      <description>One of the Olympics’ greatest dynasties was tested Sunday. But the United States survived and has now won 10 of 13 Olympic women’s basketball tournaments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4db86e0-57f5-11ef-8936-00000a1ace1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:24:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you reduce your risk of cancer? Here’s what an oncologist with a family history of diagnoses does.</title>
      <description>Taking sun protection seriously is one of this doctor’s five tips to prevent a cancer diagnosis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7b5c5a0-57f2-11ef-8201-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 15:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. women’s basketball team takes on host France for its eighth straight Olympic gold. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Team USA, the heavy favorite, is on a 60-game winning streak in the Olympics and looking to make it back-to-back wins for American men’s and women’s basketball over the French. This is France’s second appearance in a gold medal game.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f840fa70-57e5-11ef-b4a7-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 13:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e939ab0-57e2-11ef-a16b-0000a1ace146</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 13:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. gymnast Jordan Chiles must return her Olympic bronze medal for floor after court ruling</title>
      <description>Chiles won her medal Monday after a coach’s inquiry lifted her over Romania’s Ana Barbosu, but the Court of Arbitration for Sport ruled Saturday that the inquiry that benefited Chiles was filed after the one-minute deadline. The International Olympic Committee confirmed Sunday morning that the medal would be reallocated to Barbosu.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae66aeb0-57ca-11ef-acb9-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:15:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign says it is the victim of a foreign hack after the leak of a report on Vance</title>
      <description>Microsoft discovered evidence that Iranian hackers compromised the email account of a former Trump campaign adviser, a person familiar with the matter says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90ce24b0-576f-11ef-adfa-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 23:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 15 highlights from Paris Olympics: U.S. track and field stands out behind stars Sydney McLaughlin-Levrone, Gabby Thomas and Rai Benjamin</title>
      <description>Benjamin's huge anchor leg ensured the men's 4x400 team the victory. On the women's side, McLaughlin-Levrone ran away from everyone on the second leg, and Thomas followed suit en route to an easy win. Also on the track, American Masai Russell brought home gold in the women's 100-meter hurdles. And elsewhere, the U.S. women's soccer and men's basketball teams added golds of their own.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6139cd70-576b-11ef-9ab4-0000a1ace6f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 22:53:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. men’s basketball team beats host France, capturing gold for the fifth straight Olympics</title>
      <description>Led by aging stars LeBron James, Steph Curry and Kevin Durant, the Americans went 6-0 in the Paris Games and captured gold in front of rabid French fans in central Paris. The Americans last failed to win gold in 2004.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">198e1920-575e-11ef-9942-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 21:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. men take on Victor Wembanyama and host nation France in a battle for Olympic hoops gold. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Team USA was the tournament’s favorite. Backed by rabid fans, France has notched multiple upsets along the way. Now the teams will battle for gold in Paris.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0bac7fc0-574c-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 19:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. women’s soccer team beats Brazil, 1-0, to capture its first Olympic gold medal since 2012</title>
      <description>Mallory Swanson scored the winning goal in the 57th minute. With a new coach and new-look roster, the Americans stormed through the Olympic tournament undefeated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e448ca30-573a-11ef-97e4-00000a1ace91</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 17:06:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I feel pressured by my family’s hopes for my future partner</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I feel pressured by my family’s hopes for my future partner</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff4192c0-5737-11ef-9e1d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 16:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The U.S. women’s soccer team, seeking its first Olympic gold since 2012, is set to take on Brazil in Paris. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Led by a new cohort of young stars, the Americans have stormed through the tournament undefeated after a disappointing World Cup last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d8c7f80-5727-11ef-92d9-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 14:47:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pastor claimed his pro-Trump prophecies came from God. His brother called him a fake.</title>
      <description>Jeremiah Johnson found religious fame after leaning into politics. His brother, also a preacher, worried he was twisting the Lord’s word for money and power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c24b27d0-5720-11ef-9928-0000a1acecdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 13:59:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d2a7fc0-571c-11ef-aeba-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 13:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frank Zappa’s kids are still grappling with his legacy — and each other</title>
      <description>Dweezil no longer speaks to his siblings. Moon has spent decades reassessing the family dynamic — emotional labor that lies thick on the pages of her new memoir.

Ahmet and Diva, meanwhile, seem dazed still by the force of their siblings’ anger — siblings with whom they share not just a fraught business partnership but also a one-of-a-kind childhood.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8834b451-56a6-11ef-9400-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 23:24:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 14 highlights from Paris Olympics: American Rai Benjamin rules the track; U.S. women’s basketball will play for gold</title>
      <description>Benjamin breezed to a gold medal in the men's 400-meter hurdles and helped erase the foibles of the U.S. men's 4x100 relay team, which finished seventh and was eventually disqualified because of a bad first baton exchange. Elsewhere, the U.S. women smothered Australia on the basketball court, ensuring a trip to their eighth straight gold medal game, where they will meet France on Sunday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3bca4e0-56a0-11ef-b28e-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA rejects first psychedelic to treat PTSD, marking a setback and calling for more study of ecstasy-based drug</title>
      <description>The Food and Drug Administration declined to approve MDMA to treat post-traumatic stress disorder, instead calling for another large study that could take years to complete.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e97cc591-569c-11ef-845e-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 22:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imane Khelif, female boxer who was a target of online attacks over ‘gender eligibility’ test, wins Olympic gold</title>
      <description>The Algerian fighter faced online hate after a Russia-linked boxing organization disqualified her from last year's world championships.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3843df31-5696-11ef-9e61-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 21:27:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at Nixon’s resignation 50 years later</title>
      <description>On Aug. 9, 1974, Richard M. Nixon became the only U.S. president to have ever resigned. Learn more about the Watergate scandal and what led to his downfall.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e3b63b0-5691-11ef-9891-0000a1ace932</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 20:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man who pleaded guilty to assaulting police during Capitol attack gets 20 years, the second longest sentence of Jan. 6 defendants</title>
      <description>David N. Dempsey deployed chemical spray on police and attacked them with poles in one of the most violent confrontations between law enforcement and the mob on Jan. 6, 2021. He pleaded guilty earlier this year to two counts of assaulting police with dangerous or deadly weapons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7352acf0-5682-11ef-a218-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 19:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A domestic flight with 62 people on board crashed in Brazil. It's unclear whether anyone survived.</title>
      <description>The plane crashed in a residential area in Vinhedo, a city in the state of São Paulo, leaving a fiery wreck as firefighters and military police responded.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d81e1ef1-5680-11ef-afe3-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 18:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anchored by Sha'Carri Richardson, American women win gold in 4x100-meter relay, the 10th gold for U.S. track tea</title>
      <description>The American women have won the event in three of the past four Olympics and 12 times in Olympic history, more than any other country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15361410-5676-11ef-9d0d-000a1ace5b92</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 17:37:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vietnam accelerates island building to challenge rising Chinese assertiveness in the South China Sea</title>
      <description>As tensions mount, Vietnam is dredging and filling in land, fortifying barriers and erecting structures to establish new military outposts. Satellite imagery reveals that Vietnam has ramped up its effort since January and is on track to create more than 1,000 acres of island territory this year, more than in any year prior.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0a19bb90-566c-11ef-901b-0000a1acec0f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: This couple want a life partnership, but worry the institution of marriage will ruin their relationship.</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: This couple want a life partnership, but worry the institution of marriage will ruin their relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31ff9411-566a-11ef-ba6b-0000a1ace5d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 16:12:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flash flood warnings in effect for D.C. area, tornadoes possible throughout region</title>
      <description>Torrential rain has prompted flash flood warnings for large parts of the metro region through late Friday morning. A tornado watch is also in effect until 2 p.m. and multiple warnings have already been issued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">919afe31-5649-11ef-b6fc-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 12:19:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs. Harris. Rally shooting. Ukraine attack. Debby. Mpox outbreak. Cash App payout. Noah Lyles. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7eb4bd70-563e-11ef-9b82-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 10:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Lyles was a reminder of the pandemic on the night he could've become an Olympic legend, columnist Jerry Brewer writes</title>
      <description>The U.S. sprinter finished third in the 200-meter race he was widely expected to win, then revealed he had tested positive for the coronavirus and indicated his Paris Games were over. Although we thought covid was behind us, Brewer writes, Thursday felt like the pandemic-affected 2021 Tokyo Olympics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">adf79af1-55e2-11ef-bb84-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:02:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Harris and Walz in, some Democrats still consider withholding their vote in response to the Israel-Gaza war</title>
      <description>During the primaries, pro-Palestinian activists urged voters to withhold their support for President Joe Biden over his handling of the war. Roughly 700,000 Democrats nationwide checked a no-candidate option, left their presidential ballot blank or wrote in someone (or something) else. While that represents a tiny sliver of the electorate — and analysts lack data on each voter’s motivation — some strategists said the apparent protest turnout revealed weak spots for Kamala Harris’s campaign.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a77b1710-55dd-11ef-bb6b-0000a1ace954</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 23:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 13 highlights from Paris Olympics: Holloway, Davis-Woodhall win big in track and field; U.S. men's basketball survives scare</title>
      <description>Grant Holloway cruised to victory in the men's 110-meter hurdles while Tara Davis-Woodhall captured her first Olympic gold, but they were perhaps overshadowed by Noah Lyles's bronze in the 200 meters and subsequent revelation that he ran with covid-19. In other events, the U.S. men's basketball team trailed for more than 35 of 40 minutes versus Nikola Jokic and Serbia but narrowly avoided what would have been its first Olympic loss since the 2004 Athens Games.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eef0f380-55d8-11ef-9b9a-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 22:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Harris confirm they will attend ABC’s Sept. 10 presidential debate as scheduled, network says</title>
      <description>Former president Donald Trump said in a Thursday news conference that he wants to debate his opponent three times, including the Sept. 10 date that was previously agreed to by both parties’ campaigns before President Joe Biden withdrew from the 2024 race. That date will serve as the first time Trump and Kamala Harris will share a stage since she was tapped to replace Biden weeks ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2825d90-55be-11ef-89a2-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American Sydney McLaughlin-Levrone breaks her own world record and wins gold in women’s 400-meter hurdles</title>
      <description>McLaughlin-Levrone ran the event in 50.37 seconds to break the world record she set at Olympic trials in June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13afe850-55bd-11ef-bff7-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:33:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>American sprinter Noah Lyles says he tested positive for the coronavirus before winning Olympic bronze in 200 meters</title>
      <description>After struggling in his signature event, he left the track breathing heavily while riding in a wheelchair. Lyles tested positive for the coronavirus two days ago, he told NBC, adding that he was leaning toward skipping the 4x100-meter relay.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a8a6090-55bc-11ef-aa1c-0000a1aced64</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 19:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noah Lyles, U.S. sprint star who was trying for second Paris gold, takes bronze in 200 meters. Teammate Kenny Bednarek won silver.</title>
      <description>Lyles previously won the 100-meter dash and will race for at least one more gold in Paris. He was trying to become the first man since Jamaican Usain Bolt to win the 100 and 200 in the same Games, and the first American man since Carl Lewis in 1984.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45832980-55b5-11ef-bc56-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 18:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you become an athlete at 70? Ask us how to feel like an Olympian at any age in our Well+Being chat.</title>
      <description>Can you become an athlete at 70? Ask us how to feel like an Olympian at any age in our Well+Being chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0efeac60-55a9-11ef-8a00-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 17:10:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debby will bring a threat of heavy rain, flooding and tornadoes. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>The remnants of the tropical storm will sweep across the Mid-Atlantic from Thursday night into Friday. In the D.C. area, it could produce 1.5 to 3 inches of rain and a few tornadoes. Mountains to the west will see more rain and a serious threat of flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6f2168c0-55a5-11ef-b253-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surprise Ukrainian attack in western Russia stuns Moscow and raises questions about Kyiv’s use of U.S.-donated weapons</title>
      <description>A cross-border assault by Ukrainian forces into the Kursk region that began Tuesday raised questions about whether Kyiv’s forces violated Western restrictions on the use of fighting vehicles and weapons donated by the United States and other countries. The operation, which Ukrainian officials have declined to comment on, is the largest Ukrainian incursion on Russian territory since 2022. It could mark a new chapter in the war.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5e2d070-55a0-11ef-ac72-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:11:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: How to get over the hurt of a mom who never wants to get in touch?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: How to get over the hurt of a mom who never wants to get in touch?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">74257e71-559f-11ef-94bb-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 16:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump has been complaining about his campaign to friends and advisers as Harris’s poll numbers surge</title>
      <description>The GOP nominee has grown increasingly upset about Kamala Harris’s crowd sizes and media coverage since she replaced Joe Biden on the Democratic ticket. The situation has left people close to the campaign wondering why Donald Trump and his team seemed ill-prepared for Harris’s entry into the race after Biden’s disastrous June debate performance.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e17b401-5597-11ef-bcd0-00000a1ace8f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 15:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A boxer’s home country is your answer to today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88a46e21-558a-11ef-a9be-0000a1ace24f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump complaints. Harris protest. Taylor Swift. Covid surge. Toxic water. Stuck astronauts. Team USA. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">552cd1f0-5575-11ef-bab1-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz’s Army record faces scrutiny as GOP critics, fellow veterans question claims about his service</title>
      <description>The Harris-Walz campaign has cited the vice-presidential candidate's 24 years of military experience as an asset. But Republicans and some who served with the Minnesota governor have decried his decision to retire before their National Guard unit went to war and his characterization of aspects of his time in uniform.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a3f46b0-5520-11ef-bb09-000a1ace847c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 00:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nancy Pelosi says she joined the effort to urge Biden to end reelection bid because his campaign had ‘no path to victory’</title>
      <description>In her most extensive remarks yet about the the political earthquake of the past few weeks, the former House speaker said she was concerned President Joe Biden staying in the race would inevitably lead to the reelection of Donald Trump. Pelosi, who carries tremendous clout on Capitol Hill and in the Democratic Party, also said that while she did not make any phone calls seeking Biden’s ouster, “hundreds” of people who wanted to see that outcome called her.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7356eca1-5517-11ef-b860-0000a1ace404</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 23:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 12 highlights from Paris Olympics: Noah Lyles advances to 200-meter final; U.S. women's basketball cruises to win</title>
      <description>Lyles, the world's fastest human, qualified for the final of the men's 200 meters set for Thursday. American Quincy Hall came from behind to capture gold in the stirring men's 400-meter final. In other events, the U.S. women's basketball team easily handled Nigeria in a quarterfinal. And the United States ended a 20-year medal drought with silver in artistic swimming.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80bb6260-550b-11ef-b8b1-0000a1ace979</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 22:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
