<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 10:01:25 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>About 75 people were killed in Venezuela during military raid to capture Maduro, U.S. officials assess</title>
      <description>The sizable death toll adds meaning to President Donald Trump’s public remarks that the operation he approved was “effective” but “very violent.” Details of the operation indicate that there were zero U.S. fatalities, but seven service members were injured, the Pentagon said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38ac5381-eb64-11f0-adad-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 01:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House floats military option for seizing Greenland, rattling Denmark and NATO</title>
      <description>The rhetoric follows a dramatic U.S. raid in Venezuela and revives Trump’s long-standing focus on the Danish territory, transforming diplomatic discussions into fears of coercion. But U.S. military posture there remains unchanged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1446fa0-eb62-11f0-adad-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aldrich Ames, the most damaging CIA traitor in agency history, dies in prison at 84</title>
      <description>Ames turned over the names of recruited Soviet and Warsaw Pact agents and information about hundreds of intelligence operations to Moscow in return for money. His actions reportedly caused the deaths of at least 10 recruited CIA or allied intelligence agents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">547abfc1-eb5a-11f0-a1c1-000a1ace544b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brown University suspect admitted to planning shooting for a long time, prosecutors say</title>
      <description>Federal officials released a transcript of short videos they said Claudio Manuel Neves Valente recorded in Portuguese. Police found Valente dead of a self-inflicted gunshot wound Dec. 18 at a New Hampshire storage facility.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47bd79c2-eb56-11f0-8f14-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 23:20:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Baltimore Ravens part ways with coach John Harbaugh after 18 seasons</title>
      <description>Under Harbaugh, the Ravens reached the playoffs 12 times and won a Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7a54580-eb50-11f0-9bc0-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fear grips Caracas as a new wave of repression is unleashed</title>
      <description>Venezuela’s government has moved quickly to suppress any public expression of support for Nicolás Maduro’s ouster, launching a nationwide crackdown that has included the detention of journalists, the arrest of civilians and the deployment of armed gangs across the capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd7f0170-eb4e-11f0-a221-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:27:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming Supreme Court strikes down first-of-its-kind ban on abortion pills</title>
      <description>The court also rolled back a broader prohibition on abortions, citing a state constitution provision that guarantees residents the right to make health care decisions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5bdd481-eb3b-11f0-b020-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 20:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: They’ve become this mom’s free day care, and she has notes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: They’ve become this mom’s free day care, and she has notes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6ed77ef1-eb21-11f0-81d1-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump might have his hubris checked in Venezuela, David Ignatius writes</title>
      <description>The president has launched a violent process of change that he can’t fully control.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">791de040-eb1f-11f0-8ac7-0000a1ace9f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>McMansions may be making homeowners miserable. Our columnist explains why.</title>
      <description>As the size of the average American home has nearly doubled, the people living in them aren’t any happier.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65444fc0-eb1d-11f0-acde-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rep. Doug LaMalfa (R-California) has died at 65. His passing challenges the GOP’s House majority.</title>
      <description>The seven-term congressman represented a district that encompassed much of Northern California’s interior. His district was redrawn last year, taking it from a safely GOP seat to a Democratic-leaning one.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b54f2640-eb11-11f0-ba54-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 15:09:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A memorable character in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5809380-eb0b-11f0-afec-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 14:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro in court. Childhood vaccines. Pete Hegseth. FEMA cuts. Grok images. ADHD drugs. Fiber advice. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31969820-eaf7-11f0-8a19-0000a1acebdf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents outline potential cuts affecting thousands of FEMA disaster responders</title>
      <description>Department of Homeland Security Secretary Kristi L. Noem has said she wants to reduce FEMA’s staff by half. Drafted plans show how it can happen.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c486c610-ea9c-11f0-b8be-0000a1ace517</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 01:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This fun hobby may reduce your dementia risk by 76 percent</title>
      <description>There are several science-based ways to boost your brain health, Dr. Trisha Pasricha writes, but this one might surprise you.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a252000-ea96-11f0-b77b-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:24:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. overhauls childhood vaccine schedule, recommending fewer shots</title>
      <description>The new strategy would no longer broadly recommend vaccines for RSV, flu, hepatitis A and B, rotavirus and meningitis. The Trump administration says this aligns the U.S. with peer countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">47473f90-ea6a-11f0-b8be-0000a1ace517</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:11:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband does travel — just not with spouse to visit family</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband does travel — just not with spouse to visit family</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">665ec080-ea59-11f0-98bd-0000a1ace5d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:10:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela’s Nicolás Maduro is set to appear in court for his arraignment in Manhattan. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The deposed Venezuelan leader has been transferred by helicopter to Manhattan, where he and his wife, Cilia Flores, are set to be arraigned at noon at the U.S. District Court on charges that they enriched themselves through drug trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41a67e10-ea57-11f0-a3ca-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:54:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s some turbulence in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5af4ae70-ea55-11f0-b1bd-0000a1ace8f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 16:41:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth announces censure and potential demotion of Sen. Mark Kelly</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has targeted the Arizona Democrat, a retired Navy officer, over a video reminding U.S. troops they can disobey illegal orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">caf11031-ea4e-11f0-a339-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is college worth it? This quiz shows the reality.</title>
      <description>Views on the importance of higher education have fallen sharply in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3caa5cd0-ea4b-11f0-a339-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Walz drops bid for reelection as Minnesota governor</title>
      <description>The former Democratic vice presidential nominee stepped aside amid a growing fraud probe.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89f91930-ea42-11f0-bd84-00000a1ace51</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 14:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We texted 1,000 Americans about U.S. actions in Venezuela. Here’s what they said.</title>
      <description>A Post poll shows Americans are split on sending military forces to Venezuela to capture Maduro. Most say President Donald Trump’s action should have required Congress’s approval.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3c2b160-ea36-11f0-8374-0000a1ace166</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 13:01:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maduro arraignment. Venezuela poll. Midterm outlook. Secret Service. Malnutrition. NFL playoffs. Dancing benefits. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">075dac20-ea2e-11f0-ad04-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL playoffs are set. Here’s the full bracket, plus the matchups and the schedule for the first round and beyond.</title>
      <description>The Denver Broncos in the AFC and the Seattle Seahawks in the NFC are the No. 1 seeds. They’ll each have a first-round bye and home-field advantage through the conference championship games. The NFL’s 12 other playoff teams will be in action next weekend. Here is how the first round shakes out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">299de850-e9f1-11f0-8bf5-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 04:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the scientific consensus on microplastics shifted in 2025</title>
      <description>The year has been full of scary details about the tiny particles. Here’s what we know now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26375470-e993-11f0-90e0-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 17:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2290a781-e97b-11f0-80ff-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:39:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marco Rubio takes on his most challenging assignment yet: Viceroy of Venezuela</title>
      <description>The top U.S. diplomat has held many titles during Donald Trump’s presidency. Now Trump is leaning on him to help “run” Venezuela, divvy up its oil assets and usher in a new government.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4083d640-e976-11f0-89c3-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:04:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A CIA informant and elite Army commandos with blowtorches: Audacious Maduro raid relied on months of preparation</title>
      <description>Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, were taken by helicopter to the USS Iwo Jima, an amphibious assault ship positioned off Venezuela and from there were flown to New York, where they will face criminal charges of drug-trafficking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8dc63501-e909-11f0-a7d2-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 01:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump goes monster-hunting, untainted by a whiff of legality, George F. Will writes</title>
      <description>"That Nicolás Maduro is a monster is patent, as was the illegitimacy of his government, which disdained respect for the consent of the governed. But the urgent argument begins, not ends, with those two facts."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c2e06a0-e8fa-11f0-9e38-00000a1ace0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 23:18:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro and his wife arrive in New York hours after U.S. capture in Venezuela</title>
      <description>Maduro and his wife, Cilia Flores, arrived in New York on Saturday afternoon following a U.S. raid that captured the couple earlier in the day. A U.S. government plane flew the couple into Stewart International Airport north of New York City, where they face federal charges of illegally enriching themselves as they conspired to flood the United States with cocaine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8b4d7f0-e8f2-11f0-989d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 22:23:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says U.S. will ‘run’ Venezuela during transition after U.S. raid captured Maduro</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said Saturday at his Mar-a-Lago club that the United States will control Venezuela for an unspecified period after a U.S. operation captured Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro and his wife.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">089020b0-e8c5-11f0-bfb7-0000a1acebbb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump to speak following U.S. operation that captured Venezuela’s Maduro. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The United States launched a “large scale strike” on Venezuela, captured President Nicolás Maduro and his wife and flew them out of the country, President Donald Trump said in a social media post early Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfaeae80-e8bd-11f0-98cf-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:03:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s bold capture of Maduro was a victory for American interests, the Editorial Board writes. What’s next?</title>
      <description>The next challenge is setting the country up for long-term success.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0755da0-e8bb-11f0-beef-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Maduro being taken to New York by ship after his capture following Venezuela strikes</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said that the Maduros were placed on a ship, the USS Iwo Jima, to be taken to New York, and that they were removed from Venezuela by helicopter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88bd7e50-e8b5-11f0-ba75-000a1ace59b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 15:04:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de3fd9e0-e8b0-11f0-b860-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 14:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says Maduro captured in ‘large scale strike’ against Venezuela</title>
      <description>The United States carried out a large-scale strike on Venezuela, capturing its president, Nicolás Maduro, and flying him out of the country, President Trump said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b6cae80-e889-11f0-9d0d-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 09:50:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explosions and aircraft heard over Venezuelan capital</title>
      <description>Explosions were heard and smoke could be seen rising in multiple locations across Caracas in the early morning Saturday, as aircraft were seen flying over the Venezuelan capital.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73314fe0-e873-11f0-9c87-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 07:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quest for a drug that lowers an artery-clogging particle nears finish line</title>
      <description>A clinical trial will soon reveal whether lowering high levels of lipoprotein(a) can reduce the risk of heart attacks and strokes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2af948a0-e83b-11f0-a0be-00000a1ace86</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 00:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How student loans and financial aid are changing in 2026</title>
      <description>Here's a look ahead at the federal policies taking effect that will shape how students and families pay for college.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7404b3d0-e823-11f0-a3c6-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 21:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He exposed the myth of the South’s ‘Lost Cause.’ His death shook Richmond.</title>
      <description>William “Bill” Martin, 71, died Dec. 28, a day after being struck by a car near the Valentine local history museum where he had served as director more than 30 years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10aba840-e7fe-11f0-b6dd-0000a1ace147</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 best things Trump did in 2025, according to Marc Thiessen</title>
      <description>The 20 best things Trump did in 2025</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c2653be0-e7fa-11f0-aa01-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:47:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swiss bar fire started by sparklers on champagne bottles, officials say</title>
      <description>The deadly blaze spread quickly after the sparklers came close to the ceiling of the bar in the early hours of New Year’s Day, according to Beatrice Pilloud, attorney general of the Swiss canton of Valais. Investigators have analyzed footage of the incident and spoken to the bar’s managers as well as survivors, Pilloud said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd0a2e60-e7ec-11f0-bd99-0000a1acef04</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 15:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don’t forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Blurb: Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">38c0be30-e7e8-11f0-9cf4-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:35:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What a longevity expert eats in a day</title>
      <description>Cardiologist Eric Topol has studied “super agers” for years. This is exactly what he eats — and avoids.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eeeb2400-e7e5-11f0-aea4-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fire investigation. Zohran Mamdani. Trump’s jobs claim. Sinking dams. Heart risk. ‘Super agers.’ Vacation time. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87171270-e7d2-11f0-8d3e-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flu cases are rising with a strain that makes older people sicker</title>
      <description>Influenza season is ramping up in the U.S., marked by a new strain that could make vaccines less effective. Covid cases remain down.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aaf4b220-e76d-11f0-98e9-0000a1ace702</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 things to declutter right now to start the year lighter</title>
      <description>Parting with your things can be hard. Picking some easy(ish) decluttering projects is a great way to build momentum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a5a5d041-e751-11f0-a113-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About 40 killed, 115 injured in New Year’s bar fire at Swiss ski resort</title>
      <description>The fire struck the Constellation bar in Crans-Montana, in the heart of the Swiss Alps, around 1:30 a.m., as New Year’s celebrations were underway. Officials ruled out the possibility of an attack and are investigating the cause of the blaze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98087a90-e739-11f0-930d-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:44:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you eating for a longer life? Take our science-backed quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>If you want to know if you’re on the right track, answer the following simple questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67e296e0-e723-11f0-81ce-000a1ace6325</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 15:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
