<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 19:03:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Suspected driver in New Orleans attack identified as U.S. citizen with an ISIS flag, weapons and potential IED in his truck</title>
      <description>The FBI said authorities were investigating the attack, which killed at least 10 and injured dozens, as an act of terrorism. They identified the driver as Shamsud-Din Jabbar, a 42-year-old U.S. citizen from Texas. He was declared dead after a shootout with police. Investigators found an ISIS flag in the vehicle he was driving, along with additional weapons and a possible improvised explosive device, the FBI said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86295c30-c86e-11ef-a551-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 18:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Losing patience with all these ‘overly nice’ people</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Losing patience with all these ‘overly nice’ people</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12a81410-c862-11ef-aafa-00000a1ace7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 17:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What strange things could 2025 have in store? Take David Ignatius’s quiz to find out.</title>
      <description>Can you tell “humint” and “rumint” apart from straight-up nonsense?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04237860-c85a-11ef-b738-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 16:04:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year! Play today’s On the Record now.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your first points of 2025.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">20cabfd1-c84d-11ef-81ac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 14:31:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driver of truck that killed 10 in New Orleans is dead, FBI says. Attack is being investigated as an act of terrorism.</title>
      <description>The FBI said the driver of the vehicle that plowed into a crowd on Bourbon Street at 3:15 a.m. "engaged with law enforcement" after the attack and is now dead. No further details were available. At an early morning news conference, officials gave conflicting information about whether the attack was an act of terrorism.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5f707550-c84c-11ef-a703-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 14:26:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man rammed pickup truck into New Orleans crowd to create ‘carnage,’ killing 10, official says. He fired on police after crashing.</title>
      <description>New Orleans Police Superintendent Anne Kirkpatrick said a man tried “to run over as many people as he possibly could” in the incident on Bourbon Street overnight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9d821e1-c844-11ef-be8e-0000a1ace752</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 13:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 killed, 30 injured in New Orleans as vehicle plows into crowd, city officials say</title>
      <description>The emergency preparedness agency of New Orleans said the mass casualty incident took place in the Bourbon Street area overnight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59371d50-c839-11ef-b8de-0000a1ace23d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 12:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/11 plea deals. Russian gas. ‘Gone Girl’ charges. Stock rally. Cruise outbreaks. College football. Poisoned goat. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3cbb771-c837-11ef-8924-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 11:59:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following up on the stories that moved us in 2024: A penguin love story, a law student and baby, life after ‘Love Is Blind’</title>
      <description>In a seemingly never-ending news cycle, Post reporters took a step back and revisited the stories that made headlines in our region this year. Some were entertaining, some were tragic, and some were just odd.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd51d900-c7c6-11ef-9de1-0000a1ace1f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 22:30:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 was a great year for the S&amp;P 500. See how the market bet on AI hopes, a Fed policy change, the election and bitcoin.</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 ended 2024 up more than 23 percent for the year, carried in the first half by the “Magnificent Seven” stocks: Alphabet, Amazon, Apple, Meta, Microsoft, Nvidia and Tesla. They were joined in the last few months by a broader market rally, as the Federal Reserve started cutting interest rates and Donald Trump won the November election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bbf44b1-c7be-11ef-97a1-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 21:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covert killings reveal the contours of an ambitious Indian assassination program</title>
      <description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi has cast himself as more willing to take on India’s enemies beyond its borders than any other leader since independence. India’s intelligence agency, the Research and Analysis Wing, has since 2021 deployed a methodical assassination program to kill at least a half-dozen people deep within Pakistan, according to Pakistani and Western officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">60ef90f0-c7ac-11ef-9013-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 19:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She can organize the bachelorette but can’t stand up with the bride</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She can organize the bachelorette but can’t stand up with the bride</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13d7d3d0-c799-11ef-b54a-00000a1ace3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 17:02:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Olympics, Notre Dame and pandas: Here are 24 good things that happened in 2024</title>
      <description>We will remember these silver linings going into the New Year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eca15250-c793-11ef-a1c6-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 16:26:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The List: What’s out and what’s in for 2025</title>
      <description>Nepo babies. Nepo in-laws. Celebrity look-alike contests. Celebrity digital replica laws. A Post tradition since 1978, The List reveals the present and predicts the future.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d475ad20-c78e-11ef-abf9-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 15:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s the last day of 2024! Fittingly, our Year in Review continues in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2258f340-c784-11ef-a434-00000a1acefb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:32:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. strikes Houthi targets in Yemen in escalating campaign</title>
      <description>The U.S. military carried out fresh airstrikes against Houthi targets in Yemen, the U.S. Central Command said Tuesday, the latest in an escalating campaign against the Iran-backed militants by Israel and its allies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5295fa0-c782-11ef-8807-0000a1ace4d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 14:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treasury hack. Trump appeal. Carter funeral. Crash investigation. Norovirus. Arctic blast. Chess drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4d7d7e0-c76e-11ef-ba3b-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 12:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Baby in a dumpster’: A spate of abandoned newborns unsettles Texas</title>
      <description>Though the state was the first in the country to pass a safe haven law allowing parents to relinquish newborns at designated places, such “Baby Moses” surrenders remain rare here, and a recent series of abandoned babies in the Houston area has prompted much soul-searching.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2003830-c6fd-11ef-a566-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 22:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Treasury says it was hacked by China-backed actor, according to a letter reviewed by The Post</title>
      <description>The department was notified on Dec. 8 by a third-party software provider that a hacker gained access to a security key that allowed them to override certain security protocols and access unclassified documents stored on them, according to the letter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3f00cc1-c6f5-11ef-801f-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 21:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter’s funeral to be held Jan. 9 inside the Washington National Cathedral. He will then be buried in Plains, Georgia.</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden issued an executive order stating that all departments and agencies of the federal government will be closed on Jan. 9, which he has declared a national day of mourning for the 39th president. Check back for more details.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df96d6f0-c6f0-11ef-bc4b-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 20:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ridiculous was 2024? Dave Barry's year in review.</title>
      <description>How many goofs can one nation endure? The answer is Boeing in the wind.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90c0dd20-c6df-11ef-9f36-00000a1ace43</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 18:54:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A plot in paradise and India’s struggle for influence in Asia</title>
      <description>Indian agents and politicians in the Maldives held secret contacts over removing its pro-China president. The plot and its backstory offer a rare view into the much broader, often shadowy competition between India and China for dominance in a strategic swath of Asia and its surrounding waters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7e201ff0-c6cb-11ef-9983-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 16:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump endorses Mike Johnson for reelection as House speaker ahead of perilous vote</title>
      <description>The backing from the president-elect is expected to shore up support among wavering Republicans when the chamber votes on Friday. In a social media post, Trump said that Johnson (R-Louisiana) is “a good, hard working, religious man” and that he has his “total endorsement.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5516ec0-c6c5-11ef-96ed-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 15:50:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How much do you remember about the news in 2024?</title>
      <description>Part 2 of our week-long Year in Review quiz kicks off in today's On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07554ef0-c6bb-11ef-9c01-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 14:33:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter. Funeral plans. Plane crash. Trump and Musk. Deadly tornadoes. Food dye. Robot surgeries. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99861720-c6a5-11ef-bfd7-0000a1aced8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Dec 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11 facts about Jimmy Carter that may surprise you</title>
      <description>The peanut farmer-turned-president, who died Sunday at 100, put solar panels on the White House and once spent 89 seconds inside a melting nuclear reactor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d4f777e0-c63c-11ef-abe5-0000a1ace9f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 23:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jimmy Carter dies at 100, his son says. The 39th president led an extraordinary life that included a Nobel Peace Prize.</title>
      <description>The tenacious Southerner was turned out of office by disillusioned voters after a single term. But Carter had a brilliant post-presidential career as a champion of health, peace and democracy. His wife of 77 years, Rosalynn, died in November 2023.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">849e8ef0-c628-11ef-abe5-0000a1ace9f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 21:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turmoil in Trudeau’s government draws taunts from Trump</title>
      <description>As Canada’s government melts down, President-elect Donald Trump has taken to mocking embattled Prime Minister Justin Trudeau as the “governor” of the “great state of Canada” in middle-of-the-night social media posts.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7fd66ea1-c61f-11ef-aadd-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 20:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The laughs, heartbreaks and hopes of 2024</title>
      <description>When we look back on 2024, it’s easy for the campaign and the election to drown out everything else that happened. But there was so much more!</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb7c0053-c61a-11ef-8028-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 19:25:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel built an ‘AI factory’ for war. It unleashed it in Gaza.</title>
      <description>Years before the Gaza war, Israel transformed its intelligence unit into an AI testing ground. A Washington Post investigation reveals previously unreported details of the inner workings of the program, along with the secretive, decade-long history of its development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24e2ff02-c60f-11ef-9683-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 18:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00fcc150-c607-11ef-97ca-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 17:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a83fd300-c5f1-11ef-bd42-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 14:31:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nearly all 181 on plane that crashed in South Korea presumed dead, fire agency says</title>
      <description>The Jeju Air flight was coming from Bangkok when it crashed at Muan International Airport, according to officials. Two were rescued.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b58d84b1-c59e-11ef-8934-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 04:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 28 killed as plane crashes at South Korean airport</title>
      <description>The plane was carrying 181 people when it crashed in the southwestern city of Muan, according to officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea9b150-c58a-11ef-bbb2-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 02:14:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A global boom in cocaine trafficking defies decades of anti-drug efforts</title>
      <description>The cocaine trade is far bigger and more geographically diverse than at any point in history, with new routes, new markets and new criminal enterprises. South America now produces more than twice as much cocaine as it did a decade ago, and the market in Europe for the drug is rivaling the United States.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">07efa230-c552-11ef-bbf4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 19:29:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My husband thinks being cautious leads to bad things happening</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My husband thinks being cautious leads to bad things happening</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e90be5d0-c53e-11ef-a08d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 17:12:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: The very worst sports decisions of 2024, from Scottie Scheffler’s arrest to Jordan Chiles’s medal controversy</title>
      <description>Moments of splendor were accompanied by, well, less splendid narratives. Teams that chose poorly. Stars who stumbled. That whole Jake Paul thing. Thus, in what is now an annual tradition, here is our non-comprehensive list of some of the most regrettable moments of the year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3f07bb51-c533-11ef-a316-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 15:48:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a95f3f10-c528-11ef-8d9f-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 14:33:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin apologizes to Azerbaijan’s leader after plane crash for ‘the tragic incident’ in Russian airspace</title>
      <description>The Kremlin statement Saturday did not take responsibility for downing the Azerbaijan Airlines flight that was due to land in Russia but crashed in Kazakhstan on Christmas Day. The White House said Friday that evidence suggests the plane was brought down by Russia, resulting in the deaths of 38 people; 29 survived.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7b2cbc0-c521-11ef-b7ec-0000a1ace902</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 13:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump asks Supreme Court to delay the TikTok ban to allow him time to negotiate the popular app’s future once he’s in office</title>
      <description>The president-elect asked the court to push back a Jan. 19 deadline requiring the platform's Chinese owner ByteDance to divest from the app.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8abd2890-c4b2-11ef-9de1-0000a1ace1f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:27:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How did Loudoun Gateway become the loneliest Metro stop?</title>
      <description>The second-to-last station on the Silver Line was envisioned as a thriving mixed-use stop. Instead, it’s anything but.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">33de0050-c4b0-11ef-82e5-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greg Gumbel dies at 78. The longtime sportscaster was known for his work during March Madness and on NFL broadcasts.</title>
      <description>Gumbel’s family on Friday confirmed his death in a statement, which was released by CBS. Gumbel — who suffered from cancer, according to the family’s statement — was well-known to sports fans, particularly when Selection Sunday kicked off the NCAA men’s basketball tournament. He also was the first African American announcer to call play-by-play of a Super Bowl.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5cdb492-c4ab-11ef-82e5-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 23:40:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. homelessness soared 18 percent to a record level amid a surge in home prices and a decline in covid-era assistance</title>
      <description>An annual federal assessment estimated 771,480 people were living in shelters, temporary housing or outside in tents or cars based on a single night in January 2024.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13c8e751-c486-11ef-929e-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 19:09:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White House says there are ‘indications’ Azerbaijani airliner was brought down by Russia this week</title>
      <description>Thirty-eight people were killed in the crash. National Security Council spokesman John Kirby says the U.S. government has initial indications, in addition to widely circulating images of the wreckage, suggesting the Baku-Grozny flight was impacted by air defense fire.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">455318f0-c47b-11ef-929e-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 17:51:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk clashes with far right over skilled-worker visa program</title>
      <description>The online rift over the need for H-1B visas — a skilled-worker immigration program that has long been a lifeblood for Silicon Valley — signifies a potential rift between Trump’s core nationalist base and technology executives who have come to support him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78801001-c46e-11ef-a852-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seven columnists posed these big questions when the year began. Here’s where they landed.</title>
      <description>Seven Post columnists answer the questions they posed when the year began.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d053c3b0-c46b-11ef-9420-0000a1ace28f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 16:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0f8181-c45e-11ef-9de1-0000a1ace1f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 14:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes. Trump supporters. Plane crash. Western storms. Holiday spending. Hudson Meek. Missing packages. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a6d00f0-c44a-11ef-9734-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sea level rise in the U.S. South is blowing past expectations. Here’s what’s driving it.</title>
      <description>A large increase in sea levels is causing severe flooding across the region. At Georgia's Fort Pulaski, sea levels have risen 7 inches since 2010. Scientists have pinpointed the factors behind the sudden surge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc7f0220-c3db-11ef-9019-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:50:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Richard Parsons has died at 76. He was a leading executive at Time Warner and Citi.</title>
      <description>Parsons charted an impressive trajectory from his middle-class childhood in Queens to the top of his law school class in Albany, New York, to his place as one of the few African Americans in the highest echelons of U.S. business. He provided a steadying force for media and financial institutions in moments of boardroom and market turbulence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95c86291-c3d6-11ef-9b00-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2024 22:13:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
