<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:13:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>The 20 most anticipated movies of the holiday season</title>
      <description>The final weeks of the year bring Oscar contenders, horror flicks, animated sequels and more.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">586caf90-c5ac-11f0-8b29-0000a1ace635</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social Security scraps plan to limit disability benefits after uproar</title>
      <description>The policy would have fundamentally altered who qualifies for the two federal disability programs by eliminating or limiting a person’s age as a factor to consider.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">18740450-c599-11f0-adc3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:42:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump-appointed panel concluded FEMA should be strengthened. Noem wants to take it in a different direction.</title>
      <description>Instead of further shrinking and dismantling the agency, the FEMA Review Council wants to make it more independent.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62c063e0-c595-11f0-adc3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge in James Comey case questions whether the indictment of the former FBI director was properly approved by a grand jury</title>
      <description>The grand jury rejected an earlier three-count indictment. The judge noted that transcripts show no indication the panel saw the revised two-count version. Prosecutors acknowledged that they’d never presented it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df5712c0-c570-11f0-a8d2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:55:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commitment jewelry from his ex broke. He’s fixing it. Hax readers give advice.</title>
      <description>When his bracelet broke, she thought a last trace of his ex was gone. But he’s so set on fixing it that she is starting to crack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5869760-c569-11f0-853c-0000a1ace468</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These are the deadliest roads in America. See if you live near one.</title>
      <description>The number of pedestrians killed by vehicles in the United States has surged amid neglect and lack of investment by transportation authorities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5664650-c55d-11f0-8ed8-0000a1ace11f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 15:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Summers leaves OpenAI as Harvard opens inquiry into his Epstein ties</title>
      <description>Documents released by Congress showed the former treasury secretary kept in contact with convicted sex offender Jeffrey Epstein after he pleaded guilty to solicitation of prostitution in 2008.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e9e82590-c556-11f0-adbc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:49:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World leader White House visits in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa8541f0-c554-11f0-9e6a-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Mohammed bin Salman. Education Department. West Bank. Deadliest roads. Volcano energy. ‘Brain rot.’ Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d479bc0-c53f-11f0-9e42-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Things happen’: Trump’s comments on Khashoggi were weak, crass and of no strategic benefit to America</title>
      <description>Trump's distortions dishonor our colleague's legacy, the Editorial Board writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">02116d21-c4d5-11f0-a441-00000a1ace2c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 23:19:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress to send bill to Trump forcing disclosure of Jeffrey Epstein files</title>
      <description>Hours after the bill passed the House on a 427-1 vote, the Senate agreed to deem the legislation passed as soon as it arrived. Senate Minority Leader Charles E. Schumer (D-New York) offered a motion that received unanimous consent and will require no further action by the chamber. Trump said Monday that he would sign the bill if it reaches his desk.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">46358680-c4d0-11f0-827b-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:45:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes overwhelmingly to compel release of Epstein files after months-long impasse, sending bill to Senate</title>
      <description>The vote was the remarkable culmination of a bipartisan crusade by Reps. Thomas Massie (R-Kentucky) and Ro Khanna (D-California) that until Sunday had met fierce resistance from President Donald Trump, who repeatedly insisted that the focus on the Jeffrey Epstein files was a “hoax” promoted by Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e542460-c4b7-11f0-8147-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:44:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Court blocks GOP-friendly Texas voting map — a ruling that is likely to help Democrats keep 5 seats in 2026 midterms</title>
      <description>In a stinging setback for President Donald Trump and Republicans, a federal court blocked a newly drawn congressional map in Texas that Republicans hoped would have given them an edge in five more House races.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3fdd20b0-c4b0-11f0-bd03-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta is not an illegal monopoly, judge rules, dealing a major blow to government efforts to rein in tech giants</title>
      <description>The ruling by U.S. District Judge James E. Boasberg agreed with Meta that its purchases of the photo sharing app Instagram and messaging app WhatsApp, which it bought in 2012 and 2014, respectively, did not violate antitrust laws.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01ee1861-c4ae-11f0-bbbf-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 18:40:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump defends Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman over killing of Post columnist Jamal Khashoggi, saying ‘things happen’</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump said he did not hold the Saudi leader responsible for the 2018 murder, despite a U.S. intelligence report assessing the opposite. Trump’s dismissive language was the highest-level confirmation yet that Mohammed will face few consequences for the killing, as the crown prince makes his first visit to Washington since Khashoggi was dismembered.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">503473d0-c4a8-11f0-9f56-00000a1aced7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:59:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Bridge deaths could have been prevented, federal investigators find</title>
      <description>The six workers who died would have had 1 minute, 29 seconds to escape had they been alerted, the National Transportation Safety Board said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d2725e0-c4a5-11f0-b138-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: In their family, it’s holiday tradition for siblings to do squat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: In their family, it’s holiday tradition for siblings to do squat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be87aee1-c4a0-11f0-b017-0000a1ace936</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:05:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to announce dismantling of much of Education Department</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump signed an executive order in March seeking to close the department, but only Congress has the power to do that.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">135a5bc0-c497-11f0-8b81-00000a1ace9b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:55:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How baby boomers got so rich, and why their kids are unlikely to catch up</title>
      <description>The wealthiest generation holds more than $85 trillion in assets thanks to economic conditions Gen X, millennials and others would be hard-pressed to replicate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">670147f1-c48f-11f0-8fe1-00000a1ace01</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chowing down on fast food staples in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a635f10-c48b-11f0-8b2e-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A first look at Venezuela’s ‘Freedom Manifesto’ from Nobel Peace Prize winner María Corina Machado</title>
      <description>Nobel Peace Prize winner María Corina Machado pens a precursor to a new Constitution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb582070-c47e-11f0-acc0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:03:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. Saudi crown prince. Supreme Court. Gaza peace plan. Clinical trial cuts. Boomer wealth. Wolf video. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12f449f0-c476-11f0-a951-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larry Summers is stepping back from public commitments over Jeffrey Epstein emails, saying he is ‘deeply ashamed’</title>
      <description>“I take full responsibility for my misguided decision to continue communicating with Mr. Epstein,” Summers said in a statement. It was unclear whether the Democratic former treasury secretary would exit a wide array of boards and think tanks or if those organizations would cut ties with him. Summers is also a former president of Harvard University, where he still holds a professorship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">05099960-c423-11f0-8395-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 02:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This video may be the first recording of a wild wolf using a tool — a trait once thought to be unique to humans</title>
      <description>A wolf in British Columbia was filmed fishing in 2024, pulling in a crab pot from the water and eating the bait. Although the intelligence of wolves is well known, the discovery adds to an expanding list of animals capable of manipulating tools to forage for food.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">30b0a420-c417-11f0-9575-00000a1aced8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N. Security Council approves Trump’s 20-point peace plan for Gaza</title>
      <description>The U.S.-sponsored resolution turns President Donald Trump’s plan into an international mandate, allowing stalled security and reconstruction measures to move forward.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4440890-c40c-11f0-90f5-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 23:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he won’t rule out sending troops into Venezuela, despite his claim that U.S. may be open to talks with Maduro</title>
      <description>“I don’t rule out anything, we just have to take care of Venezuela,” President Donald Trump said when asked at a news conference about putting American personnel “on the ground.” His remarks appeared startlingly at odds with his claim Sunday night that the administration “may be having some discussions” with Nicolás Maduro, Venezuela’s strongman president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e81b1090-c3ff-11f0-a51e-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:53:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge blasts Justice Department over Comey case, citing government misconduct that could lead to dismissal of charges</title>
      <description>U.S. Magistrate Judge William Fitzpatrick ordered prosecutors to swiftly turn over to a judge the full transcripts and audio of the grand jury proceedings that led to former FBI director James B. Comey’s indictment in September on charges that he lied to Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7bc08620-c3e4-11f0-8596-0000a1ace539</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 18:37:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FEMA leader resigns after short tenure and criticism for being inaccessible during Texas floods</title>
      <description>David Richardson resigned as acting head of the Federal Emergency Management Agency, according to sources familiar with the situation, ending a brief tenure leading an agency the administration had publicly expressed a desire to dismantle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c064ddf1-c3dd-11f0-af63-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Grown kid’s rent-free deal with mom makes dad and stepmom ‘crazy’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Grown kid’s rent-free deal with mom makes dad and stepmom ‘crazy’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2ce4b60-c3d9-11f0-9992-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Trump loyalist prosecutor is probing former top Obama administration officials</title>
      <description>Jason Reding Quiñones's appointment to lead an office he left last year after poor performance reviews is a case study in how the administration is operating U.S. attorney’s offices across the country, plucking Trump backers with little support from staffers to serve in high-powered positions, according to people familiar with the Justice Department’s operations. 

In several cases, including Reding Quiñones’s, the appointments have led to a staff exodus and a sharp drop in morale as the appointees embrace the administration’s most controversial investigations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ca6ec41-c3d6-11f0-a8fd-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:55:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Gretchen Whitmer: If we’re going to do tariffs, let’s do them right</title>
      <description>The White House’s chaotic tariff strategy is making everything more expensive.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b84890f0-c3d1-11f0-a51e-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conserving wildlife in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">35b85531-c3c2-11f0-be98-00000a1acecb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:32:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New foreign student enrollment at U.S. colleges dropped 17 percent in the fall</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has thrown up barriers to student visas, and experts expect a continued decline as many international students decide to study in other countries. The number applying to U.S. colleges for next year has dropped 9 percent so far, according to preliminary data. Some advocates argue the decline will hurt the U.S. economy because immigrants often play a key role in business start-ups and research.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c2e5f90-c3bd-11f0-9e84-00000a1ace79</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein files. U.S. military. Flight cuts lifted. Tariff rollbacks. Foreign students. Ultra-processed foods. Snow. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6edc9e0-c3ac-11f0-909a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:59:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In shift, Trump says House should vote to release Epstein files</title>
      <description>The president’s reversal came after key lawmakers said Sunday that support is growing in the House for the measure ahead of a closely watched vote this week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">036f9450-c366-11f0-84d7-000a1ace3079</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 03:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAA is lifting all flight restrictions imposed during shutdown, restoring full operations at airports</title>
      <description>The restrictions will be lifted Monday, transportation authorities said, after mandating cuts during the shutdown that caused thousands of cancellations and delays.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6ae4580-c35b-11f0-a0cb-00000a1acef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 02:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 definitive rules for the airport bar</title>
      <description>If you don’t see a jigger, don’t order a martini — plus more unspoken guidelines from travel pros.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c84fcce0-c348-11f0-b7e3-0000a1ace328</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:03:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One man’s obsessive quest to uncover Brazil’s buried Nazi past</title>
      <description>The story of Ibirubá’s fugitive Nazis is clouded by uncertainty and conspiracy theories. But one local journalist is convinced he is closing in on the truth.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc729dc0-c330-11f0-a691-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 21:10:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">04c76420-c30e-11f0-812c-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 17:02:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GOP’s plans to replace Obamacare have failed. Here’s what lawmakers propose now.</title>
      <description>Lawmakers are racing toward a mid-December deadline, with Republicans hoping to present side-by-side legislation with Democrats’ plan to extend Affordable Care Act subsidies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32ef3740-c30b-11f0-b286-000a1acef338</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 16:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">664f9a60-c2fe-11f0-b220-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How snowy could it be where you live? Look up your area to see whether you’ll have a winter wonderland – or a snow shortage.</title>
      <description>Swaths of central and eastern states have received much less snow than average over the past five winters – a trend that may continue this season.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e15710-c2f2-11f0-a17e-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 13:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alice Wong, disability rights advocate and wordsmith, dies at 51</title>
      <description>Wong was a leader for disabled culture and author of the acclaimed 2022 memoir, “Year of the Tiger: An Activist’s Life.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b82ee991-c280-11f0-bbb3-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 00:10:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The Secret Lives of Mormon Wives’ is essential viewing. Seriously.</title>
      <description>The soapy reality show is a perfect mirror of America’s strange cultural moment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b937610-c273-11f0-b59e-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 22:36:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They bought cheap health insurance promoted by the Trump administration. Then they needed surgery.</title>
      <description>Some states have banned “short-term” insurance plans with limited coverage, and consumer advocates have warned of the drawbacks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">57f48b80-c24d-11f0-886e-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 18:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d82043d1-c22f-11f0-b175-0000a1ace787</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:31:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How America’s political unease found its way to a small town in Wisconsin</title>
      <description>In Palmyra, population 1,719, the texture of everyday life is beginning to fray as it grapples with how to deal with ICE — and a threat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df0e1632-c22b-11f0-99d4-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 14:03:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump repeals tariffs he set on some foods as Americans face high grocery prices</title>
      <description>The announcement — which includes agricultural products such as beef, coffee and tomatoes — represents the most significant shift in the “reciprocal tariffs” the president announced in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3253300-c1b9-11f0-8d7d-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 00:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epstein texted lawmaker during Michael Cohen's 2019 congressional hearing, documents show, possibly influencing questions</title>
      <description>Time-stamps on the text messages match with video from the hearing, indicating that Epstein was texting with Del. Stacey Plaskett, a Democrat who represents the U.S. Virgin Islands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e50f3d0-c1a7-11f0-8b73-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 22:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump weighs Venezuela strikes as U.S. forces prepare for attack order</title>
      <description>High-level discussions over whether to attack Venezuela — and how — have been underway for days, according to people familiar with the matter. It remains unclear if President Donald Trump has decided to pursue such an escalation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c285632-c1a1-11f0-8fb5-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 21:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
