<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 04:05:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Israeli strikes in Tehran kill the chief commander of Iran's Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps, state media says</title>
      <description>Maj. Gen. Hossein Salami was killed alongside the former head of Iran's Atomic Energy Organization and at least one other senior military officer, Iran's state-run news agency reported.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3790df50-47fb-11f0-a006-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 02:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump administration's use of National Guard in California amid immigration protests</title>
      <description>California had sued to stop the military from being deployed "for law enforcement purposes on the streets of a civilian city." U.S. District Judge Charles R. Breyer ruled Thursday evening that President Donald Trump acted illegally in dispatching the National Guard.
Breyer stayed his decision until noon Friday, and the Justice Department immediately filed a notice of appeal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">80165a31-47fa-11f0-bf8f-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 02:02:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel strikes Iran, braces for potential retaliation</title>
      <description>Israeli Defense Minister Israel Katz said Israel had launched a “preemptive strike” against Iran and declared a “special emergency situation” in Israel in anticipation of a potential retaliatory attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6101d034-47ef-11f0-ac0f-0000a1ace295</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 00:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Army parade Saturday will bring street closures, security checkpoints, tanks, troops and protests. Here’s what to know.</title>
      <description>The military parade — expected to be the largest in the nation’s capital since the end of the first Gulf War in 1991 — honors the Army's 250th birthday. Saturday is also President Donald Trump’s 79th birthday. We’ve answered some frequently asked questions about the event.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54eca880-47d4-11f0-b75f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 21:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Alex Padilla (D-California) forcibly removed from Homeland Security Secretary Noem’s news conference after he interrupted it</title>
      <description>Padilla briefly interrupted Kristi Noem’s news conference in the Los Angeles FBI headquarters, saying he had questions for her. Security pushed him out, telling him to put his hands up.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">742024a0-47bd-11f0-9ed1-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least one passenger survived Air India plane crash with more than 240 people aboard</title>
      <description>Indian Home Minister Amit Shah said he met with the survivor, Vishwash Kumar, who was slightly injured. Kumar told the Hindustan Times that he saw bodies and pieces of the plane all around him after the crash in Ahmedabad.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8fb83e1-47b5-11f0-8d41-000a1ace8074</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 17:51:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After visits to their mom’s, stepkids unleash on their stepmom</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After visits to their mom’s, stepkids unleash on their stepmom</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">936f3f12-47a6-11f0-8047-0000a1acef43</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 16:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein’s sexual assault retrial in New York ends in mistrial on final charge</title>
      <description>The disgraced Hollywood producer was convicted Wednesday on a separate criminal sex act charge.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a56745b0-47a5-11f0-b3c5-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:55:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia says it’s winning in Ukraine. The data says otherwise.</title>
      <description>Russia has paid an extraordinary price in blood and equipment for marginal gains in Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cae0d70-47a2-11f0-9924-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 15:31:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The late Sly Stone stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">50588060-4792-11f0-92bb-0000a1acefc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:36:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He’s dying. She’s pregnant. His one last wish is to fight his cancer long enough to see his baby.</title>
      <description>Cancer is no longer just a disease of later life. The rate of new diagnoses for people 50 or older has been falling for two decades. At the same time, it’s been climbing for people under 50. The story of Tanner and Shay Martin captures a growing reality for young cancer patients.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ef1d2f1-478f-11f0-9e91-0000a1acec83</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 13:13:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationwide protests. Trump at ‘Les Mis.’ Plane crash. RFK Jr. Brian Wilson. Cancer rates. Dinosaur discovery. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6b9c7d61-477c-11f0-9520-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 11:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>London-bound passenger plane with more than 200 on board crashes shortly after taking off in India</title>
      <description>Flight AI171, which was headed to Gatwick Airport, had 232 passengers and 12 crew on board, the Associated Press reported. It crashed in Ahmedabad, in India’s Gujarat state, officials said, describing it as a “tragic accident.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">162172a0-4772-11f0-ae17-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 09:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We asked 1,000 Americans about the L.A. protests. Here's what they said.</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-Schar School poll — including more than 200 California residents — finds Americans are divided in their views toward L.A. protesters and Trump’s decision to send the National Guard and Marines to the city. California residents are more critical of Trump’s actions, as are political independents.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ad4dfba0-4720-11f0-9b05-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 00:03:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Hogg to depart as DNC vice chair after months of turmoil</title>
      <description>The move caps months of party infighting centering on the Gen Z activist’s pledge to involve himself in party primaries and back challengers against some incumbents. Hogg decided not to run to retain his position Wednesday after a Democratic National Committee-wide vote that could have led to his ouster. Last month, a DNC panel found that Hogg and Vice Chair Malcolm Kenyatta were not properly elected earlier this year, since their election ran afoul of gender diversity rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4c72e560-471c-11f0-a8b1-00000a1ace94</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 23:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. picks new members of CDC vaccine recommendation panel, including critics of vaccines</title>
      <description>Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. on Wednesday announced eight new members of the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices after he ousted every member earlier this week. New picks include a longtime member of the nation's oldest anti-vaccine group and at least two critics of coronavirus vaccines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">af460041-470e-11f0-942b-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:54:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. embassies and military bases across the Middle East are on high alert amid fears of an Israeli strike on Iran</title>
      <description>As nuclear negotiations flounder, the State Department authorized the departure of nonessential personnel in Iraq and the Pentagon approved the exit of military family members at U.S. installations across the Middle East.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd7bc0a0-470c-11f0-baba-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 21:41:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA moves to weaken limits on power plant emissions, eliminating restrictions on greenhouse gas pollution</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency announced Wednesday a proposal to eliminate Biden-era regulations restricting power plant greenhouse gas pollution, a move that would significantly increase U.S. emissions that contribute to climate change.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9101f890-46f6-11f0-b28e-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 19:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harvey Weinstein convicted of sexual assault in New York retrial but acquitted of a rape charge</title>
      <description>The decision comes more than a year after his 2020 conviction for sex crimes was overturned. The jury was expected to continue deliberations on a third charge on Thursday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41dd7db0-46f2-11f0-ae5b-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:31:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Wilson dies at 82. The Beach Boys co-creator helped make the group the most popular American rock act of the 1960s.</title>
      <description>The band’s early hits — “Surfin’,” “Surfer Girl,” “I Get Around,” “Help Me, Rhonda” and “California Girls,” among others — evoked a world of fast cars, beautiful youth, eternal surf and sunshine on an idyllic and immaculate beach.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">49b79060-46e4-11f0-9c1f-00000a1ace78</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:51:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How nuclear war could start</title>
      <description>How nuclear war could start</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf872890-46e0-11f0-bf5f-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After infidelity, boyfriend retaliates with two months of ‘hell’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After infidelity, boyfriend retaliates with two months of ‘hell’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1c3c4000-46de-11f0-8100-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 16:07:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI leaders seek to move Quantico, Va.'s elite law enforcement training program to Huntsville, Alabama</title>
      <description>The proposal to move the training for state, local and federal law enforcement leaders is part of an ongoing effort by the Trump administration to shrink the FBI's footprint in and around the nation's capital. The training academy for FBI recruits and personnel would stay at Quantico, people familiar with the plans said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">152e2320-46dc-11f0-a1ed-00000a1ace30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:52:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A chef responds to diner's complaint about $155 for fish</title>
      <description>A chef responds to diner's complaint about $155 for fish</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa7e6090-46d5-11f0-85a4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 15:08:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The biggest cases the Supreme Court has left before its term ends this month</title>
      <description>The justices have deadlocked on the legality of direct public funding for religious schools, upheld strict “ghost gun” regulations and narrowed the scope of environmental reviews for infrastructure projects. They will issue new rulings on Thursday, with decisions still pending on state bans of medical care for transgender teens, age verification for online porn, nationwide injunctions on banning birthright citizenship and more. Here are the cases.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">765fdf80-46cd-11f0-975c-000a1ace2f30</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 14:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know your Tony Awards in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">642a6970-46c8-11f0-a9b5-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 13:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annual inflation rate picked up slightly in May, although less than expected, amid uncertainty about the economy</title>
      <description>The inflation data released by the Bureau of Labor Statistics on Wednesday suggests President Donald Trump’s tariffs have yet to drive up the cost of everyday products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b8940960-46c0-11f0-a057-0000a1acedb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 12:36:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spreading protests. Guantánamo Bay. Rising prices. Israel sanctions. 23andMe data. Wildfire smoke. Exam cheating. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">388a3f80-46b3-11f0-9a85-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Jersey gubernatorial race will pit Democratic congresswoman against Trump-backed Republican</title>
      <description>Rep. Mikie Sherrill was projected to win the Democratic primary to replace term-limited Gov. Phil Murphy (D), according to the Associated Press. She will face businessman and former state Rep. Jack Ciattarelli, the AP reported. Ciattarelli came within three points of defeating Murphy four years ago. Sherrill flipped a GOP-held seat in 2018. Control of the governor's mansion has toggled between the parties.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fd63ff50-465c-11f0-a340-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:42:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and China agree to new framework to de-escalate trade war, Commerce Secretary Howard Lutnick says</title>
      <description>The agreement, reached after trade negotiators met for two days in London, could also allow for a resolution around the shipment of rare earth minerals, according to Lutnick.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7b763231-465a-11f0-b0ed-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:24:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration planning major increase of Guantánamo deportations, including citizens of Britain, France and other allies</title>
      <description>Plans have begun to send potentially thousands of foreigners to the detention site as early as this week — including citizens of Britain, France and Italy — with no plans of notifying their home governments, according to U.S. officials and documents provided to The Post. The preparations include medical screenings for 9,000 people to determine if they are healthy enough to be sent to the military base in Cuba.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc30e740-4640-11f0-aee8-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 21:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department concludes that Trump can abolish national monuments and protected areas established by past presidents</title>
      <description>A legal opinion released Tuesday by the Justice Department  reverses a previous legal opinion issued in 1938 and could be laying the groundwork for President Donald Trump to abolish or dramatically shrink national monuments, which provide federal protections to millions of acres of government land.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2df06c0-463d-11f0-a493-0000a1ace3f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 20:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants to push lonely tween to work on making new friends</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parent wants to push lonely tween to work on making new friends</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b89e761-4617-11f0-8c6d-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s military response to Los Angeles protests is expected to cost $134 million for 60 days, Pentagon official says</title>
      <description>The U.S. military deployments that President Donald Trump has directed in response to unrest in Los Angeles are expected to cost $134 million for 60 days of operations, Pentagon official Bryn Woollacott MacDonnell told lawmakers at a hearing on Tuesday. The estimate includes food, transportation, housing and other associated costs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a45f61d0-4614-11f0-80ca-0000a1ace5f2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 16:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. court officials repeatedly lost track of teens wearing ankle monitors. The timing was deadly.</title>
      <description>Teens accused of committing crimes in D.C. have gone missing after they let their GPS ankle monitor batteries die, a Washington Post investigation has found. Despite deadly consequences, D.C. judges have ordered widespread use of the devices for juveniles as young as 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c5ea2fe0-4607-11f0-92dd-00000a1ace58</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 14:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A past president’s order in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">907d6781-45ff-11f0-b991-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 13:33:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 9 killed in rare Austrian school shooting, police say</title>
      <description>The perpetrator is also dead, police for the state of Styria said on social media, and several others were seriously injured. The school, BORG Dreierschützengasse in Graz, was evacuated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4a9b8bd0-45f4-11f0-a4c1-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 12:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. protests. RFK Jr. Economic warning. Austria school shooting. Sly Stone. Dangerous heat. Glowing axolotls. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">34aad4c0-45ea-11f0-a1d4-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 11:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smithsonian board says only its secretary has firing power, days after Trump claimed to have dismissed National Portrait Gallery director</title>
      <description>The Board of Regents issued a statement backing the authority of Secretary Lonnie G. Bunch III, but added that he would instruct museums to “make any needed changes to ensure unbiased content.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3438df10-45a8-11f0-8222-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 03:08:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump mobilizes 2,000 additional National Guard troops to Los Angeles protests</title>
      <description>The Pentagon, acting on orders from President Donald Trump, said 2,000 more members of the California National Guard would be mobilized to Los Angeles for “federal service," bringing the total to an estimated 4,000 National Guard troops and 700 Marines.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9925ca80-45a0-11f0-a0eb-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 02:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>T.J. Oshie is retiring. A U.S. hockey hero at the 2014 Olympics, he became a fan favorite for the Capitals.</title>
      <description>Oshie, 38, made the announcement Monday at the waterfront in Georgetown, seven years to the day after he and his teammates celebrated the franchise's only Stanley Cup title with a now-famous dive into the fountain. He did not play during the 2024-25 season while struggling with back issues, instead spending the last year of his contract on long-term injured reserve.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d489e0-457c-11f0-86d6-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:57:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is ousting all members of a key CDC vaccination panel</title>
      <description>In an op-ed published in the Wall Street Journal, Kennedy said the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, a group of experts who recommend vaccines, has been "plagued with persistent conflicts of interest." The move appears to contradict a pledge Kennedy made to Sen. Bill Cassidy (R-Louisiana) during the confirmation process to be health and human services secretary.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f3ebf821-457a-11f0-92ab-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:44:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon sending hundreds of Marines to Los Angeles to backstop National Guard as Trump escalates feud with Gov. Gavin Newsom</title>
      <description>The Marines will join National Guard troops whose deployment was ordered by President Donald Trump amid protests of his immigration policies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6ae8570-4578-11f0-9c66-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 21:30:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sly Stone has died at 82. The dazzling maestro of the Family Stone was known for the hits ‘Family Affair’ and ‘Everyday People.’</title>
      <description>He electrified Woodstock crowds with his brand of psychedelic funk but fell into a fog of drug abuse at the height of his musical powers. His adventurism and ear for the times created an enduring soundtrack of the 1960s and early ’70s.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">967124e0-456b-11f0-a4c0-0000a1ace458</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 19:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>California sues Trump administration over deployment of National Guard troops to Los Angeles, says the move inflames situation</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump ordered the deployment in response to protests against immigration raids without the consent of California Gov. Gavin Newsom (D). Newsom contends the move was illegal because it infringed on his role as commander in chief of the California National Guard.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">777692e0-455d-11f0-82f7-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frederick Forsyth, thriller writer of ‘The Day of the Jackal,’ dies at 86</title>
      <description>He wrote more than 20 novels, short stories and other works, selling more than 75 million copies in more than a dozen languages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">379980c0-455c-11f0-a726-00000a1ace09</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Craving ‘volatile’ affair partner over saving his marriage</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Craving ‘volatile’ affair partner over saving his marriage</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bf2852c0-454b-11f0-952f-00000a1ace67</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 16:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. failed to curb truancy — and fueled the biggest surge in youth crime in a generation</title>
      <description>District leaders have long linked school attendance to youth crime, saying tackling one will curb the other. But a Washington Post investigation found that D.C. officials have failed to follow through on key initiatives that promised to keep students in class and out of trouble.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0404180-4542-11f0-a81d-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 15:02:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Jersey legend in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0362c300-4536-11f0-87a5-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 13:31:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>L.A. protests. Travel ban. Trump vs. Musk. Greta Thunberg. Mental health. Carlos Alcaraz. Tony Awards. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6ba89a0-4520-11f0-af84-0000a1acecf5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 11:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
