<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:01:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: She can’t unsee it now — she’s always wrong in her husband’s eyes</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: She can’t unsee it now — she’s always wrong in her husband’s eyes</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b7de90-b8d7-11f0-9c1c-00000a1ace60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:10:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zohran Mamdani’s success is a warning, the Editorial Board writes</title>
      <description>How did a socialist with almost no governing experience become New York’s mayoral frontrunner?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">364a5a80-b8d6-11f0-90a3-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:57:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ticket sales are down in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">720aec11-b8c2-11f0-8a0a-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Climate change is supercharging extreme rainfall. See if you live in a hotspot.</title>
      <description>A Post investigation reveals where hidden rivers in the sky are making rainfall more dangerous worldwide.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c41be740-b8c0-11f0-99f1-0000a1ace309</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 14:24:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump polls. Zohran Mamdani. Shutdown impacts. Heavy rainfall. Melatonin study. Disappearing jobs. Pickleball noise. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97ebbce0-b8ac-11f0-bf44-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pickleball noise is annoying. We’ve figured out why — and how to fix it.</title>
      <description>The racket from some 70,000 pickleball courts across the United States has generated bitter fights. If we understand the sound, can we learn to ignore it?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2282070-b83f-11f0-86ca-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voters broadly disapprove of Trump, poll finds, but Democrats may not benefit</title>
      <description>A Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll finds that most Americans disapprove of President Trump's handling of top issues, and a majority say he has gone too far in exercising his powers. But a year out from the 2026 midterm elections, there is little evidence that these negative impressions have accrued to the benefit of the Democratic Party.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">59ff5571-b822-11f0-9ed4-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb2adf00-b80d-11f0-b710-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump dials up pressure on the Justice Department over the 2020 election</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump is escalating demands to freshly scrutinize ballots from the 2020 election, raising tensions with administration officials who think their time is better spent examining voter lists for future elections.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0070c6a1-b80a-11f0-8caf-000a1ace96c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97a43960-b7f8-11f0-9faf-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:31:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a young Thomas Jefferson’s plea to the King helped ignite America’s fight for independence</title>
      <description>In the summer of 1774, Jefferson retreated to Monticello and wrote a secret plea meant to avert disputes with the British — a document that instead helped set America on the path to independence.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">addf4840-b7f4-11f0-9f35-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:03:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Los Angeles Dodgers win the World Series, beating the Toronto Blue Jays in Game 7 to repeat as champions</title>
      <description>The Dodgers were heavy favorites entering the series but were pushed to the limit by the Blue Jays. Los Angeles is the first team to win the World Series in consecutive seasons since the New York Yankees won three straight from 1998 to 2000.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8011fc60-b7a3-11f0-aa2f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 04:22:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. mayor imposes citywide youth curfew after multiple teens arrested in Navy Yard on Halloween</title>
      <description>The incident was one of several in which large groups of teens caused disturbances in the city, the mayor said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7866bc50-b779-11f0-8ae8-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 23:21:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration tells Congress war law doesn’t apply to strikes against alleged drug traffickers in Latin America</title>
      <description>The Office of Legal Counsel told lawmakers that the War Powers Resolution, which requires Congress's approval for ongoing military conflict, does not apply here.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42b0be50-b763-11f0-a73a-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 20:42:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>After two years and eight doctors, the reason for her face twitching was surprisingly simple</title>
      <description>Doctors couldn’t explain why the right side of a Minnesota woman’s face kept twitching, as the convulsions turned the outgoing woman into a recluse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3894b80-b737-11f0-8868-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">edf6c501-b729-11f0-aefd-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:51:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE and Border Patrol’s use of tear gas to disperse protesters injures, sickens and tests the law</title>
      <description>Federal immigration agents say chemical agents are needed to disperse violent protesters. But videos also show officers directly firing at people in aggressive and “unorthodox” ways.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c21a2920-b726-11f0-befb-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 13:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal judge orders Trump administration to release billions in backup funds for SNAP, relied on by 42 million Americans</title>
      <description>In an oral ruling, Judge Jack McConnell said the Agriculture Department must distribute $5.5 billion in the contingency funds “timely, or as soon as possible, for the November 1 payments to be made.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab2b1eb0-b689-11f0-ba3a-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:44:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My husband’s therapist is emboldening him to cheat</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ce1f0f20-b67b-11f0-b765-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venezuela pleads with Moscow for help as U.S. ramps up the pressure</title>
      <description>Documents show Venezuelan President Nicolás Maduro drafted a letter asking Russia for missiles, radar and upgraded aircraft as U.S. forces amass in the Caribbean.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13aef4e0-b674-11f0-a3fa-00000a1ace48</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 16:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Park Police seek hundreds more officers amid Trump’s crime crackdown</title>
      <description>A hiring spree in the nation’s capital is part of a plan to become “the premier law enforcement agency in D.C.,” according to documents obtained by The Post.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de76f0c0-b66e-11f0-9bc0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:32:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ohio approves new congressional map giving Republicans a leg up in two more House seats</title>
      <description>The new map received rare bipartisan agreement because Republicans who control the state legislature did not want to risk a challenge from Democrats.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">587bbc40-b66d-11f0-8531-00000a1acef7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My family emigrated from Vietnam. Halloween in America astonished me.</title>
      <description>Coming from a communist-run nation, I was baffled by glimpses of life in my new home.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6bbdbe20-b663-11f0-9319-00000a1ace36</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 14:10:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c3d8ec0-b65e-11f0-925f-0000a1ace1f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:35:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kennedy Center ticket sales have plummeted since Trump takeover</title>
      <description>Nearly nine months into the president’s oversight, sales for orchestra, theater and dance performances are the worst they’ve been since the pandemic, according to a Washington Post analysis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f131e2f1-b651-11f0-8c36-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel’s actions. Shutdown impacts. Kennedy Center. National Guard. Former prince Andrew. Autism study. Fall back. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b70712c0-b648-11f0-8c1a-0000a1ace1bd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of science’s biggest dinosaur debates may finally be settled</title>
      <description>For decades, paleontologists debated whether fossils were of a young T. rex or a species called nanotyrannus. A new study settles it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d4641a1-b5e8-11f0-a63b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Covid in pregnancy tied to autism and developmental issues, study says</title>
      <description>A study published in the journal Obstetrics and Gynecology analyzed more than 18,100 births in Massachusetts of children born to women who contracted the virus starting in the early months of the pandemic through some of 2021, before vaccines were widely available.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56201510-b5d5-11f0-87e9-000a1ace2f48</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 21:13:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classified U.S. report finds hundreds of possible Israeli human rights violations</title>
      <description>The State Department’s watchdog says it will take years to review credible allegations against Israeli military units in Gaza, according to officials, raising doubts about future accountability.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8e581e0-b5ce-11f0-9dfb-00000a1aced4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>King Charles III strips brother Andrew of prince title and orders him to vacate his home at Royal Lodge over Epstein scandal</title>
      <description>The move marks the latest setback for the embattled royal as the scandal over his ties to the convicted American sex offender Jeffrey Epstein continues to cast a long shadow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00223b34-b5ca-11f0-bccd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 19:52:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Americans blame Trump and the GOP more than Democrats for the government shutdown, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>But the share saying Democrats are at fault has grown slightly, from 30 percent in a Washington Post flash poll when the shutdown began to 33 percent in the latest poll. Among registered voters, 37 percent now blame Democrats, while 46 percent blame Republicans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8b889020-b5bb-11f0-b544-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:09:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania Democrats know the truth about demonizing Trump</title>
      <description>Gov. Josh Shapiro and the Democratic state party leader are focused on winning back lost voters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d487bac0-b5ad-11f0-9924-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:31:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s brother knows no bounds with constant chatty calls</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband’s brother knows no bounds with constant chatty calls</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1201a1d0-b5aa-11f0-bd9b-0000a1ace191</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:04:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maryland state Sen. Dalya Attar (D) indicted on extortion and conspiracy charges as she runs in tight race for full-term seat</title>
      <description>Attar, the first Orthodox Jewish woman to serve in the state’s senate, assumed the seat in January after it was vacated and the Baltimore City Democratic Central Committee voted to appoint her. She is running for a full term against Malcolm P. Ruff (D-Baltimore City), a civil rights attorney.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82120e80-b5a8-11f0-8f5b-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nationals are expected to hire Blake Butera as their next manager. The 33-year-old comes from the Tampa Bay Rays organization.</title>
      <description>The Washington Nationals are finalizing a deal to hire Butera, according to three people with knowledge of the move. The skipper, chosen by new president of baseball operations Paul Toboni, is set to join a club that is at an inflection point in its rebuild.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ef421460-b5a2-11f0-b67c-0000a1ace7d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:13:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration makes misleading case in high-stakes asylum hearing</title>
      <description>Homeland Security asked a judge to deport a man to Afghanistan, where he expects the Taliban to kill him. What happens next could affect thousands.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4b84c250-b59d-11f0-8aaf-00000a1aceb7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mosquitoes are showing up where?! Find out in today’s On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1bc38b80-b595-11f0-bdae-00000a1ace9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:34:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon readies thousands of National Guard ‘reaction forces,’ a sign deployment in U.S. cities could become the norm under Trump</title>
      <description>The Defense Department’s newly established “quick reaction force” within the National Guard is being readied for civil unrest missions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c52f6b70-b591-11f0-8c03-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Americans oppose the demolition of the East Wing for Trump’s ballroom, Post-ABC-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Twenty-eight percent of Americans say they support the demolition project, paid for by $300 million in private donations from U.S. businesses and individuals, compared with 56 percent who oppose it, according to the poll. Another 16 percent are not sure whether they support or oppose the project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">00c64960-b588-11f0-9f4f-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclear testing. Melissa damage. Ballroom poll. Food banks. Sonya Massey. Diverted flight. Historic hike. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c8cb0f0-b57f-11f0-8706-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces that he’ll cut tariffs on Chinese imports after Xi agrees to delay restrictions on rare earth minerals for a year</title>
      <description>The president said Chinese imports would now be subject to a 47 percent tariff, down 10 percentage points from the blanket rate before the meeting. In return, Beijing agreed to delay restrictions on rare earth minerals for a year and buy “tremendous amounts” of American soybeans, the president said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3925850-b552-11f0-afbb-00000a1ace4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 05:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump directs Pentagon to test nuclear weapons, just before meeting with China’s Xi</title>
      <description>The president said he wanted testing to occur “on an equal basis” with Russia and China, raising pressure on Beijing less than an hour before he was scheduled to meet his Chinese counterpart Xi Jinping for a high-stakes summit in South Korea.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">199acba0-b533-11f0-ac04-0000a1acebdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 01:52:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump nominee at U.S. export bank withdraws amid scrutiny of Russia ties</title>
      <description>Bryce McFerran, the president’s pick for one of the top positions in the U.S. Export-Import Bank, is a former senior executive at a steel-trading business co-owned by one of Russia’s richest oligarchs and is married to a member of a Russian family with ties to the Kremlin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a4ad682-b512-11f0-92ca-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 21:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sheriff’s deputy convicted in 2024 killing of Sonya Massey, an unarmed Black woman who called 911 to report prowler, lawyer says</title>
      <description>Sean Grayson was found guilty of second-degree murder, a lawyer representing the woman’s family said, in a case that renewed national outrage over police conduct against Black Americans. He faces the possibility of up to 20 years in prison.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1fc69c70-b501-11f0-b896-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 19:54:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Louvre heist suspects ‘partially admit’ involvement</title>
      <description>None of France’s crown jewels have been recovered. Paris’s public prosecutor said she remained hopeful, with two suspects in custody.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d96959c0-b4f6-11f0-b6d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:41:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fed cuts rates again as shutdown clouds view of economy</title>
      <description>The central bank moved to steady a weakening job market as inflation stays elevated and key data goes dark.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0049b080-b4f2-11f0-8f0e-0000a1ace76b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tim Kaine and Rand Paul: Why we’re forcing Senate votes on Trump’s tariffs</title>
      <description>Why we’re forcing Senate votes on Trump’s tariffs</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e9e6810-b4e4-11f0-a836-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How bad is it that boyfriend lied in shame over money? Hax readers give advice.</title>
      <description>How bad is it that boyfriend lied in shame over money? Hax readers give advice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1a735fb0-b4e3-11f0-a02b-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two U.S. prosecutors suspended after describing Jan. 6 attack on the U.S. Capitol as a ‘riot’ in court document</title>
      <description>The Justice Department has placed two federal prosecutors in Washington on leave a day after they filed a document in court that referred to the Jan. 6, 2021, attack on the U.S. Capitol as a “riot” carried out by a “mob,” two people familiar with the matter said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8bec4090-b4e2-11f0-9252-00000a1ace05</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The government shutdown could cost the economy up to $14 billion, according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office</title>
      <description>The report by the Congressional Budget Office said the longer the government stays closed, the more costly the pause will be.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81476531-b4dc-11f0-9479-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 15:32:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
