<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 20:03:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Idaho offers little help for families needing child care. As many scrimp to afford it, one family-run center is buckling.</title>
      <description>TLC for Tots has seen an entire generation of little ones since Krystal McFarlane’s parents founded it in 2006. But economics are bearing down hard these days — one reason for a child-care crisis that is nationwide — and the red state’s leaders maintain that government isn’t the solution.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">143cfef0-ba4b-11ef-bc10-0000a1ace67d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 18:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I maintain a distant relationship with my in-laws?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I maintain a distant relationship with my in-laws?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">32a49e90-ba3f-11ef-8160-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These 10 new holiday cookie recipes are a gift worth giving</title>
      <description>These 10 new holiday cookie recipes are a gift worth giving</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1650dae1-ba37-11ef-b03d-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 16:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In this million-dollar go-kart scene, some kids arrive in helicopters. Some have bodyguards.</title>
      <description>Go-karting has become a magnet for the money and power flowing through motorsports. It is now the wildly expensive first step to the exclusive world of Formula One racing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">644fe663-ba2c-11ef-b0de-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 15:02:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2fd6b81-ba27-11ef-9be8-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 14:30:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Korean President Yoon Suk Yeol impeached after decision to declare martial law</title>
      <description>Yoon must immediately hand over power to the prime minister, who will act as caretaker while the courts review the impeachment vote. The process could take months.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">26a47130-b9f2-11ef-ad81-00000a1ace62</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 08:05:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plans to allow California to ban sales of new gas-powered cars by 2035. Trump could try to reverse the move.</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to grant the state the right to set stronger climate rules for cars, SUVs and pickup trucks as soon as next week, according to two people briefed on the matter who spoke on the condition of anonymity because the decision is not yet public. President-elect Donald Trump will probably try to reverse the move, although those efforts could run into legal obstacles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55d85231-b9a4-11ef-ab42-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 22:48:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Syrian rebels hand over American Travis Timmerman to U.S. troops near the country’s border with Jordan, photos show</title>
      <description>Timmerman, a Missouri native who has said he was taken prisoner after crossing into Syria months ago, was discovered in the days since Bashar al-Assad’s ouster as the country’s long-ruling dictator. On Friday, Timmerman was escorted by the rebels to a U.S. military garrison in southeastern Syria and later flown by helicopter to Jordan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">99bd0f10-b993-11ef-998a-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 20:48:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Russia is packing up military equipment in Syria after the fall of ally Bashar al-Assad, satellite imagery shows</title>
      <description>Images released by Maxar show cargo planes at a Russian airfield in Syria with their nose cones opened to receive heavy equipment. Russian S-400 air defense systems have also been moved. Assad fled Syria for Moscow this week as rebels took control of the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d66c74d0-b97c-11ef-a430-0000a1ace05f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 18:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax live chat: My stepson’s mom hits on my husband and is cold to me</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax live chat: My stepson’s mom hits on my husband and is cold to me</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62451290-b979-11ef-adc9-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 17:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Uyghur man escaped from China, then was deported back. He has not been heard from since.</title>
      <description>The secret repatriation from Cambodia of 23-year-old Abdureqip Rahman is a chilling example of how China exerts its will extrajudicially outside its borders, not only over Southeast Asian countries but also international bodies — including the United Nations, whose systems were designed to protect the world’s most vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ac699870-b96d-11ef-9737-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 16:16:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2cb8c400-b960-11ef-adc9-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 14:40:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jan. 6 report. Trump’s victory lap. Freed American. Electric vehicles. Bird die-off. Neanderthal babies. Meteors. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c73141e1-b949-11ef-aafd-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>François Bayrou named as prime minister of France as President Emmanuel Macron seeks stability after government collapse</title>
      <description>The new prime minister must now try to cobble together a government and get a handle on France’s spiraling deficit and debt burden — in a way that satisfies enough of the warring political factions to avoid everything crashing down again. The political and financial instability in France has unsettled broader Europe as it prepares for the Trump presidency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dc0b0bb0-b948-11ef-aafd-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 11:53:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ancient DNA has helped pinpoint when humans had babies with Neanderthals</title>
      <description>Studies in the journals Science and Nature found that interbreeding unfolded for an extended period, peaking 47,000 years ago. Faint remnants of our Neanderthal ancestry remain, influencing skin pigmentation, immune response — even whether or not you’re a morning person.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e6bf320-b8e1-11ef-9886-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 23:32:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putin made saving the Assad regime his personal project. Its collapse in Syria shows the limits of Russia’s global power.</title>
      <description>Russia intervened with a massive show of airpower in 2015 to prevent Bashar al-Assad’s defeat by Syrian rebels. His fall this week has humiliated Moscow, dealing a blow to President Vladimir Putin’s goal of forging Russia into a great world power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ea5c4a0-b8dd-11ef-bfac-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 23:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin (R) takes aim at ‘sanctuary cities’ with proposal to require local law enforcement to work with ICE</title>
      <description>Youngkin said the state budget plan he will unveil next week will seek to require local law enforcement across the state to cooperate with federal immigration authorities. Fairfax and Arlington counties are among the localities that would have to start complying with requests from immigration officials. Youngkin’s proposal would still require approval by the General Assembly.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">779ef500-b8cc-11ef-8cc3-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 21:02:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. watchdog cites missteps in FBI intelligence gathering before Jan. 6, 2021, attack on U.S. Capitol</title>
      <description>The FBI properly shared the intelligence it gathered before the violent and chaotic riot with relevant law enforcement agencies but made some missteps that may have hampered preparations, including failing to canvas field offices for information that confidential human sources may have provided, according to a report released by the Justice Department’s inspector general. The FBI and Department of Homeland Security have been sharply criticized for what a Senate committee report described as a failure to believe the intelligence tips they received in the run up to the attack.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0ee0710-b8b4-11ef-8ca7-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:14:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Injured husband ignored spouse’s pleas to take care of himself</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Injured husband ignored spouse’s pleas to take care of himself</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1445eca0-b8ab-11ef-b4ea-000a1acec017</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 17:03:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This insect flies into today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc6b20f0-b895-11ef-9750-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 14:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Dept. takes action to prevent child sex abuse by school police officers after Post investigation</title>
      <description>In unveiling the new standards for the nation’s roughly 20,000 school police officers, the Justice Department called for training and policies to protect students — a first-of-its-kind effort to create safeguards around cops with immense access to children. It began drafting the new guidance in September, after a Washington Post investigation revealed that predatory school officers have used their positions to meet, groom and sexually exploit students.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41895960-b88b-11ef-92da-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kash Patel. Luigi Mangione. Defense bill. Biden pardons. Missing woman found. Bill Belichick. Mystery drones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b962dd0-b880-11ef-b7df-000a1ace0429</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden is commuting nearly 1,500 sentences, pardoning 39 people in what White House says is ‘largest single-day grant of clemency’</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden announced he will commute the sentences of close to 1,500 people on home confinement and will pardon 39 convicted of non-violent crimes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fca3f861-b87a-11ef-9c34-00000a1ace22</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 11:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No daylight saving time? See how early or late you would be in the dark.</title>
      <description>Would you be okay if the sun rose before 4 a.m., or after 10? Not changing clocks is a popular idea, but we’d have to live with the extremes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7d19550-b817-11ef-a128-0000a1ace85c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 23:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bill Belichick finalizing deal to become University of North Carolina football coach a year after leaving New England Patriots</title>
      <description>Belichick, who turns 73 in April, won six Super Bowls in 24 seasons with New England. He was passed over in the last NFL hiring cycle after departing from the Patriots in January. Belichick has never coached at the college level.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b49396d0-b815-11ef-878c-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 23:14:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report commissioned by D.C. Council finds ‘substantial evidence’ that indicted Ward 8 Democrat Trayon White Sr. violated its rules</title>
      <description>A law firm the council hired to investigate White found “substantial evidence” that he violated council rules and used his office for personal financial gain. The report was prompted by White’s arrest on a federal bribery charge, to which he has pleaded not guilty. The council is scheduled to meet Monday to determine whether to punish White and could vote to expel him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cecb990-b80b-11ef-bb49-00000a1acec1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 22:02:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House passes massive Pentagon policy bill after a heated debate over medical care for troops’ transgender children</title>
      <description>Democrats and some Republicans expressed frustration with Speaker Mike Johnson (R-Louisiana), whose provision targeting the specialized treatment eroded the $895 billion bill’s bipartisan support.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77fab430-b809-11ef-b28a-00000a1ace2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nasdaq index breaks 20,000 for the first time as Big Tech carries the benchmark</title>
      <description>The Nasdaq composite index is now up more than 33 percent for the year. Prominent technology stocks led Wednesday’s rally, with Amazon, Alphabet, Meta and Tesla all closing higher.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8fb616f0-b804-11ef-9022-0000a1ace199</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 21:11:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI Director Christopher A. Wray to resign before President-elect Trump, who vowed to replace him, takes office</title>
      <description>Donald Trump announced last month that he would nominate loyalist Kash Patel to serve as FBI director, sending a message to Wray that he should either resign in the middle of his 10-year term or prepare to be fired. The incoming president and his allies have long criticized the FBI for investigations of Trump and of possible ties between his campaign and Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4526ab00-b7f4-11ef-9d6a-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:15:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Aunt resents 20-something nieces’ ‘massive’ salaries</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Aunt resents 20-something nieces’ ‘massive’ salaries</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">843feb31-b7e5-11ef-8a04-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 17:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Skyglow’ sounds pretty, but it’s causing major problems. Here’s how we can reduce it.</title>
      <description>All the light we would rather not see</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19a9d5a1-b7e1-11ef-87fd-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:58:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: A restaurant offered a diner $200 to change an online review. Is that bribery? Our food critic takes your questions.</title>
      <description>Happening now: A restaurant offered a diner $200 to change an online review. Is that bribery? Our food critic takes your questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d767cc0-b7db-11ef-bb71-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 16:15:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albertsons calls off merger and sues Kroger, saying it did not do its best to get regulatory approval for the grocery megadeal</title>
      <description>Albertsons said Wednesday it is seeking “billions of dollars in damages” from Kroger for its “self-serving conduct.” The lawsuit comes the day after a federal judge issued an injunction blocking Kroger’s proposed $24.6 billion acquisition of Albertsons.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b44de140-b7d3-11ef-8ef0-000a1ace72d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 15:22:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An undefeated team in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a840dfd0-b7cc-11ef-bf3e-00000a1ace44</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 14:31:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inflation increased in November, as prices appear stuck after progress all year</title>
      <description>Overall inflation has proved stubborn and hasn't come down as quickly as in the beginning of the year, because of rising housing costs and insurance premiums.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">947826f1-b7c4-11ef-a67a-00000a1acecc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 13:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione. Trump’s team. Israeli strikes. Malibu fire. The Onion. Butterfly threat. Daylight saving. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75bc5631-b7b7-11ef-9b59-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 12:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge rejects sale of Alex Jones’s Infowars to the Onion</title>
      <description>Jones had challenged the Onion’s winning bid in an auction for the site he founded. The conspiracy theorist was ordered to auction Infowars to pay the roughly $1.5 billion in damages he owes for claiming the Sandy Hook school shooting was a hoax.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a72d9780-b77e-11ef-8e13-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 05:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The suspect in the slaying of a health-care CEO ‘had so much to offer,’ friends say. Now, he sits in prison, charged with murder.</title>
      <description>Luigi Mangione, a son of a prominent Baltimore family and an Ivy League graduate, had seemingly lost his way. Brian Thompson, a son of small-town Iowa who ascended to become CEO of UnitedHealthcare, appeared to be reaching new heights. Their paths allegedly intersected on a Midtown Manhattan sidewalk, ending in tragedy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41e54240-b75d-11ef-a6ef-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 01:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Washington Nationals win MLB draft lottery, will pick first in July</title>
      <description>The Nationals had the fourth-best odds — 10.2 percent — to land the top pick, but they won the draft lottery Tuesday night and will do just that. They last picked first in 2009 and 2010, landing franchise icons Stephen Strasburg and Bryce Harper with those selections. Among the candidates to go No. 1 in 2025: Oklahoma high school shortstop Ethan Holliday, brother of the Baltimore Orioles' Jackson Holliday and son of former MLB slugger Matt Holliday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a23829a1-b749-11ef-9c75-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 22:53:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge halts Kroger-Albertsons deal for now, putting merger of two supermarket giants at risk</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Adrienne Nelson sided with the Federal Trade Commission and several state attorneys general who oppose Kroger’s proposed $24.6 billion acquisition of Albertsons. Although the block is temporary, Kroger attorney Matt Wolf said during the hearing that an injunction would effectively end the deal.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a2ab6d90-b738-11ef-aa57-0000a1ace07c</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 20:52:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The iconic monarch butterfly could soon join the endangered species list as U.S. moves to protect it</title>
      <description>The U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service’s proposal to designate the orange butterfly as threatened with extinction could have enormous consequences for landowners across its huge range, which extends across much of the Lower 48. The monarch makes an epic annual flight from the mountains of Mexico through the United States and into Canada.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">88ca34b0-b729-11ef-ae53-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 19:04:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Keeping drama at bay at a family wedding without plus-one support</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Keeping drama at bay at a family wedding without plus-one support</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8362fcf0-b71a-11ef-80ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 17:16:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unsealed criminal complaint alleges details of UnitedHealthcare CEO’s killing, including ‘written admissions’ and footage</title>
      <description>Police allege Luigi Mangione, 26, is the person who killed Brian Thompson based on evidence that includes “written admissions about the crime” and surveillance footage, the complaint says.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f2a151-b716-11ef-8ab5-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 16:48:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He was suicidal and needed help. Online predators pushed him to take his life on camera.</title>
      <description>The death of a Minnesota man offers a case study into how the sadistic online group known as 764 has used the messaging app Discord to find and torment vulnerable people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8263e4d0-b70c-11ef-9e15-00000a1ace26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 15:36:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A pair of $28 million slippers in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28fea030-b705-11ef-859f-00000a1ace64</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione. Pete Hegseth. Syria. Daniel Penny. Murdoch drama. AI videos. Golden Globes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4860f480-b6ee-11ef-bfe0-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione charged with murder in UnitedHealthcare shooting</title>
      <description>A five-day manhunt sparked by the fatal shooting of health insurance executive Brian Thompson in Manhattan ended in central Pennsylvania with the arrest of Mangione, 26. Warrant details on the New York state courts website list charges of murder, illegal gun possession and possessing a forged instrument. The criminal complaint remains sealed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06c38c00-b6b1-11ef-ba09-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 04:41:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Luigi Mangione, person of interest in killing of UnitedHealthcare CEO, arrested in Pennsylvania on gun charges</title>
      <description>Mangione, 26, faces five counts including carrying a firearm without a license, possessing instruments of a crime and providing law enforcement with false identification, according to a criminal complaint filed in Altoona, Pennsylvania. He was arraigned at the Blair County courthouse on Monday evening and denied bail.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7c754980-b68d-11ef-952b-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:27:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Police identify Luigi Mangione, 26, as man being held in connection with fatal shooting of UnitedHealthcare CEO Brian Thompson</title>
      <description>Thompson, chief executive of the Minnesota-based insurance giant, was shot and killed on Wednesday morning outside a hotel in Midtown Manhattan where he was scheduled to attend an investor conference. Police said they believed the 50-year-old was targeted. The shooting sparked a manhunt that spread beyond New York after police found evidence the shooter left the city on a bus shortly after the killing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b5238c0-b65e-11ef-ae47-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 18:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband vents his road rage onto his spouse in the car</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband vents his road rage onto his spouse in the car</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">28543c30-b651-11ef-909c-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2024 17:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
