<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:02:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sovereignty wins the 151st Kentucky Derby, the first leg of horse racing’s Triple Crown</title>
      <description>Sovereignty won the Run for the Roses on Saturday at Churchill Downs in Louisville.
The next leg of the Triple Crown is the Preakness Stakes, to be held May 17 in Baltimore, followed by the Belmont Stakes on June 7 in Saratoga Springs, New York.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3aea8f0-2873-11f0-81d9-00000a1ace4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 23:11:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yes, brown rice is healthier than white rice — except in some limited cases</title>
      <description>Recent concerns over the health risks of eating brown rice are mostly overblown, studies show. Experts contend that the nutritional benefits outweigh any concerns about arsenic in a varied diet. A caveat is that some groups, such as infants and toddlers, may be more vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b43423a0-2861-11f0-8d45-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 21:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Buffett to step down as CEO of Berkshire Hathaway by year’s end after leading the conglomerate for decades</title>
      <description>Buffett, 94, announced his retirement intention at Berkshire Hathaway’s annual meeting in Omaha. He said he would recommend Greg Abel, whom Buffett has previously said would succeed him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5ddedf20-284f-11f0-b290-0000a1ace80d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: How do I forgive my in-laws when the real issue is my skin color?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">165261b0-2839-11f0-81de-00000a1ace98</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 16:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At a Kentucky farm, star racehorses help people fight a monster: Addiction</title>
      <description>The Stable Recovery program at Taylor Made Farm changes lives with the remarkable healing power of animals. Men in the program live on the farm and learn how to care for the elite racehorses, giving them a sense of structure and purpose many of them had struggled to find.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">475fa5b0-282f-11f0-993b-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 14:59:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cd25c8d0-2822-11f0-b3ae-0000a1aceb64</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:30:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ousted national security adviser Michael Waltz had angered Trump by coordinating privately with Israel over plans to attack Iran</title>
      <description>Waltz appeared to have engaged in intense coordination with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu about military options against Iran ahead of an Oval Office meeting last month between the Israeli leader and President Donald Trump, two people with knowledge of the episode said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b62b4940-2820-11f0-98d4-0000a1ace003</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 13:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Australia’s center-left party is projected to win reelection in dramatic turnaround fueled by Trump tariffs</title>
      <description>Despite trailing in polls two months ago, Prime Minister Anthony Albanese appears to be on course for a second term, although it is not clear whether his Labor Party would be able to govern outright or would need to partner with a smaller party or independents. Albanese’s comeback would be the second by a center-left leader in less than a week, with Canada’s Mark Carney managing a similar feat on Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be499fa0-280c-11f0-9f23-0000a1aceb0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 10:52:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our best mint julep recipes, plus Hot Browns, pimento cheese and more Kentucky Derby snacks</title>
      <description>Our best mint julep recipes, plus Hot Browns, pimento cheese and more Kentucky Derby snacks</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ed1b82f0-279c-11f0-b22c-00000a1aceff</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 21:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CIA plans to cut 1,200 positions as Trump administration eyes downsizing of thousands across U.S. intelligence community</title>
      <description>The White House recently informed lawmakers that it intends to trim the workforce at the CIA and other major U.S. spy units, downsizing the government’s most sensitive national security agencies, according to people familiar with the plans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f45755a0-2795-11f0-87e5-00000a1aceb9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 20:42:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Family of slain Capitol rioter Ashli Babbitt has reached settlement in principle of wrongful-death lawsuit</title>
      <description>Lawyers for the Justice Department and Judicial Watch said they'd reached a settlement in principle with the family of Babbitt, whose fatal shooting became a defining moment of the Jan. 6, 2021, Capitol riot. Babbitt's husband filed the lawsuit last year, seeking $30 million. The case was set to go to trial until President Donald Trump took office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ec2fe1e1-2785-11f0-a294-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 18:47:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Daughter wishes I was a ‘normal mom’ who's excited for her wedding</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Daughter wishes I was a ‘normal mom’ who's excited for her wedding</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8f21c510-2774-11f0-94ea-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:43:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gregg Popovich will no longer coach the Spurs after he suffered a stroke in November</title>
      <description>Popovich, 76, is the NBA’s all-time winningest coach and led San Antonio to five championships since taking over during the 1996-97 season.
He was replaced on an interim basis this season after suffering what the team called a “mild stroke” before a game Nov. 2. The team announced that Popovich will transition to a role as president of basketball operations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">164f2a40-2771-11f0-9dea-00000a1ace5f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 16:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump budget would cut nondefense programs by 23 percent and increase defense spending by 13 percent next year</title>
      <description>The White House released a partial budget proposal that underscores how much the administration aims to reduce federal spending. There were no details on taxes or on programs such as Social Security and Medicare.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68400200-2769-11f0-b21a-000a1ace09b7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 15:23:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JD Vance writes in an op-ed: What Trump achieved in his first 100 days</title>
      <description>JD Vance: What President Trump achieved in his first 100 days</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff7c9420-2765-11f0-842d-0000a1ace054</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:59:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruth Buzzi, famed as dowdy purse slinger on ‘Laugh-In,’ dies at 88</title>
      <description>Buzzi was a comedic actress with a high-beam smile who often played sidekicks both wisecracking and wise. She scowled her way to pop culture fame on the comedy-variety show “Rowan &amp; Martin’s Laugh-In” playing a matron who wields her purse like a cudgel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2b77f4e0-2764-11f0-917d-00000a1ace97</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 14:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dcc7a750-2759-11f0-ba5f-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 13:32:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The labor market slowed in April, as employers added 177,000 jobs, a solid showing amid tariff uncertainty</title>
      <description>The unemployment rate remained steady at 4.2 percent, according to the latest jobs report from the Bureau of Labor Statistics, as the labor market largely weathered the turmoil of tariff policy in April.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cca1b7b0-2751-11f0-840b-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 12:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waltz ouster. Trump setbacks. Elon Musk. Rising prices. Missing journalist. Bird decline. Cookbook drama. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a4555300-2744-11f0-8d89-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 11:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration calls for defunding NPR and PBS in executive order</title>
      <description>The order instructs the Corporation for Public Broadcasting to cease direct funding to the services and to end grants that local stations can spend on NPR and PBS.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13d15cd1-2720-11f0-a049-00000a1ace24</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 06:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A rising Hegseth aide first appointed under Biden has drawn scrutiny inside the Pentagon — and the White House</title>
      <description>Some Republicans loyal to the president have sought to block the elevation of Ricky Buria, whom officials say Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has openly considered for his next chief of staff. The “purity” questions surrounding Buria illustrate the increasingly politicized climate enveloping the Pentagon.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09fb7030-26d8-11f0-9da4-0000a1ace337</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 22:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump taps Michael Waltz for U.N. ambassador, says Secretary of State Rubio will replace him as interim national security adviser</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s announcement on social media followed reports that Waltz, who has lost favor in the White House and among other Trump loyalists, was going to be replaced as national security adviser. Marco Rubio will continue as secretary of state until a permanent replacement for Waltz is found, Trump said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">54cc7270-26bb-11f0-915a-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:37:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says Trump cannot use Alien Enemies Act to deport Venezuelans, in first major ruling on the legality of using the act</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Fernando Rodriguez, Jr. said President Donald Trump exceeded his authority when he invoked the wartime provision to declare, without providing evidence, that the United States was being invaded by a Venezuelan gang and had the authority to deport alleged gang members without a hearing to El Salvador.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10134600-26b5-11f0-916d-00000a1acec0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 17:52:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guess who’s actually winning the trade war? Matt Bai spent the past month untangling the case.</title>
      <description>Are countries being pressured to help the world’s richest man? Or are they just making smart deals?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98113810-26a5-11f0-a284-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 16:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to replace embattled national security adviser Michael Waltz, current and former officials say</title>
      <description>Waltz’s exit would mark the first major upheaval on President Donald Trump’s top national security staff. His critics have deemed Waltz out of step with Trump’s “America First” foreign policy agenda, and he has steadily lost favor after revelations that he relied on unclassified online communications for highly sensitive government business.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39b17780-26a0-11f0-b6f9-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 15:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to block California’s ban on sales of gas-powered cars by 2035. It’s unclear whether the Senate will follow suit.</title>
      <description>Eleven other states have pledged to adopt California’s ban. The House Republicans’ vote ignores legal opinions from the Senate parliamentarian and the Government Accountability Office that Congress lacks the legal authority to prevent states from enforcing such climate rules.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c893e50-269b-11f0-a497-000a1ace4569</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 14:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal daily information requirements into today's On The Record</title>
      <description>Federal daily information requirements into today's On The Record</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae9a0180-2690-11f0-836c-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:32:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>George Clooney, Sarah Snook and Audra McDonald are among the 2025 Tony nominees</title>
      <description>The Tony Awards ceremony honoring the best of the Broadway season will be held June 8.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">69fde810-268c-11f0-ba7c-00000a1ace8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 13:01:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ukraine deal. Kamala Harris. Vaccine change. Supreme Court. Gaza map. Pacific Northwest quake. Axolotl hope. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a794250-267b-11f0-a9a1-0000a1ace973</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 10:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris condemns Trump’s policies and ‘unconstitutional demands’ in her first major speech since leaving the White House</title>
      <description>The 2024 Democratic presidential nominee urged her supporters to summon the courage to fight what she called President Donald Trump’s efforts to stoke fear and “punish truth tellers.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c0223a80-263b-11f0-b737-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 03:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capitals beat Canadiens in Game 5 to advance to the second round of the Stanley Cup playoffs for the first time since 2018</title>
      <description>Washington, the No. 1 seed in the Eastern Conference, topped scrappy Montreal on home ice Wednesday to take the best-of-seven series. The Capitals, who will meet the Carolina Hurricanes in the second round, had not clinched a playoff series at home since 2015.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba3d5c62-262e-11f0-9616-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 01:50:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. will require shift in how new vaccines are tested, HHS says</title>
      <description>The potential change outlined in a statement says all new vaccines will be required to undergo placebo testing, a procedure in which some people receive the vaccine and others receive an inert substance — such as a saline shot — before the results are compared. The Department of Health and Human Services says the move will increase transparency but medical experts fear it could limit access to vaccines and undermine the public’s trust in immunization depending on how it is implemented. HHS did not fully clarify how the change would work and for which vaccines the testing would apply.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f91d7c71-2625-11f0-8806-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. and Ukraine sign a deal to develop Ukraine's mineral resources with Washington, affirming a ‘long-term strategic alignment’</title>
      <description>The deal’s language marks a win for Kyiv, which has been seeking any concrete show of support from the United States since President Donald Trump returned to power.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c22014e1-2610-11f0-9dbe-000a1ace826d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 22:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happening now: Can the D.C. Council really say no to RFK Stadium site deal? We’re answering your questions.</title>
      <description>D.C. and the Washington Commanders this week unveiled a $3.7 billion deal to transform the crumbling RFK Stadium site into a new home for the NFL franchise, surrounded by retail, housing and park space. How are the D.C. Council and D.C. residents reacting? Post Metro and Sports reporters Jenny Gathright, Meagan Flynn, Sam Fortier and Nicki Jhabvala are answering your questions now during a live chat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">babaace0-25e5-11f0-87da-00000a1aceb0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 17:08:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems open to allowing religious public schools, a major move that would redraw the boundary between church and state</title>
      <description>The Supreme Court on Wednesday appeared open to allowing the creation of the nation’s first public religious charter school in Oklahoma. A ruling for St. Isidore of Seville Catholic Virtual School would allow taxpayer money to directly flow to a faith-based school for the first time and give government sponsorship to a curriculum that calls for students to adhere to Catholic beliefs and religious mission.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f036adf0-25e1-11f0-b1ba-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dinner guest feels ‘censored’ by one person’s no-politics plea</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dinner guest feels ‘censored’ by one person’s no-politics plea</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">93f3d9f1-25dc-11f0-ae47-0000a1ace91b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 16:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Hegseth has an unorthodox role shaping Pentagon affairs, appearing at high-level meetings, vetting job candidates and more</title>
      <description>The activities of Jennifer Hegseth throughout her husband’s budding tenure in President Donald Trump’s Cabinet has snapped into focus in recent weeks, after damaging news reports about Pete Hegseth’s stumbles as his on-the-job training plays out in public view.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fe33ecd0-25cb-11f0-b028-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 14:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An e-commerce giant and tariffs in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to get your Wednesday points</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">41449a62-25c7-11f0-bead-00000a1acebd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 13:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The economy shrank in the first quarter by an annual pace of 0.3%, as tariffs sapped economic growth</title>
      <description>In the first few months of the year, President Donald Trump's tariffs unexpectedly dragged down the U.S. economy, even before fully taking effect, according to fresh data released by the Commerce Department on Wednesday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">65893f00-25bf-11f0-9eac-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 12:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s 100 days. Kamala Harris. Tariff impacts. Fluoride ban. DEI. Strength training. Escaped kangaroo. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">40b92fd0-25b2-11f0-9937-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 10:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postal Service’s law enforcement arm is aiding Trump’s immigration crackdown, according to people and documents</title>
      <description>Homeland Security officials are seeking access to postal records, including photos of the outside of mail and other items, and the Postal Inspection Service participated in a recent raid that led to the arrest of more than 100 undocumented migrants.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ec8c660-2542-11f0-aea6-0000a1ace017</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 21:38:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump signs executive order to ease some auto industry tariffs in administration’s latest retreat on levies</title>
      <description>The move eases tariffs on imported autos to ensure they aren't “stacked” on top of other levies, such as for steel and aluminum. Automakers will also get tariff relief on imported parts for cars completed in the United States over the next two years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0f572110-2538-11f0-8a85-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 20:25:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department begins prosecuting migrants who breach expanded military zone at southern border, charging at least 28 so far</title>
      <description>The migrants were charged with crossing into the 170-mile “National Defense Area” in New Mexico, a 60-foot-deep strip of land that has effectively been turned into part of a U.S. military installation. Prosecutors added the charge to the more common misdemeanor of entering the United States illegally.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">182a7a20-2525-11f0-a10e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The EPA is canceling nearly 800 grants issued under Biden, a little-noticed court filing reveals</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency plans to cancel a total of 781 grants issued under President Joe Biden, EPA lawyers wrote in a court filing last week — nearly twice the number previously reported. The filing in the case Woonasquatucket River Watershed Council v. Department of Agriculture will affect projects across the nation, from sealing homes against wildfire smoke to addressing coastal flooding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d8cf8f0-251e-11f0-bdc2-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 17:19:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sister says they’re ‘not friends,’ so why keep making plans?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sister says they’re ‘not friends,’ so why keep making plans?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70b26070-2513-11f0-b83f-000a1acedd66</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 16:03:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Ukrainian journalist tried to expose how Russia is detaining and abusing civilians in occupied territories. She ended up dead.</title>
      <description>A coalition of 45 international journalists, led by Paris-based Forbidden Stories and including The Washington Post, continued the work of Viktoriia Roshchyna and conducted a months-long investigation into her death and the torture of Ukrainian civilians at Russian detention centers stretching from occupied Ukraine to northern Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c3ac47f0-2504-11f0-b444-00000a1ace35</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 14:18:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A fiery statement by a Democratic governor in today's On the Record.</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">424c38b1-24fe-11f0-a985-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most think Trump is serious about Canada, Greenland and third-term proposals, but oppose them all, poll finds</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has proposed taking over Canada and Greenland, imprisoning U.S. citizens overseas, and serving an unconstitutional third term. Most Americans say they think he’s serious about each proposal. And most oppose each one, including many Republicans, according to a Washington Post-ABC News-Ipsos poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c47fdab0-24fb-11f0-b967-00000a1ace38</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 13:13:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common chemicals in plastic linked to more than 350,000 deaths from heart disease each year</title>
      <description>Exposure to phthalates — a set of chemicals found in food packaging plastics, and lotions and shampoos — contributes to 13 percent of all heart disease deaths in people between ages 55 and 64 each year worldwide, researchers have found. The findings were published Tuesday in the journal EBioMedicine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d613540-24f5-11f0-8f7e-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 12:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Carney. Lie detector tests. Deadly crash. Deepfake nudes. Power outage. Plastic dangers. Shipwreck mural. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1965d790-24e9-11f0-b404-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 11:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
