<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 03:06:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>We analyzed dozens of ultra-processed foods. Here are the healthiest options.</title>
      <description>You can find less processed, healthier options by checking ingredient lists for additives, preservatives, fillers and artificial ingredients. Use our guide to find ultra-processed foods in five common categories, including bread and chicken nuggets, that are better for you than others.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a496190-cd4b-11ef-9d51-00000a1ace21</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 23:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ominous fire spreads near L.A.’s Pacific Palisades neighborhood and evacuations mount amid ‘life-threatening’ wind event</title>
      <description>A fire broke out on the Southern California coast, near Topanga Canyon and the Pacific Palisades, quickly exploding to at least 200 acres. Evacuation orders were issued for what’s being called the Palisades Fire down to the Pacific Coast Highway, as officials ordered residents in the hillside neighborhoods near the Getty Villa to leave.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37395ca0-cd3d-11ef-afe3-00000a1ace31</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 21:20:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Partner’s happy family triggers grief over loveless childhood</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Partner’s happy family triggers grief over loveless childhood</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">857743b1-cd23-11ef-93d2-00000a1acecf</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 18:16:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Peter Yarrow dies at 86. The singer-songwriter found fame as part of the influential folk music trio Peter, Paul and Mary.</title>
      <description>The group helped stir the folk music revival in the 1960s by popularizing songs of protest and social change, including “Blowin’ in the Wind” and “If I Had a Hammer.” Yarrow co-wrote the hit “Puff, the Magic Dragon.” Yarrow’s reputation was tarnished after a guilty plea on charges related to a sexual encounter with a minor. He was pardoned by President Jimmy Carter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f0fdfbd0-cd1c-11ef-a78c-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 17:29:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Cannon blocks immediate release of special counsel report on Trump classified-documents investigation</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Aileen M. Cannon barred special counsel Jack Smith and Attorney General Merrick Garland from “releasing, sharing, or transmitting” the long-awaited report or any drafts or conclusions while a federal appeals court in Atlanta weighs whether making the information public would unfairly harm Donald Trump’s two codefendants in the case.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e2dfbee1-cd1b-11ef-86ca-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 17:21:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. declares genocide in Sudan and imposes sanctions on paramilitary leader</title>
      <description>Fighters for the paramilitary Rapid Support Forces are committing genocide in Sudan, the State Department said Tuesday, and the Treasury Department imposed sanctions on the group's chief, Mohamed Hamdan Dagalo, known as Hemedti. The RSF has “systematically murdered men and boys — even infants — on an ethnic basis, and deliberately targeted women and girls from certain ethnic groups for rape and other forms of brutal sexual violence,” Secretary of State Antony Blinken said in a statement.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e71c8591-cd18-11ef-9459-0000a1ace7f4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 17:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beef-loving country turns to pork in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">202602e0-cd04-11ef-a0aa-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 14:31:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zuckerberg ends fact-checking on Facebook and Instagram, calling election ‘a cultural tipping point’ on free speech</title>
      <description>Meta CEO Mark Zuckerberg said Tuesday that his platforms would “restore free expression” by abandoning fact-checkers that he said were “too politically biased, and have destroyed more trust than they created.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a6b8b610-ccfd-11ef-9570-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 13:45:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jean-Marie Le Pen, father of the far-right National Front party of France, has died at the age of 96</title>
      <description>In recent years, the National Front under the leadership of his daughter Marine Le Pen distanced itself from him in an effort to mainstream the party and scour its image as racist and antisemitic. He was suspended from the party (now known as National Rally) in May 2015 and expelled three months later.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8c8eb030-ccf5-11ef-a233-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 12:47:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kamala Harris. Trump sentencing. Justin Trudeau. Deadly earthquake. Bird flu. Forever chemicals. Dinosaur prints. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb15ec60-ccee-11ef-93f9-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 11:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fate of nearly 1,600 Jan. 6 defendants depends on President-elect Donald Trump</title>
      <description>Many charged in connection with the attack on the Capitol four years ago have seized on Trump’s promise to pardon an unspecified number of Jan. 6 defendants. Will he extend mercy only to those accused of misdemeanors like trespassing, who crossed police lines and entered the Capitol as part of the mob? Or would he also pardon those charged or convicted of violent felonies such as assaulting law enforcement officers or others?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fab66680-cc81-11ef-9d59-00000a1aceb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 23:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First U.S. bird flu death reported in Louisiana patient who had contact with sick and dead birds in backyard flock</title>
      <description>The patient was over 65 and had underlying medical conditions, officials said. The death does not change the assessment by disease experts that the immediate risk to the public’s health from the H5N1 bird flu remains low.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ae3c59e0-cc77-11ef-8301-00000a1aceb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 21:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The D.C. region could see another burst of snow tonight, and many schools will be closed again on Tuesday. Follow our updates.</title>
      <description>After a lull, snow will pick up again in the early evening in the region. So far, snow totals have reached 5 to 9 inches in the area, with an additional inch or two still possible.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2243b200-cc70-11ef-97fb-0000a1acebcf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congress certifies Trump’s electoral college victory in a peaceful transfer of power four years after the Jan. 6 Capitol riot</title>
      <description>Lawmakers convened a joint session of Congress to count electoral college votes and certified President-elect Donald Trump’s victory over Vice President Kamala Harris in the November presidential election.

It comes four years after a violent mob of Trump supporters stormed the Capitol on Jan. 6, 2021, delaying the tally of votes showing that Joe Biden had won the 2020 election.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">62627820-cc5d-11ef-bd6e-0000a1ace7fb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 18:38:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Sadness overcomes the adult-child caregiver to a nonagenarian dad</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Sadness overcomes the adult-child caregiver to a nonagenarian dad</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cee43640-cc4f-11ef-a2e9-0000a1ace48b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 17:01:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canada's Justin Trudeau will resign as Liberal Party leader, paving the way for a new prime minister</title>
      <description>Championing progressive politics, Trudeau was elected prime minister in 2015 and viewed around the world as a bulwark of the liberal order. He won reelection in 2019 and 2021, but his popularity has cratered over the last year amid a cost-of-living crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9dee0c70-cc48-11ef-8c15-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerable Fed official tasked with regulating Wall Street is stepping down, as Trump’s advisers considered demoting him</title>
      <description>Trump advisers had been considering taking the unprecedented step of trying to strip Michael Barr of his leadership role as the Federal Reserve’s vice chairman for banking supervision, according to people familiar with their thinking. Barr is stepping down from the role, the Fed confirmed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c4553ec0-cc47-11ef-9636-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 16:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Oscars front-runners emerged, Demi Moore finally got her moment and more highlights from the Golden Globes</title>
      <description>At the annual awards show, “Wicked” failed to defy gravity and Globes voters affirmed the TV ascendancy of “Shogun.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c266fcf0-cc3f-11ef-9412-0000a1ace699</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 15:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Nobel Peace Prize winner is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14427b20-cc3c-11ef-8078-000a1ace3300</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:39:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The NFL playoffs are set. Here’s the full bracket, plus the matchups and the schedule for the first round and beyond.</title>
      <description>The Detroit Lions are the NFC's top seed for the first time as they attempt to advance to their first Super Bowl. The Kansas City Chiefs are the AFC's top seed; like the Lions, they have a first-round bye. The NFL's 12 other playoff teams will be in action next weekend. Here is how the first round shakes out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">605eae20-cc37-11ef-b109-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 14:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nippon Steel, U.S. Steel file lawsuits against Biden, others over handling of blocked deal</title>
      <description>The companies allege the president’s decision to block the $14.9 billion acquisition on national security grounds violated their right to due process. They also target the head of the steelworkers union and a rival steelmaker’s CEO in a separate filing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73f1cb50-cc2f-11ef-8bf4-0000a1ace2f8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The worst of a winter storm is hitting the Mid-Atlantic, with heavy snow to come after dumping over a foot in parts of the Midwest</title>
      <description>From Missouri to Virginia, hundreds of thousands of customers are without power on Monday morning. Heavy snow — up to a foot in spots — is expected in Washington, D.C., Maryland and Virginia in what could become the region's biggest snowstorm since at least January 2022. As it treks east, the winter storm is producing snow and ice across a distance of 1,000 miles.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a9dc111-cc29-11ef-982b-0000a1ace926</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:27:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump certification. Tariff plans. Winter storm. New Orleans. Golden Globes. NFL playoffs. Massive tuna. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8d70080-cc25-11ef-8851-00000a1ace74</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 12:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vatican names Cardinal Robert McElroy, a liberal and Trump critic, to lead D.C. archdiocese</title>
      <description>McElroy has led the diocese of San Diego along the Mexican border for decades and is known for his liberal views on immigration. He is closely aligned with Pope Francis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58c0d990-cc23-11ef-8986-0000a1ace69d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 11:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Emilia Pérez’ and ‘The Brutalist’ led the movie awards at the Golden Globes, while ‘Shogun’ dominated in TV categories</title>
      <description>Highlights at the annual ceremony also included a surprise win for Demi Moore for “The Substance,” the veteran actress’s first major award.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55c4e0d1-cbe5-11ef-8f0e-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 04:18:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>President Biden writes in an op-ed: What Americans should remember about Jan. 6</title>
      <description>“In time, there will be Americans who didn’t witness the Jan. 6 riot firsthand but will learn about it from footage and testimony of that day, from what is written in history books and from the truth we pass on to our children. We cannot allow the truth to be lost,” Biden wrote in an op-ed marking four years since the 2021 attack on the U.S. Capitol.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87dc2980-cbd5-11ef-8109-00000a1ace3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 02:25:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Golden Globes: Is it the year of ‘Wicked?’ Will ‘Conclave’ be ordained? Follow our live coverage of the awards show.</title>
      <description>The Post is watching and providing live commentary for all of the action from the 82nd annual awards, from host Nikki Glaser’s monologue to all of the night’s big winners.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">81a5a8f0-cbc8-11ef-9412-0000a1ace699</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:52:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A storm that could dump up to a foot of snow is moving into the D.C. region, and school closures are mounting. Follow our updates.</title>
      <description>Capital Weather Gang is predicting 6 to 10 inches of snow, while the National Weather Service has again increased its D.C. area forecast to 8 to 12 inches. Ahead of the storm, many school districts, including those in D.C., and Fairfax and Montgomery counties, announced closures for Monday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a8811c0-cbbe-11ef-9314-00000a1ace47</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 23:38:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New England Patriots fire coach Jerod Mayo, successor to Bill Belichick, after one season</title>
      <description>The Patriots fired Mayo on Sunday after they went 4-13 in his rookie season as an NFL head coach. They had utilized a succession plan written into the contract of Mayo, then their linebackers coach, to promote him last January to head coach on the day after they parted ways with Belichick following 24 seasons and six Super Bowl victories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90f50d80-cbb6-11ef-96f4-00000a1ace19</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 22:44:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The oldest animal ever found could reveal whether a crucial ocean current will collapse</title>
      <description>Clam shells could help scientists understand how the Atlantic Ocean’s sensitive circulation system behaved in the past — and predict whether that crucial system might catastrophically collapse.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">767dc010-cbb0-11ef-bd8c-0000a1ace3bf</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 22:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How lazy robots could help solve the world’s energy problems</title>
      <description>A group of scientists in Europe is teaching robots to use less power by thinking less, which could curb energy demand from data-hungry AI, self-driving cars and industrial robots.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">720833c0-cb7f-11ef-ac1d-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 16:09:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba8f6f40-cb71-11ef-ac40-0000a1ace759</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 14:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A winter storm will pummel more than a dozen states with snow and ice. These 10 cities will be hit hardest.</title>
      <description>Blizzard conditions are expected in Kansas and western Missouri on Sunday, with dangerously low wind chills on Sunday night. On Monday, the worst of the weather will be over the Mid-Atlantic. And by Tuesday morning, the storm will have pushed well offshore of the East Coast, leaving frigid temperatures, low wind chills and a deep snow pack in its wake.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2d86d370-cb69-11ef-add3-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 13:30:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The last days of a bizarre, glorious and outdated underground mall</title>
      <description>Walking into Northern Virginia’s Crystal City Underground is like stepping into yesterday’s idea of tomorrow. The maze of kitschy mom-and-pop stores below office buildings and above a Metro station had once seemed like something from the future. Now it’s closing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">61452490-cad9-11ef-ac68-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 20:20:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 5 inches of snow expected Sunday night into Monday night across the region</title>
      <description>Freezing temperatures will mean hazardous roads and probable school closures Monday. There is still uncertainty regarding where the heaviest snow will fall and whether ice will mix with the snow.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">dd63b710-cad1-11ef-ab0c-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 19:26:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t like to exercise? Try this simple, science-backed trick.</title>
      <description>If you’ve resolved to get more fit in 2025, “fartleks” — meaning “speed play” in Swedish — are an effective way to add intensity to activities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">517a8940-caae-11ef-8629-00000a1ace59</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 15:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">071ab7d0-caa9-11ef-b33d-00000a1acebc</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:34:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden will block future oil drilling across 625 million acres of U.S. waters</title>
      <description>President Joe Biden will move to prohibit future oil and gas leasing across parts of the Atlantic Ocean, Pacific Ocean, eastern Gulf of Mexico and the Northern Bering Sea, according to two people familiar with the matter. President-elect Donald Trump is likely to work with congressional Republicans to challenge the move.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0956c1f0-caa5-11ef-ac6a-00000a1ace66</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2025 14:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The similar paths to radicalization in foiled Taylor Swift concert attack, New Orleans carnage</title>
      <description>A troubling pattern of self-radicalization has emerged, experts and intelligence officials say, with the Islamic State’s online presence grooming would-be terrorists around the world.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a8f4bea0-ca24-11ef-ac40-0000a1ace759</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 22:47:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge upholds Trump’s felony conviction in New York, schedules sentencing for Jan. 10, days before presidential inauguration</title>
      <description>Donald Trump, the only former president ever charged with crimes, argued that his election in November to another term meant the judge should toss his conviction for falsifying business records to conceal a payment to adult-film actress Stormy Daniels.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6fdd6900-ca15-11ef-8bf4-00000a1ace4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 20:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Johnson reelected as House speaker after some GOP holdouts change votes. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Louisiana Republican Mike Johnson was reelected House speaker Friday on the first vote, overcoming skepticism about his leadership from some in his party. Johnson clinched the post after lawmakers who initially voted against him changed their votes. President-elect Donald Trump endorsed Johnson this week and urged Republican lawmakers to back him, in part so that the party could move quickly to enact Trump’s agenda.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1f7a09b1-ca0a-11ef-b232-000a1ace524c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 19:37:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: My daughter-in-law cut me off over my son’s secret child</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: My daughter-in-law cut me off over my son’s secret child</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ddc20b0-c9fb-11ef-90ac-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 17:50:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5e787fa2-c9df-11ef-98f7-0000a1ace37d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 14:31:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Surgeon general urges cancer warning labels for alcohol and a reassessment of recommended limits of consumption</title>
      <description>In an advisory, Vivek H. Murthy said alcohol consumption is the third leading preventable cause of cancer in the United States and contributes to 100,000 cancer cases and 20,000 related deaths each year. The warning label would need to be approved by Congress. It’s unclear how the next administration would handle the recommendation.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5c5f8ee0-c9d8-11ef-b184-0000a1ace446</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 13:40:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Orleans attack. Cybertruck driver. U.S. Steel. House speaker. Jan. 6 mystery. Hot 2024. Daylight saving. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3eeab280-c9ca-11ef-a3dc-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 11:59:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden decides to block U.S. Steel sale to Japanese buyer, administration officials say</title>
      <description>The move threatens the future of the once-iconic American business and is expected as early as Friday, according to two administration officials who spoke on the condition of anonymity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39cc4130-c987-11ef-b45d-00000a1ace87</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 04:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Years of inaction on ‘crisis’ at the Secret Service set the stage for the Trump rally shooting, Post review finds</title>
      <description>Three presidents and Congress failed to fix major vulnerabilities in the Secret Service that were identified a decade ago, contributing to an exodus of veteran agents that has left the service increasingly relying on less experienced members, including at the now-infamous Butler, Pennsylvania, rally where Donald Trump was nearly killed.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d61d8340-c95b-11ef-b5e8-0000a1ace649</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 22:49:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden plans to create two national monuments in California honoring tribes</title>
      <description>The Chuckwalla and Sáttítla national monuments would safeguard landscapes that Native American tribes have revered for thousands of years. The designations would come just weeks before President-elect Donald Trump's inauguration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44f50db0-c94d-11ef-8bf4-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 21:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tesla Cybertruck explosion outside Trump hotel in Las Vegas was likely a suicide, sheriff says</title>
      <description>Las Vegas Sheriff Kevin McMahill said at a news conference Thursday that the investigation indicates the driver sustained a self-inflicted gunshot wound to the head before the Cybertruck’s explosion. He said one of the guns found in the vehicle was located at the driver’s feet.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f09f5b01-c940-11ef-acc7-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Husband claims he doesn’t ‘know how’ to pack lunch for their kid</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Husband claims he doesn’t ‘know how’ to pack lunch for their kid</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fa061310-c930-11ef-bd07-0000a1aced6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 17:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
