<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 07:01:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>House panel joins Senate in launching bipartisan inquiry of Pentagon over Hegseth's order to kill boat strike survivors</title>
      <description>The Senate and House armed services committees’ pledge followed a Washington Post report revealing that Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth ordered that a U.S. strike leave no survivors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01fb6940-cd8a-11f0-baad-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 01:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playwright Tom Stoppard dies at 88. His works were among the most acclaimed and oft-performed of the past half-century.</title>
      <description>Stoppard, a Czech-born British dramatist, explored political, artistic and scientific questions — often with mash-ups of high and low culture. His most popular works include Tony Award-winning plays “Rosencrantz and Guildenstern Are Dead,” “Travesties” and “The Real Thing.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bcd24950-cd49-11f0-80b0-0000a1ace17d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my parents I didn’t dump my boyfriend</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I’m scared to tell my parents I didn’t dump my boyfriend</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">09fe2220-cd46-11f0-baad-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 17:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An investor called $140,000 the new poverty line. Experts disagreed but said he had a point.</title>
      <description>Michael Green’s tally of the costs of raising a family in the United States today is going viral, even if some economists scoff at his math.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7dc76e90-cd38-11f0-900a-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3feb60c0-cd30-11f0-a191-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FDA will impose strict vaccine requirements, claiming covid shot contributed to children’s deaths</title>
      <description>Vinay Prasad, the nation’s top vaccine regulator, told Food and Drug Administration officials that the agency will rethink its framework for annual flu shots, examine whether Americans should be receiving multiple vaccines at the same time and require vaccine makers to show far more data to prove the safety and value of their products.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b49b9550-cd23-11f0-b30b-0000a1aced8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counter-terrorism officials vetted D.C. National Guard shooting suspect before he entered U.S.</title>
      <description>Rahmanullah Lakanwal, 29, arrived in the United States through Operation Allies Welcome, a Biden-era program that helped resettle Afghan nationals after the U.S. military withdrawal from Afghanistan in 2021.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0c8e85b0-ccb1-11f0-adba-00000a1acef6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 23:22:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50 years ago, he saw a document in the JFK file. Where is it now?</title>
      <description>Despite Trump’s orders, report that Mexico believed Cuba was behind the assassination has not emerged.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c83145a1-cc8e-11f0-9644-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. police to begin patrolling with National Guard after fatal attack</title>
      <description>Troops patrolling in D.C. will be paired with local law enforcement personnel, at least temporarily, in the wake of the Wednesday attack that killed one National Guard member and critically injured another, according to an email obtained by The Washington Post and two D.C. police officials. If enacted on a long-term basis, the change would significantly shift the way National Guard members have worked with law enforcement in the District since their arrival.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">55ab3eb0-cc88-11f0-97b4-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 18:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth gave a verbal order to kill everybody in first Caribbean boat strike, officials say</title>
      <description>As two men clung to a stricken, burning ship targeted by SEAL Team 6, the Joint Special Operations commander followed the defense secretary’s order to leave no survivors.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e42ed41-cc81-11f0-94cb-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:38:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zelensky’s top aide, lead negotiator resigns amid corruption probe</title>
      <description>Andriy Yermak, the head of Ukraine’s presidential office, had emerged as one of the most contentious and powerful figures in the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e1e50d11-cc75-11f0-97c9-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:18:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And they’re off! Here are 6 names to watch in the race to the midterms.</title>
      <description>Columnists pick the top candidates to watch as the 2026 midterms begin.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">862ddea1-cc6d-11f0-bc46-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, and don't forget the bonus wager! Finish off your week with On the Record.</title>
      <description>Think you’ve got what it takes to earn a perfect score? Take today’s longer news quiz and complete your point total for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ed6e071-cc67-11f0-ac48-0000a1ace097</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:35:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>46 gifts we’re giving (and wishing for) this year</title>
      <description>We asked Washington Post staff members what items they really wanted this year, and what they deemed worthy to gift — the tech that improved their lives, the decanter beautiful enough to display, the game to make their family laugh together, the silk pillowcase their wife loves.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b7755000-cc64-11f0-a269-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. shooting. Hong Kong fire. No-cash bail. Mar-a-Lago. Black Friday. Creative hobbies. Vanished civilization. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb534820-cc51-11f0-9d51-000a1ace6c83</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the National Guard members shot near the White House on Wednesday has died, Trump says</title>
      <description>The victim, Spec. Sarah Beckstrom, was a 20-year-old from West Virginia. The second critically wounded National Guard member, 24-year-old Staff Sgt. Andrew Wolfe, is still fighting for his life, President Donald Trump said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">069103a0-cbed-11f0-b1a1-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 23:58:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 charts show who’s feeling good about the economy — and who isn’t</title>
      <description>In surveys, many people report feeling exasperated by high prices and slowing incomes. But not everyone is equally upset. And some are even feeling better about their finances now than they were a few months ago.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">672c1030-cbdc-11f0-a828-0000a1ace610</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 21:59:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A fiancé famous for waiting hurries up when sibling sets a date</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A fiancé famous for waiting hurries up when sibling sets a date</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b2d66e60-cbb2-11f0-b8cc-00000a1ace2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The location of historic Native American villages mentioned by John Smith was unknown — until now</title>
      <description>In the 1600s, English explorer Smith wrote of how he and his men were attacked by Native Americans along the Rappahannock River in Virginia. This summer, archaeologists came upon physical proof of the towns and villages that he had described.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">981b9d60-cbae-11f0-9f09-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:31:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Thanksgiving shrank down to the size of a screen</title>
      <description>The incredible shrinking all-American holiday</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bbc14610-cbaa-11f0-8de8-0000a1acec74</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 16:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National Guard shooting suspect drove to D.C. from Washington state and faces charges of assault with intent to kill, Pirro says</title>
      <description>The two members of West Virginia’s National Guard who were shot and critically wounded have been identified as Sarah Beckstrom, 20, and Andrew Wolfe, 24, U.S. Attorney Jeanine Pirro said at a news conference. Officials described the shooting as a targeted attack, but no potential motive has been established.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e872c680-cb9f-11f0-96d4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 14:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving from On The Record!</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your holiday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">484db990-cb9e-11f0-8e55-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 14:35:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. shooting. Hong Kong fire. Trump case. Economic exasperation. Ozempic 2.0. Happiness recipe. Green Wednesday. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9085e450-cb88-11f0-9056-00000a1ace34</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Afghan national has been identified as the man in custody in the shooting of National Guard members, two people familiar say</title>
      <description>The suspect, Rahmanullah Lakanwal, arrived in the U.S. in 2001 and for a time lived in Washington state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b3ebe960-cb2b-11f0-97a4-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardsmen shot in D.C. were targeted by attacker and are in critical condition, officials said in updates. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>West Virginia Gov. Patrick Morrisey initially said both Guard members were killed, but he later said he was getting “conflicting reports” about their condition. The suspect, who was also wounded, was taken into custody and transported to a hospital, officials said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">df588dc1-cb20-11f0-b0bf-00000a1acec6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 23:37:29 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two West Virginia National Guard members who were shot in D.C. have died, officials say. Police have a suspected shooter in custody.</title>
      <description>“These brave West Virginians lost their lives in the service of their country,” wrote West Virginia Gov. Patrick Morrisey. “We are in ongoing contact with federal officials as the investigation continues.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa6a2580-cb0a-11f0-bd32-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two National Guardsmen shot near White House. Their conditions are unknown. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>The shooting happened at the corner of 17th and H Streets NW, and three gunshot victims were transported to the hospital, according to D.C. Fire and EMS spokesperson Vito Maggiolo.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42e41670-cb03-11f0-9417-00000a1aced3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Death toll rises to 36 in Hong Kong high-rise fire, with 279 people still missing, official says</title>
      <description>The fire broke out at Wang Fuk Court in Tai Po, a northeastern district in Hong Kong’s New Territories. Rescue efforts have continued into the night. Officials have not yet commented on the cause of the blaze.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d05b22f0-caf4-11f0-8fc3-00000a1aced2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 18:22:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Should I wash my turkey inside and out before stuffing it? Ask our food team your Thanksgiving questions.</title>
      <description>Happening now: Should I wash my turkey inside and out before stuffing it? Ask our food team your Thanksgiving questions.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4518c830-caec-11f0-a0c2-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:20:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georgia prosecutor ends 2020 election interference case against Trump and his allies</title>
      <description>The racketeering case, brought in 2023, was bogged down by allegations of prosecutorial misconduct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5d15c01-cae7-11f0-b1a7-00000a1ace29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This Thanksgiving dish stars in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">85028de0-cad4-11f0-ab7f-00000a1acec7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 14:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At least 13 people dead after huge fire engulfs high-rise buildings in Hong Kong</title>
      <description>Two others were in critical condition, emergency services said. The fire appeared to spread across bamboo scaffolding at Wang Fuk Court in Tai Po.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9604e6b0-cacf-11f0-8be1-00000a1ace99</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump wants a bigger White House ballroom. His handpicked architect disagrees.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s desire to go big with the project has put him at odds with architect James McCrery II, who has counseled restraint over concerns that the planned 90,000-square-foot addition could dwarf the 55,000-square-foot mansion.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0da7dc20-cac8-11f0-8e7d-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:01:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI and Democrats. Trump ballroom. National parks. Drug pricing. Nuclear start-ups. Campbell’s soup. Screen detox. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6722bee1-cabf-11f0-8146-00000a1ace5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former Brazilian president Jair Bolsonaro must begin 27-year sentence for coup attempt after he exhausted all appeals, court rules</title>
      <description>In a final ruling, Brazil’s Supreme Court upheld Bolsonaro’s conviction for attempting a coup, attempting the violent abolition of the democratic rule of law and other charges.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37d3e770-ca3f-11f0-b4b3-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 20:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D.C. Mayor Muriel E. Bowser (D) will not run for fourth term, a decision bound to usher in a competitive mayoral race</title>
      <description>Bowser’s seismic decision will bring to a close more than a decade in leadership overseeing some of the city’s most booming times and also its most turbulent crises this century. In an interview Monday night with The Washington Post, Bowser, 53, said that “we’ve accomplished what we set out to accomplish.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9bde37e0-ca33-11f0-ab64-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CDC’s new top deputy had ordered his state health department to stop promoting mass vaccinations amid a flu surge</title>
      <description>Ralph Abraham, who is Louisiana’s surgeon general, has been hired as the principal deputy director at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, according to a spokesperson for the Health and Human Services Department. The CDC currently has no permanent director, so Abraham would essentially be running the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f74de290-ca26-11f0-8f1f-00000a1ace8b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:48:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EPA will abandon air pollution rule that the agency has said would prevent thousands of U.S. deaths</title>
      <description>The Environmental Protection Agency will no longer defend Biden-era limits on fine-particle pollution, which causes heart and lung disease.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">539894e0-ca23-11f0-8bab-0000a1ace676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: After he postponed wedding, fiancée split and took the sympathy with her</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: After he postponed wedding, fiancée split and took the sympathy with her</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">734a9fc0-ca20-11f0-8bab-0000a1ace676</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taiwan’s president: I will boost defense spending to protect our democracy</title>
      <description>An unprecedented military buildup by Beijing threatens peace and stability in the region.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44ec10c1-ca19-11f0-b577-0000a1ace712</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:10:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s going on with Trump’s gold ‘Oval Office’ sign?</title>
      <description>Online, naysayers have compared the ornate font to the one used in the Cheesecake Factory logo or the fanciful typefaces used to make “Live, Laugh, Love” signs. A White House spokesperson swiped back: “President Trump is making the White House beautiful and giving it the glory it deserves. Only people with a severe case of Trump Derangement Syndrome would find a problem with that.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e55bbc40-ca0f-11f0-b487-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 15:03:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A sudden resignation in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">76f3de30-ca0b-11f0-9281-00000a1ace3f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 14:31:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comey case. Ukraine talks. Oval Office sign. Gaza winter. AI hiring bias. Sleep apnea. Thanksgiving cost. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3cbafab0-c9f6-11f0-9698-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 33 definitive rules of road trips</title>
      <description>A manual for drivers and passengers who want to get along.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22ace1e6-c999-11f0-9cb8-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon says it will investigate Sen. Mark Kelly (D-Arizona) after controversial video</title>
      <description>The announcement Monday follows a viral video posted last week in which Kelly, a combat veteran, and five other Democratic colleagues reminded U.S. service members of their duty to disobey unlawful orders.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">795a3771-c969-11f0-9cd7-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:12:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge tosses cases against James Comey and Letitia James, rules prosecutor appointment unlawful</title>
      <description>The decision disqualifying Lindsey Halligan as U.S. attorney sets back Trump’s efforts to use the Justice Department to target perceived rivals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1b7c4350-c95f-11f0-820e-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:57:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Two affairs and a big lie later, can their marriage be saved?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Two affairs and a big lie later, can their marriage be saved?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56999993-c957-11f0-b19b-0000a1ace85c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A witness exposes unusual tactics used to prop up mortgage fraud cases</title>
      <description>The witness in the Sen. Adam Schiff (D-California) case exposed surprising revelations about Trump officials and their attempts to reach an indictment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3fdb620-c94f-11f0-9894-00000a1ace16</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chatting with AI bots in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79428931-c947-11f0-9f69-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 15:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gov. Andy Beshear: This slap in the face to rural America is a chance to turn it blue</title>
      <description>Democrats should be the party of aspiration — and talk like normal human beings.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2e630a1-c93f-11f0-b6a1-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
