<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 03:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to pause all deliveries of U.S. military aid to Ukraine, officials say</title>
      <description>In the wake of President Donald Trump and Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky’s disastrous Oval Office meeting on Friday, the U.S. president is halting the provision of weapons and military assistance critical to Ukraine’s fight against Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de69a7e0-f890-11ef-b255-0000a1aceb26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 00:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China is dominating almost every technology needed for the green energy revolution. Here's how it did it.</title>
      <description>China has pulled ahead of the United States in almost every key clean tech sector, from electric vehicles to solar panels. Its lead is likely to widen as President Donald Trump boosts fossil fuel production and cuts funding for clean energy projects.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">be203cd2-f884-11ef-8837-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 23:10:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Financial markets slide as Trump confirms 25 percent tariffs on Mexico and Canada will take effect Tuesday</title>
      <description>The S&amp;P 500 fell more than 2 percent and the tech-heavy Nasdaq was down around 3 percent, as the president’s comments came amid signs that tariff threats are beginning to sap the economy’s momentum.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d91dd70-f874-11ef-89f9-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: In-laws never offered condolences after father’s death</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: In-laws never offered condolences after father’s death</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d55d751-f851-11ef-9558-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 17:02:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A tribute to this actor in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3d7ad100-f83c-11ef-ae9d-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MASN agreement between Nationals and Orioles is dissolved; Nationals will control their own broadcast rights after 2025 season</title>
      <description>MLB announced Monday morning the dissolution of the contentious agreement, which was in place since the Montreal Expos franchise moved to Washington in 2005 and gave the Nationals’ TV rights to the Orioles-controlled Mid-Atlantic Sports Network.

Nationals games will air on MASN for one more season in 2025 under the terms of a new agreement, but the team can sell its broadcast rights for future seasons to the highest bidder.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">10515f40-f838-11ef-b71f-0000a1ace43c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:01:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The best Oscar moments — from showstopping performances to big wins</title>
      <description>“Anora” and lead actress Mikey Madison had a huge night, the stars of "Wicked" put on a dazzling show and some celebrities shared political messages.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45879a30-f833-11ef-a48a-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 13:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump and Ukraine. Elon Musk. Gaza aid. Oscar winners. Wildfires. Moon landing. Gray homes. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23e7edf0-f827-11ef-bbb0-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Anora’ wins best picture at the Oscars, with star Mikey Madison also winning best actress</title>
      <description>A varied field of movies walked away with statuettes at the Academy Awards, where numerous winners offered messages about Ukraine, Gaza and American politics.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d30b460-f7e2-11ef-be7b-0000a1ace22d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 03:46:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin commutes sentence of ex-officer who fatally shot unarmed man</title>
      <description>Former Fairfax County Police Sgt. Wesley Shifflett was sentenced to three years in prison on Friday. A jury had convicted him of recklessly handling a firearm but acquitted him of a more serious involuntary manslaughter charge during the 2023 encounter in which he chased and shot a man thought to have shoplifted a pair of sunglasses.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0668d3d1-f7d6-11ef-b7f2-0000a1ace17f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 02:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for a dramatic Oscars, where several movies have a shot at best picture. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>Will Adrien Brody and “The Brutalist” dominate? Will “Anora” sweep? Could Demi Moore finally take home a best actress statuette? Join our writers as the show begins at 7 p.m. Eastern time.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5a34c771-f7be-11ef-812b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 23:30:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Some Tesla owners feel buyer’s remorse — and get egged — as Elon Musk tears through the government</title>
      <description>For many D.C.-area owners, the car has gone from progressive icon to a badge of shame now that Musk has become a central figure in President Donald Trump’s administration.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b11db181-f7b1-11ef-9308-00000a1ace50</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 22:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1062ad50-f788-11ef-bdcc-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 17:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DOGE set off a crisis at a highly sensitive nuclear weapons agency</title>
      <description>The Trump administration’s dismissal of workers who maintain America’s nuclear weapons — now mostly reversed — is an example of how its scattershot approach caused deeper damage to agencies than anticipated.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b672e9b0-f785-11ef-943d-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 16:45:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The house color that tells you when a neighborhood is gentrifying</title>
      <description>Rowhouses in D.C., craftsmans in Nashville, Victorian-style homes in San Francisco and many other styles of houses in gentrifying neighborhoods across the country have increasingly been painted shades of gray, altering the aesthetics of American cities.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87a8a7f0-f77b-11ef-b0eb-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 15:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fc538880-f772-11ef-b01d-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 14:31:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel halts all aid to Gaza, as ceasefire falters</title>
      <description>The announcement signaled a breakdown in the ceasefire deal between Israel and Hamas, which are engaged in an escalating standoff over the next steps after the first phase of the ceasefire expired on Saturday.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c8df6c90-f74e-11ef-8cbf-000000a1ace4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 10:12:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump cannot fire head of independent watchdog agency without cause, judge rules</title>
      <description>A federal judge decided Saturday that the president cannot summarily remove Hampton Dellinger as head of the Office of Special Counsel, which investigates whistleblower reports filed by government workers. The case is likely headed to a Supreme Court showdown over presidential powers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a899ba90-f70c-11ef-b689-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 02:18:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commanders agree to acquire star receiver Deebo Samuel in trade with 49ers</title>
      <description>Washington will send a fifth-round draft pick to San Francisco for the 29-year-old wideout, according to two people with knowledge of the deal. Samuel, who earned first-team all-pro honors for the 2021 season, gives the Commanders a dynamic weapon to complement stalwart Terry McLaurin in quarterback Jayden Daniels's receiving corps. The trade cannot be finalized until the start of the new league year March 12.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">432950a1-f6fb-11ef-ba71-0000a1ace696</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Mar 2025 00:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE officials are seeking to use IRS records to search for fraud in benefits and student loans, records show</title>
      <description>Agency officials were alarmed at the request. It is illegal for the Internal Revenue Service to share personal tax information within the government, except to help with tax collection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aff3640-f6ef-11ef-b783-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 22:47:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Former New York governor Andrew Cuomo joins crowded NYC mayor's race that's all about Donald Trump</title>
      <description>Cuomo, who publicly sparred with Trump as governor, is seeking to unseat incumbent Mayor Eric Adams for working with the president to deport undocumented New Yorkers. But Cuomo has his own baggage, having left office amid accusations of sexual misconduct.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">77dfe702-f6c4-11ef-8381-000a1ace96d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentagon orders up to 3,000 additional troops plus Stryker combat vehicles to U.S. southern border</title>
      <description>Defense Secretary Pete Hegseth has ordered an additional 2,500 to 3,000 active-duty troops to the border with Mexico, including soldiers from a motorized brigade equipped with 20-ton armored Stryker combat vehicles, two defense officials familiar with the effort said.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">14c96e70-f6ba-11ef-a9e4-0000a1ace165</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our food critic got a table at the secretive CIA dining room. Here’s what it was like inside.</title>
      <description>There are no credit cards or cellphones allowed, and the chef can’t be named, but the menu is full of affordable pleasures.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d8cc4f42-f6b0-11ef-9b4c-00000a1ace55</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 15:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">da2ea291-f6a9-11ef-9d3a-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 14:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICE memo details how Trump officials will try to deport more than 1 million migrants admitted during the Biden administration</title>
      <description>By expanding use of the "expedited removal" law — from within 100 miles of a border to the entire country — the Trump administration will try to remove more than 1 million migrants admitted to the United States when President Joe Biden was in office.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f8a124d1-f633-11ef-bc4f-0000a1aceb37</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Hackman likely died nine days before his body was found, sheriff says</title>
      <description>Data from the pacemaker of Oscar-winning actor Gene Hackman indicates he died on Feb. 17, nine days before investigators found his body and that of his wife Betsy Arakawa in their New Mexico home, said Santa Fe County Sheriff Adan Mendoza. Carbon monoxide poisoning has been ruled out.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">39f41671-f627-11ef-89cc-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 22:56:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IRS rejected request from immigration officials for addresses of suspected undocumented immigrants, people tell The Post</title>
      <description>Homeland Security officials made the request recently and also sought skilled auditors to investigate businesses believed to be employing undocumented workers, a sign of a shift in how the government is pursuing its enforcement actions. The IRS is legally barred from sharing taxpayer information even with other government departments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fde11ac0-f61c-11ef-8f5a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 21:43:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump cancels news conference with Zelensky after heated Oval Office meeting</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky emerged from the West Wing after President Donald Trump and Vice President JD Vance accused him of being insufficiently grateful for U.S. support.
“He disrespected the United States of America in its cherished Oval Office,” Trump wrote on social media. “He can come back when he is ready for Peace.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1424a531-f605-11ef-b61f-00000a1ace00</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump, Zelensky Oval Office meeting turns contentious ahead of scheduled news conference. Follow our coverage.</title>
      <description>Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky asked President Donald Trump what his message is for allies worried that he’s aligned too closely with Russian President Vladimir Putin. Trump raised his voice, calling Zelensky “disrespectful” and saying, “You don’t have the cards” because of Ukraine’s weakened military position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb752a30-f5fd-11ef-8aaf-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 18:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMI won’t renew superintendent’s contract. Cedric Wins, the college’s first Black leader, faced criticism over DEI policies.</title>
      <description>Wins, a retired Army major general, was appointed superintendent of the Virginia Military Institute in 2021, after months as its interim leader and amid scrutiny of incidents of racism at the nation’s oldest state-supported military college. His contract was set to expire at the end of June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">057fa9e0-f5f5-11ef-89ef-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 16:56:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75142a71-f5e0-11ef-b8e8-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 14:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s firings. Zelensky visit. Gene Hackman investigation. Trans rights. Epstein files. Planet parade. The Oscars. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">89b01801-f5cb-11ef-830b-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The federal government plans to send workers a second “What did you do last week?” email. It might require a response.</title>
      <description>The message is set to come from individual agencies rather than from the centralized Office of Personnel Management. Multiple departments and offices told employees not to respond to an initial email last weekend.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d3b1b2f2-f5c7-11ef-8092-0000a1ace600</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 11:33:26 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FBI is investigating EPA’s claims of fraud in $20 billion Biden-era climate fund, escalating a contentious criminal probe</title>
      <description>A prosecutor resigned. Another refused to seek a warrant. A judge said there wasn’t enough evidence. But Citibank appears to have frozen up to $20 billion in grants as a Justice Department probe continues.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb3360e1-f575-11ef-90e9-0000a1ace2c1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:45:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iowa is poised to become the first state to revoke nondiscrimination protections for transgender people</title>
      <description>The state Senate and House debated for several hours before passing the legislation overwhelmingly along party lines after protesters packed the Capitol on Thursday. The governor is expected to sign the bill.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7a99a060-f572-11ef-89ee-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 01:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five former defense secretaries denounce Trump’s firings of Pentagon leaders as ‘reckless’ and urge Congress to intervene</title>
      <description>In a letter to lawmakers, the former defense secretaries — having served in Republican and Democratic administrations — called President Donald Trump’s abrupt dismissal last week of the chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff and six other top military officers “reckless” and implored Congress to “exercise fully its Constitutional oversight responsibilities.”

The public appeal to Congress was dated Thursday and signed by Lloyd Austin, Jim Mattis, Chuck Hagel, Leon E. Panetta and William Perry after the firings created an uproar among lawmakers and veterans.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f670d101-f567-11ef-95c2-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge blocks Trump administration’s mass firings of federal workers, ruling them likely to be illegal</title>
      <description>A federal judge ruled that the terminations at several agencies, including the Department of Defense, Park Service, Bureau of Land Management, National Science Foundation and others, were probably illegal. The ruling came in a lawsuit brought by a group of union plaintiffs and advocacy organizations.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6c86abe0-f562-11ef-99e4-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 23:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes, GOP senators including Lindsey Graham press Secretary of State Marco Rubio on legality of Trump’s aid freeze</title>
      <description>Graham, a close Trump ally, joined Democrats in expressing alarm. The senators have asked Rubio to defend the freeze in a hearing on Capitol Hill in the coming weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff410f10-f54f-11ef-b195-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 21:15:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico extradites 29 drug-trafficking suspects to the United States</title>
      <description>The announcement comes days before the Trump administration plans to impose economic sanctions related to Mexico’s failure to stop the flow of narcotics over the border.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6d44cf0-f549-11ef-9870-0000a1ace91d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 20:31:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Mom’s extra work is to pay, unknowingly, for Dad’s ‘sugar babies’</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Mom’s extra work is to pay, unknowingly, for Dad’s ‘sugar babies’</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c4f65f1-f52c-11ef-a1e4-00000a1ace95</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 17:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PKK leader Abdullah Ocalan, imprisoned in Turkey, issues historic call for militant group to disarm and dissolve</title>
      <description>The appeal by Abdullah Ocalan raised the possibility of an end to a decades-long insurgency against Turkey that killed an estimated 40,000 people.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">84d0f4e0-f520-11ef-9fd9-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 15:35:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This food delivery app is the topic of today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">90605520-f517-11ef-ab04-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 14:31:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court. DOGE firings. Gene Hackman. Measles death. Gaza ceasefire. Egg prices. Antiaging dog pill. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">56578250-f502-11ef-8742-000a1aced8fd</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Actor Gene Hackman and his wife found dead in their New Mexico home, according to the Santa Fe County sheriff’s office</title>
      <description>The actor and his wife, musician Betsy Arakawa, were discovered dead Wednesday afternoon at their home, where a dog was also found deceased, the sheriff's office said, adding that there was no immediate indication of foul play and the exact cause of death had not been determined.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">017a5bb1-f4ec-11ef-98dd-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 09:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court pauses midnight deadline for Trump administration to pay nearly $2 billion in foreign aid</title>
      <description>Chief Justice John G. Roberts Jr. granted a request by the Trump administration, which faced a lower court's 11:59 p.m. deadline for releasing the money to organizations that provide food and medical assistance overseas through the U.S. Agency for International Development.
Roberts’s brief order will give the full court time to review the case. It follows nearly two weeks of motions and hearings before U.S. District Judge Amir H. Ali, who had ordered that foreign assistance resume after President Donald Trump directed a sweeping 90-day pause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">511778e1-f4b7-11ef-bc66-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 03:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hamas turned over the bodies of four hostages in exchange for the release of hundreds of Palestinian prisoners</title>
      <description>The exchange is set to be the final one of the first phase of the ceasefire deal between Israel and Hamas. The fragile truce may now be entering an even more precarious juncture.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f95b34e2-f4a5-11ef-ac04-00000a1ace9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:58:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michelle Trachtenberg dies at 39. The ‘Harriet the Spy’ star also had major roles in ‘Gossip Girl’ and ‘Buffy the Vampire Slayer.’</title>
      <description>The cause of death was not disclosed, but it was not believed to be suspicious, according to an NYPD spokesperson. Representatives for Trachtenberg did not respond to requests for comment.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a3953b10-f472-11ef-8308-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 18:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas child is first confirmed death in state’s spreading measles outbreak, which has sickened more than 100 people</title>
      <description>An unvaccinated child was the first confirmed fatality in the state’s worst measles outbreak in three decades, Texas health officials said Wednesday. The school-aged child was hospitalized in Lubbock last week, according to the Texas Department of State Health Services.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">96b9d800-f469-11ef-bc66-0000a1ace44b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supreme Court seems poised to lower bar for White people to sue for job bias</title>
      <description>A majority of justices appeared to support making it easier for men, White people and straight people to sue for job discrimination. They heard oral arguments in the case of an Ohio woman who claims she faced anti-straight bias in the workplace, and who is challenging past rulings that set a higher bar for proving discrimination against members of non-minority groups.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db199040-f463-11ef-9529-00000a1ace42</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 17:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Real Housewives of Potomac’ star sentenced to 12 months for crashing Maserati while drunk</title>
      <description>After Karen Huger wrecked in Maryland, she refused a Breathalyzer. But on police video, she said, “Oh, God. I'm lit.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">489305c1-f45f-11ef-bea6-00000a1ace15</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 16:32:34 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
