<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 20:01:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Trump declines to rule out a recession amid tariff impacts, after previously touting his trade policies</title>
      <description>Speaking to Maria Bartiromo on Fox News on Sunday, President Donald Trump acknowledged turbulence in the U.S. economy — a reversal from previously cheering that his policies would deliver quick victories to voters and businesses. It also stood in contrast to reassurances from his own advisers that no recession was in sight.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">83828e90-fd05-11ef-b51a-00000a1ace56</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 16:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cb3030-fd02-11ef-a9b7-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 16:17:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A breakthrough in age-reversal research could soon make the jump to human trials</title>
      <description>Cellular reprogramming is hailed by its supporters as the most promising scientific approach to improving human health spans and lifespans. But there have been serious side effects during experiments on animals.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5d9f3770-fcf4-11ef-9581-0000a1acef58</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 14:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2aa5d581-fceb-11ef-aae9-00000a1ace6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 13:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anger at Elon Musk turns violent with molotov cocktails and gunfire at Tesla lots</title>
      <description>More than a dozen violent or destructive acts have been directed at Tesla facilities since President Donald Trump’s inauguration, according to court documents, surveillance photographs, police records and local media reports reviewed by The Washington Post. As Elon Musk has rocketed to prominence as Trump’s best-known supporter, his electric vehicle company has faltered. Its stock has fallen by more than 35 percent since the inauguration on Jan. 20.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4e561081-fc6e-11ef-8409-00000a1ace84</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 22:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. DOGE Service gains access to sensitive income database maintained by child support agency</title>
      <description>A federal official told The Post that the group sought read-only access to the system “to reduce waste, fraud and abuse.” The government database — created to help enforce child support payments — contains substantial amounts of personal income data linked to nearly all U.S. workers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3831a471-fc52-11ef-8ef0-00000a1ace45</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:19:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Justice Department removes key national security staff as part of purge</title>
      <description>At least three officials from the National Security Division were transferred, amounting to a gutting of leadership in the highly sensitive section, which is charged with working with the FBI and other intelligence agencies to protect the nation from threats. Their removal is part of a bigger culling of senior career officials at the Justice Department under President Donald Trump.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">82d584c0-fc4c-11ef-bd5f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 18:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Republicans unveil another extension to avert government shutdown until Sept. 30, but it’s not clear if they have the votes</title>
      <description>The continuing resolution unveiled Saturday would stave off a politically costly shutdown. But it would also mean that Republicans, who control both chambers of Congress and the White House, would largely keep funding set by President Joe Biden last year.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9b797d51-fc48-11ef-bd5f-00000a1acef0</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 18:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: I love my partner, but I also want to focus on my dreams</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: I love my partner, but I also want to focus on my dreams</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">602117b0-fc41-11ef-a2e0-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 17:18:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do you remember the first week of the pandemic? Kate Cohen takes us into covid’s great forgetting.</title>
      <description>In coronavirus, we have discovered a memory-resistant strain of pandemics, Cohen writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b1e946e0-fc3b-11ef-a062-0000a1ace277</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 16:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock forgot one of its wildest front men. He’s got a story to tell.</title>
      <description>Peter Wolf befriended music legends, married a movie star and led the J. Geils Band. His new memoir reminds us: He was there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f2de8b50-fc32-11ef-93cb-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 15:35:22 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9a8491a0-fc2a-11ef-9d04-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 14:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s Justice Department drops landmark case against a synthetic rubber facility Biden said was an ‘imminent’ health threat</title>
      <description>The lawsuit, filed under the Biden administration, accused a plant in LaPlace, Louisiana, of releasing unsafe levels of the likely carcinogen chloroprene. Republicans say the plant provides critical jobs and that the pollution concerns are overblown, but environmental and public health advocates say residents face elevated cancer risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b829d10-fbb6-11ef-852d-00000a1aceb4</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 00:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina carries out nation’s first firing squad execution in 15 years</title>
      <description>Brad Sigmon, who was convicted in a 2001 double murder, chose the firing squad method after autopsies from previous executions raised concerns over the state’s supply of lethal injection drug.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">45c63180-fbaf-11ef-824f-00000a1ace80</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 23:52:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A top arms firm made at least $120 million from what the U.N. calls the world’s worst humanitarian catastrophe, records reveal</title>
      <description>A trove of documents, phone intercepts and other communications provided to The Post show how Turkey’s largest defense company funneled $120 million worth of drones and munitions to the Sudanese army engulfed in a brutal civil war despite a web of international sanctions — providing a rare window into the murky world of wartime dealmaking.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa719c90-fba6-11ef-8a38-0000a1acec82</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:51:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gene Hackman likely died of a cardiovascular issue days after his wife died of a rare virus, officials said</title>
      <description>Hackman, 95, probably died from a combination of high blood pressure and extensive heart disease, and Betsy Arakawa, 65, seems to have died of hantavirus pulmonary syndrome, a virus that infects the lungs and is usually contracted from rodent excrement, officials said Friday at a news conference.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">44aaad30-fba0-11ef-93cb-0000a1ace088</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 22:05:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. Army Corps of Engineers knew Trump order would waste California reservoir water, memo shows</title>
      <description>A memo obtained by The Post shows federal officials rushed ahead with a plan to discharge Central Valley irrigation water in January, following a White House directive in the wake of catastrophic wildfires in Los Angeles. An Army Corps colonel wrote that officials knew the water was unlikely to reach Southern California, as President Donald Trump had promised.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8760f1a0-fb8e-11ef-85c0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 19:58:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. suspends commercial satellite imagery service to Ukraine. Soldiers on the ground are feeling the impact already.</title>
      <description>Maxar, a leading provider of orbital imagery, said that the U.S. government has decided to temporarily suspend services to Ukraine, following a pause on weapons shipments and intelligence-sharing.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d01ed0b0-fb84-11ef-85c0-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump administration to cut $400 million in funding to Columbia University, saying it failed to protect Jewish students</title>
      <description>It was not immediately clear which grants and contracts would be impacted. The Trump administration announced this week that it was investigating Columbia. Under federal law, universities that discriminate on the basis of shared national ancestry are not eligible for federal funding.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01927370-fb82-11ef-b2c6-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 18:28:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We haven’t reckoned enough with any of it’: 6 writers look back on the covid lockdown after half a decade</title>
      <description>Five years after the declaration of a pandemic, we have returned to normal. But are we the same?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">12499370-fb72-11ef-97a2-00000a1ace46</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 16:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens killed in Syria as fighting erupts, marking worst violence since Assad’s fall</title>
      <description>Fierce clashes between security forces under Syria’s new Islamist government and gunmen belonging to the country’s Alawite religious minority have killed dozens of people and threatened to plunge Syria deeper into sectarian violence. Syrian officials blamed the fighting, in Syria’s coastal regions of Latakia and Tartus, on supporters of the former regime, saying they ambushed government forces on Thursday and killed at least 16 fighters.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">db5c1e80-fb69-11ef-9335-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:35:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump threatens ‘large scale’ sanctions on Russia following its major attack on Ukraine, marking a shift in rhetoric</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump’s warning to Russia followed the first major missile attack against Ukraine since the Trump administration paused intelligence sharing with Ukraine. In a social media post, Trump characterized the attack as a “pounding” and urged Russia and Ukraine to negotiate a ceasefire “before it is too late.” The post marked a shift for Trump, who has been more sympathetic to Russia than Ukraine in recent weeks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">775a4cd0-fb65-11ef-ae69-000000a1acef</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 15:04:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cf3b0ac0-fb60-11ef-bf68-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 14:31:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employers added 151,000 jobs in February, a solid showing amid the start of federal worker layoffs</title>
      <description>The February report by the Bureau of Labor Statistics showed a labor market in decent shape, despite growing concerns that Trump administration cuts to the public sector or higher tariffs could slow the economy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">73191720-fb59-11ef-aa4b-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 13:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tariff pause. DOGE moves. Gaza proposal. SpaceX explosion. Firing squad execution. Butterfly decline. Time change. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c885b6e1-fb4b-11ef-bb9b-00000a1ace7d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 12:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the White House’s new media strategy to promote Trump as ‘KING’</title>
      <description>The Trump administration has transformed its traditional media shop into a rapid-response influencer operation, disseminating messages directly to Americans through the memes, TikToks and podcasts where millions now get their news.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0289e780-faed-11ef-a3d3-00000a1acef9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:42:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demolition of foreign aid funding hits evangelical Christian charities that view Trump as an ally</title>
      <description>In a closed-door meeting, U.S. officials touted their success in “zeroing out” foreign assistance. Christian aid groups are already feeling the impact of budget cuts in their efforts to care for the world’s most vulnerable.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8ac71330-fae2-11ef-ab5b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 23:27:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Second death confirmed in growing measles outbreak near Texas-New Mexico border</title>
      <description>An unvaccinated adult died of measles in New Mexico, authorities reported Thursday — the second person to succumb to the highly contagious disease along a sparsely populated part of the two states’ border. An unvaccinated 6-year-old died Feb. 26 of the preventable infection.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f4976cf0-fad4-11ef-9716-0000a1ace412</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:50:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge says Trump illegally fired National Labor Relations Board member and orders that she remain in her role</title>
      <description>U.S. District Judge Beryl A. Howell says Gwynne Wilcox must remain at the federal agency that oversees relations among workers, labor unions and employers. The ruling, along with several others in recent days, sets up a Supreme Court showdown over presidential powers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb597b50-fad2-11ef-8634-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 21:34:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VMI superintendent blames ‘bias, emotion, and ideology’ for decision by military college’s board not to extend his contract</title>
      <description>Cedric T. Wins, a retired Army major general, was named the first Black superintendent of the Virginia Military Institute in 2021 amid allegations of widespread racism at the college. His contract expires at the end of June.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">de01d871-facc-11ef-8dbf-0000a1acec19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:52:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump extends one-month tariff reprieve to some goods from Canada, following a similar move for Mexico</title>
      <description>The pause on tariffs applies only to imports that comply with the free-trade agreement between the United States, Canada and Mexico, signed in late 2018. Financial markets continue to be down for the day after the whiplash.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03d66480-fac8-11ef-a8bf-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 20:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Butterflies in the U.S. are disappearing at a ‘catastrophic’ rate, study finds, with potentially dire effects on ecosystems</title>
      <description>The number of butterflies in the contiguous United States declined by 22 percent this century, according to a study released Thursday in the journal Science. Shrinking habitat, rising temperatures and a toxic array of pesticides are killing off the delicate insects, it said, with potentially dire implications for ecosystems.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ab135ab2-fabd-11ef-ab0e-0000a1acef03</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE seeks access to sensitive income data kept by federal child support office</title>
      <description>The Elon Musk-led U.S. DOGE Service clashed with Health and Human Services career staffers over a system that tracks most U.S. workers’ wages. It wasn’t immediately clear whether DOGE’s access request was granted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a04ae80-fab1-11ef-aeb5-00000a1ace23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 17:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump suspends tariffs on most products from Mexico until April 2 after phone call with Sheinbaum</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump made the announcement after a call with Mexican President Claudia Sheinbaum, saying it was an accommodation based on their good relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6cd3e640-faac-11ef-b5ea-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:59:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A wartime onesie in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Thursday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4cc2fe10-faa5-11ef-9cb4-0000a1acef7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 16:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>House votes to censure Rep. Al Green (D-Texas) for disrupting President Donald Trump during his Tuesday address to Congress</title>
      <description>The Republican-sponsored resolution accuses Green of a “breach of proper conduct.” In a social media post shared Thursday morning, Green said he was being reprimanded for “standing up to President Trump.” A censure of a House member falls short of expulsion and has become a more common disciplinary action in recent years.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3ced9811-faa0-11ef-ab5b-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dalai Lama writes in an op-ed: My hope for the Tibetan people</title>
      <description>Tibetans have spent nearly 75 years fighting for freedom. Their struggle should continue beyond my lifetime.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8cd5dc50-fa9d-11ef-9078-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 15:13:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DOGE is driving broad cuts to the Social Security agency and will make mistakes, acting head says privately</title>
      <description>The Social Security Administration’s acting commissioner, Leland Dudek, told senior leaders and disability rights advocates that members of Elon Musk’s cost-cutting team are outsiders who are unfamiliar with the nuances of the agency’s programs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0ff34311-fa90-11ef-a762-0000a1ace904</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 13:36:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Federal job cuts. Abortion ban. Gaza aid. Vanishing sea ice. Pig rescue. Eagle chicks. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">7f0bb1a0-fa82-11ef-8634-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 11:59:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump set to sign executive order calling for the closure of the Education Department</title>
      <description>A draft of the order that circulated Wednesday called on Education Secretary Linda McMahon to “take all necessary steps” to facilitate the closure of the department “to the maximum extent appropriate and permitted by law." McMahon has acknowledged that congressional approval is needed to close the agency.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aeb5b690-fa40-11ef-91b2-00000a1ace08</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 04:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Appeals court allows Trump to fire independent watchdog Hampton Dellinger without cause — for now</title>
      <description>A lower court judge had reinstated Hampton Dellinger as head of the Office of Special Counsel, which protects whistleblowers and federal employees. But a U.S. appeals court said Dellinger could be removed for now while courts decide whether the president has the authority to fire the head of the independent watchdog agency without cause.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aa63eed0-fa23-11ef-87d5-00000a1ace96</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump officials are reopening a sprawling detention center in Texas to hold migrant children and their parents</title>
      <description>Four years after the Biden administration stopped detaining migrant children, a private prison contractor says it has reached an agreement with ICE to reopen the South Texas Family Residential Center. It can hold up to 2,400 people, making it one of the largest ICE detention centers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c9ec8ba0-fa13-11ef-936d-00000a1acef8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 22:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s one word to describe Trump’s address? Three columnists discuss.</title>
      <description>President Trump’s address to Congress was historically long and unusual in its style. Some Democrats booed and heckled him, and Trump did his own trolling of Democrats too. What does this address tell us about our politics and the future of Trump 2.0? Columnists Ruth Marcus, Dana Milbank and Ramesh Ponnuru get into it.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">099d5b70-fa06-11ef-96fb-0000a1ace18d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 21:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump White House allows one-month delay on tariffs for autos coming from Canada and Mexico</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has vowed to move ahead on April 2 with a new plan calling for "reciprocal" tariffs, which are expected to result in sharp increases in U.S. border levies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31099f80-f9f6-11ef-8f00-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 19:15:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Parents want to tell daughter no wedding funds till she’s 25</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Parents want to tell daughter no wedding funds till she’s 25</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23d10cd0-f9e3-11ef-90e1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dining chat: How do you handle a takeout fail once you’re home?</title>
      <description>Dining chat: How do you handle a takeout fail once you’re home?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ff1bf0f0-f9db-11ef-aa0b-000000a1ace2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 16:07:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s rally-style speech was not the true test, our chief correspondent writes. Harder days lie ahead.</title>
      <description>President Donald Trump has called for dramatic and often controversial change. Whether he can turn early disruption into effective governance and tangible results is a far different issue, chief correspondent Dan Balz writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9cc18320-f9d6-11ef-a0e3-00000a1ace54</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 15:29:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Divided Supreme Court says judge can force Trump administration to resume paying nearly $2 billion in frozen foreign aid</title>
      <description>The 5-4 ruling means the U.S. Agency for International Development and the State Department must restart payments for work already completed. The decision drew a sharp dissent from four conservative justices who said a district court judge in D.C. probably lacks the power to compel the federal government to make such payments.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bfb632b0-f9cf-11ef-9eba-00000a1aced6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 14:40:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phasing out this platform in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Wednesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4f8d1540-f9ce-11ef-84c9-0000a1ace83f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 14:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.S. pauses major parts of intelligence sharing with Ukraine, squeezing the information used to strike at targets inside Russia</title>
      <description>The rupture in intelligence sharing includes targeting data supplied by U.S. spy agencies to Kyiv to launch American-provided weapons at Russian targets. Some Ukrainian missile operators say they are no longer receiving information needed to hit targets inside Russia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1aabe3b0-f9c9-11ef-9f03-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 13:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
