<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 10:02:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mexico approves radical overhaul of its judicial system, paving way for voters to elect judges</title>
      <description>The contentious Senate vote on Wednesday is a crucial step in transforming the judicial system, allowing citizens to pick nearly all judges, even those on the Supreme Court. The amendment passed amid heavy demonstrations. Lawmakers had to move their session to a nearby building after protesters burst into the chamber during the debate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c454360-700f-11ef-9475-00000a1ace06</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 07:29:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Analysis: Kamala Harris kept Donald Trump on defense, and other takeaways from their first presidential debate</title>
      <description>The former president issued his characteristic falsehoods and focused on undocumented immigrants. The vice president drove the abortion-rights argument and turned the spotlight on Trump’s character traits.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e21b57b0-6ff8-11ef-9858-00000a1ace1b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 04:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Swift endorses Kamala Harris for president immediately after the debate</title>
      <description>Swift made the announcement Tuesday evening in an Instagram post that published minutes after the debate between Harris and Donald Trump ended.
"Recently I was made aware that AI of ‘me’ falsely endorsing Donald Trump’s presidential run was posted to his site. It really conjured up my fears around AI, and the dangers of spreading misinformation," she said. "The simplest way to combat misinformation is with the truth.

"I will be casting my vote for Kamala Harris and Tim Walz in the 2024 Presidential Election," Swift added in the post caption that was signed "Taylor Swift Childless Cat Lady."</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">833e86a0-6fed-11ef-9ed5-00000a1aceb3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 03:25:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>During first half of intense debate, Trump and Harris clashed on abortion and immigration, while moderators fact-checked claims</title>
      <description>Donald Trump and Kamala Harris argued over the future of reproductive health care in the U.S., with moderators fact-checking the former president when he falsely claimed Democrats are in favor of abortion after birth.

Trump also got moderator pushback when he made the baseless claim that immigrants are "eating the dogs" in the Ohio town of Springfield, an assertion that local police have refuted.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2146f620-6fe4-11ef-a5ff-00000a1acedd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 02:18:27 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘Wow! A handshake!’: Follow along as 10 Post columnists discuss the presidential debate</title>
      <description>Columnists and writers Ruth Marcus, Perry Bacon Jr., Ramesh Ponnuru, Kate Cohen, Jason Willick, Jim Geraghty, Megan McArdle, E.J. Dionne Jr., Alexandra Petri and Shadi Hamid offer real-time commentary during the presidential debate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0d268050-6fdc-11ef-99a9-0000a1ace3d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 01:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris and Trump will face off in their first 2024 presidential debate. Follow our coverage for live analysis.</title>
      <description>Tonight’s highly anticipated debate, which holds high stakes for both candidates, is being hosted by ABC News in Philadelphia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">13f5a720-6fd8-11ef-92c6-000a1ace3598</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 00:52:10 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two years before listeria outbreak, inspectors at a Boar’s Head plant flagged deficiencies that could pose ‘an imminent threat’</title>
      <description>Citations detailed rusted equipment, condensation dripping on the floor and green mold on the wall nearly two years before a deadly nationwide listeria outbreak, according to government inspection reports released by the U.S. Department of Agriculture. Despite repeated violations, the plant in southern Virginia continued to operate.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2f732250-6fd0-11ef-b4ff-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 23:55:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mauricio Pochettino hired as U.S. men’s national soccer team coach, taking the helm ahead of the 2026 World Cup</title>
      <description>Pochettino's résumé includes stints as boss at Southampton, Tottenham Hotspur, Paris Saint-Germain and, most recently, Chelsea. The 52-year-old Argentine arrives at a crucial moment for the U.S. men, a young group that wilted under the bright lights of Copa América this summer. The 2026 World Cup is set to be staged primarily at U.S. stadiums, along with some venues in Mexico and Canada.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5cfef2a0-6fc4-11ef-b092-0000a1acec34</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 22:31:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump faces risks heightened by gender when he debates Kamala Harris tonight, analysts say</title>
      <description>Experts say that Trump could face a penalty for coming across as overly aggressive and that Harris, a Black woman, faces competing pressures to look tough but also project fraught attributes such as “likability.” The 90-minute debate, hosted by ABC News, is scheduled to start at 9 p.m. Eastern.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5fbc3ee0-6fb9-11ef-9ea8-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 21:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Methane emissions rising at fastest rate in recorded history, scientists say, on pace with projected worst-case climate scenarios</title>
      <description>Because methane traps about 30 times as much heat as carbon dioxide over a 100-year time frame, the accelerating emissions will make it nearly impossible for the world to meet its climate goals, according to researchers from the Global Carbon Project.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a2ee2e0-6f9b-11ef-bf6f-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 17:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘We only get one chance to get it right’: Casey Cep takes us inside the highest-rated organization in the country</title>
      <description>There was no room for a parachute and nowhere to hide from the Devil.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bd382130-6f94-11ef-8769-0000a1aced2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk’s misleading election claims reach millions and alarm election officials, who are fielding new voter demands</title>
      <description>The X billionaire’s false posts about noncitizen voting spur officials to fact-check him, lead to requests to purge voter rolls, and add to worries about threats, election officials say.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d050fdf0-6f8f-11ef-ac51-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Dying father begs daughter to reconcile with her abusive twin</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Dying father begs daughter to reconcile with her abusive twin</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e12847c0-6f8d-11ef-9e4a-00000a1ace89</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 16:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris leads Trump among Virginia voters, Post-Schar School poll finds, with a margin suggesting the state is a long shot for Trump</title>
      <description>Vice President Kamala Harris leads former president Donald Trump among likely Virginia voters by eight percentage points, powered by an 18-point advantage among women and by a sense of unity among Democrats, according to a Washington Post-Schar School poll.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">929c8741-6f85-11ef-9fec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 15:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body-cam footage of Tyreek Hill’s detainment shows rapid escalation between police and the Miami Dolphins wide receiver</title>
      <description>In a portion of the footage, an officer is shown pulling a car over and telling Hill, the driver, to roll his window back down. After the officer repeats the request, the situation gets more tense as Hill is pulled from his car and placed in handcuffs, face down on the street. In a strongly worded statement, the Dolphins said the footage showed “there are some officers who mistake their responsibility and commitment to serve with misguided power.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">64fef3c1-6f7d-11ef-b9a2-000000a1aceb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 14:03:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Know your debate cities in today’s On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0812f201-6f79-11ef-95c1-00000a1ace33</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:31:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In rare rebuke, Blinken demands ‘fundamental changes’ to Israeli operations in West Bank after killing of American activist</title>
      <description>Secretary of State Antony Blinken’s comments were the strongest yet from a U.S. official after 26-year-old Aysenur Eygi was fatally shot Friday at a protest in the West Bank. The Israel Defense Forces said Tuesday it was “highly likely” she had been shot “unintentionally” by one of its soldiers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e3ac7910-6f76-11ef-b2c0-0000a1ace8d9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 13:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blinken says Iran's move to send short-range ballistic missiles to Russia will trigger sanctions</title>
      <description>Iran has denied the accusations, which come as Ukraine is demanding its allies lift restrictions on donated weapons to strike deep inside Russia. Secretary of State Antony Blinken is set to visit Kyiv on Wednesday in a rare visit by a high level U.S. official to Ukraine.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e6a50420-6f6c-11ef-9fec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 12:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump-Harris debate. Israeli strike. Hurricane warning. Kentucky manhunt. James Earl Jones. Princess Kate. Cheetos. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d2bb4b30-6f63-11ef-b8cf-0000a1ace816</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 10:59:59 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaza officials say at least 40 people killed in humanitarian area after Israel conducts airstrike it says targeted Hamas</title>
      <description>A Gaza Civil Defense spokesperson told The Post at least 60 people were also injured in Mawasi, near Khan Younis. The Israeli military said the operation targeted a Hamas command and control center hidden there.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">67f12af0-6f2b-11ef-a0d1-000000a1ace0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 04:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sen. Tommy Tuberville blocks Army general’s promotion, citing secrecy around hospitalization of Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin</title>
      <description>Tuberville (R-Ala.) has frozen the nomination of Lt. Gen. Ronald P. Clark to become the head of all U.S. Army forces in the Pacific, citing frustration with the general’s silence months ago when Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin was hospitalized for days without informing the White House or Congress.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03e7ecc1-6f07-11ef-9406-0000a1ace075</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can you spot the famous presidential debate one-liner? Take our quiz.</title>
      <description>While you're waiting for Tuesday’s debate, try filling in some of the most memorable one-liners from years past.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a1ca99e1-6eff-11ef-8283-0000a1acebdc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 23:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trump shooting pitted Democrats and Republicans in this county against each other in a way one historian called ‘frightening’</title>
      <description>Long-simmering tensions in Pennsylvania’s Butler County have yet to cool nearly two months after former president Donald Trump was shot. Angry billboards still flash around the city. The word “fight” is graffitied on streets. Democrats and Republicans are trying to ensure their candidate wins enough votes to capture a key battleground state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f848f390-6ef8-11ef-b4cd-00000a1acedf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 22:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>James Earl Jones dies at 93. Imposing on the screen and stage, he was known as the voice of Darth Vader in ‘Star Wars.’</title>
      <description>Over seven decades, James Earl Jones amassed hundreds of credits on the stage and screen, earning admiration for the humanity and charisma he brought to even the most wounded characters. He belonged to the rarefied cadre of performers who have received Emmy, Grammy, Oscar and Tony awards.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a2a65d0-6eee-11ef-a5d9-00000a1ace61</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 20:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here’s everything Apple unveiled at its September product event, from the iPhone 16 to AirPods with a hearing aid</title>
      <description>AI-forward iPhones, sleeker Apple Watches and AirPods that double as an FDA-approved hearing device: Here’s what you need to know.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a9cdd5e0-6ee5-11ef-9d5b-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 19:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trial for man accused of murdering four Idaho college students will change locations, judge rules</title>
      <description>Bryan Kohberger’s quadruple-murder trial will switch venues after Judge John Judge said the potential juror pool in Latah County, where the University of Idaho is located, is tainted by intense media coverage of the killings. A new location was not immediately announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">318ea370-6ecc-11ef-91a0-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:54:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: Is sister’s therapist ripping her off in treatment ‘forever’?</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: Is sister’s therapist ripping her off in treatment ‘forever’?</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc421ef0-6ec4-11ef-9bd0-00000a1acec2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 16:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catherine, Princess of Wales, says she has completed chemotherapy and will return to a few public engagements</title>
      <description>“The cancer journey is complex, scary and unpredictable for everyone, especially those closest to you. With humility, it also brings you face to face with your own vulnerabilities in a way you have never considered before, and with that, a new perspective on everything,” Catherine said in a statement on X. She first revealed her cancer diagnosis in March.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">387e15c0-6ec3-11ef-b816-00000a1ace7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 15:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A bullied teen found fame as the leader of a global online group that preys on vulnerable children</title>
      <description>Bradley Cadenhead was an outcast in his community in rural Texas. On the social media platform Discord, he reinvented himself at age 15 and became what authorities describe as a notorious predator of the internet age.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5bed1ae0-6ebb-11ef-8456-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 14:54:04 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It is ‘overwhelming’ how cute the answer to today’s On the Record is</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e14173f0-6eaf-11ef-a14f-0000a1ace980</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 13:31:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Black voters say they are certain to vote now that Harris has replaced Biden as the Democratic nominee, Post-Ipsos poll finds</title>
      <description>Among Black registered voters, 82 percent say they will “definitely” or “probably” vote for Vice President Kamala Harris in the contest against former president Donald Trump, up from 74 percent who said they would support President Joe Biden in April. The poll finds increased engagement among the critical Democratic constituency, which is concentrated among younger Black Americans, especially younger women, who were less enthusiastic about voting this spring.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">19580c20-6ea3-11ef-a860-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harris vs. Trump. Georgia suspect. California wildfire. Child predator. NFL Week 1. U.S. Open. New iPhones. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a7de2ff0-6e9a-11ef-9eb1-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 10:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Army is fighting to find recruits in a mistrustful, divided nation</title>
      <description>Recruiters are contending with a confounding array of political, social and economic crises that have made it harder than ever to find citizens willing to serve. At a recruiting station on the Jersey Shore, Sgt. 1st Class Dane Beaston and his colleagues aren’t just selling a job. They’re selling America.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">334a19e0-6e2e-11ef-8991-00000a1ace92</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 22:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jannik Sinner of Italy wins the U.S. Open, defeating American Taylor Fritz for his second Grand Slam singles title of the year</title>
      <description>The top-ranked men’s tennis player in the world, Sinner beat the 12th-seeded Fritz in Sunday’s championship match in New York. Sinner, 23, also won the Australian Open in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">eb221430-6e21-11ef-b36d-0000a1aceff2</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 20:35:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kendrick Lamar will headline the 2025 Super Bowl halftime show in New Orleans</title>
      <description>The rapper revealed the plan Sunday in a video posted to YouTube. This will be Lamar’s second Super Bowl performance, after his 2022 set with Dr. Dre.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">37a4d760-6e00-11ef-89ed-00000a1ace72</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 16:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">922127c0-6dfb-11ef-8aa5-00000a1acec5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 16:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctors thought her constantly running nose was due to allergies or a virus. It signaled something more serious.</title>
      <description>Treatments prescribed to Shemika Rodriguez hadn’t helped. After three months, her episodic drip turned into a constant flow that made her feel like she was drowning when she lay down. But she came to suspect she knew the cause. Eight years earlier, one of her relatives had been diagnosed with a similar problem that had an unfortunate ending.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c1f92dd0-6df6-11ef-b534-000000a1acec</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 15:26:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Washington Commanders begin their season today. This is your ultimate game-day guide.</title>
      <description>As the Commanders open their season on the road, we've got everything you need to watch from home: the key matchup, stats to know, trivia and even food recs. Here’s a helpful guide for the 4:25 p.m. Eastern game between the Commanders and Tampa Bay Buccaneers.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22d28cd0-6def-11ef-bffc-00000a1ace03</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 14:32:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boeing reaches tentative deal with machinists union in effort to avoid costly strike</title>
      <description>The agreement increases pay by 25 percent over four years and commits Boeing to build its next new aircraft in Washington state.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">478782a1-6deb-11ef-a32d-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 14:04:35 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95784e91-6de6-11ef-ab4d-00000a1acef1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 13:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aryna Sabalenka of Belarus wins the U.S. Open, defeating American Jessica Pegula for her third Grand Slam singles title</title>
      <description>Sabalenka, 26, made up for her loss to American Coco Gauff in last year's U.S. Open final with Saturday's victory over the No. 6 seed Pegula. The second-seeded Sabalenka captured her second Grand Slam title of the year after winning the Australian Open in January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">95dac1b0-6d69-11ef-b60d-0000a1ace278</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 22:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mother of Georgia suspect is said to have called school minutes before shooting, warning of ‘extreme emergency’ involving her son</title>
      <description>Text messages and a phone log reviewed by The Washington Post, along with exclusive interviews with a relative of the suspect, provide the strongest indications yet that school officials were alerted to concerns about him on the morning of the shooting and may have been looking for him in the minutes before he allegedly killed four people and injured nine with an AR-15-style rifle.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c693f571-6d63-11ef-a214-00000a1ace10</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 21:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An au pair, a husband’s affair and a double homicide</title>
      <description>Juliana Peres Magalhães, an au pair from Brazil, is charged with second-degree murder in a killing that took place in the main bedroom of Christine and Brendan Banfield’s Virginia home, where Magalhães took care of their young daughter. After the fatal shooting, she moved into that bedroom with Brendan, as the two were in a romantic relationship.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9c62fdd0-6d4c-11ef-9fec-000000a1ace6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 19:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Jayden Daniels the one who will finally stop Washington’s woes at quarterback?</title>
      <description>The Commanders are set for the NFL season and have something rare behind center: hope. Jayden Daniels, the reigning Heisman trophy winner and No. 2 pick out of LSU, has earned glowing reviews during the preseason and appears to be the answer at a position the franchise has been unable to solve for decades. A look at his upbringing in San Bernardino, Calif., and his emergence in Baton Rouge shows what might make him different than the QBs who have failed here before him.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2a0197e0-6d30-11ef-bd61-00000a1acebb</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:45:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The plan was to move migrants to a small town. Then came anger, fear and a fight over the meaning of shelter.</title>
      <description>As dozens of migrant families slept on the floor of Boston’s airport, the state decided to open a shelter in a town of 11,000 people. Inside one small corner of the nation’s immigration crisis.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba6fb260-6d23-11ef-9808-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 14:16:08 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">aea9f320-6d1c-11ef-9808-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 13:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taylor Fritz advances to U.S. Open final, will be first American man in Grand Slam singles final in 15 years</title>
      <description>The No. 12-ranked Fritz defeated fellow American Frances Tiafoe, ranked 20th, in the first all-American semifinal in a men’s Grand Slam event since 2005. The last time an American man made a Grand Slam final was 2009, when Andy Roddick lost at Wimbledon to Roger Federer. Fritz will face top-ranked Jannik Sinner, who ousted Britain’s Jack Draper in three sets, in Sunday’s final.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">24adf780-6cc6-11ef-a3b5-0000a1ace015</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 03:06:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dick Cheney, Republican former vice president, says he will vote for Kamala Harris to ‘put country above partisanship’</title>
      <description>Cheney, who served as George W. Bush’s No. 2 and in other Republican administrations, said in a statement he will cast a ballot for the Democratic nominee, confirming remarks his daughter had made hours earlier.
“In our nation’s 248-year history, there has never been an individual who is a greater threat to our republic than Donald Trump,” Cheney said. “He tried to steal the last election using lies and violence to keep himself in power after the voters had rejected him. He can never be trusted with power again.”</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2dbb0ac0-6c9e-11ef-a4fa-00000a1ace3d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 22:20:09 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Man charged with plotting an attack on a N.Y. Jewish center on the Oct. 7 anniversary of the Hamas attacks in southern Israel</title>
      <description>U.S. officials have charged a Canadian resident with plotting to travel to New York to try to carry out a mass shooting attack against Jewish people on the one-year anniversary of the attacks, authorities announced.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6a86e641-6c94-11ef-b75e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:10:16 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New York judge delays Trump sentencing in hush money case until after presidential election</title>
      <description>The decision to push sentencing from Sept. 18 to Nov. 26 means voters will cast ballots in the presidential election without knowing whether Donald Trump, the Republican nominee, could face jail time for his conviction on 34 counts of falsifying business records.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">58524440-6c73-11ef-b078-0000a1ace191</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 17:13:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
