<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest alerts from washingtonpost.com</title>
    <link>https://github.com/dwillis/wapo-alerts</link>
    <description>An unofficial feed created by Derek Willis.</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 06:03:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>For a low-stress Thanksgiving, get a head start on cooking with these make-ahead recipes for every part of your feast</title>
      <description>Preparing the Thanksgiving feast can feel like a whirlwind. Lighten the load with our menu of make-ahead dishes, including green beans, mashed and sweet potatoes, mac and cheese, stuffing and, yes, even the turkey. Everything can be made ahead, if you want to.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">75946320-ac43-11ef-ad4e-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 22:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Hezbollah have agreed to cease-fire deal, Biden says</title>
      <description>The agreement, which passed a vote 10-1 in Israel's cabinet, takes effect on Wednesday at 4 a.m. local time and will pause a year-long conflict that has escalated in recent weeks, said U.S. and Israeli officials.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">22eedc00-ac38-11ef-b98e-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:50:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We crowdsourced D.C. winter snowfall forecasts. Here's what they say.</title>
      <description>The hundreds of forecasts we gathered from readers, experts and our own Capital Weather Gang meteorologists project somewhat less snow than normal for the upcoming winter. Most people expect about a foot of snow compared to the normal amount, which is closer to 14 inches.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cfeb6420-ac31-11ef-97a0-000000a1ace3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 20:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A columnist’s first 50 years: George F. Will looks back on five decades of writing</title>
      <description>One secret of column-writing: Offer platoons of facts that give readers the delight of discovery.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">94194530-ac2b-11ef-b67e-0000a1ace5d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 19:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Want to reduce Thanksgiving food waste? Give yourself permission to cook less.</title>
      <description>Want to reduce Thanksgiving food waste? Give yourself permission to cook less.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">31b812e1-ac21-11ef-b2c4-000a1aced357</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 18:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miss Manners: We host 2 holiday parties to accommodate all our friends</title>
      <description>Miss Manners: We host 2 holiday parties to accommodate all our friends</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">668e0230-ac18-11ef-8e7d-00000a1ace18</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 17:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>These batteries could harness the wind and sun to replace coal and gas</title>
      <description>New, hulking batteries can store enough renewable energy to replace polluting fossil fuel plants and power thousands of homes. Japan’s northernmost island, Hokkaido, is experimenting with technology that could help it power itself and export clean electricity to the rest of the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fbfd79a1-ac0d-11ef-ae9a-0000a1acec73</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:49:13 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A not-so-jolly holiday season for this retailer</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Tuesday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a78a4520-ac07-11ef-af6d-00000a1ace14</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 15:03:54 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump’s tariffs. Jack Smith. Cease-fire talks. Macy’s expenses. Weight-loss drugs. Big batteries. Thanksgiving snow. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7c2c3b0-abed-11ef-8cd3-0000a1ace849</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden administration proposes Medicare coverage of weight-loss drugs for millions of people, teeing up potential clash with RFK Jr.</title>
      <description>The plan to pay for the popular anti-obesity medications for 7.5 million Medicare and Medicaid beneficiaries would cost the federal government tens of billions of dollars. But the incoming Trump administration could block the plan, and Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the president-elect’s choice for secretary of Health and Human Services, is an avowed enemy of the drugs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">15f528e0-abea-11ef-a38a-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 11:32:14 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump says he’ll impose new tariffs on Mexico, Canada and China, citing illegal immigration and drug smuggling</title>
      <description>In a post on his social media site, the president-elect said he’d issue executive orders on his first day back in office, setting tariffs of 25 percent on imports from Mexico and Canada and 10 percent on imports from China.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f7e35360-ab92-11ef-9a66-00000a1aced0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 01:08:38 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Musk and Ramaswamy race to build a ‘DOGE’ team for war with Washington</title>
      <description>Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy were tapped by President-elect Donald Trump to lead an advisory panel to find “drastic” cuts to the federal government. The two billionaire “Department of Government Efficiency” leaders have spent the past week in Washington and at Mar-a-Lago, seeking staff and interviewing seasoned political operators, legal specialists and top tech leaders, according to people familiar with the matter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c00edf01-ab78-11ef-8542-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 22:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One game, endless fun. Introducing Wridges, our new word game. You’ll be hooked from the first letter.</title>
      <description>One game, endless fun. Introducing Wridges, our new word game. You’ll be hooked from the first letter.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">87e89590-ab68-11ef-9d4b-000000a1ace1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 20:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jack Smith seeks to drop Trump from appeal of classified documents ruling but continue case against his two co-defendants</title>
      <description>The motion, coming an hour after Smith moved to drop the Jan. 6 election obstruction case against Donald Trump, would allow the Justice Department to continue appealing Judge Aileen Cannon’s ruling that Smith was unlawfully appointed as special counsel. Smith is seeking to preserve what he can of the criminal cases, while acknowledging that federal policy prohibits prosecuting a sitting president.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">78bc0f30-ab62-11ef-a126-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 19:21:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Special counsel Jack Smith asks to dismiss Trump’s 2020 election obstruction case but allows case to be revived in future</title>
      <description>The motion to dismiss charges without prejudice could put President-elect Donald Trump in the position of having to pardon himself before he leaves office to avoid future legal jeopardy.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d6178780-ab59-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 18:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax: A cheater’s new fiancée wants to hear his ex’s side of the story</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax: A cheater’s new fiancée wants to hear his ex’s side of the story</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f00eb830-ab4e-11ef-a168-0000a1ace71f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 17:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parts of your body start aging earlier than others, new research shows</title>
      <description>Scientists call this new area of research “organ aging,” and it’s redefining how we think about getting older.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">72d73640-ab43-11ef-a126-00000a1ace82</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:39:24 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A TikTok take on a classic vegetable in today's On the Record</title>
      <description>Answer now to earn your Monday points.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3153fcf0-ab3c-11ef-a249-00000a1ace85</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:47:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Taylor Bradford dies at 91. Her novels, mostly about resilient and wealthy women, have sold more than 90 million copies.</title>
      <description>Bradford, a British-American novelist who debuted in 1979 with “A Woman of Substance,” a rags-to-riches tale that she followed with more than 30 bestsellers, died Sunday. Ten of her books were made into TV miniseries and films.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ea8e38a2-ab2a-11ef-b77f-00000a1ace63</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks. Israeli strike. Climate deal. Raw milk. Student death. ‘Glicked’ box office. Look-alike contest. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdf78da0-ab24-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 12:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Still need to finish this weekend’s On the Record? We’ve got you.</title>
      <description>Play now to finish out your score for the week.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cdb0e7f0-aa85-11ef-9085-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 17:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We tried 8 popular stuffing mixes. There was one clear winner.</title>
      <description>We tried 8 popular stuffing mixes. There was one clear winner.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">52f8e4f0-aa7a-11ef-9774-00000a1ace4d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 15:39:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</title>
      <description>Crossword and a coffee: Solve the Sunday puzzle now</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">973dc990-aa71-11ef-9868-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 14:37:11 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orlando Pride tops Washington Spirit, 1-0, in NWSL championship game, capping a dominant year with a title</title>
      <description>The Pride, which stormed through the regular season, beat the Spirit on Saturday night in Kansas City, Missouri, to claim the title. Orlando's roster is headlined by 38-year-old star Marta, who is widely regarded as the best player in women’s history, and Barbra Banda, a 24-year-old Zambian striker.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e5f9eeb0-aa12-11ef-ad0d-00000a1acec8</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 03:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>U.N. talks have reached a deal to offer $300 billion a year in climate aid to poor nations. Follow our live coverage.</title>
      <description>The final agreement calls for developed countries to provide at least $300 billion a year by 2035 to help developing nations cope with climate disasters. The deal, which delegates will discuss in an open session before taking a formal vote, would cap two weeks of negotiations at the U.N. Climate Change Conference in Baku, Azerbaijan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a0719290-a9e4-11ef-852b-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 21:48:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hegseth’s combat unit was rocked by war crimes after he left, shaping the potential defense secretary’s criticism of the U.S. Army</title>
      <description>Pete Hegseth watched an extended inquiry into military misconduct upend the lives of colleagues and mentors. That experience shaped his very public position on what he now regards as unreasonable restrictions on the rules of engagement for troops.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70e0d0b1-a9d3-11ef-84ea-0000a1acecdd</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 19:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can our spending habits help explain the culture wars? Our Department of Data investigates.</title>
      <description>Americans with a college education have turned heavily toward the Democratic Party, while Republicans have made huge inroads among folks with less education. We looked at educational differences in spending and found some reasons for this split, as well as a possible explanation for why culture has replaced economics as a key voting factor.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1535cfe0-a9ce-11ef-be69-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 19:06:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Sahaj: My in-laws’ visits last for months. I’m at my wit’s end.</title>
      <description>Ask Sahaj: My in-laws’ visits last for months. I’m at my wit’s end.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">9e87f230-a9bc-11ef-8fb0-000000a1ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 17:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We made it easy to see if your city is poised to bounce back from the next climate disaster</title>
      <description>Climate risks are rising. But resilience can matter just as much. Your community’s capacity to rebound from adversity helps determine whether your home can hold its value. See how your city ranks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6c00dc0-a9b1-11ef-aad7-0000a1ace473</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 15:43:40 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>They’re roommates on Capitol Hill. Can they lead the Democratic Party out of the wilderness?</title>
      <description>Abigail Spanberger and Mikie Sherrill are strong contenders to be the next governors of Virginia and New Jersey, Karen Tumulty writes.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">fb0555a0-a9aa-11ef-b489-000000a1ace9</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 14:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</title>
      <description>How many guesses will Keyword take you today? Try to beat the average now.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a30ff7e0-a9a7-11ef-9c8e-00000a1aced5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 14:31:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump names his picks for surgeon general, FDA, CDC and HUD in a flurry of announcements</title>
      <description>Donald Trump said he had chosen Janette Nesheiwat, a double board-certified doctor, to be surgeon general. The president-elect also said he had chosen former Florida congressman Dave Weldon to head the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. He also announced the selection of Johns Hopkins surgeon and writer Martin Makary to lead the Food and Drug Administration. Trump also tapped Scott Turner to run the Department of Housing and Urban Development.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1d52a440-a939-11ef-a3ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 01:20:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump announces Rep. Lori Chavez-DeRemer (R-Oregon) for labor secretary in surprise move</title>
      <description>The Teamsters union had pushed for her nomination, which marks a sharp departure from typical GOP appointments to the position.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">86885590-a934-11ef-a405-00000a1ace6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:47:32 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump selects ally Russell Vought, another Project 2025 contributor, to run the White House budget office again</title>
      <description>Vought, who was the director of the Office of Management and Budget early in Donald Trump’s first presidency, wrote a chapter of Project 2025 on transforming the executive office. The budget office is expected to work closely with Elon Musk and Vivek Ramaswamy’s government efficiency panel.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">79810e41-a930-11ef-8d3d-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump expected to pick hedge fund executive Scott Bessent to run Treasury Department</title>
      <description>Bessent, who worked for George Soros decades ago, campaigned for Donald Trump this year. Observers say Bessent is able to translate Trump’s populist rhetoric in a way that’s palatable to Wall Street.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">70a0d830-a928-11ef-8725-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 23:21:02 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump plans to fire lawyers who worked for special counsel Jack Smith and use Justice Dept. to probe 2020 election</title>
      <description>President-elect Donald Trump plans to fire the prosecutors who worked with Smith to charge him with election obstruction and mishandling classified documents, including career attorneys typically protected from political retribution, according to two people close to Trump’s transition. One person said Trump is also planning to revisit debunked allegations of widespread voter fraud in battleground states in 2020.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">01cd4000-a924-11ef-b866-00000a1ace39</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:49:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You’ll know exactly when ‘Gladiator II’ jumps the shark. It’s the scene with the shark, our critic writes.</title>
      <description>Set 16 years after “Gladiator” and featuring whichever of the original cast aren’t dead or unbribable, the new film has all the opulence of the first film but none of the majesty. Read our 1.5-star review of one of the year’s most hyped movies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c31b6770-a922-11ef-89b6-000000a1ace8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 22:40:23 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Florida surgeon general calls for removing fluoride from drinking water, echoing concerns of Robert F. Kennedy Jr.</title>
      <description>Joseph A. Ladapo, who is being considered for senior health positions in the incoming Trump administration, cited disputed claims about health risks associated with fluoride and said the cavity-fighter is available through toothpaste and mouthwash. Although many experts hail fluoride as one of the greatest public health achievements of the 20th century, more communities are starting to question the practice.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bc80ff80-a916-11ef-ae01-0000a1ace337</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 21:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Texas state school board approves Bible-based lessons in optional curriculum for public elementary schools</title>
      <description>Texas joins Louisiana and Oklahoma in making new efforts this year to incorporate Christianity into public schools. The push aligns with President-elect Donald Trump’s plan for a more conservative agenda in classrooms.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">0e7d3c30-a8ff-11ef-a18a-00000a1ace6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 18:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband’s daughter doesn’t like me and is skipping the holidays</title>
      <description>Carolyn Hax chat: Husband’s daughter doesn’t like me and is skipping the holidays</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d5aa2c70-a8f8-11ef-9d3e-00000a1ace41</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Matt Gaetz says he won't return to Congress after dropping his bid for attorney general</title>
      <description>In an interview with right-wing activist Charlie Kirk, Gaetz said, “I’m still going to be in the fight, but it’ll be from a new perch. I do not intend to join the 119th Congress.” Gaetz had resigned his Florida seat.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c393ce0-a8f6-11ef-80e7-00000a1ace0c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 17:21:39 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge delays Trump’s sentencing in hush money case to allow more time to argue why conviction should be tossed</title>
      <description>New York Supreme Court Justice Juan Merchan set deadlines in early December for defense lawyers and prosecutors to argue whether Donald Trump’s convictions for falsifying business records related to a hush money payment should be overturned because he has been reelected as president. Merchan canceled Trump’s scheduled Nov. 26 sentencing but left room for him to be sentenced sometime after Dec. 9, before Trump again becomes president in late January.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2de5ff80-a8f0-11ef-a3ed-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 16:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘The Iron Man of America’s op-ed pages’: George Will’s half-century of columns is a remarkable feat, David Von Drehle writes</title>
      <description>The Iron Man of America’s op-ed pages</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">03f62730-a8e7-11ef-b45a-00000a1ace13</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 15:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</title>
      <description>10 questions, plus a bonus wager! It’s the weekend edition of On the Record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c069cce1-a8de-11ef-9116-0000000a1ace</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 14:33:33 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaetz drops out. Netanyahu arrest warrant. Russian missile. Beef recall. Tap water. ‘Wicked’ release. Shoe thief. Catch up now.</title>
      <description>Catch up in minutes with these 7 stories.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">458a9e60-a8c9-11ef-9dae-000000a1aced</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 11:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China’s Salt Typhoon breach is ‘worst telecom hack in our nation’s history — by far,’ says Senate Intelligence Committee chair</title>
      <description>The Chinese government's espionage campaign has penetrated more than a dozen U.S. telecommunications companies and collected information on federal wiretaps.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">bb96f210-a870-11ef-b72b-000000a1ace7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 01:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shohei Ohtani of the Los Angeles Dodgers and Aaron Judge of the New York Yankees named MLB’s most valuable players</title>
      <description>Ohtani, who played his first season in the National League after signing a record contract with the Dodgers last offseason, is an MVP for the third time after the designated hitter became the first player with at least 50 home runs and 50 stolen bases in a season. Judge earned his second American League MVP award after the outfielder hit a major league-leading 58 home runs.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3b10c4e1-a866-11ef-973b-00000a1ace27</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:10:49 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump picks Pam Bondi to be attorney general, replacing Matt Gaetz hours after he withdrew bid</title>
      <description>Bondi, a former Florida attorney general, served in the Trump White House in 2019 during his first impeachment. She is the second selection the president-elect has made to lead the Justice Department. Gaetz, who's been accused of sexual misconduct, announced earlier Thursday he would no longer pursue the Cabinet role.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e2e9520-a864-11ef-a739-00000a1ace2f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 23:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alex Ovechkin expected to miss four to six weeks with fractured fibula, an injury that comes as he chases Wayne Gretzky’s record</title>
      <description>The Washington Capitals on Thursday announced the timeline for Ovechkin, whose season has paused amid his chase of Gretzky’s NHL goals record. The Capitals’ captain has 15 goals in 18 games this season and 868 in his NHL career. Ovechkin, 39, needs just 27 goals to break Gretzky’s record.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a59c62e0-a859-11ef-b919-00000a1ace11</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 22:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming of snow this winter? Look up the forecast in your area.</title>
      <description>Most of the United States is expected to see less snow this year, continuing a long-term trend of snowfall decline as global temperatures rise. Look up your area.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">98fea940-a849-11ef-b762-00000a1ace5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 20:45:52 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
